Presented by FroZen-EviL!
daisuki datta no
I've loved him.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I've always been waiting.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
I showed off whenever he was around.
ki no nai furi shiteta
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
My career and love life?
watashi taisetsu dakedo
I do think they're both important.
aitsu no egao ga yappari
But when I see his smile,
saikou no takaramono
I know it's what I want the most.
omoigakenai puropoozu!
He proposed to me; was it real?
sukuranburu no domannaka
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
uso deshou
It's so unbelievable.
tachidomatta mama
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
Horns don't get through my ears.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
The world is silent and completely still,
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
Chu! Chu!
Kiss! Kiss!
Sign: All Sports News
Hey, Matsuda-chan!
Sign: Restroom
How'd that match go?
Great!
Hey, Kamuda!
What the...
Oh, it's you, Matsuda-san.
You seem pleased. What's the good news?
"Inokuma Yawara to appear at the Ajisai Cup Intermural Women's Tournament!"
Will that work?
Huh?
It's gonna be tomorrow's front page headline.
So Yawara-san has returned to judo?
Yep!
That's great to hear.
You've been worrying about her a lot.
Inokuma... Yawara.
Excuse me, may we have another match?
Yawara-san certainly did challenge Tsukushi U to another match.
Yawara-san, you've really returned to judo, haven't you?
And with the chief in a good mood as well,
things are going your way, huh?
The chief?
He's always inviting me for drinks, though you know I can't deal with him.
But a while ago, he was complaining about stomach problems from stress.
You mean he got diarrhea from overeating.
No one looks like that when they're stressed.
Geez, you could at least wash your hands!
Whoops, and you just did your hair too.
You see, this is why you can't get a girl.
Hell, the chief himself never washes his hands, even after a dump!
Gross!
Damn you, Matsuda!
Not again...
Fujiko, Love, and Judo
I have to say, you were spectacular.
That's enough, Hanazono-san!
No, let me say it again, Fujiko-san!
Your deadly Swan Lake technique.
To think that you perfected that masterful Ouchi Gari in such a short time...
It was... simply spectacular.
Look, Hanazono-san...
Hello?
Why are you two having all the fun?
Yes, I'll admit that Fujiko-san's Swan Lake move was spectacular,
but I've got one of them too, you know.
That's right. Paddy-field had her...
Takeshi, you jerk!
A.K.A. "Send Your Exes to Hell."
Thirteen was quite the unlucky number for them!
A-And there was Yoshinagawa-san's deadly Konaki-jiji!
Diet!
Since I lost so much weight during the match, it should be all right to eat this.
However, everyone knows that I was the biggest standout of the match.
Only because you're that much of a slut.
Feeling jealous already, Paddy-field?
What are you getting at?
Um...
Um, I know I lost today,
but I feel I can do anything if I have the will, just like Inokuma-san told me.
So, um, it will be my pleasure to work with you.
Oh please, the pleasure is all mine, Kyonkyon.
Fujiko-san.
I didn't know how it would turn out at first,
but now, our team will be participating in a real tournament.
And it's all thanks to me, the eminent coach, right, Beanpole?
However, the training's going to become even more strenuous.
That's because we'll be facing a gaggle of top-tier teams like Tsukushi U.
You're all gonna have to tighten up those fundoshi strings and step up.
Or rather, the waistbands on our panties.
Well, I guess those modern drawers aren't any different from a fundoshi anyway.
You're so informed, old man.
Grandpa, honestly.
Everyone! As long as I, Hanazono Kaoru, work together with Master Jigoro,
MJWC's judo team will remain an undying institution.
I'll be fine on my own!
Hanazono-san is right!
Let's raise our glasses again to MJWC's new departure,
and to Inokuma Yawara-san's return to judo! Cheers!
Cheers!
Now then, Yawara, we need to go home and practice!
Grandpa, I haven't eaten anything yet!
What are you saying? My stomach's full already!
Sir, shouldn't you let Inokuma-san rest today?
Yeah, don't be so hard on her, gramps!
I also ask you to let her rest, Master Jigoro!
You're just messing around because you scrapped a little in your first match.
Then after this, you plan to have a wild, drunken party at a filthy discotheque, right?
A drunken party?
I see what you're up to!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
If you've got time for all that, then train!
Grandpa!
Inokuma-san!
Inokuma!
Hanazono!
Yes, sir!
You take care of everything, including the bill!
Th-The bill?
We're going this way.
See you guys at the gym tomorrow!
Take care!
Oh, my body's all hurt and swollen!
But you didn't do a damn thing!
That was great. I had a lot of fun.
Me too!
I-I'm looking forward to the Ajisai Cup.
Inokuma is going to be there, and she's going to be the champ.
I guarantee that!
Hanazono-san.
Would you care to sit down?
S-Sure!
Did I do the right thing?
I wonder if I did something horrible to Inokuma-san?
I wonder if she really does have an issue doing judo with us?
No, she doesn't!
I haven't seen...
that expression on Inokuma's face in a long time.
That twinkle in her eyes showed that she never really wanted to quit judo.
It's because you and the others struggled and did your best out there.
No matter what happens,
I won't let her give up judo.
No, she's not someone who would give up judo.
That's what I believe.
You're right.
You must know a whole lot about Inokuma-san.
Yes. She's a fine judoka and a fine woman.
Yes, you're right.
But I only see Inokuma as someone I admire!
I swear I never had any impure thoughts about her!
Um, I...
Oh, never mind.
I said something to Inokuma-san one time.
I told her that judo burns from the bottom of her heart.
But after that match, I also realized...
that I must feel the same way too!
I'm really glad I met Inokuma-san and all the team members.
I want to keep playing judo with all of them.
Fujiko-san!
Please let me, Hanazono Kaoru, humbly support you!
We at Ebitendo Sports College also have our matches, so I can't keep coaching you,
but I'll definitely attend your upcoming tournament!
Thank you, Hanazono-san!
I'm really glad I'm doing judo!
Otherwise, I wouldn't have met someone like you!
H-Hanazono-san!
Yes, Fujiko-san?
Shut the hell up!
For God's sake, cut that out! Sheesh!
Oh, right.
We're sorry.
Th-Thanks.
Yeah.
Look, you can leave me here.
Thanks for carrying my bag for me.
U-Um, Fujiko-san?
Yes?
D-Do you...
Do you feel cold?
But my apartment's right there!
I can't let you catch a cold!
But it's right in front of us!
G-Good night!
Translation: kokujin-kun
Editing: Collectr
Timing: kokujin-kun
Encoding: Skr
QC Team: Rosti, CP, Skr, Juggen, Mamo-chan
DVD Provider: CP
Hanazono...
I hate to say it, but I can't beat you!
You should be the captain at our next match!
Right, guys?
Yeah!
Please accept, Hanazono.
Leave everything to me, Senpai.
Congratulations, Hanazono-kun!
Matsuda-san!
Can I get an exclusive interview?
Oh, really? Aw, shucks.
Hanazono-san?
Fujiko-san!
What brings you here?
Don't worry about that.
What matters is that you're the captain! That's wonderful!
Thank you, Fujiko-san!
It's wonderful, really wonderful.
It... It looks like she...
w-wants me to kiss her!
F-Fujiko-san!
I, Hanazono Kaoru, will kiss you.
Ow!
Are you that hot for my leg?
Wash these too!
Me?
Fujiko-san!
Fujiko-san, geez!
They opened the gym. We're supposed to get the mats.
Why were you grinning?
Um, it's nothing.
So what are you gonna wear at the group date?
Oh, I found these totally cute clothes in Shibuya.
The new freshmen act so much like college girls
that you can't tell them apart from the second years!
They're always talking about group dates and dance parties during class.
There just aren't a lot of college girls into judo nowadays.
Sorry, I didn't mean it that way.
Inokuma-san?
Huh?
Are you in love right now?
Forget what I just said!
Oh yeah, what did you guys do last night?
We made up for your absence by eating and going nuts!
Lucky! I had to practice with my grandpa.
Hey, do you know what Hanazono-kun did?
After a second huge helping of hamburger steak and rice,
he ate spaghetti and a chocolate parfait!
And he said that wasn't enough, didn't he?
Yes. Right on the money.
He was like that back in high school.
He'd drink twenty bottles of milk after practice without breaking a sweat!
Oh yeah, there was that all-you-can-eat pizza thing.
That's right. You two have been together since high school, so you know a lot about him.
I want to know more about him.
Oh, never mind.
G-Good night!
Fujiko-san!
Hey, Fujiko-san!
What's the matter?
Sorry.
You've been acting weird all morning.
Say, don't you think the others are late?
Yeah, those girls are late.
Sign: Tsukushi University Judo Team
Don't you dare relax!
There are only two months till the Ajisai Cup Intermural Women's Tournament!
Ogaki! You're the first one up!
You'd better take care of those four newbies from MWJC!
All of you are national champs!
Even an Inokuma can't defeat five top players!
You'll hand Inokuma her first loss!
I hope.
What happened to them?
They suffered through a lot yesterday.
Their aches and pains must've kept them in bed.
You're right. They should be coming soon.
I hope.
What's this? You need to put up more of a fight!
This doesn't amount to any sort of training!
Do you know why a person like me would condescend to working up a sweat?
It's so I can defeat that pest, Inokuma Yawara.
Now, who's next?
Yes, ma'am!
She's desperate.
Yawara-san means even more to her now.
Another reason is that
Yawara-san's father, Mr. Inokuma Kojiro, is still leaning toward being her coach.
B-Big news!
What is it, Tokunaga-san?
H-Here, read this.
Yawara-san?
It's like seeing a long sought-after oasis!
Don't look at the picture. Read the headline!
The Ajisai Cup? She's going to appear in the Intermural Women's Tournament?
Inokuma is aiming for the national championship at the tournament?
So she's avoiding a face-off with me in order to show off at that tournament?
Darn! She's always thinking of new ways to show me up!
Tokunaga, please enter me into that tournament immediately.
But, milady...
Hold on, Sayaka-san!
Your judo club at Seishin Women's School doesn't have any members!
People will join if I tell them to.
Do you think a ritzy girls school like Seishin has any good judo players?
Even if the other members are useless,
I'll simply keep winning in that elimination tournament.
Then I'll finally have my match against Inokuma Yawara.
I can hardly wait.
This is nuts.
If only Inokuma Kojiro was coaching her now...
Box: Chicken Nuggets
Here, girl! Here, girl!
Here! Here!
Nobody's coming.
Don't worry! We were all really into it yesterday, right?
I guess it's because I lost yesterday.
It's not your fault!
But...
a normal girl wouldn't want to play judo.
No, you're wrong!
Judo is a very glamorous sport!
Didn't you see how disappointed we were after we lost that match?
Why don't we three start practicing?
Paddy-field!
When I said I wanted to see him, he said, "Sure."
But then that Katsuo...
He shot me down! That makes him the fourteenth!
I was so pissed I threw him straight to the ground!
Was that what happened?
We'll make you stronger, so you can throw more people around!
Yoshinagawa-san!
Look at me!
I lost three kilos at the match!
I must look positively emaciated!
You went through a lot yesterday!
I would've lost five kilos if I hadn't eaten afterwards.
All right, I'm gonna keep practicing judo and lose more weight!
Hi!
Everyone's here!
Oh, my God! Have you seen the papers?
When I got on the train, all the old men were staring at me,
but they weren't perving over me like they usually do.
It was like they were ogling a star!
It had me wondering, but it turns out I'm a celebrity.
Take a look.
What can I say? A fine showing like mine would make the papers!
Now there's no way I'm quitting judo.
What do you mean, "a fine showing"?
My fine showing. Mine.
You saw my picture in the paper, didn't you?
What are you, some kind of ghost?
This doesn't even count!
You're always jealous of me, Paddy-field!
What are you getting at?
Inokuma-san.
Fujiko-san.
See, everybody came.
Judo is a really great sport.
Mm-hmm.
Hey!
It's way past practice time. Why are you standing around gabbing?!
When it comes to a great judoka like me,
there are no shortcuts to excellence, only practice, practice, practice!
Ah, man...
Fine. Let's get on with it.
Wow, I'm a celebrity.
All right, Yawara, Beanpole, quit lazing about and get started!
Yes.
Yes, sir!
Let's give it our all for the Ajisai Cup!
Judo is youth!
Judo is laundry.
The Barcelona Olympics in 460 Days
Yawara! Where's your fire?!
Even that Beanpole is training through blood, sweat, and tears!
Is that so?
But I have to admit, Fujiko-san is really into it.
According to Matsuda, powerful players you've never heard of
are coming from all over the country for a chance to beat you in the tournament.
Is that true?
Yawara!
Everybody Wants to Beat Yawara!
You'll get my Tomoe Nage if you don't watch!
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
koe ni dashite ienai no?
But why can I not? I really don't know.
ima anata ga iru
You're standing here by my side.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
egao wo sagashite
I say as I look for your smile.