Presented by FroZen-EviL!
I've loved him.
daisuki datta no
I've always been waiting.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I showed off whenever he was around.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
ki no nai furi shiteta
My career and love life?
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
I do think they're both important.
watashi taisetsu dakedo
But when I see his smile,
aitsu no egao ga yappari
I know it's what I want the most.
saikou no takaramono
He proposed to me; was it real?
omoigakenai puropoozu!
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
sukuranburu no domannaka
uso deshou
It's so unbelievable.
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
tachidomatta mama
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
Horns don't get through my ears.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
The world is silent and completely still,
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
Kiss! Kiss!
Chu! Chu!
It was awesome, Yawara!
Superb!
Please... feed me something.
I-I can't get out.
This is perfect!
Keep me pinned down!
Inokuma-san!
I found her!
I've found an amazing person!
I'm sorry, Jody.
That can't be true!
You can't really be quitting judo!
Tell me it's not true!
The Weakest Japanese Judo Team
Come on, we need to go there!
Totally!
Sign: Mitsuba Women's Junior College
Come on, we need to go there!
A large pork cutlet bowl, please.
Please, eat as much as you like.
Thanks a lot.
I don't carry any money,
because I'll just spend it on food.
It's my pleasure. Now just relax and eat your fill.
Still, are you sure that judo can help me diet?
Sure it can!
You can eat as much as you like and still slim down!
Arru rositive?
C-Cross my heart! I mean, take a look at them!
These girls are willow-thin thanks to judo!
Well, I've always looked this good.
Yeah, good for a slut.
Why not just say you're jealous?
But we still haven't had any judo pract—
See? So let's do judo together!
Well?
Um...
Can I have another pork cutlet bowl?
Of course. Eat as much as you like!
Then we'll do judo.
Sign: All Sports News
O-Once again...
This is awesome!
During an exhibition match at Jody Rockwell's wedding,
Inokuma Yawara defeated the big kahuna of Canadian judo,
Kristin Adams, with a spectacular Ippon Seoinage!
I knew you could do it, Jody Rockwell.
Inokuma Yawara has made her comeback!
I have tomorrow's front page right here, Chief!
Matsuda, an international call.
From who?
Someone with a thick accent.
Jody!
You did great, Jody! Gold medal material!
Thank you very much!
Matsuda, what should I do?
That was the last Ippon Seoinage she'll ever do!
She said she's going to quit judo!
It's because her dad will never return if she keeps it up.
She said her family was torn apart because of her judo.
She's really serious about quitting.
What should I have done, Matsuda?
You're the only one I can count on!
You're her steady, Matsuda,
so you're the only one I can trust.
What the heck?
Another large pork cutlet bowl.
Let's see. My school registration number and my name...
All right!
I finally have my five-member patchwork team!
We're not patchwork, are we?
You're right. We're a terrific team.
Terrific, my butt.
Now then, we'll begin practice first thing tomorrow.
Here, are we good?
Oh, of course! It's just a stupid application form!
It's just a formality. As long as we know your name...
How do you say your name?
Activity Application Form/Student Number/Name/Yoshinagawa Sayuri
Yoshinagawa Sayuri.
Here, this is for you, Grandpa. And this is for you, Mom.
Oh my, that looks perfect on you, Dad.
You look ten years old.
And you look just like the day you married my son.
Oh, you're making me blush.
Careful, this is hot!
Oh, Dad.
I hope you kept up your training while you were in Canada, Yawara.
So did you toss around ten or twenty bears?
I didn't see a single bear.
Geez...
So how was Jody-san's wedding?
It was wonderful!
Really?
Yawara, you had yourself a truly splendid rival.
Jody will get over the ordeal she suffered at the World Cup
and come back one or even two sizes bigger.
You need to start training immediately for that day!
What?
Oh, Dad, that's right! Zen-san from the electronics store left a message for you.
Oh, I forgot! I'm supposed to watch a video today!
Tamao-san! Do you know where my medal is?
I'm pretty sure it's in the bathroom.
Grandpa, please stop wearing that medal!
I'm off!
Grandpa!
Here's your present.
Thank you, Inokuma-san.
No, thank you.
Those notes you took for me really helped a lot.
A Canadian Rockies T-shirt!
I knew the Rockies would be perfect for you.
I heard we have afternoon classes off.
Do you want to go someplace?
Eh?
I-I'm afraid I'm...
Canada had such beautiful scenery that I couldn't stop taking pictures.
Do you want to see?
Today's not going to work out.
Huh?
Fujiko-san, your bag is open.
My judogi!
Um, Fujiko-san?
Look, I'm really busy today. Sorry!
Fujiko-san! I haven't seen you for a while...
and I wanted to chat.
Look, right here! Right at that moment!
Take a good look!
You see?
Well?
Wow, it looks easier than I thought.
So you're saying we just throw people around.
Wait a minute!
I can excuse Minamida-san, since she has thirteen years of judo under her belt. But Marilyn...
don't you think you're underrating judo just a bit?
Fujiko-san, listen, she doesn't have thirteen years of judo under her belt,
just thirteen guys who rejected her.
Zip it, will you?
What?
Experience?
O-Of course I do.
How much?
Hey, how much?
Th-Thirteen...
Thirteen years?
Nope, thirteen guys.
I totally get why you'd want to take up judo after thirteen guys rejected you.
I told you to can it, toots!
Anyway, we just throw people around, right?
Someone be my partner.
Okay, I will.
What?
You saw me gorge myself with food, so I have to use judo to start dieting.
S-Sure, why not?
I need to protect myself from gropers anyway,
so a partner your size will be good practice.
Just don't hurt me, okay?
So you take this here...
Then do this...
Fujiko-san.
Yes?
I think we're starting to look like a judo team.
Yeah.
Is this really going to help me diet?
Get off of me. You're heavy!
You can't just start off with a bigger opponent.
You're... heavy!
Let's go, Kyonkyon.
Sure.
Get off of me!
I stood up too fast.
Kyonkyon, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Hang in there.
Get off of me. You're heavy! Come on!
Now throw me.
Y-You go first, Paddy-field.
Just throw me, will you?
No, I insist that you go first.
Forget about me. Now do it!
Okay, go!
D-Don't mind me.
Come on, one, two...
Three, four.
Two, two...
One, two, three, four...
You're not at a school dance!
You're heavy. I can't breathe!
Get off of me!
Th-This is not judo!
...three, four. One, two, three, four.
Timing: kokujin-kun               Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
DVD Provider: CP
kokujin-kun, Skr, Juggen, Yoshu-sama
QC Team: tlynnec, Rosti, Mamo-chan, CP,
Timing: kokujin-kun               Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
QC Team: tlynnec, Rosti, Mamo-chan, CP,
kokujin-kun, Skr, Juggen, Yoshu-sama
DVD Provider: CP
Fujiko-san was acting pretty weird today.
So this is youth?
Fujiko.
Oh, Hanazono's at the faucets.
Thank you very much.
Hanazono-san?
Yes?
F-Fujiko-san!
She came again!
How the hell does that guy get a chick?
I-I see.
You recruited five members. Good for you.
But it's not going to work.
That joke of a judo team is not going to attract Inokuma-san.
At first I thought if she saw a team hard at work, she'd come back to judo,
even if the members were weak and clumsy.
But what I have now...
Fujiko-san, you can't give up!
Like I said before, I'll do whatever I can for you.
So... So...
Go for it, Hanazono!
Get her on her back!
U-Um...
F-Forgive me!
It's okay.
Still...
a woman's college is completely uncharted territory for me, I'm embarrassed to say.
I'm not sure how much help I can provide.
I've got it!
I know someone who's perfect for the job, Fujiko-san.
And that someone is...
Sign: Chojuan Soba and Chinese
What?
That dingbat is whining again about utter nonsense?
Yes. So I went ahead and...
So that's why she's been slacking on training and taking it easy!
"It's all judo's fault," my Aunt Fanny!
No real judo student gets weepy over that!
Can't she ever give that swelled head of hers a rest?
So that's why I went ahead and...
Thanks for telling me that.
I'm gonna grab her by the scruff of the neck and beat some character into her!
Th-Things will get out of hand if you do that!
Mind your own darn business!
That's how I trained her as a kid!
But Yawara isn't a kid anymore!
So what I've been trying to say is that
I'd do anything to get Yawara into judo again.
So I created a judo team at Mitsuba Women's Junior College.
But, try as I might, my judo team is completely hopeless.
So I came to you, the highly esteemed judo master,
because Hanazono-san said you can make something out of a completely hopeless team.
That is correct.
I am the highly esteemed judo master. Nothing is impossible.
Do you really mean it?
A judo master never goes back on his word.
So, what's your plan?
Thank you very much!
Yes.
What?
A match.
Excuse me?
Beanpole, that judo team you created...
must fight in a match!
Sign: Mitsuba Women's Junior College
Fujiko-san, you have a really big appetite.
I wish I'd never have to worry about my diet.
I have to build up stamina for the hard training I'm facing.
Training?
It's nothing! Forget what I said!
Hm?
What? You're busy again?
Y-Yeah.
But I wanted to show you my pictures from Canada.
Weird. Are you sure you're not hiding something?
No way!
Poster: Starting Today, You Too Can Be YAWARA!!
Is there something wrong, Fujiko-san?
No, uh... um...
Ah, I saw her on TV!
Inokuma Yawara is going to our school, right?
A-A cattle mutation!
I have to get going. Bye!
Fujiko-san!
Sign: All Sports News
She's really serious about quitting.
What should I have done, Matsuda?
You're the only one I can count on!
You're her steady, Matsuda,
so you're the only one I can trust.
Kosaku?
Kosaku!
Today I came early...
You're the only one...
the only one... the only one... the only one!
What?
A match?
That's right, a match.
We haven't found an opponent yet, but we should be preparing for an actual contest.
I'll throw them down!
Will a match slim me down?
I don't want to get hurt!
I'll just observe.
No need to worry. We won't be fighting any matches the way we are now.
That's because I've brought along a really great coach!
A coach?
Great! Is he hot? Is he?
There may be countless judo teams throughout this country,
but none has a coach quite like this one.
Enter, if you please!
I am right here.
Great, an old man.
I am Inokuma Jigoro,
the 8th degree black belt judo master, who's won five straight national titles.
So where's our hot coach?
Hey, quit being bashful and come in!
That's the guy who grabbed my boobs!
This is Inokuma Jigoro-san, the great judo master and Inokuma Yawara-san's grandfather!
We also have Barcelona Olympic hopeful Hanazono Kaoru-san,
of Ebitendo University of Sport Sciences!
Th-Thank you for your introduction!
I am Hanazono Kaoru of Ebitendo University of Sport Sciences!
Um... I like to bowl, my blood type is O, and I'm a Pisces!
God, he's too much!
So we have an old man and that gorilla.
Um... I like to bowl, my blood type is O, and I'm a Pisces!
My favorite foods are sweet red-bean soup and eel pie!
So we have an old man and that gorilla.
This is the worst.
My favorite foods are sweet red-bean soup and eel pie!
I take pride in my physical strength...
Hey, Hanazono!
Look at those! Look!
She certainly has assets.
Now we're guaranteed to win!
Inokuma-san, come back!
Sign: The Barcelona Olympics in 516 Days
Fujiko-san, what happened?
I swear, this is the most mixed-up bunch I've ever seen!
They are going to need Jigoro's Deluxe Intensive Training Program.
Intensive training program?
Nothing for you to worry about!
Grandpa!
Next time on Yawara:
The Extreme Training Program.
I'll make you their practice dummy if you don't watch.
The Extreme
Training Program!
I'll make you their practice dummy if you don't watch.
The Extreme
Training Program!
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
But why can I not? I really don't know.
koe ni dashite ienai no?
You're standing here by my side.
ima anata ga iru
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
I say as I look for your smile.
egao wo sagashite