Presented by FroZen-EviL!
I've loved him.
daisuki datta no
I've always been waiting.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I showed off whenever he was around.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
ki no nai furi shiteta
My career and love life?
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
I do think they're both important.
watashi taisetsu dakedo
But when I see his smile,
aitsu no egao ga yappari
I know it's what I want the most.
saikou no takaramono
He proposed to me; was it real?
omoigakenai puropoozu!
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
sukuranburu no domannaka
It's so unbelievable.
uso deshou
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
tachidomatta mama
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
Horns don't get through my ears.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
The world is silent and completely still,
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
Kiss! Kiss!
Chu! Chu!
Trois!
All right!
Too cool!
You did it, Fujiko-san!
This is truly incredible!
MWJC advances to the second round without the aid of Inokuma!
So that girl is the huge obstacle Kojiro-san was talking about.
Swan vs. Tanks
That was amazing!
Sign: 8th Annual Ajisai Cup Women's Intermural Tournament
We didn't get to see Inokuma's Ippon Zeoi.
Oh well, let's just hope we see it in the second round.
I'll go buy some juice.
So what do you think, Saito-san, about the solid performance of MWJC's vice captain, Ito Fujiko?
Quite marvelous. She definitely has her rhythm down.
Also, the way she used her height to launch that Ouchi Gari from so far away was brilliant.
You might also say it's that Inokuma magic at work.
You big lunk!
That was amazing, Fujiko-san!
The confidence you get from knowing
You big lunk!
That was amazing, Fujiko-san!
The confidence you get from knowing
that Inokuma Yawara is in the wings.
That was amazing, Fujiko-san!
The confidence you get from knowing
that Inokuma Yawara is in the wings.
I also felt a huge rush when I saw Inokuma take the gold medal at the World Cup.
I have to say, that's Inokuma for you.
That's Saito-san, who blushes whenever Inokuma is mentioned.
A-Again?
Don't be silly!
Looks like we won't be needing you.
Fujiko-san!
You did great, Fujiko-san!
Hanazono-san!
You can do it!
Keep up that pace, and you'll win it all!
O-Oh, come on!
There are so many strong players. You know I can't...
I, Hanazono Kaoru, am here for you! You'll be fine!
Hanazono-san...
Hey, how was my Deashi Barai?
It was totally awesome!
But Fujiko-san's Ouchi Gari was out of sight!
Hey, Fujiko—
Come on, leave her alone!
What?
First Round, Match Five, Court B:
Ferras Women's College vs. Kuroyuri Women's Sports College.
Move it.
To... Todo-san?!
Who are you calling a "sea lion"?
Note: Todo means "sea lion" in Japanese.
Tohdoh-san?
Been a while.
Yes, it has.
It has been a while since I last fought you!
See you in the second round.
We're facing Todo-san's team in the second round?
Looks like it.
I will atone for the honor I lost two years ago!
She's strong, very strong indeed!
Though the other Seishin Women's competitors are mere ciphers,
Honami continues to win with frightening fury!
Uchi Mata. Ippon!
She advances to the semis!
Now if MWJC also advances, we'll finally have the long-awaited rematch between the fated rivals!
The rematch between Inokuma and Honami!
A rematch between fated rivals?
But before you fight Yawara...
you have a big job ahead of you, Miss Sayaka.
We will now hold the second match of the second round,
between Mitsuba Women's Junior College and Kuroyuri Women's Sports College.
All right, time to kick some more butt!
Yahoo, time for some more TV coverage!
Time to lose some more weight!
Come on, we have to go, Fujiko-san!
B-But look at who we're up against!
Last year, Kuroyuri College was the runner-up in this tournament.
And this year, they definitely don't lack intensity!
Todo-san looks scary!
You're right.
The whole thing'll be over if you don't move it.
First players, forward!
Okay!
Her opponents this time around won't be nearly as easy to beat.
Bow!
Hajime!
Yeah, yeah. Bring it on.
Oh!
You make all sorts of noises, don't you?
Oh, no! Once she pulls you in, she'll do a Deashi Barai!
Ippon! Done!
They are strong!
Ow...
She threw you down in the blink of an eye. Lame!
Not like you're gonna win anyway!
I'll just go and take that spotlight.
Are you okay?
Ow... She didn't have to throw me so hard!
Hajime!
Oh God, it's like beet red!
I didn't even get a chance to hog the spotlight!
You lost already?
Are you okay, Marilyn?
Third player, forward!
Hang in there, Yoshinagawa-san!
Maybe I should quit my diet.
Bow!
Hajime!
Don't let her grab you so fast, Yoshinagawa-san!
Get out of there, Yoshinagawa-san!
Yoshinagawa-san!
Ippon! Done!
Yes! Now whup that beanpole!
Get her, Fujiwara!
This is bad.
Let's see what you've got, Beanpole.
I-I can't! I can't win against them!
God, this sucks...
MWJC's vice captain, Ito Fujiko-kun!
Honey, stop right here!
Let's see, one, two, three... Cabbie, can you make small change?
Honey, forget about the change! Come on, hurry up!
Sign: 8th Annual Ajisai Cup Women's Intermural Tournament
Her match will end if we don't hurry!
Honestly, dear! You're always, always, always slow!
I forgot the receipt!
MWJC is in real trouble.
Kuroyuri's first player, Fujiwara, has beaten MWJC's first three.
And now she's facing their vice captain, Ito Fujiko!
Hajime!
Fujiko-san! Relax!
Get her for the three of us!
Fujiwara, don't go easy on her!
Kick her butt!
Sorry. I-I'm sorry. If you please...
Excuse us. Sorry.
Where? Where is she?
O-Oh... dear!
Fujiko!
She's actually playing judo!
Dear, stop her now!
She's too delicate to participate in such a violent sport!
Stop her? Are you...
I shouldn't have let her go to Tokyo!
I didn't make her practice ballet for over ten years just to see her in judo!
Fujiko-san! Don't stand upright!
Un, deux, trois!
I can't. She's too strong!
I don't even have time to say "un, deux, trois"!
It'll be fine, you can do it!
Un, deux, trois.
Un, deux, trois. Un, deux, trois. Un, deux, trois.
Un!
...deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois!
Un... deux...
Now!
trois!
Ippon!
Done!
She did it! Ito did it again with her Ouchi Gari!
Huh, what's going on?
It looks like she won.
Eh?
Fujiko won!
You're kidding me!
I mean it!
Timing: Juggen               Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
Eyecatch
DVD Provider: CP
Juggen, skr
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, kokujin-kun
Timing: Juggen               Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
Eyecatch
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, kokujin-kun
Juggen, skr
DVD Provider: CP
Keep it up! Keep it up!
Pound them into the pavement!
Come on, you know I can't!
Forward!
That was just dumb luck! Put her down, Ikarashi!
She's just tall, is all!
Wh-Why can't she be normal?
Hang in there, Fujiko-san!
Who on earth made her do this?
Hajime!
Get her, Fujiko-san! She's just heavy!
Just do what I taught you personally, and you'll win!
Remember, un, deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois...
You taught her personally ?
So you're the one?!
You're the one who dragged my daughter into judo?!
Wh-What do you mean?
Un, deux, trois. Un, deux, trois...
What will you do if she injures that nubile body before marriage?
How dare you?! How dare you?!
Trois!
Ippon!
She did it.
She's awesome!
Looking good!
Good. Very good.
Father? Mother?
M-My name is Hanazono Kaoru from Ebiten Sports College!
Who cares about that?
Are you going to take responsibility?
Responsibility? But I haven't done anything to her.
We have no idea where this match is headed now!
Thanks to a strong showing by MWJC's vice captain, Ito Fujiko,
Kuroyuri is now sending out their third player!
Watch out for her Ouchi Gari, you hear?!
Take her out, Miyoko!
Leave her to me, Sis.
The fearsome Ohtawara twins are the great hopes for the heavyweight division
in the Barcelona Olympics. Here's the younger of the two, the third player, Ohtawara Miyoko!
Sh-She looks like a monster!
Hajime!
This time, the younger Ohtawara is watching out for that Ouchi Gari by lowering her stance!
Sh-She's very strong!
Now pin her down!
Fujiko!
Wow, now that's flexibility!
She evades the younger Ohtawara's Osaekomi with a body bridge!
Jougai! Mate!
She's incredibly flexible, Saito-san!
I call that a treasure!
A flexible body is the most valuable treasure a judo player can have.
Fujiko! I didn't let you practice ballet so you could do that!
So how will you make this right?
Look! We aren't in that type of relationship.
Why, you...
Quit twisting and turning all over the place!
Un... deux... trois!
Ippon! Ito got her with another Ouchi Gari!
This is more than I expected.
That obstacle is stronger and thicker than I imagined.
It's now a standoff between the two vice captains!
Here comes Ohtawara the elder.
Sh-She looks just the same!
Wait, if she keeps on winning, we won't see Inokuma Yawara again!
Come on, get out there, Yawara-chan!
That's right!
Right behind Ito, the team captain, Inokuma Yawara, is waiting in the wings!
Kuroyuri College really needs to defeat Ito right here!
Hajime!
Take a fall, Beanpole!
That's enough!
Send out Inokuma!
Why are you telling my daughter to lose?!
Her name's not "Beanpole," it's Fujiko!
Un... deux...
Watch out!
It's Ohtawara with a Tomoe Nage!
And Ito holds on!
Jougai! Mate!
She fended off Ito's Ouchi Gari and gave her a Tomoe Nage, Saito-san!
Indeed, Ohtawara really needs to get her in a grappling hold!
Inokuma-san...
I can't go on!
Don't worry. She'll try another Tomoe Nage!
When she does, give her your un, deux, trois!
Hajime!
I don't quite get it!
Get her!
One more time, Sis!
Un, deux...
Trois!
Ippon!
See, you did it!
That was so cool!
I don't know how, but I just won again!
Wow!
I'm pleased!
MWJC's vice captain, Ito Fujiko, is pulverizing her opponents!
She now faces the All-Japan Selected Judo Championships
72 kg heavyweight titleholder, Tohdoh Yuki!
To... Todo-san's scary!
Wh-What should I do?
Don't think about it. Just win it for us!
I can't! It's literally impossible!
Relax, you still have your un, deux, trois!
And even if you lose, we still have Yawara-chan!
Right, Yawara-chan?
You can win!
I know you can win, Fujiko-san!
Right now, you can beat anyone with your Ouchi Gari!
But I can't!
Come forward!
Bow!
You can just take a hike, for all I care.
The only opponent I want to face...
is Inokuma Yawara!
I-Is Fujiko going up against that behemoth?!
I'm putting a stop to this.
I am definitely putting a stop to this!
Ah, Mother!
I don't recall... allowing you to even call me "Mother."
You know you can't put a stop to this!
What are you doing to my wife?
Hajime!
Stop this, Fujiko!
Oh, my God! Todo-san is so heavy and strong!
Come on, quit wriggling around!
Ah! Now, Fujiko-san!
Un... deux... trois!
She did it!
Ito Fujiko has beaten all five!
All right!
All right, Fujiko!
Ito Fujiko has beaten all five!
All right!
Oh, wait! It's a Jougai!
Her feet were already out of bounds while doing that move!
That can't be!
Fujiko just won, right, dear?
This is no time to be excited!
Right you are.
I'm stopping this!
Wait, dear!
That was a fearsome Ouchi Gari.
But don't think you can last long in judo as a...
one-trick pony!
Tohdoh goes for a Kouchi Gari. Look out, Ito Fujiko!
Ito hangs on by standing on tiptoes with one foot! What great balance!
Un... deux... trois!
Yuko!
It's a Yuko! After balancing herself on tiptoes to avoid Tohdoh's Kouchi Gari,
Ito comes back with her Ouchi Gari!
Oh, no! Get out of there now!
Oh! Tohdoh immediately goes for a grappling hold after taking a Yuko!
Get around it!
Get out of there, Fujiko-san!
Get her, Tohdoh-senpai!
Pin her down, and we'll win!
Osaekomi!
Tohdoh has her in a tight Yoko Shiho Gatame!
Ito Fujiko is unable to move an inch!
What? What on earth is she doing to you, Fujiko?!
You! Stop that!
Please, get up!
Ten seconds in!
Don't give up, Fujiko-san! Move!
I reckon I'll have to teach her about grappling holds next time.
Twist your hips around! Raise your upper body!
I'll finally get to fight you, Inokuma Yawara!
Get up, Fujiko!
Don't lose, Fujiko!
Ippon!
Ito Fujiko is finally defeated!
Tohdoh Yuki showed us why she's the heavyweight titleholder!
She's not letting a white belt have five straight wins!
But you gotta hand it to Ito for getting this far!
She performed a real feat by beating four of Kuroyuri's tank squadron.
The auditorium is applauding for her as well!
You did great, Fujiko!
Though I'm not sure how.
Honey!
Sh-She's a magnificent woman!
Fujiko-san is truly fantastic!
That's because she's our daughter.
Yes. That was our own daughter!
Mother... Father.
In any case, I don't remember letting you off the hook!
I swear, it's not like that between us!
I'm sorry.
What are you saying? You beat four of them!
You were totally awesome, Fujiko-san!
But...
Forget it, I'm done!
Fujiko-san!
Yawara-chan, take her out!
Fujiko-san fought hard out there, you know!
I'm not worried!
Todo-san is no match for Inokuma-san!
She's finally here! MWJC's team captain, Inokuma Yawara!
This is her first official match since the World Cup!
The excitement from that day is coming alive once again!
Here she is.
Inokuma.
Inokuma Yawara.
Yawara.
You really went out with a bang, Beanpole.
But you'll always be the main attraction, Yawara.
This won't be like the last time.
I've studied your Ippon Zeoi thoroughly.
Hajime!
The Barcelona Olympics in 439 Days
Fujiko-san was so close!
She almost had five straight wins!
All right, Yawara. You're up!
But isn't it amazing how she beat four of them, Grandpa?
Yawara! You'd better get that Ippon in five — no, one second!
Yawara!
You Can Do It, Kyonkyon!
You'll be getting my Ouchi Gari if you don't watch!
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
But why can I not? I really don't know.
koe ni dashite ienai no?
You're standing here by my side.
ima anata ga iru
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
I say as I look for your smile.
egao wo sagashite