m 0 0 l 100 0 l 100 100 l 0 100
Presented by FroZen-EviL!
Inokuma goes for a Tomoe Nage!
Yuko!
Yuko! Inokuma's Tomoe Nage earns her a Yuko!
She gets a danged Yuko all 'cause she got cold feet the first time!
Y-You're right. She did hesitate that one time.
She used that Tomoe Nage against her dad when she was five.
Huh?
She beat her dad with that move?
Father!
Still, the fact she used that move means she's gotten past everything.
The match isn't over by a long shot, Yawara.
The real fight begins now.
Ever Since I Met You...
Only fifteen seconds left!
Honami will be looking to recover with one of her Newazas,
but Inokuma, who now has the lead, will probably avoid any direct engagement!
Well, if Honami can use her overwhelming Newazas, it's still anyone's game!
"Has the lead," my patootie!
If she's even thinking about winning on points, I ain't taking her to Barcelona!
A Yuko? Our feud will not end with a damned Yuko!
Only fifteen seconds left. Don't you dare evade me!
Come and fight me, Inokuma Yawara!
The death match of the century has come down to this!
Will Inokuma maintain her lead, or will Honami make a huge comeback?!
Hajime!
Fight me, Inokuma Yawara!
Whoa!
Both players... are engaging each...
Don't!
Ip...
Ippon!
Done!
Banzai!
I-Inokuma Yawara gets an Ippon win with her Ippon Zeoi!
It's done! She's won the death match! Holy cow!
Even with her injured right arm,
she unleashed a powerful Ippon Zeoi!
Just incredible!
Honami's still down! She's too dumbfounded to get up!
Wow, holy crap!
Oh, tomorrow's headline... Let's see. Oh, yeah!
Did you get that, Kamoda?!
Yeah!
H-Hey, let us through!
Yawara-chan!
Honami had been watching out for Inokuma's Ippon Zeoi the entire match!
Yes, but she got desperate after she fell behind on points!
Inokuma made magnificent use of that momentary lapse!
It took her that long? Retraining!
There were only three seconds left on the clock!
That Ippon came literally at the last moment!
Inokuma has won the 48 kg-and-unders!
Sayaka-san.
Oh, take a look at this! Inokuma Yawara has approached Honami's side!
You were incredibly strong, Sayaka-san.
But I really had fun. I hope we play another match.
Wha—
Also, you lost your false tooth again.
Oh! Inokuma has taken Honami's hand!
What a moving handshake! They are now receiving a thunderous ovation!
They did great! These two players have done splendidly!
This wasn't what you promised!
What did you mean, Sayaka-san will definitely win?
Yawara-chan won!
I thought you were going to take Yawara-chan after she lost to Sayaka-san! Now what?
Actually, this works out.
No, it doesn't!
You were supposed to take Yawara-chan while I took Kosaku.
It's fine.
If Sayaka-san loses, there will be another fateful showdown, and our marriage will be put on hold.
Shin-chan's outta trouble!
Hello, status and prestige!
Congratulations!
That was an incredible Ippon Zeoi!
Give us your thoughts!
Ow! Stop shoving!
Matsuda-san?
Yawara-san!
Inokuma!
Guys...
Ino... Ino... Ino...
Fujiko-san!
Inokuma-san!
Congratulations!
Inokuma Yawara is now on the Barcelona Olympic team!
Yawara.
This will be a nice victory party.
Yes!
Milady, please get in the car! I'll handle things here!
Miss Honami, a comment!
Please!
Over here!
A comment?
Honami!
"Fun"?
She said it was f-fun?
Milady!
All-Japan Women's Selected Judo Championship Barcelona Olympics Final Qualifying Tournament#
Retraining!
But first we'll have our big victory party!
So will you fine gentlemen be coming along? There will be boat-wrap sushi sets!
Is it true? I can go to Barcelona?
Not just "can"!
You're the official 61 kg-and-under representative on the Olympic team, Ms. Ito Fujiko!
No, right now I'm Mrs. Hanazono Fujiko!
Indeed, you are. Going to the Olympics as a "Mama-san athlete" is a brilliant achievement.
Be sure to show us in Barcelona
how strong a mother can really be!
Ah, the mic!
Don't, Fuku-chan! Spit it out!
Stop that, Fuku-chan! Spit it!
My mic...
Oh yeah, where did our star,
Inokuma Yawara, head off to?
Mm-hmm. So you watched, Mom?
My arm? It's fine. Grandpa took care of it.
I feel sorry for you, Mom. Grandpa has invited a lot of reporters to our house.
Dad was at our house?
He was! We watched your matches on TV together!
He did?
Where is he now?
Well, right now he's...
H-He left already.
But still, your father said...
That was a brilliant match.
Please tell Yawara...
that she did really great.
Why don't you tell that to Yawara yourself? She'll be back soon, you know.
No.
I have to get to the airport.
When I went to France with Miss Sayaka,
their judo team invited me to be their coach.
But...
But you don't have to leave so soon.
This time I'm not running or hiding from her.
Once I've settled down in Paris, I'll send her my address.
So... So that means... that means?
Yeah, I know I've made her worry all these years.
When the time comes, we'll stroll down the Champs-Élysées as father and daughter.
But...
only after the Barcelona Olympics.
Make sure Yawara knows...
that an even stronger opponent awaits her in Barcelona.
She must not lower her guard for a second, not until she leaves Barcelona.
Yawara, did you hear that? That's what your father said before he left!
The Champs-Élysées! You'll stroll down the Champs-Élysées with your father!
That's in Paris!
Yawara, are you listening?
Yes.
I'm listening.
I'm glad for you, Mom.
I'm really glad.
Really.
eye catch
Translation: kokujin-kun
Editing: Collectr
Encoding: toster     Timing: sangofe
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, Saji
\h                  Juggen
DVD Provider: CP
Honami Sayaka's Championship Victory Party
I cannot express my solemn appreciation that you would grace me with your presence!
I, Honami Sayaka, have attained numerous brilliant achievements!
Winner of the World Horse Racing Championship!
Winner of the European Skiing Open!
The one who bested Navratilova in tennis!
The one who mesmerized the crowds with her rhythmic gymnastics!
Plus other countless and glorious accomplishments!
Indeed, I have ruled as the queen everywhere I have gone!
There is nothing left that I have yet to attain!
Ladies and gentlemen,
for me, as I now sit atop of the world,
a toast!
Well, I welcome you, Kazamatsuri-san. Please, enjoy yourself tonight.
This is a magnificent party, Sayaka-san.
Also, that was a magnificent match you played.
How right you are. The victory should have been mine.
No, I was the real victor.
If it weren't for that Tomoe Nage,
that sneaky Tomoe Nage she did while faking the "injury" my Jyuji Gatame did to her arm,
I would have had her groveling on that mat!
Also, despite the fact she struggled mightily against me,
she had the nerve to engage in false bravado after the match!
She said, "I had fun! Let's play again!"
Honestly, how much of a twisted and desperate sore loser is that Inokuma Yawara?
Actually...
That wasn't false bravado, Sayaka-san.
That's who Yawara-san really is.
Yawara-san truly enjoys herself when she plays against a highly competent rival.
If she played against a really strong opponent,
she'd still say those words, even if she lost.
"I had fun."
Sayaka-san, Yawara-san has acknowledged your skills.
She sees you as a really strong judoka.
I couldn't care less!
Sayaka-san!
I don't need an Inokuma Yawara to recognize my strength!
I... I don't need her to tell me that I'm strong!
Sayaka-san...
I'm strong! There is nothing I cannot attain!
Not before, not now, and not from here on out!
I'm...
Sayaka-san, you're absolutely right. You are strong. You're...
Sayaka-san... is crying?
She's so arrogant, so domineering, so defiant, the very definition of "prideful."
And now she's crying.
Huh?
Wh-What's happening?
W-Wait...
Impossible!
Sayaka-san...
Congratulations, Milady!
...then you are a true Kuroda warrior!
Brilliant, Master!
Here's Hanazono!
Way to go!
Oh! I'm going to dance too!
I'd better not see you stripping!
Stop it, Hanazono-san!
Fujiko!
We're so happy, Fujiko!
We're going to Barcelona. It's good to be alive!
Fujiko, I'm so proud of you!
You're the world's number one daughter!
Okay, okay, I get it!
Eat up! And add 500 more sushi!
Okay, so your father said that.
Don't lower your guard until you leave Barcelona, huh?
Yes.
I still gotta say, your match was really amazing.
I hope we get to see more good matches in Barcelona.
It's thanks to you, Matsuda-san.
Huh?
Win, Yawara-san!
Win and go to Barcelona!
Get the Olympic gold medal!
Don't take away my dream!
If you weren't rooting for me, I would surely have lost.
Yeah, right!
Yawara-san.
Uh, well...
Uh, I...
I...
Ever... Ever since I met you...
I've always li—
...liked them gold medals!
Good Luck, Yawara-chan
Guts! Fujiko-san!
Yes, ever since I met you...
Ever since I laid eyes on you... I've always...
owari no kane ga natte kimi ga seki wo tatsu
The final bell rang, and you left your seat.
ki ga tsukeba itsudemo kimi dake wo mitsumeteta
Before I knew it, I was staring at you.
boku no soba de kimi wa chigau koi ni hikarete
But you flirted with others right beside me
omowazu boku wa ashi wo sukumeteshimatta ne
and I unconsciously retreated back.
peeji wo meguru to itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
Whenever I turned the page, there you were.
nooto no rakugaki itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
You were also in the scribbles of my notebook.
arubamu wo nagamete wa natsukashiku omounda
Looking at my photo album takes me back.
nigiyakana sazameki ga mimi ni nn kodama suru
The bustling sounds from back then still ring in my ears.
peeji wo meguru to itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
Whenever I turned the page, there you were.
nooto no rakugaki itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
You were also in the scribbles of my notebook.
sugiyuku toki no naka de ano toki no
As the days go past, I wonder what
nakama wa ima nani wo katatteiru darou
my friends from back then are talking about now?
peeji wo meguru to itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
Whenever I turned the page, there you were.
nooto no rakugaki itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
You were also in the scribbles of my notebook.
peeji wo meguru to itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
Whenever I turned the page, there you were.
nooto no rakugaki itsumo soko ni kimi ga ita
You were also in the scribbles of my notebook.
Go get 'em, Yawara-san! Do your Ippon Zeoi!
Thank you for watching! –FroZen-EviL#