Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
In the end, Hikari couldn't
turn down Hideo's request.
She ended up agreeing to go on a date with Sagawa.
I thought she'd be safe
because Hideo was watching.
And that led to this debacle.
Episode 30
Hikari's Lie, Hiro's Tears
But really, where the heck could they have gone ?
Hey !
Huh ?
Are you actually looking for her ?
Yeah, I am.
You're just wandering around...
Hey, wait up, Hide !
Danger:  Do Not Touch
I'm surprised.
Me, too.
Knowing you, I didn't
think you were serious.
I'm amazed.
I couldn't have imagined a beautiful girl like her.
Give it up, Risa !
You're no match for her !
Don't just stand there !
Come on down !
I hear that this idiot barged into your apartment the other day.
Yeah.
If only she'd known that you had a beautiful girlfriend like her...
...she wouldn't have done a stupid thing like that.
Sorry to trouble you.
I've been telling you. I've got
nothing to do with your girlfriend.
Yeah, I know.
This idiot has one-sidedly fallen for you.
Let go of me already !
I haven't seen you in a while.
Why don't we go get something to eat ?
Sure.
You have other plans, right ?
What ?
Oh, yes, yes.
Then you can leave now.
Yeah, sure.
Hold it !
She's way too beautiful.
I just can't believe it.
Are you two really going out ?
If you two are really dating...
...why don't you kiss each other,
right in front of our eyes ?
If you do, Risa will no
longer follow you around...
...and I can go home
with peace of mind.
She's fine.
It's Shuu, after all.
But you only knew him
up until five years ago.
But Shuu is still Shuu.
Oh ? You're certain ?
Yeah.
Then, shall we stop looking for her ?
Perhaps...
Hey, give me a break.
Unlike you, our relationship is pure.
Besides, it's been less than a
month since we started going out.
I guess you're right.
Keyaki
Hiroshima-style,
Okonomiyaki
What are we doing here,
grilling an okonomiyaki like this ?
This restaurant used to
be an old haunt of ours.
You told me that already.
What I'm saying is, we could just look inside, and then go elsewhere if we didn't find Hikari !
But...
Really, I haven't seen
you in a long time.
You've gotten bigger...
...but your face is still the same as it
was when you were in grade school !
I'm so happy to see you !
Me, too...
When she's acting so happy, do you
actually think that we can just take off ?
And look ! She treated
us to a serving of this.
Hmm...
Anyway, just eat !
It's tasty !
Then let's do this.
Let me spend an hour with
your girlfriend, just me and her.
That's okay, right, Shuu ?
I mean, you had a date
with Risa once, too.
But that's because she forced me...!
Just one hour.
I'm saying that'll make us even.
Keyaki
Now where are we going to look ?
I'm not sure.
He's your childhood friend, isn't he ?
You should know
where he might go.
If it's not here...
Where ?!
It might be the ramen
shop we used to go to.
Let go of her.
What did you just say ?
I said let go of her.
Stop it, Shuu. You know that Jin's uncontrollable when he gets mad.
I'm sure you didn't forget.
I broke two of your ribs, after all.
Thank you !
They weren't here.
I guess not.
What do you mean, "I guess not" ?
Hey, Hide !
Huh ?
I don't want to say it, but
aren't you awfully casual ?
Really ?
It's okay.
Hikari is your girlfriend.
It's none of my business.
Hey, Hiro !
Back then, I wasn't trying to kill you.
But this time, it's different.
Two broken ribs won't
end the fight today.
If you don't want to be killed, you should kill me.
She's an important person.
I have to protect her,
even if it costs my life.
Interesting.
Okay, I get it.
This is what you do to a friend who came all the way here to see you ?
We're going home, Risa.
Sure...
I'm breaking it off with you, moron !
I guess we scared you.
This is terrible.
My legs are shaking.
What a friend you have.
When you transfer to a school
where you don't know anyone...
...the easiest way to make friends is to enter the circle of bad guys.
You don't seem to have
good social skills, after all.
I wonder if I should thank you.
There's no need.
I plan to have Hide-chan take care of me for the foreseeable future.
I don't want him to break
it off with me right now.
There's a great okonomiyaki place nearby.
Do you want to go ?
You're done with me, right ?
I guess.
You brat !
Don't underestimate me !
Take that...!
Which way is the train station ?
Do you know ?
It's probably this way.
Okay then.
Well, I guess I'll go home and study for the entrance exam.
Entrance exam...?
Yeah, I don't want to get a job yet.
I plan to go to high school.
Hey, you're younger than me ?
Huh ? Hide-chan didn't tell you ?
Not a word !
Hmm ?
Stop it !
What're you talking about now ?
It's okay, right ? Right ?
But...
I mean...
Hey !
What is it ?
Um, have you seen a
suspicious man around here ?
Oh, thank you.
Sorry about that.
Dammit !
Why should I care ?!
She's your girlfriend !
You should...
...take care of her !
Amamiya
I'm home !
Oh, Hiro. Hikari is here.
What ?
I let her into your room.
What're you doing in
here with the lights off ?
Where were you ?
Didn't you promise me that you'd watch over me and rescue me ?
Um, well...
Liar.
Hikari...
What happened ?
He said he was
meeting up with a friend...
...and took me to a deserted
factory site with three chimneys.
I trusted that you'd come save me.
Hiro ?
Hey !
You're late.
Yeah.
What happened to your face ?
Um...
Did Shuu do it ?
No. I was walking absent-mindedly, and bumped into a signboard.
I see.
Hmm ? What's this ?
So this Shuu guy
really is a troublemaker ?
What ? Um, well...
You're acting suspiciously.
I see. His friend did come.
So you were a little suspicious of him ?
Hiro was.
I knew it was going to be okay.
Really ?
I guess I was a little worried, too.
It's been five years, after all.
Back then, he was like
my real younger brother.
I could always tell
what he was up to.
He's not the only one who's changed in five years.
Are you talking about me ?
Even though you couldn't
go to the Koushien...
...you've been featured
in all kinds of media...
...and you've become a celebrity who
gets letters from fans all over the country.
You've become too distant a figure for
him to just feel happy about your reunion.
Especially since he had
fallen in with bad company.
But I wondered if he had completely quit.
What ?
Baseball, I mean.
I'm not sure.
Come to think of it, I wonder if Hiro is still out there looking for you.
That's right, you should call him.
I think he should be home by now.
Hikari.
Huh ?
Call him.
Oh, right.
Oh, Hiro ? That's right.
There's no need to worry.
Yeah, bye.
Okay, I'll get him this time !
Sorry about what happened today.
It's okay.
Okay.
See you.
Yeah.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Tachibana Hideo:
Hiro's Mother:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Takizawa Kumiko
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Jin:
Risa:
Guy:
Girl:
Ohtsuka Akio
Kanai Mika
Chiba Isshin
Konishi Hiroko
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
The cheek that you
slapped is still swollen.
There's something more important going on.
The final game of the fall tournament.
Meiwa Daiichi's opponent is Eikyou High School, which features the ace pitcher, Hirota.
Because of his refreshing smile, his popularity is rising fast.
But he's kind of weird.
Yeah, he seems to have a dark side to him.
He made a signal predicting a strikeout on Hide-chan.
Next episode of H2 is,
"A New Rival ! Eikyou's Hirota."
Next episode of H2 is
A New Rival ! Eikyou's Hirota
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?