Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Fall Tournament, the final game.
Hideo's Meiwa Daiichi is playing against...
...Eikyou High School, which features the ace pitcher, Hirota Katsutoshi.
Hirota declares a strikeout, and then hits Hideo.
Hideo...
Episode 32
Genius Tachibana
An At-Bat Full of Spirit
Tachibana !
He's more timid than I thought.
He let the ball get away because
he was scared of Hideo's presence.
But for someone who was scared, he had great arm motion.
He's right.
Ball three.
Ball four.
So he pretends to be
shaken after hitting a batter.
Strike !
You mean to say he
did it on purpose ?
No one's saying that.
There's no evidence.
It's something that
only he himself knows.
Sure Victory ! Eikyou High School
If he were in bad shape, they'd pinch-run for him.
Do you think Hide-chan would leave the game midway ?
Strike ! Batter out !
Are you okay, Tachibana ?
I'll never say I can't play.
If you feel I'm not okay,
please feel free to say so.
Okay then.
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
Hirota.
You should keep it to one hit-by-pitch per game.
I got a little tense and
let the ball get away.
It wasn't on purpose.
Of course not.
But your arm motion
was the same as always.
It would be bad if people get
the wrong idea, so be careful.
I understand.
Certain
Victory
Win! Meiwa Nine
Victory for Meiwa!
Meiwa
Good Luck!
Out !
Certain Victory! Eikyou High School
Good Luck
Give It Your Best, Eikyou Nine
They're such high-level performers.
It must feel great to
coach teams like those.
But if they're this good from the start, it probably doesn't feel as rewarding.
Our team will soon be able to play the game at this level.
Right, Kunimi ?
Where's Kunimi ?
Hey !
I'm getting some food !
I'll come with you.
What ?
Shall we buy some
rice crackers for Noda ?
Are you sure we can ?
We have to have him act like a coach from time to time.
This is my brother's wallet.
I see.
This time, you're
buying me one, Hikari.
Okay, sure.
Go on ahead !
I'm going to take a look !
Foul.
Oh.
Just a foul ball.
Thank you.
What happened ?
It was just a foul ball.
Tomoko, sorry for the wait.
Here, this one's yours, Kunimi.
Here, this is for you, Hikari.
Hello.
I'm worried about Tachibana.
Yes.
He'll be fine.
He's a tough guy.
What ?
He'll be fine.
He's a tough guy, he says.
That's right...
That's right, she says.
Um...
Let's go.
See you.
Bye.
Kunimi !
Did something happen
between you and Hikari ?
No, not really.
Honestly, it was a hard hit.
Are you talking about the pitch that hit Tachibana ?
I guess.
Hikari ! Hikari !
Why are you spacing out ?
Tachibana is coming up next.
That's right.
If I were Meiwa's coach, I'd give him this advice.
Return him the favor and hit him good.
It's not that easy. The game has been scoreless so far.
They're playing this
game at a high level.
Aim for the Koushien
Such a high caliber performer...
Honestly.
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
He'll get another at-bat.
I'll have to make sure that I don't
get tense and let the ball slip away.
Good job, Tachibana.
Great job, Hideo.
It's amazing.
You're amazing !
Fukui.
Yes ?
You're going in as
the third baseman.
Okay, Tachibana ?
Yes.
Batter out !
Three outs. Change.
He slammed the door on the rest.
Yeah.
But that run Hideo put
on the board is huge.
He hits a homerun after
getting hit by a pitch.
Star players really know
how to distinguish themselves.
How many swings do you think Hide-chan takes every day, to hit that homerun ?
Meiwa Daiichi High School,
third baseman, Tachibana is out.
Iwakiri
Shimoike
Murabe
Tachibana
Nakai
Tachikawa
Fukui will replace him.
Fukui
V   Victory
Show Your Mettle
Do Your Best
He would have made one more plate appearance.
Yeah.
Is it because of that hit-by-pitch ?
Who knows ?
Hide-chan !
Hey !
Are you okay ?
It's nothing. Coach told me to go to the hospital and have it looked at, just in case.
I see.
Continue to cheer for the team, okay ?
Strike ! Batter out !
So cool !
How was Hideo ?
He went to the hospital.
So, how's the game ?
He's been declaring strikeouts every
time he gets two strikes on a batter.
He's got eleven strikeouts so far.
Strike !
He gets double-digit
strikeouts on Meiwa...
I wonder whose pitch is faster.
Kunimi's is faster, by far !
Great, huh ? Haruka's eyes
are biased, but they're good.
Oh, I see.
Strike two !
Strike ! Batter out !
Three outs ! Change !
Ogasawara
Arai
"Ogasawara, Arai, Hirota, Kokubu, Suzuki"}
This is such a great game.
Of course !
Meiwa's Ichinose Makoto,
Eikyou's Hirota Katsutoshi.
They're two of the best lefty ace pitchers in Kantou.
Was Hirota perhaps in Shizuoka when he was in junior high ?
Yeah, that's right.
Coach Shiroyama discovered
him and recruited him over here.
Coach Shiroyama is amazing. He found an incredible pitcher.
Hirota Katsutoshi...
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
Yeah, it was fine. We won.
More importantly,
how is your elbow ?
What ?
You kept the powerful Meiwa lineup
to four hits, and got twelve strikeouts.
Nice pitching, Hirota.
It doesn't mean much if the team loses.
The only run you gave up is the homerun by Tachibana. You came really close.
He totally deceived me.
I guess I didn't have to worry about the effect that my hitting him had.
No, apparently, the examination at the hospital showed that he has a fracture.
He had a fracture and still hit a homerun ? I feel ashamed.
Well, you went easy on him, right ?
That's right. You declared a
strikeout on him in the first at-bat.
Oh, please give me a break.
I've told you this many times.
It's just a habit I have, when I try to pull myself together.
The strikeouts are just coincidental.
Oh, don't say that.
More importantly,
will Tachibana be okay ?
Fortunately, there's plenty of time before the Invitational.
I hope he makes a quick recovery and comes back slugging like he has been.
Otherwise, I'll seem like a villain.
I'm looking forward to your Invitational appearance !
I'll go see your
game at the Koushien !
I'll go cheer for you !
Thanks for your work !
Hey.
Did you come to cheer
for your childhood friend ?
I plan to have Hide-chan take
care of me for a while, after all.
What's the point of telling me that ?
The real bad guys keep quiet and
smile secretly when no one's watching.
Right ?
Yeah.
See ya.
It's Hirota !
Hirota !
Please look this way !
The real bad guys keep quiet and
smile secretly when no one's watching.
He's right.
Good luck !
Hirota !
Restroom
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hurry it up.
Okay.
Hi.
It's been a while.
I saw you just a bit ago.
This is the first time we've talked since you slapped me hard in the face.
I mean, whose fault was that ?
It was mine.
That's why I didn't punch you back.
Is Hideo okay ?
He has a fracture.
What ?
I was just told on the phone.
And he still hit that homerun ?
For pitchers,
he's such a nasty hitter.
Are you waiting for someone ?
Yeah. Tomoko is in the bathroom.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
What ?
I'm telling you, it was my fault.
Umm...but resorting to violence is...
...sometimes necessary, I think.
There are some things you
don't learn until you're slapped.
What did you learn ?
I learned that Hiro...
What is it ?
...is a good guy.
You want me to slap you again ?
I dare you. Right here !
You little...!
I'm gonna do it !
There ! There !
It hurts ! How dare you !
There ! There ! There !
Haruka !
Let's go !
Sure !
Wait up, Big Brother !
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Koyasu Takehito
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Meiwa Coach:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Tomoko:
Umpire:
Announcer:
Fangirl A:
Naka Hiroshi
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Neya Michiko
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
Shimazaki Noriko
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
You're going to play an invitational game for Senkawa's school festival, right ?
Yeah, against Eikyou, where Hirota, who broke Hideo's arm, plays.
I suppose it's a fated face-off.
It seems something had happened between Sagawa and Hirota, too.
Eikyou's Coach Shiroyama tried to recruit you once, didn't he ?
Anyway, it's just part of the school festival. I'm going to take it easy.
Next episode of H2 is, "Senkawa Festival:  Welcome, Eikyou High School !"
Next episode of H2 is
Senkawa Festival:
Welcome, Eikyou High School !
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?