Original file: DH2:H2Ep33.txt.js
H2, Episode #33, "Senkawa Festival: Welcome, Eikyou High School !"
0:00:10.00 0:00:11.00
0:07:44.00 0:07:45.00
0:07:46.00 0:07:47.00  from right to left, "Takoyaki" "Yakisoba"}
0:08:22.00 0:08:23.00
0:08:32.00 0:08:33.00
Note: this is a pun. The word "tateshima" [pinstripes] means "vertical stripes."
The word for "evil" that Shuu uses, "yokoshima," can phonetically mean "horizontal stripes."
He's saying, "Vertical stripes don't look good on you because you're a horizontal stripe-type [i.e. evil]}
Processed by Central Anime's NUMIT On 07/15/2013
0:00:26.00 0:00:27.00
0:00:32.00 0:00:33.00
Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Eikyou's ace pitcher, Hirota
Katsutoshi, hit Hideo with a pitch.
But in his next at-bat, Hideo gets a hit
off him despite having a fractured arm.
Seeing how great Hideo was, we resolved our small disagreement.
Episode 33
Senkawa Festival
Welcome, Eikyou High School
This is an announcement.
Those on the Senkawa
Festival Executive Committee...
...please report to the
Biology Room immediately.
I repeat.
Those on the Senkawa
Festival Executive Committee...
Senkawa Festival
...please report to the
Biology Room immediately.
Baseball Club
An invitational game ?
We're playing baseball
during the cultural festival ?
Yeah.
I thought it would be a great opportunity to meet girls from other schools...
Don't worry about that.
It's not like we'll play
the game all day long.
It's just one game.
After that, you're free.
That's good.
So who's our opponent ?
Now don't be shocked when you hear !
It's...
Hold it for a second !
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't tell me our opponent is going to be Meiwa again ?
Close !
It's Eikyou.
Yanagi.
Huh ?
What exactly is your father ?
What do you mean, "huh" ?
You couldn't normally get Eikyou to come
over as an attraction for a cultural festival.
Oh, that ?
It wasn't him.
They requested it.
You're lying.
Unless they commit
a crime or something...
...they'll be going to the
Spring Invitational next year.
Why would a team like that
come all the way over here ?
They probably want to check you out.
Why ?
I heard that Eikyou's Coach Shiroyama...
...has been interested in him
since Kunimi's junior high years.
Coach Shiroyama ?
Yeah.
His career highlights include one spring
and two summer Koushien championships.
He's the famous coach who took the field manager position at Eikyou last year.
Oh, that old guy.
Come to think of it, he gave me a call when I was in junior high.
What ?
This is the first time
I've heard about it !
What did that famous
coach say to you ?
He said, "Why don't we go
to the Koushien together ?"
And...?
I turned him down, of course.
It goes without saying !
If it's with a cute girl,
that's one thing...
...but why would I want to go to the Koushien with an old guy like him ?
That's not what he meant...
Well, whatever the case...
...he learned that we'd be in the same
block, and that our ace pitcher is Kunimi.
So I guess he wanted
the chance to see you.
So they want to scout him.
I'm flattered.
What are we going to do ?
Let's see.
We don't need to worry an elder unnecessarily.
It's just going to be
a part of the festivities.
It doesn't matter if we win or lose.
It's better if they'd just overlook us, rather than tightening their guard against us.
That's right.
We should make our guests feel good about themselves as they head home.
I don't have any complaints as long as the game ends before the folk dance starts.
There's no need
to worry about that.
Are they serious ?
Who knows ?
All right !
Eikyou High School
Is that the fastest pitch
the machine can throw ?
Yes.
Then move up it two meters.
What ?
Two meters closer.
This is going to be a problem.
It's going to be a problem.
Why did you do that ?
I heard you.
Then you should respond.
Then you should just tell us
without waiting for a response.
Oh well, you sure are one to talk.
You have no room to talk.
The baseball club is playing a
game for the cultural festival, right ?
Yeah.
To tell the truth, the
soccer club has a game, too.
Plus, it's at the same
time as the baseball club's.
Really ?
Yeah. If I had two bodies, there'd be no problem.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Huh ? Hey !
So, I mean...
Is the Soccer Club done
with practice, too ?
Koga...
To tell the truth, there's a problem.
The Soccer Club is playing an invitational game, too, right ?
Oh, you knew ?
As the ace striker of the soccer club, I have to play the game.
But if you insist...
You don't have to force yourself.
Huh ?
They don't intend to win anyway.
Really ?
But if you insist...
I can't come cheer for you,
but good luck with the game.
Koga...
So, I mean...
You don't have to come with me to the hospital anymore.
Why not ?
It's embarrassing. I'm a guy.
Then how about I wait for you outside the hospital ?
Well...
That's fine.
Oh ?
Shuu.
Yo.
What are you doing, standing there ?
You could have
gone in and waited.
Liquor and Food:
Tachibana
I just came to buy coffee and a nighttime snack.
Thanks for your business.
How's your arm ?
It's not a big deal.
We don't have to play any
games for a while, anyway.
I have time to heal.
Man, it's amazing.
You hit a homerun with that arm.
I'm insensitive to pain, I guess.
Anyway, you were right
not to take that last at-bat.
Huh ?
Oh, yeah. About the money I
borrowed from you the other day...
You don't have to worry about it.
Ironically, I'm busy studying for the entrance exam.
I don't need any money for recreation right now.
See you.
Is your studying going well ?
No need to worry about that.
With all the fistfights I've had,
I've become great at focusing.
His hands...
Did they have calluses from holding a pen and studying too much ?
Yeah.
Brother, you're going
straight home today, right ?
Yeah.
Give me a ride home, then.
Sure.
Koga !
Do you want to go eat some yakisoba ?
Take these. Thanks.
Hey, Little Sister...
Sagawa
Hello.
Were you sleeping ?
I'm studying for the
entrance exam, you know ?
I was just taking a break.
You were doing practice swings ?
So you did continue to play baseball.
Yeah. So what's up ?
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Do you want to go to Senkawa this Sunday for their cultural festival ?
I told you, I'm studying for the exam.
I'm just saying, give
yourself some time off.
Their baseball club is
playing an invitational game.
It's going to be an interesting game.
Okay. So who's the opponent ?
Eikyou High School.
... !
Hello ?
I think I'll pass. Bye.
Shuu !
That's a problem, Sagawa.
If you want to play baseball at this
school, you should do what I tell you.
Hirota...!
Aim for the Koushien
If...
If we defeat Eikyou
in the upcoming game...
...we'll be thought of as one of
the elite teams, don't you think ?
They're going to the Spring
Invitational next year, after all.
It doesn't matter. I don't
intend to beat them anyway.
Right ?
That's right.
How to finish the game
before the folk dance starts...
...is the biggest task for us in our game against Eikyou.
I mean, they played a tough game against Meiwa.
No matter how you look at it, there's no way we can defeat them as it is.
If that's what you're concerned about, we almost beat Meiwa, too.
Yeah, that was a good game.
It began with my hit that scored the first run of the game.
Then there was my
super defensive play.
Then, in the ninth inning, with two outs,
we closed the gap to one run with my RBI hit.
It was a great game.
When I think about it...
...my defensive play
got us out of a jam...
...and my bat put all
our runs on the board.
Yeah.
Why are you wearing
a baseball uniform ?
What are you talking about, Koga ? I'm a baseball club member, too !
I know, but you hardly
ever come to practice.
Yeah, that's the issue.
This time, too, if only
I could play the game...
...we could easily defeat
any team, including Eikyou.
But we have a soccer game, too.
I really feel terrible about it.
I'm the key cog of
the offense and defense.
Without me, there's no
way our team can win.
Kine.
Hm ?
Don't worry about it.
Eikyou's goal for this game
is to gather data on our team.
Do you think we can afford to
let you play in a game like that ?
What do you mean ?
You're the key cog of
our offense and defense.
We'll keep you under
the radar until next year.
In other words,
you're our secret weapon.
Secret weapon...?
Yeah.
Kunimi !
Good luck with your soccer game.
I'll do my best !
Okay, let's do some road work !
Sure !
I'll go with you, Kunimi !
I'm the secret weapon.
Huh ?
I feel there's something amiss...
But I'm a little disappointed.
About what ?
Don't you kind of think we can win ?
You're still talking about that ?
I mean, your fastball is
faster than the Eikyou pitcher's.
Don't you think, Noda ?
You don't need to be impatient. You'll find out when next summer comes.
Rather, the most important thing is to
finish the game before the folk dance starts.
You could win and finish
the game before the folk dance.
I'm telling you !
I know, I know.
It's better not to give them much information until we play them in a real game, right ?
That's right.
Oh well. Kunimi throws
harder than Eikyou's pitcher.
Take it easy today.
You're pitching in the game the day after tomorrow.
You're using your ace pitcher for an
exhibition game at a cultural festival ?
We asked for the game.
We can't be disrespectful.
I see.
Coach, is it true that a pitcher you wanted before you recruited me is at Senkawa ?
That pitcher throws so hard...
...that you have to move the machine
two meters closer to prepare for him ?
Are you jealous ?
I don't like to hear
other people being praised.
Because I couldn't get him, I may be overvaluing him.
As they say, the fish that got away is always big.
From time to time, you should feed the fish you caught.
I know. If I leave you alone, you might eat each other.
Senkawa Festival
Oh, Eikyou is coming ?
That's impressive !
Next Year's Spring Invitational
Candidate, Eikyou High School,
Led by the Famous
Coach Shiroyama, Is Coming !!
Game Starts at 1: 00 PM,
Senkawa Baseball Club
We might be able to meet Hirota !
It starts at 1 PM. Let's go there !
It'll be fun !
Oh, the soccer club plays a game, too ?
But it's such a shame !
Both games start at 1 PM.
No-Name School Comes !
Soccer Club
Invitational Game.
Kickoff at 1 PM
I want to watch baseball,
but I can't miss the soccer game !
This is the era of soccer !
I totally agree with you !
Yeah, yeah.
Baseball is so tacky !
Where are you looking ?
We're right here !
I think we have a
similar outlook on life.
Really.
Now, let's go.
Please buy us some mitsumame.
Ladies, do you have older sisters...?
Good luck, Kine !
We're pulling for you !
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
I guess the names of "Eikyou" and
"Coach Shiroyama" are powerfully magnetic.
They get to watch the stars of the Koushien who will appear on TV next spring, after all.
Anyway, it's a matter of
how we'll lose the game.
I don't want us to be a laughingstock.
What happened to the
Soccer Club's invitational match ?
Well, if we keep it within a five-run gap, it won't make us look too bad.
What happened to the Soccer Club's invitational match ?
Hirota !
Look this way !
He's so popular.
Only until next summer.
Once summer comes, I'll
monopolize all the girls in Japan.
That's right.
Silly, don't take me seriously.
Tachibana !
Give us an autograph !
Tachibana...
The pinstripes don't look good on an evil person like you.
Sagawa...
I'm looking forward to seeing your advance declaration of strikeouts.
Oh, yes.
Can you also tell me what you do for an advance declaration of a hit-by-pitch ?
The fish that got away...
Yeah !
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Arikawa:
Kokubu:
School Broadcaster:
Girl B:
Koyasu Takehito
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
Shirakawa Mayu
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
The fated match against Eikyou High School finally begins, Hiro.
We're a no-name school. I have no intention of giving them any data.
You don't intend to win ?
There's more to baseball
games than just winning or losing.
You say so, but you always get
worked up when you give up a hit.
There's no pitcher who
enjoys giving up hits.
See ? You got angry.
Next episode of H2 is,
"I Don't Dislike a Serious Fight."
Next episode of H2 is
I Don't Dislike a Serious Fight
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?