Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Eikyou, a candidate for selection to the Spring Invitational...
...features Hirota, the ace
pitcher who broke Hideo's arm.
As well as the famous field manager...
...Coach Shiroyama, who tried to
recruit me when I was in junior high.
And with Sagawa, too, there's some bad blood between him and Hirota.
Episode 34
I Don't Dislike a Serious Fight
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Eikyou High School
He can't spot his pitches.
That's the pitcher you took the trouble
to arrange a practice game to see ?
The catcher seems very calm for someone catching a wild pitcher.
I don't like pitchers who
can't control their pitches.
With that kind of pitcher,
I can't make any game plans.
I recruited you because of
your exceptional pitch control.
You can pitch where you aim.
Whether it's the mitt or the batter.
And this pitcher intrigued me.
He's pitching where
he's aiming just fine.
All right !
The fish that got away
is that impressive ?
I wonder if he's trying to
show that he's wild today.
No, he's trying to warm him up.
Warming up Noda, that is.
I see.
Okay, I'm warmed up now. Thanks.
Was that about right ?
Yeah. It's not good to sit in
the same place for too long.
Damn him...!
Senkawa Festival
What shall we eat ?
I hope there's something...
Senkawa Festival
Next Year's
Spring Invitational
Candidate,
Eikyou High School,
Led by the Famous
Coach Shiroyama,
Is Coming !!
Game Starts
at 1: 00 PM,
Senkawa
Baseball Club
No-Name School Comes !
Soccer Club
Invitational Game.
Kickoff at 1 PM
Our opponent is a candidate to make a Koushien appearance.
We're the challengers.
Let's give it our best !
Yeah !
The upperclassmen are fired up.
We have to give them some work to do, so let's pitch-to-contact.
Kunimi.
Let's go with this.
What's that ?
It's how you'll
declare a strikeout.
Oh...
It's a decent-sized crowd.
I can see contrails, too.
He seems more
serious than I expected.
Yeah. Hiro is
serious about baseball.
Play ball !
Well...
Strike !
That was the first pitch to say nice
to meet you. How did you like it ?
Right on the inside corner.
What great control.
Yeah.
Strike two !
You're not pitching to contact...
That's fine.
Oh. He won't swing at a
pitch right down the middle ?
I mean, you're throwing too hard.
Incredible.
He's declaring a strikeout.
Eh ?
Huh ?
I guess they can slug away at a
soft pitch right down the middle.
I guess it was just his habit.
What do you think about the fish that got away ?
In a normal ballpark, it would just be a routine fly right field.
He's supposed to be aware of how small the park is.
That was generous of you to give up a homerun right from the start.
It's just a part of the festivity.
It doesn't matter if we win or lose..
It's better if they'd just overlook us, rather than tightening their guard against us.
Your facial expression
doesn't match your words.
I want them to
think that I'm upset !
You're actually upset, aren't you ?
Shut up.
Homeruns don't do much for fielding practice, so let's make them hit infield grounders.
Okay.
He picked the right
time to talk to the pitcher.
Hiro gets worked up pretty easily.
Yeah.
Noda took the timeout
at the perfect time.
They meant to pitch-to-contact,
and it ended up being a homerun.
But there's no pitcher who likes giving up homeruns.
He has a closed stance, so that means he has the tendency to open up.
Low and away. Let's get him
out on a grounder to third base.
Third base ! Arikawa !
Out !
Okay ! Okay ! One out ! One out !
The three hitter is
shortening up his swing.
He's swinging for contact.
He'll react to any pitch ?
Then let's pitch him in, just outside the zone, for a hit to the shortstop.
What an unsteady infield.
Nice back up !
Hirota !
He's amazing !
So handsome !
Next up is the pitcher,
hitting cleanup, Hirota.
Wow, scary.
I know.
I'm counting on you, Yanagi.
A grounder to second,
for a double play !
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Foul !
I guess I was being too hopeful, trying for a double play.
If he's going to pull it, let's get
him out on a fly ball to center.
I'm counting on you, Kine.
Foul.
He's a first-rate batter, too.
He's seen you hit.
Hiro's not fazed.
I don't dislike a serious fight.
That's his signal
to predict a strikeout.
Oh...
Aim for the Koushien
That's his signal to
predict a strikeout.
Oh...
Your eyes are brimming
with a thirst for blood.
Fall baseball...
...must be...
...wholesome.
Out !
Wow ! Amazing !
Phew.
Punk...!
The fish that got away...
A strikeout to a double
play. That's timely.
Yeah.
Noda was moving well, too.
It's going well.
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
Let's pull ourselves together.
Um, well...
We'll pull ourselves together, sure.
All right !
Batting first, center
fielder, Kine Ryutarou.
Batting first ?
Batting first ?!
In my baseball,
I value the lead-off hitter.
The cleanup batter may or may not get a plate appearance in the first inning.
The leadoff batter always gets the most plate appearances.
Be the Ichiro of Senkawa, Kine.
Got it, Coach Ohgi.
All right !
Just kidding.
Hirota !
I love your smile !
Smile, huh ?
That's a problem, Sagawa.
If you want to play baseball at this school, you should do as I tell you.
Somebody stole underwear from our volleyball club.
Do you know who might have done it ?
Kine, you're tacky !
Give me back my lunch money, please !
Come on !
Strike !
He's underestimating me !
Strike two !
Dammit...
He's swinging like a cleanup hitter.
I guess he hasn't adjusted
to his role as lead-off hitter.
He's a proud man,
like that pitcher, Hirota.
Kine is proud in a
way that's cute, though.
What's the next pitch ?
It goes without saying.
I'm locking onto a fastball !
Strike ! Batter out !
Humph !
Kine, lunch money !
Hirota !
Amazing !
No one will praise him
if he overpowers us...
...so he has to beat us while
humming a song or something.
He can use that as an excuse
when he gets batted around, too.
He's so easy to understand.
Yanagi, why don't you
pounce on the first pitch ?
His pride will get in the way, and
he'll probably throw a soft fastball.
Good job.
Even in a normal-sized ballpark, it would have directly hit the fence and gone for extra bases.
You're so thoughtless.
When you hit it so well, he won't throw us any more meatballs.
If I were thinking about the future,
I'd quit baseball and focus on studying.
Impressive.
He really is wholesome.
I guess I'll name
our strategy today as...
...the autumn sky, the wholesome look, or something like that.
A homerun off of a tease ball.
But...
You're probably pretty
worked up, aren't you ?
It won't make it in time.
You shouldn't stay
that far behind the base.
Your first step is slow anyway. You should know your range.
Baseball is...
Baseball is a sport where we feel
the spirit of our eight teammates...
...and the guys on the opposing team
through the acts of throwing and hitting.
Of course, winning and losing is part of the fun.
But it's more rewarding because we can learn who we all are as people.
Huh ?
Dang !
Damn !
It was a hard-hit ball.
Anyone could've hit that pitch.
You're so confident.
He underestimated Senkawa's cleanup batter's power.
Of course.
Noda is a great player, too.
They're still feeling
each other out right now.
I think it's going to
be an interesting game.
This game is still being played like part of the festivities.
Once Hiro becomes serious...
...he'll start throwing so hard
that there'll be no stopping him.
That's right.
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
All right.
Let's pull it together !
Yeah !
Pitch-to-contact, Kunimi !
I'll catch it next time !
Let's play some good defense !
I'm counting on you all !
Man, these guys are
such wholesome people.
Hello. Hello.
I'm Kine Ryutarou !
I'm great at soccer, too !
Nice to meet you all !
Before you act so endearing, you
should give me back my lunch money !
Except for one person, that is.
That's not a problem, though.
He hasn't thrown his best stuff yet.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Hazumi Jun
Koga Fujio
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Hironaga:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Arikawa:
Kokubu:
Girl A:
Girl B:
Koyasu Takehito
Takagi Wataru
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
Shirakawa Mayu
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
Note:  "Ohgi" was the field manager for Orix BlueWaves, back when Ichiro was playing on that team.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Hiro, it looks like you're getting away
with your pitch-to-contact strategy so far.
Yeah, fielding practice is important.
But how much longer can
you sustain such pitching ?
I'm not flashy like Hirota, who retires the side with three consecutive three-pitch strikeouts.
You're not beneath him.
As long as I finish an inning with
nine pitches, it's the same, right ?
See ? You don't like to lose.
Next episode of H2 is,
"You Want Me to Declare a Strikeout ?"
Next episode of H2 is
You Want Me to Declare a Strikeout ?
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?