Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Give It Your Best, Meiwa Ichi !
In the finals of the Fall Tournament...
...Hideo's Meiwa battled against Eikyou High School and its ace pitcher, Hirota.
The pitch thrown by Eikyou's Hirota...
...fractured Hideo's arm.
And winter, which is harsh on
those who are injured, has come.
The First Date !
Episode 39
The Cast in Your Heart Isn't Gone Yet
Let's go !
There you go !
Yeah !
Good job !
Third !
Okay !
One more !
Let's go !
Tachibana.
Yes ?
Looks like you're out of the cast.
Yes, yesterday.
Don't push yourself too hard.
We're fine as long as you recover by spring.
I don't know if we can wait that long.
There are things to do, like doing
infield drills and practicing sign plays.
A first year doesn't need to worry about those things.
I want to win at the Koushien.
It's not official yet that we're going.
Besides, this spring won't be your
only chance, since you're a first year.
You're a first-year, after all.
Dammit !
You're working hard.
You were watching me ?
I don't have my
arm strength back yet.
You shouldn't push yourself.
I need to get recover and join
my teammates as soon as I can.
To be able to win without practicing team plays...
The Koushien isn't such a cakewalk.
So I do need to
push myself hard.
You can go ahead and go home.
Hide-chan...
That was fast !
How was it ?
There's no way anyone can hit that. It was a great pitch.
A liner directly hitting
the right field wall.
That's what Hirota hit off
of Hiro's max-effort pitch.
Okay, I'm done.
It's too cold.
My arm can't get warmed up.
Kunimi Hiro's homework
is to add more power.
A coach must be able to
withstand the cold weather.
Shut up.
It's true that we can't advance
unless we beat Hirota's Eikyou.
Thank you !
But I think you're too hung up on giving up that hit.
It's not just about defeating that guy.
What is it, then ?
It's my own problem.
It's a hurdle I have to overcome in order to go to the Koushien.
I guess.
There will be better
hitters at the Koushien.
Yeah. There's the son
of the liquor store, too.
Huh ?
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
What's the matter ?
It's just a small thing.
See ? You understand
how he feels, right ?
Yeah. I get it.
He wants to look cool,
especially in front of you.
He doesn't want to show you that he's struggling.
What should I do, then ?
You should leave him alone. You know better than anyone how stubborn he is.
But as the girlfriend of
such a stubborn guy...
...I feel that I should prevent him from re-injuring himself through overwork.
"You should cure your elbow pain with your will power !"
You were so hard on me.
Hide-chan will actually try
to cure it with his will power.
And he's my boyfriend.
Now, go !
I guess you two can't do it.
You two are kind of reserved
toward each other sometimes.
"Good manners even between friends."
Lame !
I'm powering up ! There !
What ?!
Showing your underwear
is an unfair attack !
You saw them ?
I won't forgive you !
You should be firm with Hideo, too.
Be firm.
Kunimi !
Hey, Manager !
How's Tachibana doing ?
He's had his cast removed.
But it's amazing. He hit a
homerun, even with a fractured arm.
Yes.
Are you walking the dog ?
I'm on my way
to do some shopping.
Come to think of it, you run a bookstore, right, Hikari ?
Yeah.
That's convenient.
Hm ?
Hey, stop that, Third.
Koga, this is what I recommend.
That doesn't work. I need one that's more hardcore.
What ? Something more hardcore ?
That's tough. Let's see...
People under the age of 18 can't buy age-restricted materials, you know ?
The hardcore ones are wrapped in
plastic and I can't see the contents.
I'd like to get these five books.
New Power-Up
What did you buy ?
It's a secret.
Let's go home, Third.
Bye.
Thank you for your business.
Yeah. See you later.
Hey, what did you buy ?
Let me see them.
No, I won't let you.
Why not ?
I guess Hiro is busy, too.
Be firm and tell him. Be firm.
Wonderful.
Don't think with your head. Learn it with your body.
Where's that from ?
It's the words of Mr. Bruce Lee, whom your brother admires.
Oh.
Sweet potatoes baked in hot stones !
Do you want one ?
No.
Oh, yes.
I pilfered these from Father.
Special complimentary tickets for a sports gym. One month free.
This isn't good.
The glitter in your eyes is one of someone who wants to help our ace pitcher bulk up.
That's bad.
Why ? You said that he needs to build some strength, too.
Even if he's our ace pitcher,
all players must be treated equally.
We can't give him special treatment.
You're talking like a coach.
I am a coach.
But...
If you're going to give them to him as a friend, that's outside of my domain.
Huh ?
Well, anyway, I don't need them myself. I guess I'll leave them here.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Hikari !
Good evening.
How long have you been there ?
Just now.
You should have said something. You surprised me.
Your arm.
You're such a worrier.
It's fine. See ?
There's no way he's fine.
But I don't think you
should push yourself.
I can't sit still.
Give me the bat.
Don't give it to him, Hikari.
You should be firm and tell him.
Here.
Why did she give it to him ?!
Was it the wind ?
Hide-chan.
Oh, am I in the way ?
It's not that, but it must be cold. It's getting windy, too.
There he goes again,
trying to look cool.
Hide-chan, don't overwork yourself.
Geez.
Bye.
Take care.
Thanks.
Oh, man.
Do I have to intervene ?
No, I don't.
Right ?
Aim for the Koushien
Good morning, Kunimi !
Hey, Manager !
Kunimi.
What's the matter ?
I have a favor to ask.
Think of this as a date.
Can you come with me ?
As I told you, I'll go with you as long as we're splitting the tab.
Oh, don't worry about the cost.
This gym is part of my father's company, so we can use it for free.
Kunimi Taro of the Third Section of the Sales Department....
...has never received such a great offer.
It's no good ?
If he gets promoted to executive rank, like tomorrow, there's no issue.
Should I ask my father ?
No way.
I was just kidding.
Anyway, it's good to
build strength at a gym...
...but I'm not suited for
working out with machines.
I love to run with the wind like this, and feel the smell of the land.
If I were a professional ballplayer...
...I'd be in the envious position of being able to work out in a warm, southern country.
Okay. We'll go with
however you want to do it.
I did study a lot about what kinds of
muscles are needed for a power pitcher.
It would be ideal to give
yourself all-around training...
...but I reached a conclusion that this would be the best option.
The dorsal muscles are hard to train through routine workout, after all.
I'm impressed.
What ?
You're impressive.
Um...
Third ! Good boy !
Here you go !
Senkawa High School
There !
Here you go !
Oh, I'm sorry !
There !
This red-bean jam bun is tasty.
Are you done eating ?
I might be a lucky guy.
What are you talking about ?
If I think that way, it gives me some peace of mind.
Oh, so you're not eating.
It broadens your mind, and you start to see things you didn't before.
It's a little weird between Hikari and Hideo.
Those two ?
When I see them, it frustrates me.
They've always been
like that, haven't they ?
They got together because you played go-between.
I see.
But I'd say they should be able to manage by themselves now.
Yeah.
You're not eating this ?
It can't be helped.
This will be the last time.
What ?
What did you do here ?
You said you weren't going to eat.
I didn't say that !
Give me back my bun !
Didn't you say you've become peaceful ?
Here.
Are you sure it's okay ?
Yes. Please let them use those.
Thanks. See you !
You did it ?
Hm ?
You gave them to him ?
Yup.
Marvelous.
Hey, Hiro.
I didn't know you were here.
What are you doing ?
You surprised me.
The fact that you're favoring the left arm means you're still far from recovered.
I only recently got the cast off.
It goes without saying.
Come with me.
Hm ?
Open
A complimentary ticket for the gym ?
Yeah.
That's nice of you.
You really are my best friend.
Hey.
I have one more ticket here.
Then why don't we go together ?
You should work out some, too.
Moron.
Huh ?
Idiot.
What's that about ?
You don't seem to understand why I brought you here.
Welcome.
Hi.
Hiro, what is it that you
wanted to talk about ?
Hm ?
Hide-chan...
Anyway, I'll give these
tickets to you and Hikari.
You should go there together.
Why ?
You probably think that the behind-the-scenes effort needs to be kept to yourself.
Huh ?
You probably think that you want to
continue to look cool in front of Hikari.
Hey !
Don't read my mind.
Honestly, you haven't
changed since junior high.
Hmm...!
You'd try acting cool in front of Hikari.
Whether you were nervous
or whatever, you'd never talk.
I always had to play the clown.
But that should be over,
don't you think ?
Anyway, you should know that
this is the last time I'll intervene.
Hiro ?
You shouldn't talk to me. The rest should be decided by you two.
Thank you for coming.
What the heck am I doing ?
The cast on your arm may be gone,
but the cast in your heart isn't gone yet.
You shouldn't stay so stiff anymore.
By this time, you two should be
beyond acting cool in front of each other.
The draft through the space
between you two is way too cold.
What is Hiro talking about, really ?
He's the one who's
trying to act cool.
That's right.
Anyway, you should know that
this is the last time I'll intervene.
He's such a meddler.
There's no draft through
the space between us.
Right ?
But if it looked that way to him...
Would you come with me ?
I love you, Hide-chan.
Oh...
There !
I see. Hikari and him are going.
Yeah.
I have to think of some other way to build your strength.
I'll work hard on that.
Your smile gives
me enough strength.
Eh ?
If we're late,
Kine will get yappy again !
Let's go, Third !
That's right. Good. Slowly.
Hikari.
If it were Hiro...
If it were Hiro...?
You'd be harder on him, right ?
Be firm and tell him. Be firm !
Firm !
Huh ?
You really are different from Hiro.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Matsumoto Yasunori
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Meiwa Coach:
Hironaga:
Child A:
Child B:
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Konishi Hiroko
Asada Yoko
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
Various signs in the episode. None were really crucial.
Food Stall: 450 yen per basket
Shops: Taguchi Store, Manpukutei
Sign above Hiro and Noda eating apples: Main Street Shopping Center
Ticket: Special Complimentary Ticket
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
Various signs in the episode. None were really crucial.
Food Stall: 450 yen per basket
Shops: Taguchi Store, Manpukutei
Sign above Hiro and Noda eating apples: Main Street Shopping Center
Ticket: Special Complimentary Ticket
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
This is a story of a snowy day. Yes, we
have some memories from snowy days.
Memories ? What are they ?
I'll give you a hint.
Elm. Essay. Baseball.
I don't get it at all.
Geez. I guess I'll give you
one more hint, just for you.
The schoolyard of
the elementary school.
Anyway, I guess I'll
have to go and see it.
That's right. I hope you'll remember the dream you had back then.
Next episode of H2 is,
"The Unchanging Dream."
The First Date !
Next episode of H2 is
The Unchanging Dream
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?