Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Her name is Amamiya Hikari.
She's my childhood friend.
When she's with me, she
shows her strong-willed side...
...but in front of Hideo, whom she loves, she becomes an awfully attractive girl.
But that's not supposed to be all there is to her.
The First Date  !
Episode 40
The Unchanging Dream
Baseball Club
Koga.
What is it ?
Practice ended early.
I guess.
You have time, right ?
Not really.
Let's go home together.
I'll buy you a hot monja.
I'm not hungry.
Do you want to go home together ?
Um, well, yes.
Let's go home together, then.
What ? What ?
You're going to treat
me to some monja ?
What ?
I'm Koga, you know.
What ?!
Koga, which do you like better, takoyaki or imagawayaki ?
It's tasty !
If you're looking for cheap but good food, you should leave it to me, Noda Atsushi.
Imagawayaki
He's been eating out a lot since elementary school.
The soy-flour candy at that
candy store in front of the school...
That was the best ever.
Wow.
Hiro would put so many of them into his mouth at once that he'd choke on them.
He kept wheezing, so the candy store lady called an ambulance one time.
That happened ?
Shut up.
Hey, is your elementary
school far from here ?
No, it's just a ten-minute walk.
I want to see it.
I don't want to see it.
Oh, I should show you the
graduation totem pole that Hiro broke.
What's that ?
There's also the wall that Hiro tried to jump over and failed when he was late for class.
I'm not going.
I said I'm not going !
Snow...
What was that ?
Hey, Hiro !
You're not coming, Kunimi ?
I guess I'll go.
Shouwa Year 47 Graduation
Commemorative Totem Pole,
Made by the Graduation Class
This is the totem pole that Hiro threw a stone at and broke.
He did that ?
According to him, he thought he could pull off a "daruma otoshi."
That was a pure and innocent idea, appropriate for a child.
Please Do Not Run
in the Hallway
Year 5, Class 3
Hiro
It feels small now.
This is where you two
started playing baseball ?
Yeah.
This elm tree never changes.
We used to make throws
from here to those iron bars.
When you were in elementary school ?
We reached there when we
were in fifth grade, right, Noda ?
Even when you were
little, you were amazing.
Shall we make a throw ?
All right.
Here I go !
Okay !
Hiro, here it comes !
Like that elm tree, I...
Hiro !
Kunimi !
What was it ?
Kunimi ?
I forgot.
Please.
You're back, clean-up guy.
Yes.
Please.
All right.
Rehab is complete.
Amamiya Hikari,
thanks for your work.
It's cold.
Sanpou Sports
Tachibana !
Reporter,
Amamiya Takaaki
Tokyo,
Adachi-ku,
Kobayashi
0-00-0
I'm Amamiya from Sanpou Sports.
Hello.
Mr. Amamiya...?
A memory from a snowy day ?
I think that's what it is,
but I can't remember.
A snowball fight.
That's not it.
You made a snow hut.
That's not it, either.
Is it about when we drew pictures in the snow with our pee ?
That's definitely not it at all.
Is it about Hikari ?
Um, well, it's probably nothing.
I hope it'll accumulate.
If it does, you might remember.
Moron ! We won't be
able to practice if it does !
That's true.
But today will also be a
memorable day, wrapped up in snow.
Really, it's nothing.
That's what I said,
but it bothers me.
Crap !
Hiro, you have a phone call !
Hikari's essay ?
When Haruka mentioned
Hikari's name, I remembered.
Something about snow, and the elm.
She wrote something about that.
That must be it !
Can't you find it in the
graduation essay collection ?
I can't read mine because of the scribbles you made.
Wait.
Found it.
Amamiya Hikari
Memories of
Elementary School
Maybe not.
This might be it. You remember that we buried a time capsule, right ?
Didn't we put "My Treasure" into it ?
Huh ?
You put a ball in. I put a cap in.
And I think Hikari put her essay in it.
Do you want to
dig it up and see it ?
Moron ! That's meant to
be a present for future kids.
Then there's only one way.
If you want to know what's in that essay, you should just ask Hikari.
It's nothing important.
It's not worth asking her about.
Just forget about it.
Well, even if they're
not the tastiest things...
...you get nostalgic about cheap snacks and you somehow feel like eating them.
Aim for the Koushien
It's nothing important.
It's not worth asking her about.
Just forget about it.
It's cold.
Hey.
You're playing pachinko again ?
What do you mean "again" ?
I always see you near a pachinko place or a bar.
I've only seen you tending the store once or twice.
That's not nice to say.
I get up early in the morning...
...open the boxes of books delivered to us, and display them in the store.
And after everyone goes to sleep,
I organize the receipts and do bookkeeping.
Man, I'm so busy.
Why don't you do all those things during the day...
...when you're otherwise just dawdling around ?
Pachinko places would close, you know ?
Pachinko places are open late, too.
In the evening hours,
the good slots are all taken.
Oh, well. Because you're hardly ever home, people think that you've left.
Don't be silly.
Then do you know what Hikari's treasure
was when she was in elementary school ?
Well, why don't you come to our
house for a cup of tea, for once ?
I always stop by your house.
You're just hardly ever there.
It's just that you're hardly ever there.
Really ?
Amamiya
Oh, how rare.
You're such a liar.
What do you mean,
"I always stop by your house" ?
"How rare," she says.
I was talking about you, Dad.
Oh, I see.
Oh, Uncle is here.
Takaaki is here ?
It's been a while.
Takaaki is a newspaper reporter, right ?
Yeah, he's going back to the
main office in Tokyo next year.
Oh.
Hey, Hiro, come here !
Sure.
Good evening.
Hiro, you've grown.
What happened to baseball ?
Are you still playing ?
Yes.
Which school do you go to ?
It's Senkawa.
Senkawa ?
Their baseball club was
established just recently.
Oh, is that true ?
Yes, it is.
Speaking of which, I just went to see Meiwa, the leading candidate for the Invitational.
So he says.
That guy, Tachibana Hideo, lives up to his reputation.
I think he's going to be a star player
who will get people to come to the park.
So he says.
Yup.
He's smart, and he's thoughtful.
He'll do well in
professional baseball, too.
If it's about Tachibana, it's
way easier to just ask Hikari.
Huh ?
I just remembered.
Remembered what ?
The essay you wrote in elementary school, about your dream for the future.
It was to become a
newspaper reporter, right ?
Yeah, a sports reporter.
That's right.
Wednesday, May 21st
Class Newspaper
This Week's Kunimi and Noda
He threw 70 meters !
Like that elm tree, I'd like to be
someone who will never change.
Can it be...?
Can it be what ?
Is that still what you want to do ?
You think it's impossible, don't you ?
No.
I think you can do it.
When I told Hide-chan about it, he didn't take me seriously.
It's because you never
show your true self to Hideo.
Huh ?
When you're with him,
you act like a docile, nice girl.
Hideo doesn't know how
stubborn or strong-willed you are.
Hmm.
Boys want to show their good sides when they're with girls, too, right ?
If you don't show him your true character from time to time, it'll be stressful.
Oh ?
Didn't you say you're done playing the go-between ?
Hmm...
Hikari and Tachibana Hideo...
Are you surprised ?
Well, I have no complaint about it.
But as a pair,
it feels a bit strange.
Is that a news reporter's intuition ?
Well, it's not anything reliable.
My image of Hikari is that of her when
she was in elementary school, after all.
I see.
It's cold.
My treasure...
...is my dream.
Memories are memories.
I'm home.
Oh, he's home now !
He's home now !
Hey, moronic son.
You have a phone call from the company president's daughter.
What's up ?
Hey !
The snow is beautiful ?
Are you a moron ?
Ugh...!
All the powerhouse schools
have indoor workout facilities.
If this weather continues,
they'll get even further ahead of us.
Tomorrow, we'll start to remove the snow from the field in the morning.
So get up early.
Speak more politely...
I can't wake up by myself, so come pick me up.
What have you done...?
Six o'clock ?
Moron ! It's too early !
Honey...
Yeah, I guess that sounds right.
Okay.
Huh ? What ?
The snow is beautiful ?
You're still talking about that ?
You have to live for the future !
For the future !
Like that elm tree, I want to be someone who'll never change.
He remembered.
My treasure.
It is my dream.
When I see that elm tree in the schoolyard, I always feel it.
In snow or rain, that elm tree has always encouraged me.
That's why I want to
be like that elm tree.
I like baseball. I like how everyone works hard and plays the game.
I want other people to know this feeling, so I'd like to be a sports reporter.
I think that, if I work hard like that elm tree, my dream will someday come true.
You think it's impossible, don't you ?
No, I think you can.
Yup.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Kunimi Tarou:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
KSuzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Mitsuya Yuji
Matsumoto Yasunori
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hiro's Mom:
Meiwa Coach:
Hikari's Dad:
Hikari's Mom:
Amamiya Takaaki:
Shimoike:
Takizawa Kumiko
Naka Hiroshi
Shioya Kozo
Ikemoto Sayuri
Tobita Nobuo
Takagi Wataru
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
"Monja" is like okonomiyaki, but a thinner version of it.
"Imagawayaki" is a type of Japanese muffin, containing bean jam, and served hot.
"Daruma otoshi" is a type of game.
See http: //en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daruma_doll under the subheading, "Children's games"
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
Various signs in the episode. None were really crucial.
Food Stall: 450 yen per basket
Shops: Taguchi Store, Manpukutei
Sign above Hiro and Noda eating apples: Main Street Shopping Center
Ticket: Special Complimentary Ticket
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Finally, Meiwa makes their
appearance at the Spring Invitational.
Hide-chan flourishes at the Koushien.
Damn Hideo ! He's done it !
He's always dreamed
of being there, after all.
Yeah.
But that dream-like time
is so short, isn't it, Hiro ?
Once it's over, right ?
Hiro, aim for the summer Koushien.
Yeah, my dream starts now.
H2, the final episode is,
"The Pledge For Summer Starts Here !"
The First Date !
Next episode of H2 is
The Pledge For Summer Starts Here !
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?