Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Dream.
A great aspiration that I began
to hold sometime in the past.
Whether we stumble or fall,
we never cease to chase after it.
Because...
Congratulations
on your
Invitational
Appearance,
Meiwa Daiichi
High School
Episode 41(Final)
The Pledge For Summer Starts Here !
Tachibana, whom would you like to
tell first how happy you are right now ?
This way, please !
This way, also !
Let's see.
It's probably my parents.
Man, what a liar.
Couldn't you have
said something better ?
It was a national broadcast, after all.
Hey, you guys should come and cheer for me at the Koushien with Hikari.
Moron ! When we go there, we'll be on the field !
We have no business
in the bleachers !
Right ?
Right !
I guess.
Manager for the baseball club ?
Yeah. If I ask,
I'm sure they'll let you.
You can count on me.
Wait. I'm a member
of the archery club.
What ? You aren't going to come and cheer for me ?
Of course I will.
I plan to go to the Koushien, too.
It's no fun just going there, is it ?
You'll get to stay at the same inn, from marching into Koushien Stadium to game day.
Right ?
But there are other managers.
Yeah, and there are many
more who want to do it.
Then that's all the more reason.
What about it ?
It feels too presumptuous.
I am ?
For me to be a manager.
Do you think so ?
Besides, the manager job isn't something
you can do just because someone asks you.
Are you mad ?
No, not at all.
Really ?
Really.
Hide-chan.
Hm ?
Congratulations.
Yeah.
And thanks.
I'll cheer as hard as
I can at the Koushien.
Yeah.
When I look at your practice swing, it just doesn't seem like you're any good as a hitter.
Shut up.
Hey.
So are you mad at her ?
No. It's just that I didn't expect her to turn it down, so I was surprised.
What's so surprising about it ?
I mean, don't you think so ?
In junior high...
...she did pretty well as a long-distance runner for the track and field team...
...but she joined the archery club for trivial reasons like how good the "hakama" looks...
...or how great it probably feels when the arrow hits the target, and stuff.
You wouldn't expect her
to be that committed to it.
I thought she had
the same dream as me.
I wonder if she actually loves me.
Hold the bat tight, okay ?
Hey.
Hm ?
If you were a pathetic guy who couldn't show even half of his potential without Hikari...
...she'd come flying to help you, even if you didn't ask.
Really ?
It's because she trusts you that she feels safe to leave you be.
So I should be a pathetic guy ?
What kind of a guy is pathetic ?
Um...
What are you doing, Hiro ?
You should blow your nose. You need to button up, too !
I told you to do your
homework when you got home.
It's fine, Mrs. Kunimi. I'll be
sure to keep an eye on Hiro.
I'll keep an eye on him.
It's so pathetic.
So what kind of a
guy is pathetic, really ?
Well, I don't know if Hikari would fall for that kind of a guy, though.
She's a level-headed girl.
She joined the archery club
because she had her own ideas.
I'm sure of it.
She just chose something
that would allow her to grow.
She's always been
firm since she was little.
Since she was little ?
Yeah.
Ever since she was
in elementary school...
...she's wanted to be a sports journalist and she wrote about it in her essay.
You don't seem to take
her seriously, though.
You guys are alike in that you're both firm and level-headed.
That's why Hikari feels safe with you.
I see. She feels safe
and leaves me be.
I guess it's better to have her feel safe than think of me as a pathetic guy.
Probably.
Okay, I got it !
Huh ?
I see. She feels safe and
that's why she leaves me alone.
Now I get it.
When we were teammates,
I used to love that sound.
But now it's a really
unpleasant sound.
I feel the same way about the sound Noda's mitt makes when he catches your pitches.
Thanks.
Hiro, I'm going to be
the best hitter in Japan.
You should become
the best pitcher in Japan.
And let's meet at the
Koushien this summer.
Yeah.
I can share that dream with you.
I'm here.
I'm here at the Koushien.
It starts here, Hide-chan.
Yup, it's perfect.
It's flying away !
It's gone.
Is it going ?
I said it's gone.
And it's gone ! A homerun !
One of the noteworthy
players of this tournament...
...Tachibana Hideo from Meiwa Ichi High School, a second-year player hitting fourth.
He makes his Koushien debut with a huge homerun to the middle of the left field stands.
Well, life is pain.
Don't be blinded by the temporary spotlight
and lose sight of yourself, okay, Hide-chan ?
He hit it really well. He's going to be a tremendous force...
Ah, how frustrating.
Hey...
If you get ahead of yourself now, you won't last till summer.
Hideo is getting ahead,
hitting a big one at the Koushien.
Kunimi !
Newspaper people
want to interview you !
So can we have a comment from you as a representative of Tachibana Hideo's friends ?
What ?!
Tachibana ?!
Hold it right there !
Let me speak about Tachibana !
When we were in
elementary school...
...he and I competed for the cleanup hitter spot on the Hakusan Angels !
Without my genius, Tachibana would not have become who he is now !
Did Tachibana say something
before he went to the Koushien ?
Hey ! You ! Listen to me !
Shimada.
Yes ?
Could you take
a few photos of him ?
Oh, but all we needed was his comment.
They said we didn't need any photos.
Doesn't matter.
Please do it anyway.
I'm sure we'll need them
some time down the road.
Okay.
Aim for the Koushien
Sanpou Sports
Special Report:
Tachibana Hideo
Meiwa Ichi
High School's
Second-Year
Clean-Up Hitter
In his first-at bat, a homerun to
the middle of the left-field stands.
A hero makes a flashy debut at
the Koushien.
Hmm.
Hide-chan is amazing.
This is nothing, given his talent.
If you feel frustrated, you should make your way into the newspaper, too.
I'm in it already.
Huh ?
Where ?
"Friend A" ?
"He had always been on a different level than us."
"For us, the Koushien is
a dream within a dream."
"But for Tachibana, it's just the
first step in his baseball career."
"I'm proud of the fact that I was once Tachibana's teammate."
Who said anything like this ?!
Hello.
Is this the home of "Friend A" ?
Hey...!
Koushien
Stadium
Hiro, the Koushien is amazing.
Huh ?
Because it's amazing, way too amazing, you have to see it with your own eyes.
What are you talking about ?
Work hard, and come here this summer.
This summer, come
to the Koushien, Hiro.
Yeah.
Well, the second-round game is starting.
Hit it, hit it, Tachibana !
You looked at the fastball up and in.
In the batter's box is Tachibana Hideo,
the slugger from powerhouse Meiwa Ichi.
Now, on the mound is
Senkawa's ace pitcher, Kunimi.
What will he throw next ?
Am I in the way ?
You were imagining yourself at the Koushien, right ?
You're early. Practice
doesn't start until afternoon.
As I was watching TV at home, I couldn't sit still.
You, too ?
I guess.
What is it ?
No, nothing, really.
You're weird.
Hey, Hiro !
Hey !
We, the Senkawa Baseball Club, have great team chemistry.
Hey, thanks for the wait !
Genius Kine Ryutarou has arrived !
No one was waiting for you.
Kunimi, let's all go
together, to the Koushien.
Yeah, including you.
Well, let's do some work !
I...
...hate high school baseball.
Principal...
I can't focus on my work.
I see.
In summer, it'll
probably get even worse.
I can totally guarantee that.
Homerun !
Right at the back screen...
...a three-run homer to even up the score, coming back from a hopeless situation.
Listen to the crowd cheering.
With their back against the
wall in the bottom of the ninth...
...Tachibana's homerun sends this game into the third extra inning game of this tournament.
It's hot.
My chest feels hot.
The passionate feelings turn into cheers...
...and it becomes a big swell
that envelopes the Koushien.
The voices, the commotion...
It's amazing.
It really is amazing, Hiro.
The Koushien unites everyone.
Come.
Come here, Hiro.
Kunimi.
It must be hard on him with his friend getting one step closer to his dream.
But...
You're not alone.
You have all these teammates.
The seniors are improving.
Yeah, they're all working hard.
They love baseball so much that they initially formed the baseball fan club.
Maybe I did a bad thing.
What ?
That was fun in its
own way, after all.
From now on, it'll get
harder and harder for them.
If they had remained just friends...
If they had remained just friends,
it would have continued to be fun.
The more you love, the more pain and hardship you have to endure.
Even if that's the case...
Even if that's the case,
people still fall in love.
I see.
After all, we're trying to get a date with the Koushien...
...whom 4000 schools across the nation are going after.
That's a huge love romance !
Youkou
Meiwa Ichi
The game is decided in the thirteenth inning, with the score of 4-3.
Much to their disappointment,
Meiwa Ichi did not advance to the semi-finals.
They lost, with Tachibana in the on-deck circle.
But honestly, it was a tough battle.
With just a matter
of a few centimeters...
...the winning run was scored, and
that was the difference in the game.
Hiro, we'll both be
here this summer.
As the best hitter in Japan,
and the best pitcher in Japan.
We'll face off in the summer.
It's only just beginning.
Yeah !
What're you doing, discouraging your own team during free-style batting practice ?
Sorry about that.
Kunimi, do you remember
when we met for the first time ?
"What are you burning ?"
"It's the springtime of my youth."
That's what you answered.
I don't know of anyone
who'd answer like that.
You run straight toward your goal, with all you've got.
I wanted to chase after you.
Now, and from now on.
Why do I play baseball ?
Why do I aim for the Koushien ?
Because I love it.
I want to meet baseball
at my beloved Koushien.
I just want to meet her.
Isn't that enough of a reason ?
I have no complaints !
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
No matter how loud the cheers become...
...I can still tell it's your voice.
Even if you get a hit, or make an out...
Instead of answering you...
...win or lose, I won't be broken.
I will move forward again.
...without artifice or affectation...
Because that's how you find a dream.
...I'll throw a fastball right down the middle.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Yes, pursue, and continue to pursue...
I cower in fear, but...
...and you can find it.
That's what a dream is.
One down, two down.
I can say it now, in raw words.
Hiro, I'll become the best hitter in Japan.
Embracing the red-hot courage...
You become the best pitcher in Japan !
And I'll see you at the Koushien this summer !
...let's smash it into the clouds.
I can definitely share that dream with you !
It's a rainbow Grand Slam !
It's a rainbow Gland Slam !
And
it all
starts from here
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Kunimi Tarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Mitsuya Yuji
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Principal Yanagi:
Koga Fujio:
Amamiya Takaaki:
Announcer:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Reporter:
Shimada:
Komura Tetsuo
Matsumoto Yasunori
Tobita Nobuo
Ooba Mahito
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
A "hakama" is the divided skirt-like pants that Japanese archery, kendo, etc. players wear.
The Senkawa team during the end. I didn't want to dirty the screen up. The first number is when they bat and the second number is their uniform number:
1 - Kine 8, 2 - Yanagi 4, 3 - Kunimi 1,
4 - Noda 2, 5 - Arikawa 5, 6 - Hironaga 3, 7 - Sagawa 6, 8 - Moritani 7, 9 - Tanaka 9
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
If you want to see what happens from the end of this episode on start watching the H2 Live Action release. Watch it from the beginning. It covers nearly everything -
from episode 1 of this series all the way to the end
of the manga.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.