Planning & Production
NAOTAKA YOSHIDA (SOEI SINSYA)
HISATOSHI MARUYAMA
(PONY CANYON)
Original Idea
KATSUHIKO NISHIJIMA
YUJI MORIYAMA KAZUMI SHIRAISHI
Screenplay
TOMOKO KAWASAKI
Character Design &
Director of Animation
YUJI MORIYAMA
Production
SHOICHI MASUO
Art Director SATOSHI MATSUDAIRA
Music Director YASUNORI HONDA
Director of Photography
NORIHIDE KUBOTA
Music HIROMOTO TOBISAWA
Title Song Get a Chance!
Sung by BaBe with CARYAN
Production Producers
TOMOHISA IIZUKA
HOKO ENOMOTO
Producer
KAZUFUMI NOMURA
Director
YUJI MORIYAMA
I win! I beat you!
I'm sick of taking tests.
Well, today's the last day.
Spring break starts tomorrow.
We'll have lots of fun!
I hope so. I want
to find a boyfriend.
A normal boyfriend,
like any normal girl.
We'll go to Disneyland,
and I'll get popcorn,
and ice cream
and French pudding!
I'll need a new dress. I'll lose
two centimeters around the waist,
And I have to
get my hair done.
I wish it was
already spring break!
Sorry, didn't mean
to disturb you.
And then, at the movies,
he'll say, "Your waist!
It's so slender!"
What is A-ko
smirking about?
This break, C-ko
will be mine!
We'll go on a picnic, and
I'll bring a pink lunchbox.
That's right!
I have to make lunch!
Winter was so long!
These damn tests
are almost over!
What a boring
girl's school!
The flowers
are in bloom!
Just two more centimeters,
and I'll have a boyfriend!
The Riviera or somewhere
in the south of France.
Or maybe I should buy
C-ko a castle in Germany.
And I'll bring my Koala
backpack and some cake...
Yes!
I'll remember this
vacation forever!
Yes! A single night
of romantic bliss.
And I'll wear my
yellow bunny undies!
What did you say?
What? Did I say something?
It's finally over!
We did it!
Now start
the planning!
It's finally time
to celebrate!
That's great!
I want one!
Stop that, C-ko, you're
embarrassing me. Let's go.
I was just looking.
What's the hurry?
It's spring. I want
to buy some new clothes.
Come on, this way.
Gorgeous!
That blouse is beautiful.
What's wrong,
A-ko?
It comes to
240,000 yen.
Then just buy
one piece.
It's too much. I can't even afford
shoes or a purse or anything.
Wanna have
a crepe?
No thanks.
How about some
snack cakes?
They're 92
calories each.
How am I going to find a
boyfriend if I'm always with C-ko?
Are you tired of
shopping, yet?
Well, maybe...
not!
How pretty!
Care to try it on?
I can't...
It won't hurt,
just to try it on.
Yeah, but...
I guess it's no good, after all.
You look great in it!
Really cute!
Here, try on these shoes.
We could put your
hair up like this...
You think so?
But now your ears look lonely,
so how about these earrings?
She looks terrible.
A-ko, let's go!
Just a minute.
What do you think, C-ko?
You look stupid!
Acting so grown up!
I know you're still wearing
your panda undies!
Quit it!
I am not!
And, and...
I hate those
earrings!
Wait!
Are you okay?
Hey, wait!
C-KO!
Excuse me!
Damn it! I had to go and buy
them, just 'cause C-ko lost one.
But that dress
was so beautiful.
It would change
my life, if only...
That's just what I
need, this spring.
But it costs
25,900 yen.
I know!
What's your analysis
of this situation?
Stop stuffing yourselves!
All right. Asa,
what's your opinion?
I think they're
just out shopping.
Ine?
Maybe she's going
to a costume ball.
Your analysis is flawed. A-ko must
have something special planned.
This must be thoroughly
investigated. Understand?
Yes!
She's no match for my meticulous
planning and covert intelligence.
Good afternoon.
May I take your order?
It's me, C-ko!
Hello. How
may I help you?
Let's see...
A teriyaki hamburger
and a Coke.
Would you like
fries with that?
I've always wanted
to say that!
The apple pies are
great today. Want one?
I'll have
whatever you say.
Okay. A 16-pack of
nuggets, a large fries,
and a rum-raisin ice cream,
all in a jumbo-size happy meal.
C-ko, you've come three days in a
row. Do you have any money left?
No!
Why don't you
wait in the park?
I'll be over as soon
as I've finished work.
I feel sorry for her.
Coke.
Yes, sir.
I'm really, really sorry
about running you down.
I didn't think I'd ever
be meeting you again.
He's so handsome!
Here's your Coke.
"Was he trying to find me?"
"What should I do?"
Hold it right
there, A-ko!
This is a violation of Graviton
High's conduct regulations!
B-ko!
Part-time jobs are prohibited!
I'll have to report this
to the discipline board!
And the... uh... repercussions...
"Who IS that man?"
But don't worry. I've
decided not to turn you in.
So, who's your friend?
Kei!
What am I doing?
This is our second time...
Only the second time?
My shift's over! I have to go!
I have to meet someone!
I mean, I have to meet
a girl! Her name's C-ko.
I'll never make
it in time!
A-ko, hurry up! You can't
leave your lover waiting!
Really? Are you sure it's okay?
You'll give me a ride?
That's great!
See you, B-ko!
So I fibbed a little. The long
route is much more scenic.
I can hear his
heart beating.
It's like a dream!
I could die!
Sorry I'm late, C-ko.
Oh, this is Kei.
Stop it!
Sorry, she's
always like this.
Thank you for the ride.
It was wonderful.
What?
What the hell?
What the hell
is this?
He walked
right past me!
In all my sixteen years,
I've NEVER been so humiliated!
He was wonderful!
So quiet.
I've always dreamed
of riding a motorcycle!
We watched the sunset together.
He told me I was pretty.
What?
He said that?
Not exactly, but I
could see it in his eyes.
I dream about
him, every night.
My heart's pounding.
I wish B-ko would give us a
raise. I'm tired of ramen.
He's here.
He's gorgeous!
What a hunk!
I want that man!
Hello again!
One Coke?
Here you go!
Thanks.
Hey!
Get a move on!
Help the next customer.
I'm sorry.
Oh, there he is.
He's sitting with C-ko.
He's waiting for me!
Why'd he go home?
Did he say anything?
No, nothing.
Oh, no!
It's true.
Here.
What? There's a party!
It's an invitation!
He must have been too shy
to give it to me directly!
This Sunday,
at six,
at the Spaceship Hotel.
Got it.
Excellent job, team.
You may have the night off.
Goodnight,
ma'am.
What is this trembling I feel?
Could it be what men call love?
Oh, Kei, my first love.
But I can't! It
wouldn't be right.
I've made a commitment to
C-ko. How can I abandon her?
I feel such anguish.
I... I love C-ko!
And yet, I can't
ignore my love for Kei.
Oh, well!
Here we go!
Oh, this'll never do!
Just three short days.
In three days, I'll
be wearing that dress.
I'll look so beautiful.
I'll be a brand new me!
To the loyal patrons
of the Spaceship Hotel,
we have good news.
The resort will be reopened
tomorrow night at ten.
There will be a commemorative
party to celebrate the occasion.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I had to work late.
What's up,
A-ko?
I'm getting in
shape! Wait here.
In shape?
Rotten!
No!
Yuck!
Another try.
I worked out, and lost
the two centimeters!
I'll tell him at the
party. "I love you."
I'll have to build
up my courage.
That's it! I'm
going to do it!
I can't laugh, or I'll get
wrinkles. But look at A-ko!
She looks
simply monstrous!
I'm surprised she
doesn't crack the mirror.
No one would ever go out
with her! But I can't laugh.
I've finally finished work,
and now the dress is mine!
What? It's gone?
Gone, gone, gone?
Completely vanished?
But the party's tonight! I'd
do anything for that dress!
I'm sorry, but we
sold it yesterday.
I'm sure we can find
something else for you.
No.
Why can't we wear
the same thing?
But I wanted THAT dress!
He'd take me in his arms, and
carry me up the red velvet stairs.
Like in
Gone With the Wind!
Just forget it!
You're mean! You never
used to be this mean to me!
C-ko!
Why do you always have
to be so mean to me?
This thing's heavy!
It's so pretty here!
Yeah.
How do I look?
You look really good.
Where are your
wrist bands?
Oh, you noticed?
They didn't go with the
dress, so I left them home.
A-ko!
Uh, hi.
My dress!
Oh, no!
My beautiful
dream!
Oh, A-ko, what are you doing
here? What a coincidence.
And what's with the dress?
It's sooo attractive.
Shut up! What I wear
is my business!
What's B-ko doing here?
I'd like to thank
you all for coming.
Thanks to our customers, we've
been able to reopen the resort.
And since
I'm so happy,
I'd like to sing a song
I wrote for this occasion.
Please feel free
to clap along.
Pappan ga,
pan pan pan!
We got hot water,
In our
spaceship bathtubs,
Pappan ga,
pan pan pan!
Oh, A-ko, what are you doing
here? What a coincidence.
And what's with the dress?
It's sooo attractive.
How did B-ko
get in here?
I'll never let
A-ko have him!
With his good looks, Kei's
a perfect match for me.
So why would he fall for a cow like
A-ko? What could he see in her?
Why's he interested
in a gorilla like her?
If you're going to have a
monologue, keep it to yourself!
Kei! Thank you so
much for the invitation!
Yes, Kei. I was overjoyed
to receive your invitation.
But why did you
send it through A-ko?
There's no need
to be so shy.
Not where
I'm concerned.
Say, B-ko...
I don't remember seeing
your name on the invitation.
Poor A-ko. You just don't
understand how subtle Kei is.
If you insist on
being so dense,
Kei will think
you're an idiot.
B-ko, if you want a fight...
Oh, no! I took off
my wrist bands!
Oh, you and
your jokes, A-ko.
Yeah, here's a
joke for you!
What?
Unit A to Unit B. Destruction
of the spaceship has commenced.
Alert the director.
Roger.
The director says his ulcer hurts,
and he's going to lie down.
What?
What should we do?
We can't do anything without
the director's approval.
Oh, I give up! Soldier,
you didn't see anything!
Yes, sir.
Mr. Okao!
Yes, sir?
It's an emergency. Our pathetic
defense force has abandoned us.
It's up to us, now.
Send forth the call,
throughout the city!
Emergency alert! Emergency
alert! Calling all public workers!
North Side team, assemble at
Pier 4. East Side to Wharf 3.
West Side team to Warehouse 7, and
South Side to the Spaceship Hotel!
What are you doing?
Just be quiet.
No, don't!
Sorry to interrupt boys,
but it's an emergency.
Everyone mobilize,
pretty please.
It's a
mobilization alert.
We're sorry.
Please come again.
Come on.
You know how irritated the
shift manager gets if we're late.
It's starting.
It's beginning.
How I've waited
for this!
All systems:
Code GREEN.
Launch!
An alert!
I've been
waiting for this!
Now entering L Formation.
Evacuate all non-essential personnel.
All non-essential personnel
must be evacuated.
All units in
position, Mr. Mayor.
If the conflict escalates,
we'll have to move in.
Until then,
stand by.
You don't know how hard I
worked to make tonight perfect!
Kei's not looking
for a clod like you.
He's much better suited to
a person of my intellect.
Shut up!
Make me!
C-ko...
I just wanted to say,
I...
...love...
...you.
Of course.
What a nice couple.
No! He was only using
me to get close to C-ko.
I...
He won't get
away with this!
...hate you!
The conflict has
escalated! Move in!
What? I'll be
right there!
What'll it be?
My beautiful ship!
Captain!
What a show!
Oh, there's a
festival today?
Hold out your hand.
How cute!
For me?
Yeah. You had to buy those
earrings because of me.
I was waiting all night
to give this to you.
I'm sorry,
C-ko.
Well, what do
you think?
It's great!
It's late.
Let's go home.
You may have won this round,
A-ko, but I'll beat you yet.
Just you wait!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Cherry dance bloomin' tonight
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Hot kiss give me tonight
Your shy heart can't get
burning love
My hot heat just like a hurricane
Will change you sexual animal
Gonna make a wonderful night
Your sweet voice can't knock
charming Eve
My cute dance just like Norma Jean
Will make you midnight crazy
Gonna take a miracle time
Thunder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating to mine
Wonder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating
Down with you baby, Want you
Down down down down
Never give up!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Cherry dance bloomin' tonight!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady
Hot kiss give me please
I'm in trouble Hold me tonight
Your shy heart can't get
burning love
My hot heat just like a hurricane
Will change you sexual animal
Gonna make a wonderful night
Your sweet voice can't knock
charming Eve
My cute dance just like Norma Jean
Will make you midnight crazy
Gonna take a miracle time
Thunder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating to mine
Wonder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating
Down with you baby, Want you
Down down down down
Never give up!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Cherry dance bloomin' tonight!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady
Hot kiss give me please
I'm in trouble Hold me tonight
Thunder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating to mine
Wonder lady, Dancin' Dancin'
Passion is heating
Down with you baby, Want you
Down down down down
Never give up!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Cherry dance bloomin' tonight!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady!
Hot kiss give me tonight
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady
Cherry dance bloomin' tonight!
Get ready!
Get a chance, lady
Hot kiss give me please
I'm in trouble Hold me tonight