Deciding on pierced earrings or
looking for a flashy mini-skirt
Boys along the building wall, look,
they're waiting to ambush you
Turn your heart into a game
If you have many things you want to do,
start the one you can
You can take it day by day, it's okay,
wherever you start from
If you can hold me tight,
I can treasure your smile
You can take it day by day, all right,
I've already realized
What the first piece to the
puzzle in my heart is
Ah, what nice weather!
It's the peak of spring right now, isn't it?
It really is.
Spring is the season of love.
Let's go out and seek new love!
Rather than seeking new love, why don't
you go seek new work?
Damn, when you say something to me,
it's always the same thing.
When the time comes, the work
will come to me.
So you've been saying, and how many
weeks have passed now?
How many months, you should say.
Damn, there you go again.
I don't care what it is, but I wish some
work would fall from the sky.
What a joke!
Ryo, that Cessna...
Yeah, something is definitely wrong!
It isn't coming this way, is it?
It's coming straight for us!
Kaori!
Big Revival of the Funny Pair
The Beauty Fallen from the Sky
We're alive, aren't we?
I think so.
Anyway, you said that you
didn't care what it was.
You just wished some work
would fall from the sky.
Hey, don't blame this on me!
Jeez!
Why is there a building here?!
A female pilot?
Ryo?
Hi, I'm a doctor.
The shape of your bust has not
been destroyed, I gather.
Well, well, take off your clothes,
and lie down here please.
We don't know what part of your body
you might have injured.
Excuse me...
Ryo!
I can't believe you're joking around
while our place is like this!
Oh, I am so, so...
Sorry!
The plane suddenly went out of control,
and I tried my best, but...
I'm really sorry.
Well, nobody got hurt, and
that's a good thing.
By the way, what's your name?
My name is Shoko Amano.
Shoko, what a nice name.
My name is Ryo Saeba.
This must be our fate.
Why don't you have some tea with me?
Excuse me, but the lady behind you...
My name is Kaori Makimura,
and my job is to protect women
from this jerk's mokkori.
What?!
When did you start a job like that, Kaori?
No questions accepted. Eat this!
100 ton hammer!
Disgusting!
I guess I crashed into an amazing place.
Air Freight Logistics - Transportation
Kodama Air
It wasn't my fault!
It's so obvious that the accident
was caused by sabotage.
Why am I the only one being punished?
I don't understand!
When an accident occurs, the pilot is
punished. It's a matter of course.
But the cause was...
I can't believe that you crashed the
plane into an apartment.
Fortunately, those people were unharmed,
but think about it!
Anyway, until the investigation of this
accident is over, you are not allowed to fly.
Am I clear?!
I can't fly.
Not being able to fly...
I guess you really love to fly through
the sky, don't you?
Of course! Flying is everything to me.
I guess you can't understand how I feel.
By the way, you said that the plane suddenly
went out of control while you were flying?
It was probably engine failure.
Maintenance didn't do their job.
Just thinking about it makes me mad!
Forget all that bad stuff and...
Come with me...
And have dinner! How about it?!
Mr. Saeba!
Yes?
I'm so frustrated!
Let's party and have fun!
Oh, yeah! That's right! Let's party,
just the two of us!
Three of us.
She's here!
Am I a ghost or something?
I'm so stuffed!
The best feeling in the world!
The last piece of chicken...
Be careful, the last bite will make you a pig.
Not a pig, but I can be a bird.
Wings will suddenly grow on your back.
I wish they would.
Miss Shoko, you really love flying,
don't you?
Thank you for everything. I haven't felt
this good in a long time.
By the way, that was an F-15 Eagle.
I sleep really well when I hear that sound.
Well, goodnight. Bye!
Goodnight.
Her sense is something else, isn't it?
Ryo?
WHOOOOOOOOOSH!!
Hopeless!
Falcon, you shouldn't laugh at him
that much! Right?
Right!
You can escape from a bullet,
but you couldn't escape from
a Cessna, could you?
Shut up! Stop laughing right now,
or I'm going to make you into pickled
octopus and feed you to the cats!
By the way, Ryo, where are both of you
going to sleep tonight?
The Cessna destroyed your apartment,
and only your bedroom is
undamaged, isn't it?
No!
He's right. This is the only room we can use.
Only one bed...
I don't want to sleep in the same bed as you!
Excuse me!
Don't think you're the only one
who doesn't like the idea.
Damn, that Umibozu jerk. He could've
let us stay there.
I am not that senseless.
I won't forgive you if you approach me.
What a cold-minded woman you are.
This bed was originally mine, wasn't it?
Are you saying that I should catch cold?
Well, I won't do anything, so please
let me under the covers, please!
Do you promise that you won't do anything?
Have I ever approached you before?
Am I that unattractive to you?
What?!
Hey, do you want me to do
something to you?
No way!
Fine, if you want to get in, get in.
Why are you mad at me?!
What's the matter?
You came on my side, didn't you?
No I didn't.
Liar! I heard the bed squeak.
This floor is old, and on top of that,
the heavy shock and our combined
weight made the floor fall.
Hey, hey, don't get so close to me!
I can't help it! Jeez!
If I fall asleep in a situation like this,
I don't know what he'd do to me.
I wish I were with Shoko.
You're the only person I won't mokkori.
Ryo's going to go straight to sleep!
Shut your mouth! Hurry up and go to sleep!
Why are you so mad?
Idiot!
He really is an idiot!
First of all, it's all Ryo's fault.
You get mokkori immediately
when you see a woman.
Right? You're just like that.
Even though you say you wouldn't
mokkori me, I am a woman.
It's natural for me to feel
endangered, isn't it?
If possible, I don't want to use
my hammer, but...
Ryo?
Ryo...
It's a little too late to visit someone's
house, isn't it, Mister?
Damn!
Well, well, since we have a huge hole
like this, a thief snuck in.
His target was the Cessna?
Oh, my, are those drugs?
Well, probably.
I guess this was not a simple accident.
You let them find out about the drugs!
You idiot!
I'm so sorry, boss.
In this situation, they'll have to die!
I can't leave this to someone like you!
Well...
You have a troublesome man as your enemy.
Who are you?
You're the one I've heard about,
the professional saboteur.
I am Koumori.
Drugs were found in my Cessna?!
Recently, a new type of LSD has
been spreading quickly
throughout the central Kantou
region, and this is it.
Why was something like that in the Cessna?
Think of it as someone using a Cessna
aircraft to operate a drug running business.
It can't be. Someone in the
company is doing that?
Then Miss Shoko has been transporting
drugs without knowing it?
No, if so, this is too small a portion.
I checked the Cessna, and I found
sugar in the fuel tank.
And there was a cut in the vertical
rudder control wire.
What did you say?!
Which means they tried to kill you
and blame everything on you.
Officials would find the drugs and your dead
body in the wreckage of the crashed Cessna.
The officials would think that you had an
accident in the middle of a drug run.
Dead people tell no tales.
Oh, no, I was almost killed.
Don't worry. I will protect you.
You, who are you?
Leave things to us.
We are professionals at this sort of thing.
Professionals?
Right, Ryo?
Yes!
She was so shocked, wasn't she?
Hello, Amano residence?
What? Really?
Oh, sorry. I was a little too mean
to you yesterday.
Yes, we can't turn these clients down,
so please help me.
You can fly this afternoon?
What about your punishment?
They have some urgent job to do,
I guess. How lucky I am!
Jeez, she totally forgot that someone
is trying to kill her.
Hi, good morning, Miss Shoko.
Good morning.
Without you, our work will be delayed,
and I'll be in a jam.
You flatter me!
Well, come with me.
Yes!
What's that?!
Oh, man! This is the legendary adult video
that I was never able to get!
Wow!
I've really wanted to watch this!
No way! That many?!
Am I dreaming or what?!
Wow, I hope this isn't a dream!
I really wanted to pilot this one.
The load is pretty big, so I chose this one.
Wow, how nice!
What? Ryo?
I can't believe this!
Jeez! This happens every time
I take my eyes off of him!
I'm so happy.
Wow!
It's a pile of underwear!
Yahoo!
I'm so moved!
What?
Where did you go, Ryo?
What are you going to do
to guard Miss Shoko?!
Are you sure the death will
look like an accident?
Don't worry. I'm a professional.
Once she takes off, she won't
be able to land.
When she tries to land and
lowers the front tires,
the plastic bomb will explode.
Nothing will remain.
This is terrible!
Dumb!
Well, stand up.
Jeez, I wonder what happened to
Mr. Saeba and Miss Kaori?
Miss Shoko, it's time. Take off.
Yes!
I trust you, Mr. Saeba.
Such an easy job.
Neither of you put up much resistance.
Ryo? What did you do to him?!
Him?
I guess he's in...
I'm right here.
Ryo!
You?! How?!
Do you really think you locked me
in there using things like that?
First of all...
I can't satisfy myself with just software.
Damn!
Are you all right?
Miss Shoko is in danger!
What?
A bomb?!
Yes, the bomb was set in the front tires.
It will explode when you lower
the landing gear.
What did you say?!
Listen, do exactly what I say.
Oh, no! In that case, I can't land the plane.
What were you doing?! You're my
bodyguard, aren't you?!
Calm down, Miss Shoko!
Trust me! I promise I'll get you
back on the ground.
Do exactly what I say.
I understand. I believe you.
Tell me what to do.
Good girl, come back here immediately.
Ryo, here she comes.
All right.
Get ready to land without
lowering the wheels.
Fly really close to the runway.
Can you do that?
I'll try.
Mr. Saeba, just what...
Stay like that. Concentrate on
manipulating the plane.
I believe you, Mr. Saeba.
Kaori, change drivers!
So suddenly?!
Why me?!
Idiot, be careful!
Sorry, sorry.
That wire!
Idiot, he isn't looking at anything but
the plane, so he can't see me.
Die, Saeba!
What the hell?!
Ryo, look out in front! Front, front!
The runway will end soon!
Keep driving like this, Kaori!
Mr. Saeba, don't overdo it!
Believe in me and keep flying, Shoko!
It's okay now. You can land, Shoko.
Mr. Saeba...
Mr. Saeba, you're such a...
You're trying to be cool, but do you
know where you are?
Thank you, Mr. Saeba.
If you're feeling, even though you
tend to your accessories
You can't compete against the
rainbows and stars
Tidings from the wind taught me
Your smile is important,
all of my love forever
Raise your downcast face
and look up at the sky
Give me peace in my hands, starting over
Smile and smile, you are the angel
on a shooting star
Heart and heart, at this very moment
Smile and smile, you are the angel
on a shooting star
Heart and heart, at this very moment
Smile and smile...
Ryo!
Goodbye, Kaori.
No way, Ryo.
Ryo...
Ryo!
Farewell, Kaori!
Arrest Warrant for the City Hunter