Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Aim for Ryogoku Kokugikan
Episode 02
Hey, newcomer !
Yes ?
What's your name ?
I'm Kunimi Hiro.
Kunimi, huh ?
You're not very cute.
Huh ?
Normally, when newcomers are
made to run this much, they collapse.
I see.
Then we upperclassmen
would proudly preach to them...
...and that makes it easier
for us to coach you later.
That's the objective of
this running exercise.
Oh.
You really aren't cute.
Look.
See how cute the other newcomers are.
If I do another 50 laps,
I'm confident that I'll collapse.
Don't bother ! You're in the way,
so just sit there or something.
Hey, first years !
You're pathetic !
Pull yourselves together !
Oh, there it goes !
Fore !
Moron, that's golf.
What's this ball ?
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it right away.
Please give it to us.
I'm really sorry.
Don't come in here with
your dirty spiked shoes !
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Sorry for the intrusion.
What is it ?
I thought there wasn't a
baseball club at this school.
It's not a club.
It's a fan club.
They can only play catch and stuff.
They just play around in the backyard.
Fan club...
Soccer Club
Come in.
Um, I came here to bring the photo that I forgot to put on the club registration.
Oh, Kunimi.
I've heard about you.
I'm Kawamura Hikari, a second year
and the manager of the soccer club.
You can call me Hikari.
That's what everyone calls me.
Kawamura Hikari...
I heard about it.
During the welcome rite for newcomers, the hellish running exercise...
...you didn't even break a sweat.
But don't get cocky. Those newcomers are just general admission members.
General admission ?
That's right. That excludes
those with previous experience.
I see.
Here it is, Kawamura.
You can call me Hikari.
Sure...
...Kawamura.
You can call me Hikari, I'm telling you.
Hikari.
Huh ?
Is Hideo out somewhere ?
I've been telling you.
Our baseball club is well-known.
He can't be lying around during the day, unlike somebody.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Koushien...
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
For high school baseball players,
that goes without saying.
Well, I wish Hide-chan well.
I've found a new goal for myself.
Aim
Hey, where does the national
tournament for soccer take place ?
Ryogoku Kokugikan.
Oh, I see.
Aim
Ryogoku
Koku
Gi
Kan
Aim for
Ryogokku Kokugikan
Hiro
Does it seem weird ?
Not as much as your head.
Hey.
Hi, Noda.
How's your back ?
It's doing well these days.
Maybe my rehab is doing some good.
What are you doing for rehab ?
Butterfly style.
Swimming, I mean.
Butterfly ?
Is it okay for you
to be doing that ?
The doctor says so,
so it should be fine.
Hikari, do you know where the
half-eaten bread that was here went ?
It was getting moldy, so I threw it away.
Oh, really ?
It was only three days old.
That's right.
It's getting warmer these days.
Oh well.
Hey, friend in idleness.
What is it ?
Let's idle around.
Don't idle around me.
Stop it.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Stop it.
Idling. Idling.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
I'm telling you to stop it.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Meiwa Daiichi High School
How is it going, Tachibana ?
That's our ace pitcher, Maruyama.
His pitches are fast, aren't they ?
He's ranked among the best in terms of
right-handed power pitchers in the prefecture.
A power pitcher, huh ?
Alright !
It went right down the middle !
It doesn't matter where
that pitch was located.
People can barely get to it.
Seriously ?
Yeah.
Then next, I'm going to
throw my specialty, the forkball.
Hey, hey ! Don't !
Wha...?
How is that a forkball ?
That was just a 140km pitch that bounced !
It dropped a little.
Right, Hide ?
I don't know.
A 140km forkball...
What ? Did you say something ?
Um, it's nothing.
See ? Kids nowadays
prefer soccer to baseball.
Yeah, I guess.
It's only for old people who watch the
night games and sip of beer these days.
Yeah, I guess.
You don't sound very
committed when you agree.
Really ?
Anyway, soccer is great.
Swimming is good, too.
I'm going running.
I'm going to run, too.
I'm going.
Oh, Hiro, hold on a second.
What ?
I've been meaning to tell you...
...that the daughter my company's
president is enrolled at your high school.
Make sure that you're courteous to her.
Who cares ?
No way I'm bringing parents'
hierarchical relationship into school.
Don't be such a square.
Do it for the sake of my promotion.
Geez. You can't get promoted unless
you suck up to the president's daughter ?
Of course I can. Don't you
know how well I do my work ?
What's her name ?
Let's see.
If I recall, her name is Koga...
Oh, yeah.
It's Koga Haruka.
I'm going.
Dammit, I'm running late. Kawamura's small talk goes on way too long.
Um, I'm sorry.
Are you okay ?
Um, I haven't heard
your name yet, have I ?
Kunimi Hiro.
I'm Koga Haruka.
What are all these balls for ?
I just tripped a little.
Oh, didn't you know ? Our school doesn't have a baseball club, but it has a baseball fan club.
Oh, I see.
I love high school baseball, so I'm going to be the manager of the club starting today.
Oh, good luck.
I've got to go to my practice, too.
Is it the soccer club ?
Yeah.
Soccer is certainly popular.
That's right.
I like baseball better, though.
Well, that's fine.
Hey.
Yes ?
There's one more.
Thanks.
This is the smell I remember from my younger days.
Huh ?
There.
Thanks.
There, there, there, there, there !
Here I come !
Shoot it !
Goal !
Honestly, he's noisy.
He's not just a noisy guy.
Kine Ryutarou.
He was the ace striker
for Kitano Junior High...
...the second place team in
the Prefectural Tournament.
Really ?
He's an exceptional talent, even among
the special admission first year members.
There's no doubt that he'll
immediately be a regular, huh ?
I'm envious.
Hey, general admission members !
Stop chit-chatting and get back
to plucking weeds already !
Okay.
Hey, running-lover Kunimi.
Hm ?
Go get some coffee.
Oh, then for me, too.
Yeah, I want oolong tea.
I want grape juice.
I want hot oolong tea.
Hey, you.
Get mine, too.
He certainly isn't just a noisy guy.
After a brief spring break, I suddenly go from the highest grade in school to a newcomer.
It's all sold out ?
Two cans of orange juice.
A can of Coke.
And three cans of coffee.
It's heavy.
Aim for Ryogoku Kokugikan
Hiro
Dammit.
It's a long path to get there.
What kind of swing is that ?
It's so slow a fly
could land on the bat !
Be quiet. You don't belong here, so don't butt in.
I can't watch this.
Hey, Koga. Dont waste your time on such a helpless fan club.
Why don't you become the
manager for the soccer club ?
You can aim for the Nationals with me.
Nationals ?
Ryogoku Kokugikan
Hiro
Aim for
National
Ryogoku Kokugikan
Hiro
Aim for
National Ryogoku Kokugikan...?
Leave me alone.
I like the Koushien better.
How can a fan club without even a practice field get to the Koushien ?
We'll try hard and
make it an actual club.
You don't know anything, do you ?
No matter how hard you try,
it's hopeless at this school.
Right, Seniors ?
Um, what is he talking about ?
Well, we aren't really
focused on the Koushien...
We just love baseball.
We can play two bush-league games a month at the municipal park, after all.
Of course. No real baseball club will play with you guys.
Shut up !
Just go away already !
You're getting in the way of our practice !
Well, I hope you'll wake up soon and come to the soccer club.
Canned coffee. Canned coffee.
She's cute, isnt she ?
She's in my class.
Her name is Koga Haruka.
As far as I can tell, she's the best among the first years.
Just watch. I'm going to score
a goal with her by summer.
Before that...
...shouldn't you thank a guy
who made a long uphill run...
...with twenty cans of coffee and oolong tea and stuff ?
Um, thanks.
Take half of this.
Sure.
Um, you don't know who I am ?
I'm Kine from Kitano Junior High.
I'm fairly famous
in the soccer world !
I didn't see anything about you in the rulebook I read.
Hey...
You're late, Kunimi !
Shoot it !
Damn him !
Hey, Kunimi !
Yes ?
Go get the ball !
Sure.
I'm giving it back to you.
Hey...
Damn him...
Hey, newcomer !
Yes ?
It's a decade too early
for you to kick the ball !
I don't want to be in
high school for a decade...
Run !
Just watch. I'm aiming for...
...Ryogoku Kokugikan.
Was it National Ryogoku Kokugikan...?
Is sumo fun for you ?
Hey.
Are you having fun with sumo ?
But it was unexpected.
Even though it is popular with girls,
I never thought you'd choose sumo.
Huh ? What are you talking about ?
I mean, you joined
the sumo club, right ?
Who did ?
Aim for Ryogoku Kokugikan
Hiro
Damn that Hikari !
Moron. It's your fault
for not realizing it.
Since you were a child, all you
cared about was baseball, after all.
Hey, stop the videotape !
Don't watch ahead !
Is your baseball club really okay ?
To think that your baseball club
has lots of these videotapes...
Don't worry. There's no correlation
between baseball skills and lewdness.
Right, Hiro ?
Shut up.
All right, it's done.
Aim for Nihon Budoukan
Hiro
This is good, right, Hide ?
Are you having fun
with rock & roll music ?
I'm impressed,
Hideo the grown-up !
Did you trick me ?
I never thought anyone would be
stupid enough to be fooled like this !
Damn you !
Hey !
Oh, silly.
It might seem to go without saying, but I will explain to you good kids.
Ryogoku Kokugikan is where sumo matches take place.
Nihon Budoukan is known to be a concert hall where rock bands aspire to perform.
By the way, the national tournament
for high school soccer takes place at...
Hey, who the heck are you talking to ?!
No ! Don't do it, silly.
This guy is a moron !
It's not me !
Stop it ! Cut it out already !
Don't stop it ! More, silly !
Huh ?
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryotaro:
If you have a hand...
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryotaro:
If you have a hand...
Mitsuya Yuji
Mizuhara Rin
Takagi Wataru
Ugaki Shuusei
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Neya Michiko
Konishi Hiroko
Mr. Kunimi:
Kawamura Hikari:
Hironaga:
Akagi:
Sato:
Tanaka:
Meiwa Captain:
Young Hideo:
Child:
If you have a hand...
Mr. Kunimi:
Kawamura Hikari:
Hironaga:
Akagi:
Sato:
Tanaka:
Meiwa Captain:
Young Hideo:
Child:
Mitsuya Yuji
Mizuhara Rin
Takagi Wataru
Ugaki Shuusei
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Neya Michiko
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Mr. Kunimi:
Kawamura Hikari:
Hironaga:
Akagi:
Sato:
Tanaka:
Meiwa Captain:
Young Hideo:
Child:
Mitsuya Yuji
Mizuhara Rin
Takagi Wataru
Ugaki Shuusei
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Neya Michiko
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
Ryogoku Kokugikan is a famous indoor event venue in Tokyo, primarily for sumo, though it has been used for wrestling, boxing, concerts, etc.
Nihon Budoukan is a venue for Japanese martial arts, but in some ways, its more famous as a venue for music concerts.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
Ryogoku Kokugikan is a famous indoor event venue in Tokyo, primarily for sumo, though it has been used for wrestling, boxing, concerts, etc.
Nihon Budoukan is a venue for Japanese martial arts, but in some ways, its more famous as a venue for music concerts.
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Notes:
Ryogoku Kokugikan is a famous indoor event venue in Tokyo, primarily for sumo, though it has been used for wrestling, boxing, concerts, etc.
Nihon Budoukan is a venue for Japanese martial arts, but in some ways, its more famous as a venue for music concerts.
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
Timing
Todd Perkins
Editing
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Translation
Toshiaki
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hey, Hiro, is soccer fun ?
It's fun. There's someone that makes me passionate, too.
In truth, you might still have an attachment to baseball.
There's no baseball club at our school.
But there's a fan club, right ?
Sounds like it.
They're going to play a practice
game against the soccer club, I hear.
It doesn't concern me, probably.
Next episode of H2,
"Hey, Hey, Soccer Club..."
Look forward to it !
Hey, Hey, Soccer Club...
Next episode of H2 is
Next episode of H2,
"Hey, Hey, Soccer Club..."
Are you having a refreshing workout ?
Next episode of H2 is
Hey, Hey, Soccer Club...
Look forward to it !
Next episode of H2 is
Hey, Hey, Soccer Club...
Look forward to it !