Original file: DH2:H2Ep05.txt.js
H2, Episode #5, "Do You Require a Registration Form ?"
0:00:04.00 0:00:05.00
0:00:12.00 0:00:13.00  ...!
0:00:42.00 0:00:43.00
0:02:40.00 0:02:41.00
0:03:42.00 0:03:43.00
0:06:22.00 0:06:23.00
Processed by Central Anime's NUMIT On 04/16/2013
Do You Require a Registration Form ?
Teams
Soccer Club
Fan Club
Now, leadoff batter,
let's get on base !
Kine is in top shape.
He begins to pitch in the
bottom of the fourth inning.
Five, topping, soba !
Hit by pitch.
I'm sorry.
It slipped through my fingers.
I'm fine.
Maybe "five topping soba"
wasn't the right one.
Pot, sticker, rice !
Ball.
Sautéed, green onion, liver !
Grilled, beef, meal !
Ball.
Ma, po, tofu !
Four balls.
A scoring chance !
Oh my, what's happening to you, Kine ?
Oh, I see.
Ah, shall we have ramen ?
The fact that you made the
call means it's on you, right ?
What ? It's on me ?
It's okay.
I'll order a mapo tofu.
Ball four.
Great ! The bases are
loaded with no outs !
Oh, no !
Kine, hang in there !
Now, the bases are loaded with no outs. Kine is in a tight spot.
From the set position...
...he throws the first pitch !
Strike !
...!
Then the second pitch !
That's similar to Hiro's pitching motion.
Really ?
Come to think of it, that guy
also hurt his elbow and retired.
Wasn't it the shoulder that
he had acupuncture done on ?
Thank you for waiting.
It looks delicious !
It's even more so when I realize that it's a treat.
If I were told that my elbow would break down in three months if I kept pitching...
...I wonder if I would
feel like eating ramen.
Strike ! Batter out !
Kine is impressive !
Three consecutive strikeouts !
Kine escapes the jam.
He's thoroughly toying with them.
Ball.
But honestly, baseball
is such a boring sport.
Really. You get to sit in
the dugout during offense.
It would be unthinkable in soccer.
My body is going numb from inactivity.
Ball three.
Come on ! Come on !
I wouldn't want to walk.
Yeah !
Don't worry !
It was just bad luck !
This isn't baseball.
This isn't baseball at all.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for the meal.
Um, yeah.
But...
I never thought that the
battery-mates from junior high...
...Hiro and Noda would go to Senkawa
High School, which has no baseball club.
Mr. "swimming club member who
just happened to be passing by,"...
...you know a lot about baseball ?
I'm Noda, who was a catcher, but hurt his back and retired...
...then came to Senkawa because it doesn't have a baseball club...
...joined the swimming club to rehabilitate his back, and is practicing the butterfly style.
That's such a straightforward self-introduction.
One out with a runner on second.
The batter is Kunimi,
a catcher, hitting ninth.
I suppose we'll have to place our hope in the next batter, Nabe.
Leave it to me.
Oh ?
Wow...
It's a homerun.
You can't brag about hitting a
homerun off such a lousy pitch.
Yeah. It's embarrassing,
so don't tell anyone.
Humph.
Call me Hikari.
8 to 1.
Are you frustrated ?
Of course.
But it's not about losing.
Meow.
Ball. Ball four !
That was close.
My forkball dropped too much.
Again ?
Ball.
Once again, he's intentionally loading
the bases and then striking out the side.
Aw...
Ball. Ball four.
Hm ?
What are you doing ?
Warming up.
Ball.
That's strange.
I'm borrowing the mitt.
Play catch with me.
Huh ?
Ball three.
Ball. Ball four.
Oh, no !
Kawamura.
Huh ?
Kunimi Hiro, a first year on general admission...
...is leaving the soccer
club as of this moment.
Then sign this withdrawal form.
Here, right ?
Do I need a stamp ?
There's no need.
...?
Do you require a registration form ?
Um, well, no.
First, can you give us your name ?
Kunimi Hiro.
And Noda Atsushi.
Kunimi Hiro ?
If possible, in this bases
loaded scoring opportunity...
...it would be great if you could use me as a pinch-hitter.
Um, sure, with pleasure.
I guess I'll have to be the catcher.
It's regrettable.
If you had hung in there for a year...
...you would have gotten a pretty good position with our soccer club, too.
The score is 8-1 in the
bottom of the fifth inning.
This crappy game is already over.
In baseball, nothing is over...
...until the last three outs, no matter what the score.
EYECATCH
Hey.
Could it be that "Kunimi" and "Noda" are...
No way.
I didn't think so.
Kunimi Hiro...
I feel like I've heard
his name somewhere.
All right.
I'm going to show you my real stuff.
Wow, cool !
Kine, good luck !
This is my true ability !
Bases-loaded...
...homerun...
One run.
Two runs.
Three runs.
Four runs.
8-5.
I'm going to teach you the fun
of the game without time limits.
It's embarrassing, so don't tell anyone.
Damn him.
Another pinch-hitter.
There are mis-pitches once in a while.
How about this ?
Foul !
Hooked it.
I didn't think I could
move my back this easily.
Um...
Are you from the same junior high ?
Yes. From Seinan Junior High.
Seinan Junior High ?
Kunimi and Noda ?
Then you two must be the...
That's right. It's Kunimi Hiro. There's no mistaking it.
No wonder I thought I heard your name somewhere.
Then just as I thought...
That's right.
He's the son of an employee at my father's company.
He gets 5000 yen per
month of allowance.
He spends most of it on porn.
That Kunimi Hiro !
That's me.
Um, well...
Hey, Kunimi, your father works for
Koga Commercial Company, doesn't he ?
Come to think of it, that may
be the company's name.
I knew it !
Um, that's not what
we are talking about.
I mean...
Nice play.
Out !
Damn him...
Hang in there !
Show your fighting spirit !
Give it your best !
Dammit.
Baseball idiot ?
Who are you talking about ?
Me ?
Yes. And...
...Hiro and Noda.
You're all...
...baseball idiots.
We're all baseball idiots, huh ?
Strike ! Batter out !
Three outs ! Change !
Hey, Hikari.
Hm ?
Do you have Kunimi's registration form ?
Let's see...
Here you go.
...!
Hiro.
Do you need some warm-up pitches ?
Nope.
As for the signs, the rock will be the fastball, and scissors will be the curveball.
There's no paper ?
No.
Oh ?
What's wrong ?
You need more than just
fastballs to go up against us ?
But I'd get bored
calling pitches that way.
And I can't catch it if he throws a
curveball without giving me a sign first.
Being the baseball idiots that they are,
will they be able to quit baseball so easily ?
Here.
What if it were you ?
I'd still continue to the last,
until my body breaks down.
Hiro is in the soccer club.
Noda is in the swimming club.
This is my last game.
Mine, too.
Let's begin.
Play !
First...
...this.
What's the call ?
S...strike !
Okay, okay.
W...what is he ?
That's way faster than a regular fastball.
Of course.
They formed the battery...
...on a team that won the junior high
regional tournament two years in a row.
Our school doesn't have a baseball club. Why would such guys come here ?
Right ?
Who knows ?
It's rock.
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryotaro:
Kawamura Hikari:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Mizuhara Rin
Next Episode
Hironaga:
Akagi:
Baseball Fanclub A:
Baseball Fanclub B:
Lady:
Baseball Fanclub C:
Baseball Fanclub D:
Girls:
Takagi Wataru
Ugaki Shuusei
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Neya Michiko
Yanagisawa Eiji
Narita Ken
Konishi Hiroko
Notes:
Battery = the regular pairing of a certain catcher and pitcher because they work best together.
The "No paper" line for the signs was probably referring to Hiro's Forkball that he really can't control.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
Hiro, you're pitching ?
Yeah. My elbow is doing just fine.
It's the revival of the battery that won the junior high regionals two years in a row.
But this is our last.
Why ?
I can't continue to pitch
and wreck my elbow.
You say so, but you're fired up.
Don't read my feelings.
Next episode of H2,
"This is Kunimi Hiro !"
Next episode of H2 is
This is Kunimi Hiro !
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?