Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 08
The Elbow is Made of Glass, He Says
If they hear such a sound...
If pitchers hear such a sound on the
mound, they'd just want to run away.
Hey, minor.
That's a beer vending machine.
Don't worry.
My father asked me to get some.
Right now, I have no interest in bitter drinks like this.
Then do you want a Coke ?
You don't know who you'll be playing in
the summer preliminary tournament yet ?
No.
How's your team this year ?
We're the favorite to win
the tournament of course.
But as prestigious as Meiwa Daiichi is...
...it hasn't gotten past the
semi-finals in the past three years.
And in the spring invitational, too, it was one of the candidates but ultimately wasn't chosen.
That's because I wasn't there.
What about pitchers ?
Including the reserves,
we have enough pieces.
The only thing is that the ace pitcher, Maruyama, is experiencing some elbow pain.
Elbow...
He's fine.
He's had it properly looked at.
What was that physician's name ?
Doctor Uetake.
Yeah.
He says that it's just fatigue...
...so he  should be good to go in the preliminary if he rests it well for several days.
That's good to hear.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
If your...
Hm ?
Um, no, never mind.
If my elbow were fine, then what ?
Would you have come to my school ?
If you and I were
on the same team...
...the regional tournament would
become boring for three years.
I guess you're right.
Just as I thought,
it started to rain again.
The rainy season will be over soon.
Right.
Oh ?
Kunimi !
Hi.
You run every day ?
Yeah. It's been a habit
of mine for a long time.
Besides, leg strength is important for every sport, not just baseball.
Regardless of what I end up doing, it won't be meaningless.
If you haven't decided what you're going to do yet...
...can you temporarily be the
coach for the Baseball Fan Club ?
Hm ?
If you're just coaching, you
don't have to tax your elbow.
You don't have to do it,
unless you have free time.
I'm not good at telling people what to do.
Oh, I know.
If you're going to get someone
to coach, Noda would be better.
Noda ?
Yeah.
From pitch-calling to defensive
alignment, the flow of the game.
Catchers always have to keep an eye on all aspects of the game.
Temperamentally, too, he's better suited for the role than a selfish pitcher.
Kunimi.
Hm ?
You don't play any
position other than pitcher ?
Thanks to my selfish personality.
Anyway, Noda is the best.
Then, I'll ask.
He finally caught up to me.
Hey...Hiro...!
You should slow down.
Are you trying to kill me ?
Good morning.
Hoo...hoo...hoo...
Are you an owl or something ?
What is your relationship to Hiro ?
We attend the same school.
We only recently met, and that's it.
That's good.
This guy is a pervert, so you
shouldn't get involved with him.
Hey...
In that respect, as much of a pervert as I am, I'm older and have more self-restraint.
So girls are much safer with me.
Huh ?
Moreover, this guy has a monthly allowance of just 5000 yen.
But as for me, look.
As you can see, I have cards...
...and a secret savings account that my wife doesn't know about, so I live quite comfortably.
Hey...
Would you like to have
dinner with me sometime ?
Well, the company's entertainment expenses will pay for it, so you shouldn't feel shy.
...
You can learn a lot by
going out with an older guy.
Let's see...
Oh, I'm Koga.
Yes, Ms. Koga.
Well, I'll think about it.
You can fire him.
...?
I have to go. I need
to get to school early.
Hm ?
I'm going to put up some posters to
recruit new members for the Fan Club.
Someone has been tearing them
down no matter how many I put up.
I see.
Good luck.
Bye, Ms. Koga.
Huh ? Ms. Koga...?
You should look forward to
getting called in by your boss.
What ?
President Koga's daughter...?
If you're transferred to a post in some other city, you should go there alone.
It's torn down again.
I'm not going to back down.
Haruka, I'm done here.
Oh, thanks, Asako.
I appreciate it.
But it's probably useless.
You're the hero !
The hot
springtime
of youth
Now play ball !
Hot-blooded
Baseball Fan Club
is Looking For
New Members !
Baseball is an old people's game. No one's interested.
Then I like old men ?
You like old men ?
You didn't fall for
my father, did you ?
What ? What're you talking about ?
Oh, that's not what
I'm talking about.
Oh, that's right.
Show your best stuff, old man.
What was that ?
Um, Noda.
Yeah ?
I have something I want to ask you.
Can you spare some
time for me after school ?
W...what ?
What...?
No way...
I can't believe it.
Hey, hey ! Come on !
...!
Hey, Maruyama.
My elbow...
Hello ? Hello ?
What's wrong, Tachibana ?
No one's here.
Uetake Clinic
The windows are closed
and the curtains are closed.
They're not supposed
to be closed today.
It can't be helped. Let's have him examined at another hospital.
Goal !
An amazing talent, Kine
has a gold medal right leg.
Huh ? They're...?
Why are those two...?
Hey, Peeping Tom.
Don't scare me.
Just as I thought,
you're feeling uneasy.
What are you talking about ?
Those two have been bonding since the baseball game the other day.
It can't be true ! There's no way Koga would go out with a guy like him !
Oh, they disappeared.
Where are they ?
Women's Dressing Room
Probably the unoccupied dressing room of the girls' swimming club.
How do you know ?
Noda is good at it.
Taking a girl into the
dressing room, I mean.
W...what ?!
Get out !
So can I really ask you to do it ?
Yeah. As you can see,
my rehab is going well.
More importantly, there's no way I can turn down your request.
But I had never heard that butterfly-style swimming is good for rehabbing a bad back.
That's what the doctor says,
so it must be true.
I have to be able to
hit some fungo at least.
Okay, I've got to do one more lap.
Don't call me.
eyecatch
Maruyama hurt his elbow ?
Yeah. Right before the preliminary, we lost our ace pitcher.
But didn't you say that Maruyama's sore elbow was just fatigue ?
That's what that doctor
named Uetake said.
But it turned out differently when they had him examined at the University Hospital.
Dr. Uetake is famous around
here for sports medicine, right ?
Yeah.
607...
Hey, Hiro. Can you
get me some beer ?
Sent Onono Imoko to Sui.
608...
Emissaries to Sui return
to Japan via Kudara.
Honey, this is strange !
Hiro is studying.
It's going to rain hard.
What's wrong with him ?
Just let me kill time however I like.
First-Year
Mid-Term
Top 50 Scorers
They should stop doing this sort of thing in this day and age.
But for those who worked hard, it will
be kind of a reward, don't you think ?
So who worked hard ?
You got into the top 50 just because you guessed right. Don't get too carried away.
You have to narrow
down the target pitch.
If you swing at everything, you
won't be able to hit for average.
"44 Sakurai Kinzou 47..." "45 Nemoto Jun 471" "46 Koga Haruka 452" "47 Kunimi Hiro 449" "48 Koyama Junko 447
Koga Haruka
Kunimi Hiro
Hi. We're neighbors.
Oh, hello.
If I'm just down by three points, I can take the lead in the second term.
Moron.
Huh ?
Haruka had a perfect
score on one of the exams...
...but she forgot to put her name on it, so she received zero points there.
It's like a superstar who hit a homerun but forgot to step on home plate.
Beaten by 103 points.
It's totally a called game.
And you're down by how many points ?
Don't dodge the question by laughing.
What are these "plate" and "called" about ?
Those are baseball terms.
It's proof that they love baseball.
Oh.
See ?
Although he doesn't do well in school, he has a baseball brain.
He's going to be a good coach.
Yes.
There's no one at this clinic.
What ?
They went out of business ?
I'm not sure.
But it's been closed for a week or so, and I haven't seen anyone come in or out.
I see...
Uetake Clinic
How much longer are you
going to be holed up in there ?
Just come out already, crappy father !
Crap and father won't
come out at the same time.
Crap would have to come out first.
Get it out of there already !
Hiro, you have a call.
From who ?
Hikari.
Hikari ?
Hey, what is it this
early in the morning ?
Hiro, did you read the
newspaper this morning ?
I just got out of the shower.
Read the "society" page now.
What is it ? Did some idol get engaged to a sumo grand champion again or something ?
Just hurry up and read it.
Here it is.
The "society" page ?
Yeah.
"Pistol robbery on the rise." "A small
airplane crashes. Two Japanese found dead."
No, those aren't it.
"Jail sentence for nine people,
including the company president."
"Unlicensed doctor..."
"...arrested" ?
That's it !
Uetake Hiroshi [58]
Unlicensed doctor arrested
"Uetake"...
Hello ?
Hiro, are you listening ?
Hiro ? Hiro ?
Unlicensed...
Arrested...
I'm coming over right now.
Wait for me there.
Hiro ? Are you listening, Hiro ?
Exam Room
How did the exams go ?
The elbow is made of glass, he says.
I see.
It's made of glass...
...but it's bulletproof and won't break even if someone shoots at it.
What ?
They didn't find anything
wrong with my back, either.
Then...
Just as we thought...
Screw that fake doctor, Uetake !
Hey, are you really going to do this ?
Don't you think it's childish ?
No.
This is minimal revenge.
I can't just go quietly.
Be a lookout for us.
No.
Are you going to stop us ?
I'm going to do it, too.
What ?
Moron
Quack
Liar
Screw you
Dumb ass
Dummy !
Someone's coming !
Ugh !
Ah, I feel content.
Right, Hiro ?
Hiro ?
From here on...
...it's something they have to deal with.
What are you going to do ?
About what ?
You know.
Of course.
If you're seriously aiming for the Koushien, transferring to another school is an option.
Don't you feel that it's shameful to do that at this stage ?
A little.
Do you dislike this school ?
No.
Then let's do the right thing.
It must be fate that both of us came to a school without a baseball club.
It'll be interesting to start from scratch.
Yeah.
We're going to start the history of this school's baseball club.
All right.
The Koushien doesn't matter.
We get to play baseball again.
With our golden battery.
I have no complaints.
Let's surprise those
powerhouse baseball schools !
All right. Let's do it !
What ? Why ?
Are you all right, Manager ?
Yes, I'm fine.
I have band-aids.
Manager, I'm sorry to say,
but I have to decline being the coach.
What ?
I'll be a player.
Player ?
How about that ?
It sounds great.
But what about Kunimi's elbow ?
Noda, don't jam your fingers.
Okay.
Nice sound ! It's amazing !
This is what it is.
That's right. This is what it is.
So this is what it is ?
Okay, I'll throw a forkball now.
No ! Don't do that !
Strike !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Hiro's Dad:
Hiro's Mom:
Coach:
Asako:
Maruyama(pitcher):
Baseball Player:
Girl:
Mitsuya Yuji
Takizawa Kumiko
Naka Hiroshi
Neya Michiko
Yamazaki Takumi
Yanagisawa Eiji
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Hiro Studying: This is probably from Japanese History book.
As you may know, Sui is a Chinese dynasty circa 581-619,
and "Onono Imoko" is a famous emissary that Japan sent to Sui.
Rain Superstition: It's a common superstition that there will be a rainfall after something weird happens.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
It's great that you can
play baseball again.
Yeah. I have to catch up again.
Catch up ?
Hideo is now a hero of the high school baseball world, right ?
You'll catch up to him soon.
Of course. I can't wait till
I face him in a game.
How confident.
That's all I have, after all.
Next episode of H2 is,
"God Must Have Wanted to See It."
Next episode of H2 is
God Must Have Wanted to See It
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?