Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 09
God Must Have Wanted To See It
Got him !
What ?
Now, Senkawa High School
has a big scoring opportunity.
The ace striker, Kine,
does his super drive shot !
"Not a Baseball Club..."
What ?
"...Fan Club," fight !
Oh !
Fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh...
That messes up my rhythm.
Baseball Fan Club, fight !
Fight ! Fight !
She's so cute.
Koga...
Fight, fight.
One, two, one, two.
We have to put up this many again ?
That's right. With one more member, we get upgraded from "fan club" to an official club.
I'm actually more interested in soccer, to tell the truth.
No, if you're Japanese, it should be "chazuke" and baseball.
But no one will probably
see this poster here.
Principal's Office
It's really coming down now.
Rain...
Yeah. It's supposed to
be sunny tomorrow.
Oh.
Finally, on the powerhouse Meiwa
Daiichi High School Baseball Club...
...an emerging first year star who hits cleanup...
...and is the second son of the
Tachibana Liquor and Food Store...
...Tachibana Hideo, age 16, will make his debut in high school baseball.
Your narration is long enough.
Well, let's have him flourish for now.
You're the
hero !
The hot
springtime
of youth
Now
play ball !
Back up the spirit
Baseball Fan Club is Looking For New Members !
I hate high school baseball.
What ? It's not going to
become an official club ?
By the Principal's decision ?
What's going on ?
Well, I mean...
To explain...
It's the Principal's decision.
The Principal's decision ?
Is that even valid ?
It can't be. No way.
Um, where are you going ?
I'm going to ask the Principal why he isn't making the Baseball Fan Club an official club.
But the Principal is on a field trip and won't return till next week.
The Principal is on a field trip ?
And won't return till next week ?
What's going on ?
Um, well...
The Principal is on a field trip.
Safe !
Meiwa Ichi
Eikou
Mikami
Nakajima
Furukawa
Tachibana
Tamura
Murabe
This is what he does
in his first at-bat...
He sure isn't cute.
He should get more nervous in his first at-bat of his first game.
How is your effort to turn a fan club into an official club going for you ?
We haven't been able to contact the principal, so I can't say anything.
Either way, it's too late for
this year, so I'm not flustered.
With Hideo in it, this lineup is the
best in the region, without a doubt.
If you were pitching, how many runs could you keep them to ?
How many runs ?
I wouldn't give up any runs.
Well, assuming that I will
give up two hits to Hideo...
...the rest would be kept to just one blooper, and it would be a three-hit shutout.
You're so confident.
Sure.
That's all I have, after all.
I'm happy about your elbow.
Yeah.
If you had only had it examined at a proper hospital first...
God must have wanted to see it.
The match between
Hideo and me, I mean.
Kunimi !
Coming !
Tell Hideo.
If he wants to go to the
Koushien, now is his chance.
Meiwa Ichi
Eikou
Even without their ace pitcher...
...the reserve pitcher throws a shutout and they win in a called game.
Meiwa surely is impressive. They have a deep lineup.
We don't have time to be envious.
We will be short of members once the third years leave after the summer.
We can't expect much from people...
...who haven't already joined a
club and are just fooling around.
Should we recruit promising ones from other clubs ?
What's wrong ?
Nothing.
Shoot !
He got it ! Genius Kine's ultra hyper turbo shot !
I've been in contact with a few people since, but I haven't received a favorable response.
The major issue is that
we're not an official club.
Goal !
Shut up.
How about it ? If you bow and beg, I might be willing to lend a hand.
It's a piece of cake for me to play for two clubs at the same time.
Playing on two clubs at the same time will be difficult.
We have to go to the Koushien in the spring and summer.
In the fall, we have the Nationals, too.
If you're going to play soccer just in
the winter, then you might be able to.
Stop joking.
He hasn't sharpened his punning skills, it seems.
What are you talking about ?
Just think hard about what I offered.
Let's ignore him -
bases loaded with no outs.
Fine Arts Room
I guess the rumor that the Fine Arts Club uses a nude model is just a rumor.
Huh ?
Yanagi from Kita Junior High ?
That second baseman ?
Yeah.
In junior high, I saw lots of second basemen from different teams...
...but his defense was
the most memorable.
He sure was a
great second baseman.
He ran fast, and he was a tough out at the plate, too.
You must have mistaken him with someone else.
There's no mistaking him.
Yanagi.
See ?
Yeah, it's him.
He's Yanagi from Kita Junior High.
Kunimi and Noda ?
Why are you in this school ?
What do you mean why ?
You didn't know that this school doesn't have a baseball club ?
Oh, I quit baseball after junior high.
You quit ?
Did you get injured ?
Was it your elbow ?
Was it your back ?
Did you have it checked
at a proper hospital ?
It wasn't Uetake Clinic, was it ?
That's not it.
I'm not injured anywhere.
Then why did you quit ?
It's such a waste !
I made a promise with my father.
Your father ?
Yeah. I promised him that I'd play baseball through junior high and quit after that.
Why did you make such a promise ?
Didn't you play baseball
because you loved it ?
I love baseball.
Then play with us.
Right now, we're just a fan club, but
we'll definitely make it an official club.
My father won't let me.
Your father shouldn't matter !
You should do what you want to do !
You can say that because you don't know my father.
But...
Yanagi.
Kunimi, Noda, it's a waste for you to be in a school like this, too.
You should aim for the Koushien at a
school that has an official baseball club.
Bye.
Wait, Yanagi.
His father ?
Do you believe that ?
He's as much of
a baseball idiot as us.
Hideo
( Note - Can be read as "Hero" )
Hero of Meiwa Ichi
Tachibana
Homeruns in back-to-back games.
Third Homer.
First Year Cleanup Batter,
Tachibana Hideo
Wow. I heard he was good...
...but when it's in such big print, it feels as though he's someone I don't actually know.
He's definitely the
Hide-chan that you know.
Hideo equals Hero.
His parents must be happy that he
turned out to be the same as his name.
You must be happy, too.
Your daughter is shining,
just like her name.
I was chosen as "Miss Meiwa"
of the incoming students this year.
That's not because of your name. You just inherited my beauty.
Oh.
What's happened
with the other hero ?
What ?
Hero equals Hiro.
What happened since ?
Huh ? About what ?
What do you mean, "about what" ?
It goes without saying !
The principal returned from his trip, right ?
Um...he did return.
So ?
Well, we talked to him through a teacher, but he won't meet with us.
What's going on ?
Um, well...
I mean...
He wouldn't meet with us.
Then we should approach him directly.
Principal's Office
So ?
What brings you here ?
Is it true that the fan club cannot become
an official club because of your directive ?
It's true.
Why ?
I hate high school baseball.
It makes me sick just
looking at the uniform.
You can prohibit a club activity just
because of your personal preferences ?
The school brochure states that
this school has no baseball club.
If you want to play baseball,
you can just go to another school.
That's not the issue.
Anyway, as long as I'm the principal here, there will be no baseball club at this school.
You should give it up.
Are you transferring to some
other school in the near future ?
Not likely.
Has there been any voice
of concern from the PTA ?
Everyone is happy with my educational philosophy.
Okay then.
Let's go.
You...
I'm not giving up. We'll return after we explore our options.
That's not it.
Aren't you going to ask why
I hate high school baseball ?
No. It's probably a
silly reason, anyway.
70 Years Since Establishment
The History of Sousei Prefectural High School
- The Overview of the School -
Sousei High School ?
Our generation might not know...
...but all high school baseball fans over
the age of 20 probably heard the name.
Oh, that school that lost a no-hitter with the score of 0-30 in the summer Koushien tournament.
Yeah. That was my
father's high school.
It seems that the school was
academically well-regarded...
...so Sousei High School graduates could feel proud of their hometown.
But ten years ago...
Sousei High School
It appeared in the Koushien by pure luck.
Since then, they talk about that game whenever the topic of Sousei comes up...
...no matter where you are in this country.
People might not know that the school was well-regarded academically...
...but they know about that 30-0 game.
The school tradition that my father
and other graduates built over time...
...went down the drain
with that one game.
I see.
The Koushien has become a taboo subject at my home.
I can understand the feeling.
But it's wrong not to
let you play baseball.
No matter who says what,
your father should feel proud.
You can't go to the Koushien on just
pure luck, without making any effort.
That's true.
While studying hard, the players maximized their practice time...
...and somehow managed to reach the Koushien.
Your father, of all people, needs to understand how hard that is.
He understands,
but he still can't accept it.
It may be the same
high school baseball...
...but opponents are often
professional baseball prep schools...
...that gather baseball recruits from all over the country.
Playing against an opponent like that all of a sudden...
Moron ! It's just a matter-of-course
that the playing field is not level !
Climate, environment, facilities, the way
the players are recruited, the coaches.
They all differ.
But if you keep using that as an excuse, you can't have a national tournament.
Everyone should feel proud.
There's no shame in
going to the Koushien.
What did he say ?
What ?
You met my father, right ?
Your father...?
Aren't you going to ask why
I hate high school baseball ?
You swing as though you're going to hit the ball with your hips.
Swing from your hips.
And swing all the way through.
Moriya, don't twist your wrist.
Principal Yanagi...
That was really surprising.
So now we know that there is only one obstacle left.
It's less troublesome that way.
The opponent seems pretty tough.
Yeah.
Now, how are we going to go after him ?
Everyone seems to be working hard.
Hi. Are you going to
put up more posters ?
Yes.
If they're going
to tear them down...
...I'm going to put up more.
Act before thinking, huh ?
We're not good at thinking things through, after all.
Clang !
Um, I just imagined myself
on a big field hitting a big one.
A big field...
Clang !
All right, me, too !
It went over the center fielder !
Clang !
A hit to left field !
A homerun hitting the center field display !
A homerun to clean up all the runners !
This is still usable.
Sorry. I'll do it.
That ball...
Since we don't receive club funding, these
are all precious, but this is a bit too worn out.
Shall I ask my father ?
Huh ?
My father and the chairman of the PTA of this school are longtime friends.
If we approach from there...
Moron ! I don't want to
get help from adults !
I'm sorry.
Is what I would say...
Our opponent is an adult, too. It might be a good idea.
Ask him. I'll count on you.
Hey, hey ! Lower your waist.
You almost got it !
This one is for the left fielder !
Fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh...
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
If you have a hand...
Principal:
Hikari's Mom:
Yanagi:
Asako:
Kids' Baseball Coach:
Yamaguchi:
Nemoto:
Fanclub Member:
Komura Tetsuo
Ikemoto Sayuri
Izaki Hisayoshi
Neya Michiko
Sugawara Junichi
Yamazaki Takumi
Yanagisawa Eiji
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Kine Joke: The joke here again is a homophone kind, so it's not really translatable.  What he says is "It's a piece of cake for me to play concurrently on two clubs, and my child is a four year-old." The "my child..." part is the homophone joke.
Another phonic joke that is totally banal. To "stop" is "yosu / yose / yoshite," and there's a common Japanese female name, "yoshiko," so Kine combines the two sounds.
And another phonic joke. "Think about it" is "kangaete oke" and Kine turns the "oke / oki" part into "Okinawa."
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
"Hideo" also can be read as "Hero" or "Eiyuu."
"Hikari" means "light."
Kunimi's first name, as you recall, is "Hiro." Hiro and Hero
sound similar, of course.
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
How's it going ? You're trying to turn the
fan club into an official club going, right ?
What do you mean "how" ? That stubborn principal !
You asked the chairman of the PTA, right ?
I didn't want to get help from adults, but our opponent is an adult, too.
I can't be choosy with my methods.
Oh, well.
But...
What happened ?
That principal set an outrageous condition.
Next episode of H2 is,
"Things Are Not Turning Out Well..."
Next episode of H2 is
Things Are Not Turning Out Well...
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?