Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
The practice game between us Senkawa and Meiwa Daiichi...
...where if we win, we become an official club, and if we lose, we'll be disbanded...
...began with a promise we made with our principal.
We fought hard to the end of the
game in the bottom of the ninth inning.
And we lost.
We lost the game...
...but the Senkawa Baseball Club was born.
That's right, the story of love between me and baseball begins now.
Episode 20
Pursuit ! Hiro vs. Haruka
Koushien
Senkawa
Takamori
The game is set.
In their first appearance at the Koushien, Senkawa High School wins its first game.
Kunimi did it !
The score is 7 - 6. It's their
first victory at the Koushien !
7 - 6...
Since it's a dream, it should let me win more decisively.
Ouch...
You should have a
doctor take a look at it.
Some place that isn't a
quack clinic like Uetake's was.
You finally have a baseball club, and your elbow is fine.
I guess I really do need to
have a doctor take a look at it.
Hmm...
Nice shot !
Wow, amazing !
You're single, right ?
Well, yes.
Kunimi, it's my turn.
Oh, I'm sorry, President.
Huh...?
Oh, the daughter of President Koga...
Um, is Kunimi home ?
I'm here.
Oh, you mean my stupid son.
He's out right now.
I see.
Did he do anything rude ? Like touching your chest or being a peeping tom ?
No, I'm worried about his leg injury.
My father knows the doctors at the university hospital...
...so I wanted him to have a thorough examination there.
Injury ?
Is he injured ?
Do you know where he went ?
I have no idea.
But rest assured. He definitely
comes home when it's mealtime.
To make sure that happens...
...I don't give him any extra
allowance so he can't eat out.
Hey, Hikari ! Let me
borrow your bicycle for...
I'm sorry. Hikari is at
archery club practice.
Oh, this ?
I borrowed it to keep
the dust out of my hair.
Does it look good on me ?
Oh, wait.
Can you deliver this to her ?
She made her lunch box,
but forgot to take it with her.
This is hers,
and this is Hide-chan's.
Please.
I'd really appreciate it.
Senkawa Private High School
Well, first years, Kunimi and Noda. That should be everyone.
Hm ?
Umm, who are you ?
I'm Yanagi, a first year.
Yanagi Morimichi.
Yanagi.
Well, that should be everyone.
Nice to meet you all.
We welcome you.
Oh, we're still missing one more person. That guy who caught a cold isn't here.
Yanagi here is the son
of our school's principal.
In junior high, he was the well-regarded second baseman at Kita Junior High.
Since the principal hates baseball, he
was told to quit baseball after junior high.
So he played the game against
Meiwa without telling the principal.
He was the "guy who caught a cold,"
wearing a mask and hiding his face.
Oh !
Hey, Baseball Clubi !
What's this "clubi" thing ?
You're not a baseball
club yet, so it's "clubi."
How about it ? My jokes are
funnier than ever today, aren't they ?
Right ? Right ? Right ?
Where's Kunimi ?
He's off today.
He's off ? What ?
I went out of my way to
participate in your practice...
...as I go between the soccer club and the baseball club.
He must be at the hospital.
What ? He injured himself ?
Then I'm the only one who can be the ace pitcher.
All right.
Now, let's start pitching practice.
Next one, please.
Sure.
Even when the pitcher moves that much
closer to the plate, he hits them easily.
That practice game wasn't a waste. Rather, it yielded a huge harvest.
Kunimi Hiro...
Yes. Hikari is at
the top of her game.
Sir, that's the dressing room.
I saw you.
I didn't do anything
to feel guilty about.
Oh, you brought them ?
I forgot to bring them.
Oh, geez.
I worry about your future.
What kind of future
are you talking about ?
After you get married, I mean.
I'll be fine.
...even if I forget my lunch box...
...I'll get a husband who will always deliver it to me with a smile.
There is no such husband.
See ya later.
I'm done with the delivery.
Thanks.
Oh, Hiro, you went to the hospital
and had your leg looked at, right ?
I'm going there now.
You've hated going to the hospital ever since you were little. You need to go.
That's why you were
deceived by that quack.
An elbow made of glass that will break down in three months.
But thanks to that phony diagnosis...
...people can watch the match of the century between me and Hideo for the next two years.
All baseball fans
across the nation, I mean.
So look forward to it !
By Kunimi Hiro.
Was that Hiro ?
Yeah. He brought
us our lunch boxes.
I included your favorite,
kinpira-style sautéed burdock.
I put in a lot of
time preparing it.
Let's eat.
Come to think of it, Hiro likes
kinpira-style sautéed burdock, too.
Thanks for the meal.
Eh ?
I'm really aiming
for the Koushien !
eyecatch
Well, what can I say ?
Even if he's stupid, he has the baseball
talent that he inherited from his father.
From his father, meaning me, Kunimi Tarou, of the third section of the Sales Department.
It's fine.
He'll be home by lunchtime.
He's not home yet.
This is strange.
Um, I'll go look for him.
...
Take care ! Please give
my regards to the President.
I'm Kunimi Tarou of the third
section of the Sales Department.
Let's see.
That hospital is far away.
Katou Clinic
Well...I should pass on this one.
Yamazaki Clinic
Internal
Medicine
Gastroenterology
Surgical
Department
Orthopedic
Weekdays
Saturday
I prefer someone slimmer.
Koide...
Oh ?
I want someone bustier.
Mr. Kunimi.
Oh, Hikari.
It's hot again today, isn't it ?
Did Hiro actually go to the doctor ?
Well, that cursed boy
is currently missing...
...even though the President's
daughter came by car to pick him up.
The President's daughter ?
Yeah, she's the manager, and her hair is shorter than yours.
You mean Koga ?
Yeah, that's right.
That moronic son doesn't understand the position his parent is in...
...so it really makes me worry.
I see. She's daughter of the president of the Koga Trading Company.
If he does something rude to her and the President hears about it, I'll be fired in a jiffy.
You'll be fine.
It's more likely you'll get
promoted because of Hiro.
I don't think you need to
worry about getting fired.
Seriously ?
Oh, I found him.
Stop here.
Kunimi !
Hi.
Did you go to the doctor ?
Um, no, I'm going there now.
Then let's go.
I know a reliable doctor.
Hey, wait. The bicycle...
I'll drop you off here on the way home.
Don't worry about it.
I'll find a hospital myself.
That's not good.
You need to have it properly
looked at by a reliable doctor.
The baseball club was finally created.
If anything happens to our
ace pitcher now, it'll be a problem.
Then if you tell me the name and location of that hospital, I'll go there myself.
I'm not a child.
No.
Why ?
I'm the "manager" of the baseball club.
The manager needs to be able to
manage their player's health conditions.
But you're not my personal manager.
...!
This time, it's not a miss.
Sweets Café,
Kuromitsuya
Hey !
I remember eating shaved ice here when I was little.
Huh ?
Well, it feels so nostalgic !
No. I know that this café has a door on the other street.
Oh, U...
There's a UFO flying out there, right ?
The sky is blue !
Oh ?
What ?
Hey, wait up !
Hm ?
No matter how I look at it,
this is my bicycle.
That means...
Kunimi, you must listen to what your manager says !
What an incorrigible guy.
Ouch...
Thanks. I'm not injured.
I have a band-aid.
Nice job !
Now, Kunimi, your
futile resistance is over.
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm telling you,
I can go there by myself.
No.
...!
Freeze, Hiro !
If you move, I'll shoot you.
There's an arrow that's aimed at you.
You should listen to your manager, and go to the hospital with her.
Got it ?
Father, Mother, I surrender.
Well, if he can run like that,
there's probably no need to worry.
My leg is fine, I think.
No, it's not about that.
Did you actually think
Hikari would shoot you ?
If she actually had an arrow, yeah, she might just do it.
She's always been like
that since she was little.
What are you angry about ?
It's nothing.
Aim ! Right ?
I'm sorry to say...
...but it's just a bruise.
Keinan University Hospital
Ambulance
Entrance
There's no bone or ligament damage.
It should heal in a few days, but just in case, follow up with me again.
Do you want to come in ?
Oh ?
Aim for the Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
It's been my dream,
to post this up here.
I wanted to show you this.
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Hiro's Dad:
Hikari's Mom:
Meiwa's Coach:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Yamaguchi:
Announcer:
Mitsuya Yuji
Ikemoto Sayuri
Naka Hiroshi
Izaki Hisayoshi
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Clubi Joke: In the Japanese alphabet, the sound "bu" that ends the word "club" comes after "bi,"
as in "ba bi bu be bo." So before the club becomes a club [or "kurabu"], it is "clubi" [or "kurabi"].  To make the joke work in English you can see what we had to do.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Kunimi, do you regret
introducing Hikari to Tachibana ?
What ? Don't ask me
such a startling question.
I just wanted to ask.
Ocean. Sky.
Sudden evening rain shower !
Ah, it's summer !
You like summer ?
Yeah, my mind is occupied by thoughts of going to the Koushien next summer !
We're going to the Koushien, right ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"Haruka, Hikari, Hiro and the Ocean."
Next episode of H2 is
Haruka, Hikari, Hiro and the Ocean
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?