Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
I'm Kunimi Hiro, a first year pitcher with Senkawa High School's baseball club.
Our dream came true, and our fan club was upgraded to an official club.
Aim for the Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
I have rediscovered my dream.
Aim for the Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
At the Koushien, I'll have a
date with my beloved baseball.
To make that happen, our manager,
Koga Haruka, takes care of my leg injury.
Koga, let's fall in love...
...with baseball.
Episode 21
Haruka, Hikari, Hiro and the Ocean
Reception / Cashier
I've already told you.
A follow-up just means that they'll take a quick look just to be safe.
It's better than some fake doctor, isn't it ?
Hey...
No Entry
The driver has a bad attitude.
True.
We're ready to go.
Oh, sure.
Seriously, you're making it a
big deal, taking me by car.
But you wouldn't have gone
there otherwise, would you ?
Of course not.
Why would anyone want to go to
the hospital on a nice day like this ?
It has air conditioning
and it's cool inside.
Don't treat me like an elderly person.
Do you want to go somewhere ?
Moron ! That's wrong !
Oh, the squeeze bunt failed !
The third base runner is in a rundown.
What are they doing ?
He's tagged out !
Geez, they should read the flow of the game better.
He's talking about baseball.
So, do you want to go somewhere ?
Hmm...
Hi, Mr. Kunimi.
Oh, Hikari.
Are you looking for Hiro ?
No, I'm just passing by.
Oh, that's good.
He's out ?
Yeah. He's out again today, riding in a car with the president's daughter.
The hospital ?
She might be the manager, but she doesn't have to do so much for him.
Isn't that a good thing ?
Really ?
It is.
Oh ?
Hm ?
Don't you have to go to work today ?
Oh. You know, it's
hot every day these days.
I don't feel like going to work.
What ? Then you're skipping ?
Not.
Even for us adults,
there's summer vacation.
I see.
See you.
Bye.
But I'm really glad.
Well, as far as I'm concerned,
I was hoping more had worn bikinis.
If they're going to wear a one-pieces,
I wish they'd wear white see-through ones.
I wish I had brought binoculars.
I'm talking about your leg injury.
Oh.
Check it out.
That's the opposite leg.
There.
Anyway, there's no need to be impatient.
Everything starts after summer break.
That's right.
The club room, the field, the coach.
Getting new club members after the third years leave.
We have so many things to do. These preparations will take up the entire fall.
Right.
After the new first
year students come in...
...we'll make a splash into the
preliminary for the Koushien next year.
Ice
Cream
Hey, Kunimi, should we have some ?
Hmm...
I prefer that.
flag, "Ice" [shaved ice]}
Iso Chidori
Swim Ring
for Rent
Shaved Ice
Gather up !
We'll wrap up practice for today.
Instead, we'll have a week
long camp, starting tomorrow.
What's wrong, Tachibana ?
Um, nothing.
You have something
else on your schedule ?
N...no.
And of course,
there shouldn't be.
By all rights, we should be at the Koushien right now.
Well, we'll let you rest up for today.
That's all for now.
Thank you.
I wonder if Hikari
will be angry with me.
Iso Chidori
Swim Ring
for Rent
Shaved Ice
Oh, it's cold.
Are you okay ?
I'm fine.
You're gulping it down too fast.
It's fine.
I like this ringing pain.
Right, Ma'am ?
That's right.
You're right on, young man.
See ?
Honestly, the shaved ice that you
eat under the summer sun is the best.
Exactly !
The summer sun...
The summer sunlight...
I'm Haruka.
Did you say something ?
Um, nothing.
Kunimi, which do you like better, spring or summer ?
Summer of course.
I knew it.
Why ?
No reason.
Just a hunch.
I mean, the spring one is nice, too...
...but if you're going to go to the
Koushien, the summer one is the best.
The Koushien ?
Besides, we're not going to make it in time for the spring one next year.
After summer break, the fall
tournament starts right away.
I see. You're right.
Our primary goal should be
summer's instead of spring's.
Yes, the summer !
So cold.
You're weird.
Oh ? What happened to practice ?
We finished at noon.
Oh, that's rare.
That practice-loving coach ?
It might rain.
But I wouldn't want it to rain.
We're going to an
outdoor concert tomorrow.
Sorry.
Huh ?
I can't go.
Why ?
We're doing a training camp, starting tomorrow.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Defeat Meiwa Ichi !
It can't be helped.
Yeah, it can't be helped.
But it's a waste not to use the tickets.
Why don't you go ?
With whom ?
Well...maybe Hiro ?
I guess.
EYECATCH
Did you know, Kunimi ?
There are crabs that can walk forward.
You're pulling my leg.
It's true. I read it in some illustrated encyclopedia.
Oh, really ?
Geez.
Hey, watch out.
Why ?
You're a klutz.
I'm not that much of a klutz.
Dummy !
Are you okay ?
It's salty.
Man, that was embarrassing.
You don't need to care
about what others think.
If I were on the mound, yeah.
But they probably think
that we're on a date.
Huh ?
Even though it's
not at all the case.
Let's see who can
reach the car first !
Okay.
Oh, it's raining.
Hikari, are you there ?
I am.
It's raining.
Get the laundry inside.
Okay.
No postponement for rain.
Okay, there ! Hit-and-run !
Ugh !
Um...
Come to think of it...
Come to think of it,
I think it was around here.
What ?
Well, when I was in elementary school, I slipped and injured my leg badly.
It must have been hard...
...to carry me on their back and walk back to that beach house where my parents were...
...while I was bleeding from my head.
Who did that ?
Well, my height and weight
were below average back then...
...so it may not have been that bad.
Wow ! It's cleared up !
Do you regret it ?
What ?
Introducing Hikari to Tachibana.
Hmm...
You don't have to think that hard.
If I had introduced her to someone other than Hideo, I'd clearly have some regret.
Really ?
It feels like the opposite.
Hmm...
Well, let's go.
Too bad. I was hoping that
you'd carry me on your back.
Moron. To be honest,
my leg still hurts a little.
Even if that's true, I still think you'd carry me on your back.
Hey, hurry it up !
Where were you ?
I was watching high school
baseball on the TV at the café.
He gets another hit ! With this, he's 4-4 with a homerun today.
This is why I said
they should walk him !
They know he's on a roll, right ?
Why don't you fire this driver ?
Right.
How can a coach like that take a team to the quarterfinals ?
I don't know.
More importantly, you should be watching the road while you drive, Brother.
Okay.
But honestly, high school baseball is really interesting. Don't you think ?
You're right, Mr. Brother.
The sacrifice attempt...is a foul.
What are they doing ?
That's not the right move !
They should let me coach the team.
Hello.
Oh, Hide-chan. Welcome.
Hey, you look like you have a lot of free time on your hands.
What kind of a greeting is this ?
What kind of greeting is that right after you barge into my room ?
From the looks of it, you'll probably have lots of free time on your hands tomorrow, too.
Are you trying to pick a fight ?
Your leg seems to be fine, too.
Hey...
What's this ?
I want you to pinch-hit for me.
Pinch-hit ?
Yeah. Our baseball club is having a week long camp starting tomorrow, all of a sudden.
Good for you.
Hikari asked me to get these tickets, and it was hard work.
So I'm the pinch-hitter ?
Why don't you have her go
with one of her female friends ?
Moron !
It's well-known that the audiences
at these concerts are rude and rough !
You have to go with her and make absolutely sure she stays safe !
What a hassle.
Seriously, this unexpected
camp came about...
...all because of that practice game with you guys !
I was looking forward to going to that concert, dammit !
Then you should have
gone to the Koushien.
Anyway, I've already told Hikari.
I'm counting on you !
Is this your way of
counting on someone ?
Well, I have to prepare for
tomorrow, so I'm going home.
Aim for the Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
Your handwriting is awful.
Scumbag.
I'm counting on you !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Hiro's Dad:
Chauffeur:
Hikari's Mom:
Meiwa's Coach:
Announcer:
Mitsuya Yuji
Matsumoto Yasunori
Ikemoto Sayuri
Naka Hiroshi
Chiba Isshin
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Signs/Writing in Hospital: In case you were wondering about all that here it is. We weren't going to clutter the screen.
Signs above nurse: "For first-time patients" "Hospital Hours."
Card in change tray:  "Hospital Card" "Kunimi Hiro"
"Keinan University Hospital."
Sign on counter: "Once you leave your hospital card here, please take a seat and wait until your name is called."
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
Haruka thinking about summer sunlight: "Hikari" means light, and here, Haruka uses the word "hikari" for sunlight.
Koushien stuff: The result of the fall tournament is part of whether or not a team will be selected to play in Spring Koushien Tournament.
Kunimi's crab joke: It's another homophone pun. "Really ?" is "hontokana ?" But Kunimi changes it to "honto-kani ?" because "kani" means "crab."
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hiro, do you feel nervous
about going out with me ?
That's silly.
Who would get nervous ?
But just the two of us going out
brings back a lot of memories.
I don't want to hear
about old times.
Then shall we talk about
our dreams for the future ?
Dreams ?
What is your dream ?
Well, what do you think ?
Next episode of H2 is , "Pinch-Hitting for a Date:  The Two Unable to Return Home."
Next episode of H2 is
Pinch-Hitting for a Date:
The Couple is Unable to Return  Home
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?