Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Hideo and I frantically looked for Hikari.
We were seriously worried about the possibility of her being assaulted.
But all that came out of it was an uneasy feeling.
Episode 31
A New Rival ! Eikyou's Hirota
Municipal Ballpark
High School Baseball Fall Tournament
Finals - Meiwa vs. Eikyou
Certain
Victory
Win! Meiwa Nine
Victory for Meiwa!
Meiwa
Good Luck!
Meiwa Ichi
Iwakiri
Shimoike
Murabe
Tachibana
Nakai
This is really great.
Yeah. It's heating up.
Certain Victory! Eikyou High School
Good Luck
Give It Your Best, Eikyou Nine
Fight ! Fight !
Tachibana, this is an easy win !
Who do you think is going to win ?
Hmm...
Wow...
Boom, boom, boom.
Pop, pop.
Wow...
What are you doing over there ?
The final game has started !
The ballpark is just next door.
Get a move on ! Run ! Run !
That's right. I guess we
came here to watch baseball.
Of course.
I'll go on ahead.
She could have given us a ride.
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
After the top of the 2nd, the score is 0-0.
But once you've come this far, you'd
probably be able to go to the Invitational.
Yeah. Two schools are
selected from Tokyo every year.
But I'm happy for you.
About what ?
That you two don't have to play
against each other in the preliminary.
The what ?
That's right ! Perhaps we'll face off against Meiwa in the Koushien next summer !
What ?
Huh ?
I mean, we're located right on the boundary between the north and south parts of Tokyo.
Meiwa would be from southern Tokyo.
And Senkawa would be from northern Tokyo.
Oh, you didn't know ?
It's a double.
Sorry about that.
Oh, I'm fine.
That's such a nice spectacle, just as it should be in high school baseball.
Hmm...
He's Hirota Katsutoshi
of Eikyou High School.
He's a first year who got tapped as the ace pitcher, hitting cleanup, out of nowhere.
A first year who's in the starting lineup. He's just like Tachibana.
Yeah.
North Tokyo.
Yes, Eikyou High School is.
Meiwa is from the south,
and Senkawa is from the north.
We won't face Meiwa.
I wonder if we should be happy...
Or disappointed.
It's kind of a let down.
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
Out.
He paints the corners.
Yes, he does.
I got it. I got it.
A pitch-to-contact guy ?
If you can pitch-to-contact and hold down the Meiwa lineup, that's impressive.
Murabe
Tachibana
Nakai
What happened in
Hideo's first at-bat ?
No idea.
He struck out swinging.
Well, that happens sometimes.
Moreover...
...it wasn't just a strikeout.
Strike !
I guess it wasn't just a rumor.
Huh ?
He touches the cap once and
then raises his arm. That's his sign.
He's predicting a strikeout.
A predicted strikeout ?
Yeah.
He can pull a stunt like that ?
Of course he denies it.
He says it's just coincidental.
Senior.
Huh ?
That's my spot.
Oh, sorry about that.
You should be more attentive.
But...
If this "coincidence" occurs in every game, the cheer squad will expect it regardless.
Hold it !
So you're saying that Hideo struck
out when it was predicted like that ?
Well, who knows ?
Okay, let's play-to-contact !
EYECATCH
Meiwa Ichi
Eikyou
Hikari, I'm going to get some juice.
You want some ?
If you're buying me one, yes.
Your lack of reservation is so refreshing.
I'll get going.
Hey.
Hey, exam student. What are
you doing in a place like this ?
I'm taking a study break.
Out.
The Invitational appearance is all but decided. He's finally going to be a national star.
And eventually, he's going to be a professional baseball player who earns a huge salary.
I'm counting on you, Hide-chan.
Take care of me,
in place of my dead brother.
You don't have to bring up
your dead brother all the time.
Hide-chan isn't going to
abandon you regardless.
I suppose.
But the truth may be that he thinks of me as an unwelcome reminder.
He had almost forgotten
about it all by now, after all.
It's your brother who taught Hide-chan baseball, right ?
Then the fact that he hasn't given up baseball is evidence that he hasn't forgotten.
...is evidence that he hasn't forgotten
You should rest assured.
No matter how famous he becomes, Hide-chan will always be what he is.
Your childhood friend.
You're really preachy today.
Once I learned that you were younger than us...
...your way of acting bad started to seem kind of adorable.
Um, Hikari...
Thanks.
Now, go.
This is my friend's seat.
Oh, Shuu.
Did you give it up ?
Give up what ?
Hide-chan wasn't the only one your
brother taught baseball to, was he ?
Out !
Hirota.
We don't need a perfect
game or a no-hitter.
I know, Coach.
We first need to win.
Senior, you're going at it halfheartedly.
If you're going to do it,
you have to go all the way.
If it's an accident, you won't be
blamed for it, no matter what it is.
Fight ! Fight ! Meiwa !
I guess it's his turn.
This is the second at-bat for the liquor store's son.
Strike !
That punk...
Strike ! Batter out !
It was close.
That was the fifth
predicted strikeout.
Tokyo really is a big world.
What a phenomenal pitcher.
Eikyou High School, Hirota Katsutoshi.
Starting next year, they'll be one
of the perennials at the Koushien.
In north Tokyo, there's Senkawa.
Kunimi Hiro.
Both are certainly phenomenal pitchers.
But in terms of their team as a whole, the difference is apparent.
The depth of the roster.
Excellent training facilities.
And above all, the total respect that the coach commands.
Coach Shiroyama.
He's a famous coach who's won one spring and two summer Koushien championships.
He's coached for a long
time, in many places.
Once you reach his age, you'll be called a famous coach, too.
Ball.
This is the first time that
there's been a full count.
Yeah. He's not wild.
Safe.
Senior, your start is slow.
You should value
your starting lineup spot.
There's a good first year reserve third baseman.
Murabe
Tachibana
Nakai
Batting fourth, third baseman, Tachibana.
Go get them, Tachibana !
Fight, Hide-chan !
He's amazingly popular.
Ball.
...?
His motion...
Can it be...?
Strike !
Strike two !
Was it such an unhittable pitch ?
No.
I think he's returning the favor.
If you can declare it, go right ahead.
Hey, you...
That was a little different.
Serves him right.
I guess he's not a
run-of-the-mill luck-pusher.
Hideo, crush his pride !
Hide-chan...
Hideo...
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Koyasu Takehito
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Meiwa Coach:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Tomoko:
Umpire:
Left:
Announcer:
Naka Hiroshi
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Neya Michiko
hiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hit by a pitch. Hide-chan is down.
He's fine. He'll get up
like nothing happened.
That's right.
Hide-chan is a talented hitter.
Yeah, he's a big guy.
He's going to show us how big he is.
But really, I can't like how Eikyou plays baseball.
Is it possible that
they hit him on purpose ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"Genius Tachibana, An At-Bat Full of Spirit."
Next episode of H2 is
Genius Tachibana
An At-Bat Full of Spirit
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?