Original file: DH2:H2Ep35.txt.js
H2, Episode #35, "You Want Me to Declare Strikeouts ?"
0:00:04.00 0:00:05.00
0:00:06.00 0:00:07.00
Senkawa Festival
0:00:18.00 0:00:19.00
0:00:42.00 0:00:43.00  {poster, "Next Year's Spring Invitational Candidate, Eikyou High School, Led by the Famous Manager Shiroyama, Is Coming ! !
0:00:44.00 0:00:45.00  Game Starts at 1: 00 PM, Senkawa Baseball Club"}
0:05:18.00 0:05:19.00
Note:  "ho-hokekyo" is the onomatopoeia for the crooning of a nightingale
0:07:04.00 0:07:05.00
0:07:48.00 0:07:49.00
0:07:56.00 0:07:57.00
Processed by Central Anime's NUMIT On 07/17/2013
0:00:26.00 0:00:27.00
0:00:32.00 0:00:33.00
Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
The practice game against Eikyou High School started out as part of the cultural festival.
The fun of baseball is, in part, the battle of wits between us and our opponent.
But there are also those who want to do away with tactics and just go with a head-on fight.
Senkawa Festival
Episode 35
You Want Me to Declare a Strikeout ?
Senkawa Festival
Welcome !
Yakisoba
Let's eat those.
Would you like some yakisoba ?
Sweet
Red-Bean
Soup
Takoyaki
It's reasonably priced !
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Second !
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Out !
Next Year's
Spring Invitational
Candidate,
Eikyou High School,
Led by the Famous
Coach Shiroyama,
Is Coming !!
Game Starts
at 1: 00 PM,
Senkawa
Baseball Club
Good job, Second !
One out ! One out !
Let's pitch-to-contact !
Yeah !
Let's bait him with a ball up and in.
Make him pull it
and pop it up to third.
Good. Third !
I got it. I got it.
Out !
Good job, Third.
When he's throwing at that velocity, he can pinpoint his pitches.
He won't miss his spot.
He dominated Meiwa's
second string with it, after all.
Pitch-to-contact and
make his fielders catch.
There are many who aren't
used to playing actual games.
Real game fielding is
good practice for them.
Smart.
That's how a practice
game should be used.
Make him chase it and get
him out on a grounder to first.
Foul !
What a shame. It went foul.
But has Hiro ever pitched a whole game like that ?
There's no way he could,
given his disposition.
I wonder if that's his
strength or weakness.
Either way, I like that about him.
Strike !
Our guys don't seem to get it.
Why don't you tell them, Hirota ?
About that pitch you struck out on.
I didn't time it right.
That's all it was.
Oh.
Because you praised him so much, I was expecting a faster pitch.
I see.
Sorry about that.
One more !
All right !
Out !
Three outs ! Change !
He's gotten senile.
That punk.
Don't compare me to
that good-for-nothing.
Play !
Strike !
Strike two !
Strike ! Batter out !
Change !
Wow, Hirota !
So cool !
Hirota !
Three strikeouts, all in three pitches. Nine pitches and done.
And he's only using
80% of his power.
All right, we can do it, too !
Don't fall behind a guy like that !
An eye for an eye
and a tooth for a tooth.
Let's go, Noda.
Okay.
Shall we go for three strikeouts ?
Then...
...this.
Ball.
The next one is a little more in.
All right ! A grounder to short !
Out !
Are we going to make the outfielders work now ?
This time, here.
Ball.
Next, here.
He's missing by one
ball's width, it seems.
No, he's intentionally throwing there.
Now, throw here, and
it'll be a fly ball to left.
Out !
Good job, Left !
What part of it is "good" ?
It looks so shaky !
If you're going to make him hit, make them hit it toward me !
Oh, sure.
Then let's do that.
Next, it'll be a weak pop-up to center.
Now, will Kine be able to catch it ?
... Ah !
Nice back up, Right !
Ouch...
Don't dawdle around !
You suck !
Hey, Kine !
What're you doing there ?
You're lousy !
Three more pitches left.
The seventh pitch will be here.
Ball.
The eighth pitch.
Now, let's finish it with this ninth pitch.
Okay.
Out !
Yeah !
I see.
Yeah, you saved me, Noda.
Of course.
So this is it.
What is ?
You weren't counting ?
Counting what ?
I returned the favor by retiring
the side in precisely nine pitches.
Huh ?
No doubt about it.
It really was nine pitches.
Wonderful !
So what ?
Nothing.
Oh, okay.
Aim for the Koushien
Good luck !
You're so handsome !
Give it your best, Hirota !
Hirota !
So cool !
Hirota...
Play !
Strike !
Hirota...!
Mifuji Junior High
Hey, Sagawa.
I guess we weren't
meant to be, Sagawa.
Strike two !
Our relationship doesn't
seem to be over yet, Hirota.
Strike ! Batter out !
With that swing, the ball won't move
forward even if he connects on a pitch.
You're right.
Add 100 more swings
to his training menu.
Sure.
Hm ?
The second time through the lineup, we have a chance.
Kine, shorten it up
and swing for contact !
There's no way I'm going to just swing for contact.
Strike !
Wonderful. If he connects, it'll have some distance.
He has it timed right.
He wasn't late on that fastball.
In terms of his athletic talent
and running speed, he's good.
If he weren't so hung up on looking good, he could be a great lead-off batter.
It's just a matter of time, then.
Before, he was sort
of popular with girls.
But these days, everyone
knows what he's really like.
Marvelous.
I'm declaring a ho...
...hokekyo.
Strike ! Batter out !
It will take time, I guess.
Strike !
Strike two !
Strike ! Batter out !
A "shoot," a curveball, and then...
The last one was a slider.
And it had such a sharp break that you couldn't get to it.
He's good. No wonder
he's going to the Koushien.
He's in the same block, and
he's a first-year, the same as us.
We can't just wait for
his graduation, I guess.
I guess.
After three innings, the score is 1-1.
What do you think of this
development, Analyst Tachibana ?
It will be a tight pitcher's duel
for the next few innings, I think.
Nice batting !
Go for it !
I mean, there's a large individual talent gap between their players and ours.
Oh ? Is it just the players ?
Huh ?
Don't you think the largest talent gap is the one that exists between their coach and ours ?
Ho...
...hokekyo.
After all, he is the
famous field manager...
...who has the experience of winning one spring and two summer Koushien championships.
Wonderful.
Hey, Hirota...
Just leave it to me.
Okay, then.
I'll show you just how small the fish that got away is.
Hirota ! Hit it !
This at-bat won't be an easy one.
I agree.
First, this.
Low and away.
Strike !
The same pitch in the same spot.
I don't get the feeling that he
doesn't like low balls, though.
Strike two !
What is he waiting for ?
...?
You want me to declare a strikeout ?
That's stupid. This is just a
practice game at a cultural festival.
But...
Hey now...!
Hiro is getting serious.
Let's do it, then.
Fastball...
...right down the middle !
Wow !
He did it !
He let him hit ?
No, he got beat.
That was his max effort ?
Yeah.
Home in.
A small fish is a small fish.
Hmm...
There's no need
to worry. He's fine.
Unlike Hirota, who is pretty much already perfected as a high school pitcher...
...Hiro is still in the
process of growing.
That's why his max
effort isn't always stable.
If he gets tense, like he gets mad or moody, his pitch quality fluctuates.
That's his weakness
at the current stage.
It's not a part
of his strength, is it ?
Regardless, I like that about him.
Hey, Hiro.
Ugh !
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Umpire:
Girl A:
Girl B:
Koyasu Takehito
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Konishi Hiroko
Shirakawa Mayu
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
"ho-hokekyo" is the onomatopoeia for the crooning of a nightingale.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
In the game against Eikyou, Hiro's
competitive spirit is starting to show.
Shut up, outsider.
You want them to underestimate you until summer, don't you ?
Coach Shiroyama and Hirota.
The baseball they play isn't the only kind of baseball.
Yeah. Let's feel good
about playing baseball.
Besides, it's too long
to wait till next summer !
Next episode of H2 is,
"In My Scorebook, It's 3-1."
Next episode of H2 is
In My Scorebook, It's 3-1
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?