Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Hirota shows off with flashy plays like
three consecutive three-pitch strikeouts.
In other words, he retired
the side in just nine pitches.
He's an enemy of my
pitch-to-contact style of pitching.
Episode 36
In My Scorebook, It's 3-1
Senkawa Festival
He let him hit ?
No, he got beat.
That was his max effort ?
Yeah.
There's no need to worry.
Hirota is pretty much already
perfected as a high school pitcher...
...but Hiro is still in
the process of growing.
He isn't consistent yet,
even if it's his max effort pitch.
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
It's so similar.
Huh ?
The face you made is just like the one
Hiro is making on the mound right now.
Yours, too.
What ?
Ugh ! Ugh ! Ugh ! Ugh !
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
I got it ! I got it ! I got it !
Huh ?
Ugh !
Strike ! Batter out ! Change !
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
Don't worry.
It's cultural festival day today.
That's right.
It's a part of the festivities.
It's just an invitational game.
Yes. Wonderful.
Strike !
He's amazing, too.
Yeah !
Dang !
It was close...
Nice catch, shortstop.
After six innings, the score is 7-1.
Getting to the Koushien
isn't so easy, I guess.
It's 3-1.
Eh ?
In my scorebook, that is.
Kunimi is giving up hits,
but he's painting corners.
On a team with ordinary fielding skills,
most of those would have been outs.
See ? All we need is an
ordinary fielding team.
We don't need any amazing plays.
We just need people who can catch things within their range without panicking.
If we had that, this one, this one, and this one would also be outs.
The homerun in the first inning would've
been a routine right field fly in a normal park.
It's 3-1.
Ordinary fielding ability...
This is enough, right, Coach ?
For a game like this, there's no point in making the ace pitcher throw a complete game.
Right.
There's no point,
if Kunimi stays like that.
Safe !
That one, too. If he were a
shortstop with a strong arm...
You just need ordinary defense, right ?
He did catch the ball.
That's right.
We shouldn't be too greedy.
Don't worry, Satou.
You did well on that one.
Okay ! I'll make them put the next one in play, too !
All right !
You have a good arm, Sagawa.
On our baseball club...
...there's never been anyone who's
become a regular shortstop as a first year.
I'm pulling for you.
Out !
Good ! Two outs ! Two outs !
Yeah !
In place of Hirota,
Mukai will pinch hit !
They're saying that it's a waste to have the ace pitcher throw anymore in this game.
As it is...
...that coach would probably thank you for turning down his invitation to come to Eikyou...
...I bet.
They got Hirota because of that, after all.
Yeah. He should be able to go home with no lingering attachment now.
We got them to underestimate us until a real game.
Yeah, until the preliminary next summer.
Until the preliminary next summer...
That's right.
It's going according to plan.
I think it's about time.
What ?
Until then, they'll continue to underestimate me.
I'm telling you, it's all
going according to plan.
Later.
Hmm...
Play !
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Next summer is a long ways away.
When you get this far...
...there's no need to
give them any real data.
There's no need, but...
Strike !
Oh no...
I guess this is what happens.
Today is a cultural festival day.
We've got to have some fun, right ?
Wow, amazing !
Strike ! Batter out !
It's so fast !
So he finally shows his real power.
But honestly, he throws hard.
Aim for the Koushien
Our top pinch-hitter swung three times and didn't even come close to making contact.
Nice pitching !
I was going to praise him if he had kept up his frivolous pitching till the end.
In the end, he's just
a baseball-loving boy.
For a superior team,
the first contest is always tricky.
Regardless of whether he
could actually fool me or not....
...there was no need for him to
introduce himself to us in a game like this.
When the inferior team
exposes its true ability...
...the contest always ends up the same as what the ranking says.
If he can't even throw away a meaningless game like this...
...there's no way they
can pull an upset.
Play !
Now, come on !
Kunimi !
It starts here !
Yep.
He did it !
Good job, Kunimi !
Honestly, this is more like Hiro.
Yeah.
I don't need guys who enjoy baseball.
Hirota...
...you like winning
better than baseball.
That's how it should be.
What you do to win is
always the right thing to do.
Whether it's practice, strategy, or tactic, no matter what it is.
All right.
Yeah ! We're now
down by just one run !
One run ?
Yes, wonderful.
Player substitution, shortstop.
Shortstop ?
Why ?
Who knows ?
Why did you change your defensive positioning ?
Based on how the batter was squaring up and where the catcher's mitt was...
...I decided that it
was best to do so.
Have you ever seen a chess piece move on its own ?
Huh ? No, I haven't.
Why did you change your defensive positioning ?
Like I said...
...based on how the batter was squaring up and where the catcher's mitt was...
...I decided...
I decided...
I'm sorry !
Now, we need one more run.
Yeah.
Out !
Don't worry about that !
Strike !
Oh, they can't even get
a sacrifice bunt down ?
Just like Hiro, this
team is still growing.
Strike ! Batter out !
Don't worry about it !
Yeah !
What's the point of getting the
sacrifice bunt down with two outs ?
Um...
Out !
Don't worry.
Coaches are evaluated based on the numbers.
Whether the coach is a good person or not doesn't mean anything.
In order to win, I've ruined or
abandoned many players over the years.
Players are disposable,
but there's only one coach.
Players graduate and leave, but I stay.
Three national championships total, in spring and summer.
Because of that record, I am the
"Great Field Manager Shiroyama."
Listen, Hirota.
I'm going to use you
to enhance my status.
I won't forgive you
if you become useless.
I'll pitch-to-contact !
But he doesn't really intend to.
That's right.
What a weird team.
Oh well.
Strike !
Hey...
Start videotaping.
Y...yes, sir.
Strike !
Strike ! Batter out !
Let's pitch-to-contact !
They're videotaping.
He's a reputable coach.
He probably has ways of
attacking any type of pitcher.
But...
There's no guarantee that this data will still remain viable next year.
Hmm...
High school players change dramatically in half a year.
He probably takes that
into consideration, too.
Mmm...
Strike ! Batter out !
Two strikeouts in a row !
No, it started last inning.
Three consecutive strikeouts !
Yeah.
Wonderful !
Even if he takes that
into consideration...
...he's probably only thinking along
the line of a cat turning into a tiger...
...or a dog turning into a wolf, right ?
Strike !
He probably doesn't think about a cat turning into a whale or a dog turning into an eagle.
Um, I guess.
With an inflexible mind like that...
...there's no way he can project Hiro half a year from now.
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
Strike ! Batter out ! Change !
Yeah !
That's right. There's no way to
project Hiro half a year from now.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Koyasu Takehito
Next episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hironaga:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Arikawa:
Sato:
Takagi Wataru
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
"ho-hokekyo" is the onomatopoeia for the crooning of a nightingale.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hiro, the game against
Eikyou has ended, right ?
Yeah, it's over. We lost, though.
Let's move on.
See ? The school festival folk dance is starting.
Oh, no !
You've got to find your partner.
I'll be fine. I know
a dream Miss Senkawa.
Next episode of H2 is, "Achoo ! Waiting in Vain Inside the Cardboard Box."
Next episode of H2 is
Achoo !
Waiting in Vain Inside the Cardboard Box
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?