Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Welcome, Eikyou High School
Senkawa Festival Baseball Club Invitational Game
A culture festival invitational game against Eikyou High School.
The result was a
definitive loss for Senkawa.
But we're still developing as a team.
Now, let's go enjoy the culture festival.
Episode 37
Achoo !
Waiting in Vain Inside the Cardboard Box
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
Team
Eikyou
Senkawa
Hiro. Noda.
Good work today.
Good work.
Hey, you two. What did you think of the game ?
For now, I'm looking
forward to next year.
That's helpful to us, too.
I agree.
You guys are worth
waiting for, after all.
Hide-chan, it's time.
That's right. Let's go.
Oh, you're leaving ?
You guys aren't going
to the folk dance ?
No. We're going to watch a movie.
We have a free ticket
that expires after today.
Work hard to find
a folk dance partner.
If you don't want to
dance with a guy, that is.
Thanks for your extraneous concern.
See you.
I'm envious.
They'll be holding hands and
stuff inside a dark movie theater.
In this day and age, that
would still be wholesome.
That's right. They've been together for a long time, so perhaps...
Perhaps...
Well, let's find some cute girls.
Sure.
Kunimi, Noda !
Where are you going now ?
It goes without saying.
Right ?
That's right.
It's none other than the folk dance.
We're preparing to
go to the folk dance.
What about you ?
My class is doing a café,
so I'm going to help them.
I see.
Well, we'll get going.
Good work today.
You did great today.
Good luck with the Spring Koushien !
Well, we don't know
if we're going yet.
Oh, you're so humble !
Please go easy on me.
I'm looking forward
to going to high school.
Judging from your hand, it looks you continued to play baseball.
Just practice swings, to kill time.
Everyone, I'm sorry,
you'll have to excuse me.
He's an underclassman
from my junior high.
Sure. We're looking
forward to the Invitational !
Please win the championship.
Bye !
As always, you're cautious, Hirota.
If you want to play baseball,
I can introduce you to our coach.
Give me a break.
I don't want to get banned from the
club again for a crime I didn't commit.
Hey, it wasn't my fault.
It was something that all of the club
members decided to do, including the coach.
Well, I guess we'll leave it at that.
Wait, Sagawa.
Looking back on it...
...I guess I'm to be blamed for doing
something that caused a misunderstanding.
I feel sorry for that.
There wasn't a misunderstanding. I think I know you pretty well.
You definitely aren't sorry.
Is that someone you know ?
No.
I see.
I'm sorry that I dragged you into a meaningless game.
Even with Kunimi, those position
players and the coach are worthless.
You can forget about this team.
That coach's name is Koga, right ?
Yeah, I think that's what it was...
Hmm ?
Koga ?
It can't be.
According to my scorebook, it's 3-2.
The famous coach,
Shiroyama Yoshiaki, huh ?
I doubt he remembers me.
Now, time for the culture festival !
Senkawa Festival
Our proud tradition, the Miss Senkawa
Contest, starts at 4 PM in the gymnasium.
And the main event of the
Senkawa Festival, the folk dance...
...will be held in the
schoolyard at 5 PM.
Please join us.
I knew you were from
Fukutomi High School.
No wonder you look so classy.
Oh, please, I wouldn't say that.
Can I ask you a question ?
Sure.
What's the color of
your underwear today ?
Huh ?
As always, you're smooth with
girls you meet for the first time.
What's that supposed to mean ?
This here is a good guy.
He's honest, so he'll show his true self soon enough.
Thanks for that.
Yay.
Oh, well.
So what's the color ?
What ?
Huh ?
Even though there are so many people here, it's really hard to find a cute girl.
Men's Bathroom
That's not true. Isn't it because
you're comparing them to Hikari ?
You shouldn't make her the standard.
Standard...
Whatever it is,
you're taking a long time.
Shut up.
Light Meal Café
Coffee
Tea
Sandwich
Spaghetti
Pilaf
Pork Cutlet Bowl
Thank you for waiting. Please enjoy.
She might be cute.
Haruka !
I'm going to draw some water. Give me a hand.
Okay.
Oh, it's Koga.
What's the matter ?
Nothing.
Then let's go find
some cute girls !
Yeah.
Let's get fired up !
Wait, Asako !
What are you going to do
about the folk dance, Haruka ?
I have no interest whatsoever in it.
Kunimi didn't ask you out ?
What ? Why ?
I mean, you guys
look good together.
Really ?
Oh, I see.
Then I might ask out Kunimi.
Huh ?
Phew ! You're making a suspicious face.
Give me a break, Asako.
You look suspicious.
We have to get water and go back there. Everyone's waiting for us.
Sure.
Light Meal Café
Um...
Do you have plans
for the folk dance ?
Not really. Right ?
Right.
Then won't you join us ?
But...
No ? Let's go together.
What should we do ?
It's okay, right ? You said you didn't have plans.
Let's go.
He's with us, too.
Hey, Hiro.
You should ask them, too.
Let's go, Yamada.
I'm Kawakami.
Please. I'm begging you. Please go out with us !
Huh ?
Please !
What's with that prostrating guy ?
He's so dorky !
Really !
And the other one is totally spacing out. He's a waste of good looks.
Are you actually trying ?
What do you mean ?
What are you talking about ?
The key to successful flirting is to be aggressive, you know ?
They say that the casual style works better these days.
Let's part here.
If I stay with you, I have the feeling that I really will end up dancing with a guy.
I see.
Good luck.
To you, too.
Aim for the Koushien
Light Meal Café
Welcome.
Coffee.
Sure.
Hey, Kunimi !
Do you know where Koga is ?
She's not here ?
I can't find her here or anywhere !
The selection of Miss
Senkawa is starting soon !
She was selected as one of the ten finalists from the preliminary contest the other day !
Oh.
I need her to participate, Kunimi !
You need me ?
Idiot !
Oh, crap !
Koga, where did you go ?
Koga !
Is that girl going to be in the
Miss Senkawa Contest, too ?
You mean the girl we saw on the rooftop just now ?
Yeah, I'm sure she will.
She was the cutest among the girls I saw today.
First Year, Class B, Miss Koga Haruka.
Please come to the Miss Senkawa Contest Committee Waiting Room immediately.
I repeat.
First Year, Class B, Miss Koga Haruka.
Oh ?
Please come to the Miss Senkawa Contest Committee Waiting Room immediately.
Don't catch cold, Manager.
I'm fine.
It's actually warm inside.
You're not confident ?
About what ?
Miss Senkawa.
I'm not participating. Never.
Why not ?
It's an honor for a girl, I guess.
It's a mockery to rank
girls based only on looks.
I don't like it,
and that won't change.
Sorry about that.
About what ?
I voted for you in the preliminary, too.
Being dutiful is an important quality.
Yeah. You help us out
all the time, after all.
Are you sure you're not cold ?
I'm fine.
I see.
Can I come get you when the folk dance starts ?
I don't have a partner.
What are you talking about ?
You'll be fine, Kunimi.
You can ask anyone,
and most girls will say yes.
That's a "yes," then ?
Huh ?
I can wait for you here ?
Yeah.
You really aren't cold ?
No. Not at all.
Can you come with me ?
I won't take up too much time.
Can you pitch to me ?
I want to bat against you.
I'm sorry to say. We don't have a
batting center at our culture festival.
It's a no ?
How about three
pitches for 100 yen ?
And if you put it in play,
I'll pay you 200 yen.
If it's a hit, it'll be 1000 yen.
You sure are confident.
Oh, come on.
It's just modest confidence.
I didn't say I'd pay 10,000 yen.
Do you want to try ?
With pleasure.
Stay low and keep
your eyes on the ball.
Oh !
There !
What're you doing here ?
After the game,
it's free time, right ?
Yeah, we're free,
so we're practicing.
It's the culture festival today.
You should...
I told them that, too, but...
Well, we let you down
so many times today.
We felt responsible, so
I didn't feel like playing around.
I feel sorry for Yanagi,
but we had him coach us.
But maybe it's meaningless...
If we practice hard,
we might improve, right ?
Or is it useless...?
So what brings you here, Kunimi ?
Yeah.
This is Tachibana Hideo's childhood friend, Sagawa.
He'll join our baseball club next year.
Right ?
I'm on the borderline for Senkawa, so I might not make it in.
That depends on
how hard you work.
Right ?
You want me to make you feel
like you want to work hard, right ?
Yanagi, count my pitches.
Here I go !
Repeating seasons.
And accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
...tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground.
A smile heals the wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
Aren't his pitches faster than they were in the game ?
Yeah. He shouldn't be so
competitive against a junior high kid.
He's going to lose his confidence...
No, if he goes easy, he'll be hit hard.
What ?
Sitting on the shoreline that I'm supposedly used to seeing.
If you put it in play,
you get 200 yen, you know ?
It's so beautiful...
That's right.
...I'm surprised at myself for feeling cleansed.
He's not giving up.
I still remember the smell...
Yanagi, what's the next pitch ?
It's 45.
45 divided by 3...
...of the rusted, old school building, so...
...equals 1500 yen !
Back to the ground.
Regaining the innocence and purity, that was disappearing from me.
That was disappearing from me
Back to the ground.
He did it !
The nostalgic warmth...
...keeps encouraging me now.
Okay. 1500 minus 1000. You can pay 500 yen.
It's a double.
What ?
It's worth two hits.
Moron. You can't reach
second base with that.
I can.
For me, it's a double.
Okay then.
In exchange, you've got to get
admitted here and prove it to us.
Oh, the folk dance
seems to have started.
That's right.
Oh...!
Hmm ?
Um, if you like, would
you dance with me ?
Huh ?
Ugh !
Achoo !
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Coach Shiroyama:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Hazumi Jun
Matsumoto Yasunori
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Hirota Katsutoshi:
Hironaga:
Asako:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Arikawa:
Fan B:
Fan A:
Koyasu Takehito
Takagi Wataru
Neya Michiko
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Konishi Hiroko
Shirakawa Mayu
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
Shuu getting into Senkawa: Shuu is talking about his projected exam score. He's saying that his projected score is borderline for Senkawa, so he might or might not be admitted.
Pitch count on blackboard: Yanagi counting by using a kanji,
which is made of five strokes and is often used
for counting numbers.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hiro, you're going out
on a date with Haruka ?
It's because I missed the folk dance.
You're going to do
anything she wants ?
Just one day, though.
I wonder what will
happen on a date with Hiro.
You've got to be a good escort.
I know.
Next episode of H2 is, "The First Date !
Best Regards To Us For The Future."
Next episode of H2 is
The First Date !
Best Regards To Us For The Future
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?