Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
At the fall cultural festival,
I asked Koga to the folk dance.
But Hideo's childhood friend, Sagawa...
...challenged me, saying
he wanted to hit my pitches.
I got so engrossed in the duel that I
totally forgot about my promise with Koga.
Koga, I'm sorry.
Episode 38
The First Date !
Best Regards to Us for the Future
Give It Your Best,
Kunimi Hiro !
I'm going to go, Third.
Would you like some ice cream ?
Thanks.
Oh, that's right.
I don't need to
thank you today, do I ?
Certainly, Miss.
I'm glad that you
actually came today.
As I said, I'm sorry.
I just got so engrossed in it.
I'm not mad.
I did want to do the folk dance with you, though.
Besides, you're going to
spend the entire day with me.
You're going to pay for everything,
and you'll do anything I ask, right ?
Don't ask for too much.
I have to pay for all this ?
If a cute girl is asking,
you should do it.
Even if you were cute,
you're just my kiddy cousin.
Hey, that looks so cute.
Huh ?
Can you buy that for me ?
I just bought you
a similar one recently.
Why are you looking
envious, Ryutarou ?
That's silly.
Why should I be envious ?
You're right.
You're with me, after all.
There's no way you'd
be envious of anyone.
What ? Why with you ?
You're happy, aren't you ?
Now, Miss. You can tell me
any of your whimsical wishes.
You can give me any of your whimsical wishes.
My whimsical wish #1.
You really want to ride this ?
My whimsical wish #2.
Let's not ride in the first row.
#3.
What ? It's a standing ride ?
#4.
What was that ?
It was scarier than I thought.
I didn't know that you'd
get scared so easily.
You don't act that way,
so I didn't know.
Well, you're considered a great one if you can read the pitcher's mind by just looking at his facial expressions.
Well, you're considered great if you can read a pitcher's mind just by looking at his face.
Hey, what are you doing there ?
Hey, popcorn.
Do you want some ?
You're going to buy me some ?
Of course.
Thank you very much.
Sure.
Kunimi.
You didn't force yourself to come with me, right ?
It was an obligation.
Obligation.
Don't put on an act.
I know you're having fun.
Hey, how old are you ? How old ?!
There's no way I could enjoy
being with a cheeky kid like you !
Shut up and eat !
Huh ?
That show of anger is really an expression of love.
I'm happy that it's
an amusement park.
What ?
Instead of the folk dance, I mean.
Weekdays are great.
It's not crowded.
Yeah.
Koga.
Yes ?
The carp here are so gluttonous.
You're right.
Hey.
You're high school
students, aren't you ?
Yes.
What about school ?
We had a cultural festival on Sunday, so we have an off day today instead.
You're off today ?
Yes.
Fine, then.
Let's go there now.
The surprise house ? Don't be
surprised by your own face, okay ?
That's mean.
That goes for you, too.
But really, some of those
make you look scary.
Nowadays, high school kids should hold hands. You two should, too.
Right ?
Amusement park. It's so joyful.
Amusement park.
What was that about ?
You know ?
Yeah.
Let go of me.
Don't be bashful.
We're just holding hands.
I'm not being bashful.
Ryutarou.
You want one ?
I don't want one.
Just finish it already.
Oh, man.
My clothes got sticky, too !
You two.
What happened to school ?
What ?
Well, we have a day off
because of the cultural festival.
Right ?
One boy ticket and
one girl ticket, please.
You mean one adult
and one child, right ?
Why are you so flustered ?
Shut up !
Leaves turning red. Walking while holding hands. The autumn sky.
That's a great haiku.
What is that about ?
Hey, what's your next whim ?
Jumping over the puddles one by one...
I was just trying to think
of one. My next whim is...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Umm, what's the next one ?
It's #23.
You've been counting, Kunimi ?
I'm just kidding.
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Is that it ?
No.
I'm saving that one for last.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Let's go.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
I guess we're riding that one, too ?
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
It was a mirror, but you
were acting like it was real.
Kunimi.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Yeah ?
Let's stay strong and move forward.
Hmm.
When I'm by myself I notice, that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
Hey, it's well-made.
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow, there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ? My eyes will look kinder.
Hey, Koga.
This one looks interesting, too.
Let's go.
Sure.
Wait up, Kunimi.
Where are you, Kunimi ?
Aim for the Koushien
No Reentry
Allowed
I can't find him.
What happened to your boyfriend ?
You two lost each other ?
Yes.
That's why I told
you to hold hands.
A minor cross-up
leads to the end of love.
Sorry about that.
I'm telling you.
The lost child is a long-haired, lecherous-looking high school boy.
He's totally useless without me.
He's aimless and helpless.
Really, he's such a handful.
Why are you making such a face ?
I was afraid that
you'd left me behind.
That maybe I asked for too much.
I promised to spend the day with you.
Honestly ?
Honestly. You should have confidence in yourself.
Ring Toss
Three rings per game, 200 yen
The prize of the ring toss must
be completely inside the ring.
Here are the three rings.
That one !
All right.
I wanted to come to
the amusement park.
At an amusement park, we can go back to feeling like children.
I thought I'd be able
to see your everyday self.
Well, it's a date today.
I guess I'm a little tense.
A date ?
Don't repeat what I said.
You're being bashful.
Peerless
You can throw it away.
Why ? I wanted this one.
You've got to be kidding.
I'm being honest.
Well, what's next ?
Shall we go for the one we've saved ?
Sure.
Wow, it's a great view !
I guess so.
Look, Kunimi !
I'll see it later.
Are you afraid of heights ?
A little.
But you said you
wanted to ride this.
You looked like you wanted to.
Don't move !
It's losing balance !
When I first met you, it was spring.
Were you able to burn it ?
Kunimi Hiro.
I'm Koga Haruka, the manager for the Senkawa High School Baseball Club.
It's coming up soon.
What is ?
Look, Kunimi !
To tell the truth, I wanted us to see this together.
What is it ?
You wanted juice ?
Yeah.
Thanks.
It feels good.
Sorry about that.
Since when ?
It's been like this since
I woke up this morning.
That's stupid ! You should
have called me and canceled !
No way !
It would be such a waste.
You're paying for everything today.
You're the daughter
of a company president.
There's no need to be stingy !
I've been looking forward to this, since yesterday.
We're going home.
You promised to
spend the day with me.
Today isn't the only off day.
If you don't mind splitting the tab, I'll go out with you anytime.
Really ?
Yeah.
Then we'll go home.
In five years, you'll be cuter, even if not as cute as Koga.
It's hot !
What did you do that for ?!
It made a mark on my cheek !
Oh, well.
It's hot.
Koga ?
Oh, pardon me.
Oh.
Could you take a photo of us ?
Today, too.
Romance begins at the amusement park.
And I make happiness.
Too many syllables.
Say cheese.
You shouldn't take
a photo of us like this.
It's to commemorate our first date.
Oh, well.
I look forward to spending time with you.
Kunimi Hiro:
Koga Haruka:
Kine Ryutarou:
Akina:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Suzuki Masami
Takenaka Shinichi
Yoshida Konami
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Next Episode
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Guard:
Couple(Man):
Couple(Girl):
Sugawara Junichi
Yamazaki Takumi
Takemasa Hiroko
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
The security guy is making fake haiku during the episode.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hiro, Hide-chan's arm
is finally out of the cast.
So he's starting his rehab ? He must have lost a fair amount of muscle.
But if he pushes himself too hard, it might set him back.
Then you must be firm and tell him. You shouldn't need to refrain.
But I can't quite say it
in the way that I want.
If it's Hiro, it's easier.
Next episode of H2 is,
"The Cast in Your Heart Isn't Gone Yet."
The First Date !
Next episode of H2 is
The Cast in Your Heart Isn't Gone Yet
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?