Presented by FroZen-EviL!
daisuki datta no
I've loved him.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I've always been waiting.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
I showed off whenever he was around.
ki no nai furi shiteta
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
My career and love life?
watashi taisetsu dakedo
I do think they're both important.
aitsu no egao ga yappari
But when I see his smile,
saikou no takaramono
I know it's what I want the most.
omoigakenai puropoozu!
He proposed to me; was it real?
sukuranburu no domannaka
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
uso deshou
It's so unbelievable.
tachidomatta mama
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
Horns don't get through my ears.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
The world is silent and completely still,
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
Chu! Chu!
Kiss! Kiss!
Ippon! Done!
Another Uchi Mata!
Are you clear?
You should really watch out for Ito Fujiko,
especially her Ouchi Gari.
Just one more before I face Inokuma Yawara.
Listen to me, Sayaka-san!
Soon we'll settle everything!
Sayaka-san!
Good luck, Fujiko-san!
Fight her!
S-Sorry if I lose in an instant!
Keep fighting, Fujiko-san!
Just one more.
Bow!
Get Out of My Way!
Now, here comes the juggernaut of the tournament, Ito Fujiko!
The cheers are growing louder!
Inokuma! Inokuma! Inokuma! Inokuma!
However, these cheers are in anticipation
of a match between Honami Sayaka and Inokuma Yawara!
Beanpole, take a fall, any fall!
We're here to see Inokuma take on Honami!
Please lose!
Bastards! Why are you telling her to lose?!
What the hell is my daughter to you?!
She's a prima donna!
Prima donburi?
I know I'm going to lose anyway.
But I won't lose without a fight.
I need to wear her out at least,
then pass her on to Inokuma-san!
Hajime!
Un, deux, trois. Un, deux, trois.
Just one more.
Just one more!
Just you wait, Inokuma Yawara!
Un, deux, trois.
I just need to take care of this obstacle!
Un, deux...
Get away, Sayaka-san!
Trois!
Waza Ari!
Incredible, a Waza Ari!
Ito's Ouchi Gari got her a Waza Ari!
You're awesome, Fujiko-san!
Take that!
Honami Sayaka is in a state of shock!
That's the ugly truth, Miss.
H-Has milady...
She's still in it. Now quick, to the arena.
O-Of course. Milady!
P-Perhaps Yawara-san won't even be in tomorrow's headlines!
How about "Inokuma Jigoro's Superb Coaching!" above and below the fold?
We've come to an unexpected development!
Who would've ever predicted that Honami would be on the defensive?
I was just a little unfocused.
Un, deux, trois. Un, deux, trois.
It's time for you to get out of my way!
U-Un, deux...
Now!
Trois!
There she goes!
There it is, Ito's Ouchi Gari!
And it's Honami who literally fell on her back!
Fujiko!
I'm so moved!
She got her.
All right!
Fujiko-san!
J-Jougai.
The referee has declared it a Jougai!
Jougai! Mate!
Ito Fujiko was so close.
Her feet were slightly out of bounds when she did her Ouchi Gari.
That means Honami Sayaka has narrowly escaped a loss!
No way! Fujiko should've won that, right, honey?
That's right! Although I don't quite understand.
There's no need to worry.
Fujiko-san already has a Waza Ari, and as you can see, she's overpowering Honami.
So please relax,
Mother, Father.
"Mother"? "Father"?
Don't call us that!
O-Okay...
Ah, thank God!
I thought we weren't gonna see Honami and Inokuma face each other.
Don't give up, Sayaka-san!
Just keep going till you get to Inokuma!
Yeah! Yeah!
Sayaka! Sayaka!
Cut that out, you people!
Our daughter is fighting for her life out there, why?
Sayaka! Sayaka!
Now that Honami's down a Waza Ari, how is she going to counter?
Only three minutes left!
Sayaka! Sayaka! Sayaka!
And the whole arena's shouting out Sayaka's name!
That's as it should be,
because most of the crowd has come to see a match between Honami and Inokuma!
They won't see the star player that easy!
Simply magnificent, Master Inokuma Jigoro!
Coach Yutenji!
I can't believe she mastered that skill in such a short time!
I have once again come to recognize your greatness!
So you've come, have you? I see your face has gotten even bigger.
Yes, glad to be here.
We at Saikai University will be facing Tsukushi University in the second semifinal match.
So that means your team's still winning those matches, correct?
Yes. But I'm afraid this year the Tsukushi University team is nearly unbeatable.
On the other hand, we at Saikai University still have a ways to go.
I still regret not being able to land Inokuma Yawara.
On top of that, there's that tall girl.
Her rhythm, her flexible body, the smoothness of her moves...
She's an amazing talent!
And you discovered that talent and used your expertise to train her!
It's enough to make me kowtow to you!
You're quite the silver-tongued devil!
Here, take one, Yutenji.
Yes, allow me to partake.
Still, will having Yawara-san on our team remain just a dream?
You can have her.
I'll let you have her.
Hey, that's unfair!
You're taking that Waza Ari and running out the clock, aren't you?
Don't let her grab you, Fujiko-san! Watch out for her Uchi Mata!
Fujiko-san, her Uchi Mata!
Inokuma Yawara!
Another Uchi Mata?!
Pull up your left foot!
Incredible, she avoided it!
Jougai!
Honami is desperate to make up for that Waza Ari!
Yes.
But she does need to be careful here.
Sayaka-san, don't rush it!
If you do, your moves won't be decisive!
Sayaka! Sayaka! Sayaka!
Those are loud cheers.
I won't be able to avoid her forever anyway.
No matter what, I need to wear her out!
Hajime!
Fujiko! Fujiko! Fujiko!
Give it your all today! Your mother will allow it!
Her parents once wanted to cancel the match.
You did it, Fujiko-san!
We have your parents' approval!
Hold it! I still don't approve of Fujiko associating with you!
O-Of course.
Did you just say I can have Yawara-san?
Yes, you can have her.
Plus you can also have Beanpole as a bonus.
Two for one, whaddaya think? Can't beat that, can ya?
H-Hey, wait! What are you trying to say?
Yawara-san and Fujiko-san are still enrolled in MWJC.
You caught that, you media jackal?
That's right, those two are in their second year of junior college.
And they still haven't decided what they plan to do next.
You're not saying...
You're sending them to Saikai University?
Fujiko-san! Grab her back collar and lower your stance!
Oh no you don't!
You damned obstacle!
Trap her feet!
How long are you going to stand in my way?
It's not you I want to fight!
My only real opponent is...
Fujiko-san, it'll be all right!
Inokuma Yawara!
Fujiko-san, hold on just a little longer!
Fujiko-san!
He's... sending Yawara-san to Saikai University?
Translation: kokujin-kun
Editing: Collectr
Timing: Juggen               Encoding: Skr
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, Rosti,
Skr, kokujin-kun, Juggen
DVD Provider: CP
Milady, hold on!
Tokunaga-san, have some salmon roe and relax, willya?
I wouldn't be able to swallow that!
Not when Milady is in a hard fight!
Then I'll have some.
A hard fight? I knew that before it began.
Just be thankful you didn't get beaten by an Ippon.
Milady, I'm coming for you!
Now don't be so impatient.
Here's some mackerel. It's good.
Less than a minute remaining in the match!
Will that Waza Ari lead to Honami's loss?
Sayaka! Sayaka! Sayaka!
Yawara! Yawara! Yawara!
The crowd is chanting both Sayaka and Yawara's names!
But at this rate, MWJC will win without the aid of Yawara!
Fujiko! Fujiko! Fujiko!
Only 40 seconds left, Fujiko-san!
Come on, you're almost there!
Fujiko-san's so amazing!
She's so cool!
You can do anything if you work hard for it.
It's still anybody's match. She mustn't let her guard down.
She's still facing Sayaka-san.
She's so close. I can practically reach her!
Inokuma Yawara!
Why should I work myself into a sweat over this?
It's so I can topple Inokuma Yawara!
I won't let this opponent get in my way!
I said you will not get in my way!
Waza Ari!
It's a Waza Ari!
Honami switched from an Uchi Mata to an Ouchi Gari to get a Waza Ari!
Only twenty seconds left on the clock!
Now both players have a Waza Ari! It's all tied up!
Oh, wait a minute! She's in danger!
Get away, Fujiko-san!
Oh, Honami takes an arm!
Is she going for a joint lock?!
Or is she going to turn her over and go for an Osaekomi?
She can score an Osaekomi even with one second remaining!
What are you doing to Fujiko?
Stop this!
Only ten seconds left! Get away!
Come on, just a little more!
Ah, she's got her!
Eight seconds left!
Seven... six... five...
Get out of my way!
Oh, she's trying to turn her over! Ito Fujiko's in trouble!
Fujiko!
Don't give in!
Honami flipped her over!
Fujiko-san!
Honami's going for an Osaekomi!
Wait! Ito avoids it by entangling her legs!
Even now, you're still trying to obstruct my rematch with Inokuma Yawara?!
I'm done!
Done!
The clock's run out!
Honami did not get an Osaekomi!
It's over!
All right! You held her off, Fujiko-san!
Fujiko!
Is it over? What happened? Did Fujiko win?
Of course she did.
Fujiko-san most certainly won,
Mother, Father!
Stop calling us "Mother" and "Father"!
We've seen something truly incredible!
The Herculean match between the Seishin Women's School's captain,
Honami Sayaka, and MWJC's vice captain, Ito Fujiko,
has now come down to a referee's decision!
Will it be a stunning upset?
Or will Honami Sayaka prevail, leading to a face-off with her fellow captain, Inokuma Yawara?
Both players have a Waza Ari under their belts!
But in terms of total offensive moves, wouldn't Honami have the lead, Saito-san?
But Ito did have that Ouchi Gari at the beginning, even though it was ruled out of bounds.
That looked like an Ippon, and it must've left a very deep impression.
Honestly, that obstacle has caused me too much trouble.
In any case, my only objective is to fight Inokuma Yawara.
Come, it's time for battle!
Fujiko-san's going to win, right, Inokuma-san?
You're darn right! Fujiko-san won any way you look at it!
That's right!
It'll be fine.
Don't worry.
Your calls!
It's one red and one white flag from the sub-refs!
So what's the head ref's decision?
It's a draw!
H-Holy cow, a draw!
Since the Seishin captain, Honami, received a draw, MWJC wins without their captain, Inokuma!
Yay!
There will be no rematch between Honami and Inokuma!
What did you say?!
Have you gone blind? Didn't you see all of my offensive moves?
Return to your position!
This isn't the time for that!
Honami simply won't accept the outcome!
The folks hoping for a Honami-Inokuma rematch are booing the call.
You could say Honami entered this tournament just for that rematch!
And she had it within her reach!
She fought all the way to Inokuma's presence, only to leave here with a draw!
It's time for you to bow!
I won't put up with this farce!
Your decision is invalid! Call a lawyer immediately!
It's time for you to bow!
Bow!
Honami exits!
Honami Sayaka is mortified!
It's regrettable, Sayaka-san.
Sayaka-san?
On the other hand, Ito Fujiko did marvelously!
She's truly an astonishing newcomer!
You did it!
Fujiko, well done!
She was such a timid girl.
That's really our daughter!
I'm so moved!
Fujiko-san, you're out of this world!
The trophy's ours at this rate!
You're incredible!
Fujiko-san!
Fujiko! What's wrong?!
Hang in there, Fujiko-san!
Are you all right?
It hurts.
My left shoulder... hurts really bad.
Honami-san, a word...
Sorry about the way things turned out.
Milady...
"The Gentle Way Was Not Built in a Day," right?
Get in.
Okay, I've put it back.
Fujiko-san?
All you need now is my patented boiled newt medication to stop the pain.
Is our daughter Fujiko all right?
Sure, it's just a minor dislocation.
Dislocation?
Calm down. I put it back in place.
You put it back in place?
Fujiko, you poor dear!
I'm fine. It doesn't hurt as much now.
Master, will Fujiko-san be able to compete in the final round?
Don't be ridiculous!
Yes, it would be better if she doesn't.
She'll be shouldering the future of judo, so she needs to take care of that body.
She doesn't need to overwork herself for this rinky-dink tournament.
The future of judo?
She'll be shouldering that?
I-It's fine. I'll compete.
You mustn't overdo it.
A ballerina's body isn't soft!
Stop this, Fujiko!
Just leave everything to Inokuma Yawara-san!
I'm fine, honest!
Fujiko-san.
The result of the second semifinal match is in!
Tsukushi U's team advances!
What's more, they took care of Saikai University with just their first two players!
They're much stronger than when we saw them last time.
See?
I need to get out there and help out, Inokuma-san.
That's crazy, Fujiko-san.
I'm telling you, I'm fine! Ow!
See?
Let us handle it, Fujiko-san!
You busted your hump out there!
It's time for us to step up!
Sh-She's right! It's time for us to carry our weight!
Paddyfield... Kyonkyon...
We'll wipe the floor with Tsukushi U!
You can also leave it to me!
So just watch, knowing we're in good hands.
Just don't be our albatross, okay?
What the heck? And we were just getting pumped up too!
Guys...
Yay!
All right, let's get out there and fight!
Yeah!
What? That beanpole hurt her shoulder and won't appear in the finals?
So it went from five versus two to five versus one, eh?
That means you five will crush Inokuma Yawara!
Yeah!
The Barcelona Olympics in 418 Days
Yawara, at last you've reached the finals of this stupid tournament.
It's not stupid! We'll fight hard and win the championship!
You know you can't treat those Tsukushi girls the same as your other opponents.
I know.
And since Beanpole ain't playing, you might be out there quicker than you thought.
Yawara!
The Lightning-Fast Ippon Zeoi.
The Lightning-Fast
Ippon Zeoi
You'll get my Harai Goshi if you don't watch.
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
koe ni dashite ienai no?
But why can I not? I really don't know.
ima anata ga iru
You're standing here by my side.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
egao wo sagashite
I say as I look for your smile.