Presented by FroZen-EviL!
daisuki datta no
I've loved him.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I've always been waiting.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
I showed off whenever he was around.
ki no nai furi shiteta
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
My career and love life?
watashi taisetsu dakedo
I do think they're both important.
aitsu no egao ga yappari
But when I see his smile,
saikou no takaramono
I know it's what I want the most.
omoigakenai puropoozu!
He proposed to me; was it real?
sukuranburu no domannaka
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
uso deshou
It's so unbelievable.
tachidomatta mama
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
Horns don't get through my ears.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
The world is silent and completely still,
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
Chu! Chu!
Kiss! Kiss!
Un, deux, trois!
This is it.
This is what I've been waiting for all these years.
I get to be close to Yawara-san as her coach,
and Sayaka-san has gone off somewhere to train secretly with Kojiro.
If I let this chance slip...
it will be the biggest mistake of Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke's life!
Un, deux, trois!
Your "Swan Lake" is getting better and better!
Still not there. I need to win at the All-Japan tournament!
That way, I can go to Yugoslavia with Inokuma-san!
I guess I did mess up badly.
But I did so many interviews.
Why hasn't at least one company called back?
The Selected Judo Championship of Love
Thank you for waiting.
This train, Yamabiko #74, will be arriving in Tokyo.
Ueno. This is Ueno.
Thank you for riding with us.
Matsuda.
Wanna get a cold one?
Sorry, today won't work.
Payday's coming up, and I'm out of cash.
Come on. We hardly go out anymore.
Wow, it says Inokuma Yawara's going to the Nationals!
And then it's on to the World Championships!
Yawara-chan's so cute!
Come along! It's not like you have a girl waiting at home.
Lay off, willya?
Yes, this is All Sports.
D-Dad?
Sign: Chojuan Soba and Chinese
This is a surprise! You came without giving me a call.
Is something up?
Nope, nothing's happening. That's exactly why I came.
I came here because I don't see you getting yourself a woman.
Anyway...
Have a look.
Wh-What's this?
You know what it is.
She's a nice girl who works as an elementary school teacher in the next town.
When I told her family about you,
they jumped at the idea.
N-Now wait a minute!
Haven't we discussed this before?
I already have a girl—
You mean Yawara-chan?
Didn't you say that Inokuma Yawara is the girl that's going to the Olympics?
Yeah.
Give it up, will you?
That's who she is, right?
She's bound to become a National Achievement Hero or something.
She's way out of the league of a third-rate reporter at a third-rate paper.
You're better off marrying some lovely, normal girl.
A man can't go without a girl forever.
Get yourself two kids, and you'll have a happy home even if you're poor.
Don't plan my life out for me.
Is that a problem?
Are you saying you made it with Inokuma Yawara?
Did you at least touch her boobs? Or even kiss her like this?
You're pretty frank, Dad.
So did you?! So? So?
W-Well...
See? She's not gonna give you a second look.
Now trust me, pair up with this girl here.
You're wrong!
We get along fine.
That's bull.
I'm not lying!
Y-Yawara-san and I... we, you know... have an enviable relationship.
Then introduce her to me.
I-I can't!
Sh-She's really busy right now.
M-Meeting you out of the blue would be a big shock!
Then I'll watch her from a distance.
I want to see just how close you two are.
If people really do envy your relationship, you can make it happen.
W-Well...
B-But...
F-Fujiko-san—
H-Hanazono-san—
Wh-What is it?
No, you go first.
Nah, it's just that running early in the morning feels nice.
That's what I wanted to say!
The All-Japan Selected Judo Championships are coming up.
Yeah.
Hanazono-san, how do you feel before a match?
W-Well, I feel nervous about everything.
I think that every one of my opponents is at the top of his game.
I even wonder if there's anyone weaker than me.
So you get like that too.
All I know is that I'm scared, so scared.
Still, Fujiko-san, whenever I feel that way, I do this:
I'm the strongest one here!
Want to try it?
Shaddap!
Do you know what time it is? It's just dawn!
Sorry!
What is it, Matsuda-san?
Why did we need to talk?
U-Um... well, actually...
I didn't call you here for anything special.
Th-That's fine, right? We always meet up like this.
Always? You're usually doing a story when we meet.
Wait! W-Well...
I'm so busy doing stories that I don't get to see you often.
What are you saying, Matsuda-san?
Are you okay, Matsuda-san?
Uh, yeah, just a little dizzy.
S-Speaking of that, how are you feeling before your match?
Fujiko-san's very excited, and she's improving at an incredible rate.
But aren't you excited too?
You'll be going to the All-Japan Selected Championships,
then the World Championships,
then you'll transfer straight to Saikai University.
I'm not going to enter the World Championships, and I'm not going to Saikai University.
I'm only entering the coming tournament
because Grandpa said Fujiko-san would feel lonely.
You can't be...
I'm going to start working.
Work?
What about judo?
If you and Fujiko-san go to Saikai U,
Japanese judo will become much more riveting!
And that will make your articles more riveting, right?
N-No, I'm just saying...
I know that all you're interested in is a good story.
You don't care about what I feel.
Wh-What?
You're cute when you're angry. Just kidding.
What are you, dumb?
That's not going to change how I feel.
I'm leaving.
H-Hey, wait!
Damn...
I-It's not easy going out with an independent girl.
You thought you could fool me?
What's with him? He only said that because he'd have fun covering it.
He never thinks about how I feel.
But what will I do if I can't find work?
Translation: kokujin-kun
Editing: Collectr
Encoding: Skr
Juggen
Timing: Juggen
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, Rosti, Juggen
DVD Provider: CP
You call that an enviable relationship? That was an outright disaster!
Look, wake up and smell the coffee!
Marriage interviews were made for guys like you!
D-Don't make it sound like I can't get a girl.
Then what? You can get a girl?
Kosaku!
I've been looking for you everywhere.
The Chief is furious!
Wait, aren't you...
Oh my! Kosaku's father!
Oh, my heavens!
Kosaku, you should've told me your father was coming to visit!
I really wanted to meet him!
Let me go!
You two look like a very fine couple!
Kosaku, if you're with her, then I have no complaints!
K-Kosaku, are you meeting your father to discuss marriage?
Oh, Kuniko's so happy!
Y-You're wrong!
You are!
N-No, I'm not!
Really?
Matsuda-san said that?
Well, that man is all about his job.
You don't look happy. What happened?
Oh, come now, are you still suspicious about me and Sayaka-san?
No, I...
I've told you this many times before.
That engagement was all Sayaka-san's idea.
I flatly refused her.
I'm just an employee of the Honami Group.
I was never able to see you because I was always on overseas business trips.
That comes with the important position I hold.
But my heart was yearning while I was away.
Ah, those were hard and sorrowful days.
Now then, let's have a quiz!
Who do you think I'm thinking about?
Yes, you're correct!
No, you don't look happy at all.
Um, this is Tsurukame Travel—
What? You're not getting any return calls from your interviews?
Yes, I interviewed four times, but no one's called back.
Strange indeed.
You're the flavor of the month.
People should be fighting for you.
I guess I don't have any real talent.
No, there must be some mistake.
I'm sure you'll get some good responses.
Do you think so?
Still, Yawara-san... is working at a company the only future path?
For example, if there was someone who wanted to drink your café au lait every morning,
or someone who wanted to eat your freshly-baked cakes,
or someone who wanted to see your smile every day...
You mean a coffee shop?
But that's just a part-time job.
Th-That's not what I meant!
Maybe I'm being a little too vague.
Yawara!
Y-Yes?
What in blazes are you dawdling for?
Get your fanny to the dojo!
Right!
S-Son of a...
Master, a-actually this was...
Actually, I was showing Yawara-san some sparring techniques.
Kazamitori!
Dang it! If you do anything to Yawara just 'cause you're near her,
you'll be hurting a lot more than this!
Got it?
Okay! I understand! Now let me go!
I swear, you're certainly more than stubborn.
I wonder where you get that from?
Listen, we're doing that marriage interview even if I have to drag you there myself!
Everyone else is wondering when there will be grandkids.
Your mom's always going on about wanting grandchildren.
She's so worried about you she gets nervous attacks all the time.
Marriage is great! You get to eat right every day and get it on every night!
Pipe down and go to bed, will you? I still have work, you know!
Of course, Inokuma Yawara will show us her lovely moves
at the upcoming All-Japan Selected Tournament.
Inokuma's vivid and brilliant Ippon Zeoi will...
I found her! Here's our future superstar!
You did it, Yawara-san! You're finally debuting in an official match.
Incredible, Yawara-san! You're the national champ!
You have the greatest smile, Yawara-san!
Top: Finally the World!!
Right: Yawara in Free-Weight World Cup Tournament?!
It's the beginning of the World Cup. Yawara of Japan, aim for the world!
Congratulations, Yawara-san! You're finally the world champ!
You really are my superstar!
You dumb mug.
Sorry, Hanazono-san, for making you come with me every morning.
O-Oh, don't worry.
In any case, the All-Japan Selected is tomorrow.
Yeah.
When I first saw Inokuma play judo, I was thrilled from the bottom of my heart.
She used her tiny body to flip bigger opponents one after the other.
But I didn't feel that I could never do what she was doing.
Seeing her gave me the confidence that I can do anything if I try!
I know!
I had no goals after quitting ballet.
I had no pride, and I didn't know what to do, until I met Inokuma-san.
Thanks to Inokuma-san, I feel that I can accomplish anything!
Let's give it our all, for Inokuma's sake!
Yes!
I will win next year's Japan Judo Championships, dammit!
Y-You're sweating a lot!
Here's my towel.
Fujiko-san's scent!
A-Are you okay?
Hanazono-san, your face is crimson!
Th-This is the latest I've ever been!
Dad?
What to do?
Yawara-san, Kosaku has fallen deeply for you!
Is there any way you can show him some pity?
Hm, maybe I'm getting too far ahead of myself?
Forgive me!
It's okay.
Thank you.
You must be Inokuma Yawara-san, right?
Yes.
I'm Kosaku's...
Yawara-chan!
Um...
Oh, the thing is my son is a big fan of yours.
Every time you win a match,
he practically turns cartwheels.
Please do your best in tomorrow's tournament, for that idiot son of mine.
I will. Thank you very much!
Who's that old fart?
He looks like a lecher.
Did he do anything to you, Inokuma-san?
Did he touch your butt?
No, he didn't.
But he's been wandering around here for a while now.
He's definitely a peeping tom!
Or maybe he's a thief?
No, he's not. I feel that he's very kind.
You're kidding!
God, he's still looking over here!
I'm scared!
Should I toss him?
Sign: All Sports News
Matsuda.
I heard the big news!
A-About what?
That you got your dad's permission to marry Kuni-chan, of course!
Peace!
N-No! That's a total mistake!
Don't try to hide it!
"When I say 'No,' I actually mean 'Yes'!"
You only acted like you wanted nothing to do with her, you horndog!
I'm telling you that you're wrong!
Hi, this is All Sports News. Dad?
Where were you this morning?
You're leaving?
Come on.
But you don't have to leave.
At least you could do some sightseeing around Tokyo.
Though I'm not doing a marriage interview.
I can't afford to do that.
If I don't give your mom massages, her nervous attacks won't subside.
I thought Yawara-chan would be unfriendly because she's famous, but she's actually sweet.
Dad! Don't tell me you met Yawara-san!
Relax, I didn't say anything out of bounds.
What's to be done? You can keep doing what you want.
If you're serious about her, then go after her!
You need persistence to win at love!
Dad.
There it is! Her deadly "Nutcracker"!
Yay!
Wow, that was awesome, Fujiko-san!
Fools!
That was just dumb luck!
Now get back to practicing!
Okay!
The way you've helped her improve in such a short time is truly masterful!
Fujiko-san's efforts and my coaching can't compare to your expert instruction!
Once again I, Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke, bow my head to you!
Oh you, but you still ain't getting Yawara.
Still, Beanpole has improved a lot thanks to my superior instruction.
I can't wait to see her in action...
at tomorrow's All-Japan!
Sign: The Barcelona Olympics in 383 Days
Yawara!
Beanpole is all fired up about the All-Japan Selected Judo Championships,
so what's your deal?!
I can't believe no one has called me back.
Relax, everything will fall into place.
Grandpa, did you do something behind my back again?
Actually, there was a call from Something-or-Other Travel.
What?
Yawara!
I'm So Mad!!
You'll be getting my Harai Goshi if you don't watch!
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
koe ni dashite ienai no?
But why can I not? I really don't know.
ima anata ga iru
You're standing here by my side.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
egao wo sagashite
I say as I look for your smile.