Presented by FroZen-EviL!
I've loved him.
daisuki datta no
I've always been waiting.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I showed off whenever he was around.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
ki no nai furi shiteta
My career and love life?
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
I do think they're both important.
watashi taisetsu dakedo
But when I see his smile,
aitsu no egao ga yappari
I know it's what I want the most.
saikou no takaramono
He proposed to me; was it real?
omoigakenai puropoozu!
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
sukuranburu no domannaka
It's so unbelievable.
uso deshou
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
tachidomatta mama
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
Horns don't get through my ears.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
The world is silent and completely still,
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
Kiss! Kiss!
Chu! Chu!
Yes. I know I've come too late.
But I wish to work for Tsurukame Travel—
I mean, for your esteemed company.
You gonna throw one of your hissyfits again!
You lying, no-account girl!
You made a very public, very firm declaration yesterday!
You can do it! You can do it, Fujiko-san!
You said we'd go to Yugoslavia together, didn't you?
Listen, Yawara!
You're going to win the World Championship
and go to Saikai University with Beanpole, and that's final!
I-Inokuma-san!
I... I... I've been chosen as a training player for the Yugoslavia World Championships!
All right!
I won't get to play in any matches,
but I can still go to Yugoslavia with you!
Fujiko's First Training Camp!
This is a good night to celebrate.
After all, you're going to the World Championships with Yawara.
Yes!
Thank you very much for making this food for me!
Yes, eat up, Beanpole, while I eat and drink.
Okay.
Let's have a toast, Inokuma-san!
Inokuma-san, I'm very moved by all this.
Fujiko-san, the truth is...
I'm not going to the World Championships.
What is it, Inokuma-san?
Oh, it's nothing.
Hey, what gives? The sake will go stale!
Cheers!
Training camp will begin soon.
I have to build up my strength so that I won't hold Inokuma-san back!
Gosh, what am I supposed to say to Fujiko-san?
I'm not going to the World Championships, and I'm not going to training camp either.
You're going to be a training player for the World Championships?
That's wonderful, Fujiko-san! Truly wonderful!
P-Pardon me!
Thank you.
But I can't believe I'm going to Yugoslavia with Inokuma-san.
It's like a dream.
It's... It's not a dream! You're strong, Fujiko-san. Very strong.
Unlike me.
I too want to be a judo competitor.
I'm simply pathetic.
Hanazono-san?
I feel that you'll become really good and go beyond my reach.
Just like Inokuma.
That won't happen.
I'm no good at all.
Back at the tournament, if it hadn't been for your support, I would've lost for sure.
F-Fujiko-san.
Sign: All Sports News
The training camp for the World Championships is about to begin.
Teleshikova from the USSR and Jody from Canada:
we have the two main players, which leaves Yawara-san.
Kosaku!
H-Hey!
What are you trying to pull?
Kuni-chan made a very special lunch for you!
Ta-da! Doesn't it look yummy?
I worked very hard on it just for you, Kosaku.
Isn't it wonderful?
Why don't you use that time to do some actual work?!
Hey, don't be so bashful, Matsuda!
We know you're thrilled.
Quit showing off!
When's the wedding?
Now those look good.
I know. They're all yours.
Good.
Magazine: Izu-Ito
Fun in the Hot Spring Steam
Hot springs?
It's Tsurukame Travel's Cordial Hot Springs Tour.
It's quite popular.
Haven't you seen the TV commercials?
"Travel with Tsurukame. Cordial Tsurukame."
I see they have heaps of good eats.
Maybe a hot spring ain't such a bad idea.
I agree!
But we can't.
Practically everybody is going on those trips,
and all the popular hot springs are booked solid.
However, there's no need to worry, Grandpa.
If I was working as a travel agent,
I could easily get us a good room, along with delicious food...
Who's gonna be working for who? Huh?!
Wait, I was just saying "what if."
You know, "what if."
I ain't having your "what ifs" or chive liver!
Playing judo at Saikai U should be the only thing on your mind, you nitwit!
I wanted to do something nice for you.
If you wanna do something nice,
then play judo, become the world champ, win the gold medal,
and get the National Achievement Award!
I just wanted to take you to a hot spring!
If you wanna go to a hot spring, do it on your honeymoon!
That reminds me. I spent my honeymoon with Kaneko at the Atami Hot Springs.
Coincidentally, it was the night before the outbreak of the Pacific War.
Geez, I've heard that story a hundred times!
Today, I'm going to tell Fujiko-san.
This time I'll be treating you, Inokuma-san.
Huh? You don't have to.
You came along when I applied for my passport, even though you were busy practicing.
You must tell me what it's like inside an airplane and all that!
This is my first trip overseas, after all!
Also, I've been running a lot, so I'm pretty hungry.
Keep it up, Fujiko-san!
What's wrong, Inokuma-san?
You should be eating, since training camp's coming up.
Oh, about that...
Look at this! Look! It's a guidebook for Yugoslavia!
Book: Eastern Europe
I'm checking for what to bring back.
Yugoslavia has so many delicious foods!
Oh, there's Madera's sarma.
It says there's no point going to Yugoslavia if you don't try it.
It looks so good. I'm definitely going to eat it!
Raznjici, cevapcici, Bosnian hotpot...
We... We need to talk.
What is it?
U-Um...
The thing is... um... I...
I...
Wh-What's wrong?
Fujiko-san, I'm sorry!
Inokuma-san, do you need to go to the bathroom?
Come on. It's nothing to be embarrassed about!
You can go! It's not good to hold it in.
I actually wanted to speak to you about something.
I'm only able to talk about this now.
When I lost due to that referee's call, I cried when I got home.
I smiled in front of everyone,
but actually, I was really upset.
I'm only able to say something so shameful to you, Inokuma-san.
Whether it's Yugoslavia or Saikai U, we'll always be together.
Sign: World Championship Training Camp
We will now begin our training camp for the World Championships.
I'm the director, Yanagizawa.
Listen to your coaches and get into your best condition for the day of the championships.
Yes, sir!
Let's do our best, Inokuma-san!
Y-Yes, let's.
Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
Juggen
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, sangofe
DVD Provider: CP
Timing: Juggen
Encoding: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: kokujin-kun
Timing: Juggen
DVD Provider: CP
QC Team: CP, Mamo-chan, sangofe
Juggen
Uh, it appears that Inokuma Yawara is leaving. Is that okay?
We are done with our morning training.
She's one tough chick!
She left me completely immobile!
Kill me!
She was dressed pretty smartly. Where is she going?
Not yet!
Sign: Parlor
We're so glad you came to see us.
Though if you'd asked, we would have met you anywhere you like.
Oh, I wouldn't think of that.
Training camp must be stressful.
We saw it on TV and in the newspapers.
She's taking on the world, after all.
That's right. Taking on the world is no easy task.
We would like to be the top travel agency in the world someday.
The world's top travel agency? I'd like that!
So what became of your attempt to turn your grandfather around?
Well...
Forgive me, but I will convince him somehow.
So can you give me a little more time?
Of course we will!
We'll give you as long as it takes!
Sign: Travel Consultation
So you're looking for the best hotel in Yugoslavia?
In that case...
Just splendid.
Sorry.
I was just thinking how splendid it would be to travel to Yugoslavia with someone like you.
But this time, I'll be traveling alone.
Actually, it's not just this time. I always travel alone.
Perhaps it's because I work too much?
Even a soldier needs a break once in a while.
How strange.
When I'm with you, I feel more relaxed.
Th-Thank you very much.
How about it? Why don't we go out to dinner or something?
Kazamatsuri-san?
Y-Yawara-san, what are you doing here?
It's Inokuma Yawara!
Yawara?
It's really her!
Work?
Yes.
W-Wait a minute! Why that company?
He's right!
You could've done much better for yourself!
That's not the problem here!
What is the problem?
What about your transfer to Saikai U?
So that's it?
I'm not going to Saikai U.
What? Then what about judo?
Does Tsurukame Travel even have a team?
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't? Then how will you play judo?
Honestly, all you talk about is judo!
Yawara-san has had enough of judo, what with the World Championships coming up.
Let's not talk about judo over her noon break.
Right?
I have to get back to camp. It's time for my training.
Now wait! Why are you bending over backwards to get a job?
Must you always be the aggressive reporter?
I told you before that my first career choice was to be a travel agent.
Yeah, you want to work using your own abilities,
and you'll be able to see the world at a travel agency.
Isn't that great? I admire your motivation.
I actually have one more reason.
I thought...
that working at a travel agency would make it easier for me...
to search for my father.
If I work at a travel agency, there's a chance I'll meet someone
who gave my dad a boarding pass or saw him at one of his destinations.
Oh, yeah...
Th-That's good thinking.
Don't you agree, Matsuda-san?
Oh, no. I'm really going to be late!
What should we do now?
What should we do? Why are you asking me?
If that's the case, then I'll take her to him!
I'm reuniting her with her dad!
Come on, Kazamatsuri!
Tell me where Kojiro-san is!
Where's Kojiro-san right now?
Kojiro-san is Sayaka-san's coach.
If you let Yawara-san see him, how do you think she'll react?
Geez, why didn't you stop him from becoming her coach?
Sayaka-san practically begged him.
You think I could've stopped it?
I was going to pick up the check, but forget it!
Pay for your own coffee.
All Sports really does pay you peanuts, doesn't it?
I'll pay for Yawara-san's drink!
No need to strain yourself.
You're paid below market, so I'll take care of it.
No, I will!
I have this!
No, you don't!
Yes I do!
O-One more time, please.
Come on. That's enough.
I have to go spar with the guys on the national team.
Please!
Just one more round! I think I'm beginning to understand!
All right.
Un, deux, trois...
So that's the Ito Fujiko I've been hearing about?
Yeah, she's pretty good, Yamashita.
Un!
Not only is she good, it's a waste of good talent to use her as just a training player!
Master Inokuma Jigoro, when did you get here?
Deux!
Doesn't it taste great?
This is Beanpole's home brew.
Oh, this is good.
Her tea is as good as her judo.
Yes, only because I taught her well.
She has the height and the balance.
She'd be evenly matched with a foreign opponent. Right?
By the way, Director Yanagizawa, have you decided on the free-weight player yet?
No, not yet. However, we'd really like it to be Yawara-san.
Trois!
Y-Yamada-san?
His head took the entire blow!
Hey, are you all right, Yamada?
Nope, he's out like a light.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! Oh gosh, wait... why?
S-O-R-R-Y!
Sign: The Barcelona Olympics in 320 Days
We're finally going to Yugoslavia.
Fujiko-san's really relishing this trip.
Yeah, she should enjoy it while it lasts.
What do you mean by that?
This tatsuta-age is delicious!
I know you're up to something, Grandpa.
You can expect some very interesting developments.
Yawara!
The Opening Act of the Yugoslavia World Championships!
You'll be getting my Harai Goshi if you don't watch!
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
But why can I not? I really don't know.
koe ni dashite ienai no?
You're standing here by my side.
ima anata ga iru
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
I say as I look for your smile.
egao wo sagashite