Step on the gas
Soaring too high
Nemurenai gozen niji
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
Nemurenai gozen niji
Iradachi ga doa o tataku
Hashirenai ookamitachi
Yami ni tsume o tate samayotteru
Kimi o saigo ni mita no wa
Hokori no mau zattou no naka
Semeru you na manazashi ga
Tachisaru senaka ni itami nokoshita
Kiri ni tozasareta mootaauei
Ima demo kotae sagashiteru
Tegakari no nai yozora ni
Chiheisen ga yokotawaru
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, seiza no kieta sora
Wow, wow, wow, joushiki no nai michi
Wow, wow, wow, yasashisa tada motome
Wow, wow, wow, yowasa to mukai au
Wow, wow, wow, sonna kimi wa iranai
Asaoka Law Firm
Write down whatever sum you
want on that check.
It's my way of expressing my gratitude.
You are truly a successful president
in the construction business.
But I cannot accept more than what
the bar association ordains.
I'm impressed by your skill, with which
you soundly defeated
the residents' lawsuit against my
building of a condominium.
I only defended you in a legal manner.
The verdict was given by a court of law.
I like you even more.
Do you mind if I smoke?
May I ask you not to?
How about it? Won't you become
a little friendlier with me?
I hope we will be very good
business partners.
Miss Mei...
That's fine, but it's a tough world for
a woman to live alone in.
If you ever change your mind,
come visit me anytime.
He's so cheesy!
An electronic notebook?
The Greatest Flagrant Love Committed!
How to Hit on a Beautiful Lawyer
XYZ
I will be waiting in
Central Park at
noon tomorrow.
XYZ
I will be waiting in
Central Park at
noon tomorrow.
"I will be waiting in Central Park at
noon tomorrow. Akira Asaoka."
Akira Asaoka? A man?
Ryo is going to pass!
So, you secretly came to see
the message board again.
Oh, my! A second straight week
with a job! And it's a man!
Of course, you'd better be taking this job!
But jobs from men are...
What?!
Nothing, I will gratefully take it.
Now, since we've got a job lined up,
I'm going drinking!
Oh, Ryo! Wait!
He's hopeless.
Love, don't go away!
Love! I need you, I've looked...
I'm drunk tonight!
...so long for you!
Don't stop the love again!
Who the hell fired an air gun at me?!
What's this prank about?
Let go! You're hurting me!
Your voice... You're a woman!
I was just testing your abilities
before I hired you.
Hired?!
It should have been written on the
message board at Shinjuku Station.
From Mei Asaoka.
Mei Asaoka... Asaoka...
I get it! You write "Akira" and read it "Mei"!
It was a girl's name!
You are nothing like what they say.
I cannot hire a sweeper who can't
even dodge a toy gun.
No need to rush to conclusions.
If you want to test my abilities,
you'll have to get to know me.
If you get any closer than that,
I will exercise Penal Code 36!
What?!
Legitimate self-defense!
I think that's aggravated assault.
Please don't follow me anymore!
It was all a mistake.
It's dangerous for a woman to be
out alone this late at night.
I'll walk you home.
No, thank you. I have a car.
Watch out! Get back!
They only did the tires.
They would've detonated the whole thing
if they wanted to kill you.
It was about three days ago when
strange things started happening.
Any idea who the perpetrator is?
No, not at all.
This is it, my office.
Asaoka Law Firm
I didn't know you were a lawyer.
That's strange. I turned my
light off when I left!
Oh, wait!
How awful.
Mr. Saeba?
Mr. Saeba, please get up! Mr. Saeba!
Before I die, I want to feel these
breasts a little more.
Attempted murder, illegal use of explosives,
breaking and entering, and
destruction of property.
If you list the charges,
they would be endless.
It looks like they're looking for
something that you have.
As I said before, I have no idea
who might be doing this.
Anything missing?
Just one thing.
This is a pair of my spare underwear.
When did you...
What?
I know! This is a tactic to cause confusion!
I'm innocent!
Guilty
You are nothing but guilty!
Give me the right to hire an attorney.
I'm home.
Cleaning up took all night. I'm exhausted.
Exhausted my ass! Coming home
in the morning with company!
Wait, Kaori! She's our client!
Oh my, a hundred ton hammer!
You're Miss Kaori, aren't you?
Yes! You are?
My name is Mei Asaoka. I am an attorney.
It is nice to meet you.
Mei Asaoka? Asaoka...
Then that job was for you?!
Last night, my office was attacked.
Mr. Saeba said it would be safe here.
I am sorry to bother you.
Same old routine as always.
Compliments are so embarrassing.
I'm not complimenting you, you moron!
Don't worry, Miss Mei. I'll protect you
from this mokkori man.
Mokkori man?
Miss Mei, would you like some tea?
Oh, thank you.
You didn't sleep last night, right?
Maybe you should rest a little.
Yes, but I have a lot of work piled up.
Being a lawyer must be tough work.
You have to properly defend your client,
no matter how bad he is, right?
It is not the job of a lawyer
to lessen his guilt.
Even bad people have rights, you know?
It's my duty as their attorney to protect
their basic human rights.
Wow, that's great. I admire people
like you, a career woman.
You know, women who do
professional work. Really!
Special Investigations
Hello?
Ryo?!
What do you want?
Actually, Saeko, I just remembered
something very important.
Pay up the mokkori you owe me!
What the?
I'm going to hang up! I'm busy!
You want information on a certain attorney?
That's going to cost you.
That'll be three mokkori.
Three?! One! One!
No, three.
One!
Three!
Then let's take the middle and say two.
Very well, we have a deal.
And? What's the attorney's name?
Mei Asaoka?
All right, Ryo. I think I can give you
a report tomorrow.
Mei Asaoka...
Yes! Stage six clear!
All right, I'm on a roll!
Damn tough bastard!
Take this, and this, and this!
Bastard! How about this?!
All right! Lucky!
Oh, sorry, was it too loud?
No...
Hey, want to try it a little?
No, I can't...
Oh, come on, just a little.
Here, front row seating!
Go ahead.
I just...
Come on. There, it's starting.
Oh, no way!
I... have work to do.
Amusement park on a weekday, not too bad,
don't you think, Mei?
Well, yes.
Hey, Ryo, what's the big idea?
Suddenly bringing her to
an amusement park...
Never mind, never mind. Let's play
until we drop today.
Man, she's a target. What is he thinking?
Here we go!
Hello.
Okay, one coming up.
Ever since I was little, I always
wanted to eat cotton candy
without worrying about people
watching for once.
Well, I just thought that you might
like cotton candy and...
Mister, three, okay? Three.
Kaori, hold this for me.
Oh, hey! Where are you going, Ryo?
Toilet! Toilet!
Right on time.
Noriyuki Ikeda, President of Ikeda
Construction Company.
He got involved in the redevelopment
of the city,
and using that position, he set about
buying up prime property.
He appears to be making a huge profit.
It seems he's trying to get into politics
by using that money now.
Just the other day, he went to court
over whether he could build a condominium
on land that the government sold.
And the person who defended him
on that occasion was...
Mei Asaoka?
Well, that's about it on the surface,
but it seems he's doing a lot of
other things on the sly.
And...
Here, it's Ikeda's address.
He's got a huge mansion in Izu.
Thank you.
But you sure are being nice this time, Saeko.
Really? Well, it is two mokkori's
worth after all.
I wonder what's taking Mr. Saeba so long?
No kidding, what a long trip to the bathroom.
But it's been really fun today.
I haven't played around like this
in a long time.
Me too! Well, I have a ton of
free time though.
Watching you work with Mr. Saeba
makes me sort of envious.
You're kidding, right?
I envy you. You can work openly in
the court system as a lawyer.
Do you think so?
The court is where people's greed
and egos are laid bare.
In order to survive in there,
everyone wears a mask to hide
their wavering emotions.
Mask?
My mask is this fake pair of glasses.
I wear these and always maintain
my bold front.
Miss Mei...
Hey, over here, over here!
Hello!
Oh, don't mind us. Go on and
play with the kids.
Stop it! What is this?! It's an anesthetic!
Kaori, wake up! Kaori!
Ryo! Miss Mei...
I know. Can you stand?
Yeah, I'm okay.
All right, let's go after them!
Looks like you're awake.
I'm glad you look well.
This wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't betrayed me.
Mr. Ikeda! So, you're the one
who's behind all of this!
What in the world did I do?!
Still playing dumb?
Oh well, take your time and
think about it here.
My, what tight security.
There!
Bye-bye! Do well!
What's that?!
Where the heck did that come from?!
What the?!
Looks like it's started.
Yo, how've you been?
Mr. Saeba, how did...
Hold on, no time to explain now.
Let's get out of here.
Mr. Saeba, you've committed breaking
and entering and assault.
You can't fight my enemies
with the statute books.
There's something more important than
words between a man and a woman.
That's feelings.
That's as far as you go, Mr. Bodyguard.
It looks like all you can do is
rub me the wrong way.
What's that guy talking about?
I have no idea.
Mei, this is goodbye for us too.
I hope we can be better friends
when you're reborn.
What's with him? Let's go!
This just might be the City Hunter's
greatest crisis.
Mr. Saeba!
Looks like we're in a bad fix.
Mr. Saeba...
Just kidding!
See you later, alligator! In a while, crocodile!
There's more where that came from!
Yes?
This is where your unseasonable
fireworks show ends.
Ryo!
Hey!
Stay away!
He's dodging the bullets!
Monster!
Your game is up.
Now...
What?!
Hi, Ryo. Good work.
Saeko!
You used me again, didn't you?!
Oh, but you're the one who
used my information.
I was only continuing my investigation
to gain evidence
in support of the flow of money recorded
in Ikeda's notebook.
That notebook...
Yes, it's the notebook you brought
to us as a lost item.
What?!
I just didn't know anything about it,
and since it was left behind,
I took it to the police.
I see! That's what Mr. Ikeda was looking for!
You know...
Thank you, Ryo.
Thanks to your rampage, we have
on him kidnapping,
illegal possession of a firearm, etc.
We have plenty of perfectly good charges
to bring against him now!
Mr. Saeba, from now on, I'll take my mask off
and go back to being truer to myself.
Good, but you have one other mask
you should remove.
The mask of love between a
man and a woman.
I wonder if this counts as an
extenuating circumstance?
One shot for the guilty!
Why is it that you can't dodge hammers?
Ryo doesn't get it either!
Mou kuchibeni kaete mo tokimekanai no yo
Yume no iro ni wa toui kara
Hi no tama no you na asahi o mini iku tabi e
Moshi anata mo sasoetara
Hane no you ni maiagaruwa sora e
Atsuku naretara sore de ii
Kono mune ni kitto mienai hi ga noboru
Ookina mono o mitsumetai
Chiiisana tsuyogari mo hadashi no mama
Nigete yuku yo
I'm living the sweet newlywed life with
Kanako, so don't bother me.
What?! You got married?!
When in the world?!
Just kidding! She's a super rich girl,
so she's got a lot of suitors
after her money.
Ryo got there first!
That's the act I'm performing.
Don't misunderstand. It's a
perfectly good job!
Oh my, I mistook it for a serious marriage.
City Hunter 3:
"Even Kaori's Pissed!
Ryo & a Young Lady
~Pinch Hitter Marriage Story~"
I'll get married if you don't watch.