Step on the gas
Soaring too high
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
Frustration comes knocking on my door
Wolves that can't run
Wander around, clawing at the darkness
The last time I saw you
Was in the dusty crowds
Your accusing gaze
Left an ache in my back as I walked away
The roadway has been blocked by fog
Even now, I'm still looking for the answer
In the clueless night sky
The horizon stretches out
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, a sky
without constellations
Wow, wow, wow, a path
without common sense
Wow, wow, wow, seeking only kindness
Wow, wow, wow, facing loneliness
Wow, wow, wow, I don't need you like that
Miss Aiko Kamimura runs a
detective agency, right?
What kind of job does she want us to do?
She says she wants to learn
how to use a gun.
Is the job she accepted that dangerous?
She's looking for a lost dog.
Oh, man! Why does she need a gun
for a job like that?
Apparently, there are some guys
following her around.
But that was Miss Aiko's uncle,
who's worried about her, right?
No, this time, her uncle was
the one that got attacked.
Then...
Dangerous Detective Game!
A Python for the Lady
(Part Two)
The Kamimura Detective Agency is in
such a wonderful environment!
I can peek all I want! Watch all I want!
Divine Retribution
Kamimura Detective Agency
Wall-creep exterminated.
Say, Aiko, I'm not saying this because
I'm afraid for myself.
A leg or two is nothing if it's for you.
Rather, I can't help but worry about
you, working as a detective.
I can't let you go through what I am!
Uncle, you care for me that much, even
after what I put you through?
Of course. Now that my younger brother
has passed away,
I think of you as my own child, since
I don't have any of my own.
I can't make my kind uncle suffer
any more than he already has.
All because of my silly, spoiled ways...
Uncle, I'll quit!
I wonder what it could be? Hello?
Yes? Oh, Mr. Saeba?
You found the dog?!
Uncle, he said he's already brought
the dog to the office.
He's called the owner and they're coming
to pick him up tomorrow.
I'm so glad. Now that the dog's been found,
there's no reason for you to be
targeted anymore!
But...
I have to hurry. Take care!
I'll come again tomorrow.
Ai!
Kamimura Detective Agency
Just a little bit further...
The dog will be handed over
to the owner tomorrow.
Tonight's my only chance.
Damn it!
Welcome.
I'm amazed that you could climb this far
with a broken leg, Uncle.
You!
What?! The dog hasn't been found yet?!
You tricked me!
We're even. You tricked us about your
broken leg too. Remember?
I found this in the bushes outside.
Uncle, why did you do this?
I've got other evidence too.
Do you want me to tell her?
That's right. I did it.
I tore down the posters and hindered
the search for the dog.
I faked getting hit by the car too, but...
But I did it all to make my dear Aiko
quit such dangerous work.
That's why... That's why I put on
this monkey show and...
Please don't cry. I was wrong.
I didn't realize how much you cared for me,
and I acted so spoiled.
I'm sorry.
Good! Then you'll quit being a detective?
Now that that's decided, let's hurry
and dispose of this office.
That's a good idea!
Then you can build a big hotel here,
right, Uncle?
That's right! I own the buildings on
both sides of this place too.
If I can take this land and turn it all
into one luxurious hotel,
then I can make a lot more money...
How did you know about that?
I heard that you were in the
real estate business.
So, I looked into things a bit.
Uncle! I can't believe this!
You were going to turn Father's
precious agency into a hotel?!
Yes, but...
But it's true that I care about you too.
Please believe me, Aiko.
Well, why don't you forgive
him already, Aiko?
But I do think you went a little too far with
phone threats and things like that,
just to make her quit being a detective.
Wait a minute, what are you talking about?
I don't know anything about cars or
threatening phone calls!
Aiko, you're being targeted
by someone after all!
Quit this dangerous search for the dog!
You're not fit to be a detective!
Please, enough is enough!
You're just lying again!
I can't trust you anymore!
You won't stop at anything to
build that hotel, will you?
Aiko!
Go home! I don't want to
talk to you anymore!
I don't think he was necessarily lying.
But then, who? Why would anyone
interfere with a search for a dog?
It means that there's someone
who wants to get their hands on the dog
before Ai or the owners.
Anyway, you didn't drag me way out here
for nothing, right?
Oh, that's right. When I went to the
station this morning,
there was a job for us on the message board.
What?! You're going to make me
do two jobs at once?!
Meanie! Demon! Miser! Skinflint!
Never mind! Just take a good look
at the client's name.
I will be waiting on the roof
of the Kamimura Building.
Koichiro Kamimura
I will be waiting on the roof
of the Kamimura Building.
Koichiro Kamimura
This is Ai's uncle.
I will be waiting on the roof
of the Kamimura Building.
Koichiro Kamimura
That's right.
I will be waiting on the roof
of the Kamimura Building.
Koichiro Kamimura
Come to think of it, he doesn't know
that you're the City Hunter.
What?! You're City Hunter?!
Well, I'm not surprised that
you don't believe it.
Anyway, you probably don't like me,
so I'll be going.
Wait!
Please protect Aiko.
There really is someone after her.
Please, I'm begging you.
She won't believe anything I say anymore.
This is the best I can do for her now.
I'm begging you! Please protect Aiko!
If that's the job, then you don't
need to hire me, Mister.
I've already begun to guard Aiko
on my own discretion.
Oh, and one more thing.
I haven't helped in her search
for the dog so far,
and I won't help her from now on either.
After all, that's a bet that's just
between you and Aiko.
That man...
I see. My uncle did that?
But Mr. Saeba, I don't need you to guard me.
Because accepting it would mean
accepting help in my search.
I want to win the bet that I made
with my uncle fairly.
But that's dangerous.
I see. Then good luck on your own.
Ryo!
But instead, take this with you
in case of an emergency.
Here!
What is this?
A charm to protect you from evil.
Open it when you think you're done for.
It should come in handy.
Okay!
Really, thank you very much.
Well, I should get back to
searching for the dog.
Wish me luck!
How admirable.
I feel bad for her uncle,
but seeing her like that makes me
want to help her.
By the way, how did it go?
It was such a pain in the butt!
After all, I sent that poster to all the veterinary
clinics in the city by express mail.
Let's see.
Here, the receipt for making the
copies and mailing them.
What?! This much?!
Hello, Kamimura Detective Agency.
What?! The dog is over there?!
Sasaki Veterinary Clinic
Yes, I took in an injured dog
about a week ago.
Yes, I was trying to find his owner
and I saw this poster.
All right!
Oh, I'm so sorry. I'll come to pick
him up right away. Okay!
As you requested, I didn't
mention you, Mr. Saeba.
Thank you, Doctor. I've got
my reasons, you see.
You've sure caused a lot of trouble.
But still...
What a stupid looking dog.
What's scary is that he looks even
stupider than this drawing.
It'll be great to get him off my hands too.
He goes around prying open the
cages of my female patients.
He's such a mokkori dog.
That hits a little too close to home.
By the way, this dog's injury...
You think that it might be a gunshot wound?
Yes, but it's only a scratch, so
it's hard to say for sure.
She sure left looking happy.
You think she found the dog?
If so, we've got no choice.
All we care about is getting that dog.
Sasaki Veterinary Clinic
Thank you very much, Doctor.
Not at all, I hope he gets better soon.
I'm glad that I finally found him, but...
What's with this dog? I don't think
he just likes female dogs.
Good grief, at this rate, it's
just like being with him.
Oh, Ryo, I found it.
Exactly one week ago,
three men robbed a branch of
the Kitahara Bank.
That same night, they got into a fight
and weapons were fired.
They say that one of them
is in critical condition.
All right, that's it.
What's wrong?
Looks like we've finally found him.
Well, I guess it's okay if we think of it
as you having saved us the trouble.
Please let me go. Who are you?!
We've got business with that dog!
You're coming with us too, Lady!
All you have to do is come quietly with us.
Owowow! My leg! My leg!
Damn! After them!
Who are those people? They have guns!
I see. They're the ones who were
interfering with my search!
Aiko!
Damn it! Where'd they go?!
They're quick little bastards!
Do Not Enter
There they are.
I'm sure we've cornered them.
There's nowhere else that
they could be hiding.
Hey! Hiding's useless! Come on out!
What should I do? At this rate,
they'll eventually find us.
I know! I have the charm that
Mr. Saeba gave me!
This must be the kind of situation
I should open it in.
Contains Brandy
Whisky Bon-Bon
What is this?
What's this mean?
Am I supposed to eat this to
calm down or something?!
There you are. Come on out!
I don't care what happens anymore!
All right, if you won't come out,
we're coming to get you!
We'll drag you out of there!
Shut yer frickin' mouths!
Damn!
That Saeba bastard gave me
only one whisky bon-bon!
What a cheap bastard!
Hey, you sissies!
If you've got some, you'd better
hand 'em over, or else!
Hey, what's with that girl?
It looks like she's drunk.
Her eyes look dimmed. Is she
really the same girl?
What're you blitherin' about?!
Huwwy up and hand over
the whisky bon-bons!
Don't mess with us! Who cares
about whisky bon-bons!
You'd better hand over the dog fast!
What d'you say?!
You'd wather give it to the dog than to me?!
You won't get away with that!
I fell down too!
Hey, you okay?
Damn it, that little bitch.
What?!
Hey, don't move.
I might not look it, but I'm a sharpshooter.
A sharpshooter?
You couldn't hit anything wobbling
around like that!
All wight, then I'll show ya what I can do.
In other words, I'll aim at the
steel ceiling beam and...
I have a feeling that I might be wasting
a great deal of my time.
Hey, mutt, quit scurrying around.
You'll get into trouble.
That's impossible!
How 'bout it? It's called the
Wicochet Two Stage Shot!
Next, I'll aim at your gun...
Don't get cocky! That was luck!
You won't make it again!
Take that!
Here's an extra one.
This can't be happening...
How 'bout it? Give up now?
After all, I'm the invincible woman detective!
Damn!
That bitch, messing with us...
Never mind, just stay asleep a while longer.
But that's stwange. I only shot twice,
but the gunshots...
Oh, well!
Bank robbers? Those men
were bank robbers?!
Yes, the third member betrayed them
and tried to keep the money for himself.
He hid the key to the safe on a dog
that happened to wander by.
They were looking for the dog,
using that wound as a clue.
So, they thought it'd get complicated
if Ai found him first.
I can't believe it.
How did I beat such people by myself?
I don't remember anything.
Nana!
Dummy, where've you been?!
Oh, I'm so glad!
Mr. Saeba, I think I sort of know
how my father used to feel.
Why my father worked so hard as
an unprofitable detective.
Why my father's eyes used to sparkle so.
There's one other thing that you've gained.
You now have the same sparkling eyes
that your father had.
Mr. Saeba...
Wow!
You sure you guys aren't actually brothers?!
Your behavioral patterns are
exactly the same!
Kamimura Detective Agency
You're going to quit being a detective?
Why, Aiko? You won our bet.
No, I was able to solve the case because
I had Mr. Saeba's help.
Miss Aiko...
What are you saying? You solved
this on your own.
I can tell.
I'm sure that Mr. Saeba was
behind the scenes
helping me find the dog and
beating the robbers.
Then this office...
But that doesn't mean I'll let you
turn it into a hotel, Uncle!
Oh, I've given up on that already,
ever since you got mad at me.
Anyway, I know now I don't have
what it takes to be a detective.
But I could be an assistant.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Mr. Saeba, please make me your assistant!
Please! Forever, if possible!
Wait a minute, Aiko.
Aiko!
Then how about making this place into
an office for the two of you?
Uncle!
Hey, now!
Saeba, I like you.
Please take care of Aiko, and also...
See? Take a look at this diagram.
This way, my hotel will be big and the
detective office will still stand.
So, what do you think?
Don't you think you could peek into
the hotel windows easily?
Yeah! And maybe holes in the ceilings!
Super Big
Oh, wait! How about a connecting
corridor instead?
Super Big
Right? That's a much more convenient,
much better idea!
Super Big
Changing the color of my lipstick
doesn't excite me anymore
Because its color is far from that of dreams
A journey to see a sunrise
like a ball of fire
If I could invite you too
I would take to the sky like a feather
If I can become passionate,
that's all I want
An invisible sun will surely rise in my heart
I want to gaze upon something grand
Even my bit of courage goes barefoot
And runs away
Miki's going to marry the Samonji family boy.
Talk about the lap of luxury!
There's no way Umibozu will
allow that to happen!
He said, "It's got nothing to do with me."
But that can't be!
This might be my chance to make Miki mine!
All right, I'm going to go save her!
Hold on a minute! Oh, men!
None of you understand how a woman feels!
City Hunter 3:
"Stubborn Umibozu!
Tale of the Jealous Kitten"
I'll make you mine, if you don't watch!