Step on the gas
Soaring too high
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
Frustration comes knocking on my door
Wolves that can't run
Wander around, clawing at the darkness
The last time I saw you
Was in the dusty crowds
Your accusing gaze
Left an ache in my back as I walked away
The roadway has been blocked by fog
Even now, I'm still looking for the answer
In the clueless night sky
The horizon stretches out
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, a sky
without constellations
Wow, wow, wow, a path
without common sense
Wow, wow, wow, seeking only kindness
Wow, wow, wow, facing loneliness
Wow, wow, wow, I don't need you like that
I could never wear such a bold, high-leg
suit in front of people.
But you just happen to be in front
of another person.
It isn't fair of you to hide
such a splendid figure.
You have a trim, streamlined body.
It's like high-leg swimsuits
were made just for you.
Well...
I'm no one to be suspicious of.
I came here to escape the din of the world
and find a moment of peace...
What?!
I tried a suave routine, unlike my usual
approach, but it didn't work either!
Ryo's going to be depressed now!
Love is Diving!
When a Beauty Puts On a Swimsuit
What are you doing?! Please let me go!
Come with us for a bit.
Who's there?!
Pick-up lines sure have become
extreme these days.
Using force to sweet-talk a girl?
You making fun of us?!
Don't mess with us!
Bastard!
Just you remember this!
Jeez, isn't there anything else
they could've said?
You aren't hurt, are you?
Well, thank you very much.
Oh, hey...
I'm sorry!
Oh, why?
Saeko!
What?! Ryo?!
Oh, my, I'm sorry. I couldn't
stop my momentum.
Why are you here?
Sorry, but I don't have time to explain. Later!
What? Why? What's going on?
Ryo, how late are you going to stay in bed?!
It's already lunchtime!
There's a client here, so make
yourself presentable.
Ryo, this is our client, Miss Ayano.
Woo-hoo, the client's a girl!
You are...
Have we met somewhere?
Well, thank you very much for last night.
I didn't recognize you since your
hair's different from last night.
You two know each other?
It's Miss Mokkori-High-Leg that
I met at the hotel pool!
What's with this change in attitude?
A female client?
Saeba Firm's finances won't allow us
to pick and choose clients.
So, you're a researcher.
Yes...
I work aboard Professor Jean Louis
Thoreau's underwater research vessel.
Jean Louis?
He's the Frenchman famous for
his production
of underwater documentary films, right?
After we completed our research
of the Hawaiian Islands,
the research vessel was raided
while we were at anchor.
The culprit who raided the research vessel
did it in search of something he
couldn't find in Hawaii.
That can't be possible. We only did
some fundamental research.
Say, Miss Ayano, we're about to have lunch.
Would you like to join us?
Oh, no, I have work to do, so
I'll be going back now.
Well, in any case, leave it all up to me!
Relax as if you were on a big ship!
I just hope it isn't a pirate ship.
The Laetitia, this is it.
Hey, Mister, do you know where Ayano is?
Mister?
You must be that unique detective
that Ayano was talking about.
Oh? How did you know about me?
Could it be that you're...
I am Jean Louis Thoreau.
Nice to meet you! I'm his partner,
Kaori Makimura.
You are?
To think that a beautiful lady like you
is a detective's partner.
Kaori is...
Beautiful?
Looks like Ayano has come back just in time.
Mr. Saeba!
Darn, I guess she's not wearing her
high-leg swimsuit today.
Ayano doesn't own any high-leg swimsuits.
Wow, you look used to doing this.
Of course, it's part of my job.
The wetsuit isn't bad either!
Usually this is about when Kaori's
hammer comes flying.
Exactly!
There are many French dishes
that use seafood as well.
I see.
Jean Louis has a quick hand
when it comes to women,
so you'll lose Miss Kaori if you
don't guard her well.
That's perfectly fine with me.
I'd love nothing better than for them
to take nitro-girls like her
and sink them in the Japan Deep
or something.
Now, I'm not going to lose either. Mokkori!
I'm sorry!
Noisy bastard.
Are you worried about Monsieur Saeba?
Me? No way!
The one I'm worried about is Miss Ayano.
I'm worried that she might fall prey
to Ryo's poisonous bite.
Her lover is the ocean.
She doesn't know how to love
anything other than that.
That's why her defensive instincts
keep men away at such times.
I'm so stupid.
I'm sorry for panicking over
such a trivial thing.
I think you're overdoing it.
What am I, an invalid who can't even walk?
But you know, if something like this always
shocks you, you'll never fall in love.
I've always been like that.
Every time a chance comes my way,
I become afraid at the enormousness
of it and run away.
Mr. Saeba...
You went to the trouble of buying
a fashionable swimsuit,
so don't be shy and learn to
wear it boldly in public.
I don't have the courage to
wear it in public, so...
You must have seen many mystical sights,
diving in the Seven Seas.
But something even more miraculous
happens between a man and a woman.
Mr. Saeba...
And in that crucial moment, work up your
courage and take one more step forward.
Work up my courage and
take one more step...
That's right.
Be brave.
Really! What a troublesome bastard!
You did something weird again when
no one was looking, didn't you?
You idiot!
Miss Kaori, Mr. Saeba didn't do...
I'm sorry you had to see that.
Even though you've hired him
as a bodyguard,
you can't let your guard down
around that man.
That was true in the beginning,
but just now...
I felt like I learned something very important.
Is that so?
But I know what you're really thinking.
Just one more step to mokkori.
Oh, here's the marine chart drafting
graphics system
that we've been waiting on for so long.
Merci! We've been expecting you!
Now we can do more detailed research
than we could before.
This looks rather light.
Hey, is this really what I ordered?
Are you not satisfied with this?
Who are you men?!
Mr. Thoreau!
Don't move!
Do not lay a hand on this mademoiselle!
She has nothing to do with this!
At this rate, our positions will be reversed.
Where's the other girl?!
Yo, we meet again.
I almost didn't recognize you guys
dressed the way you are.
You're the guy from...
Damn it! Kill him!
Mr. Thoreau!
I once fought in the resistance.
I'm capable of protecting a beauty.
This is bad. Stay here and don't move!
Mr. Saeba!
What a bastard!
Persistent bunch.
What could they be after?
Why? Why me?
Ayano, Saeba is a pro.
He will fully protect us until we leave
port the day after tomorrow.
Let's put our trust in him.
Until we leave port the day after tomorrow...
The day after tomorrow, I'll say
goodbye to Mr. Saeba.
The real graphics system is finally here!
Miss Kaori, would you connect
the cables over there?
Okay, got it.
But which one could it be?
Now, the cables over there.
Okay, leave it up to me.
And now, the main cable...
All right! It's on!
Thank you, Miss Kaori.
Now, we can set out to research the ocean.
Well, Mr. Thoreau?
You travel all over the world with
Miss Ayano, just the two of you.
Why don't you have any interest in her?
In Ayano?
She is a partner in my work.
Besides, she hasn't become a
full-fledged woman yet.
Her feminine charms still have
a long way to go.
Really? She's very beautiful and
her sweet personality...
The way you think of others...
I think Japanese women are wonderful.
But...
Say! Speaking of Ayano, I haven't
seen her around today.
Ayano's been shut up in
her room since noon.
She seemed to be turning her
closet upside down.
If you're going to be a bodyguard, you
should know where everyone is!
Well, I'd like to travel the Seven Seas
in my old age too,
but with an assistant like Ayano. Not like her.
Old age?
When I was your age,
there were beauties at every port in the world
who were far more beautiful than Ayano!
Wow!
Impressive!
Mr. Saeba...
Ayano, that dress...
Yes, since we'll be departing
Japan tomorrow,
I wanted to show my gratitude to Mr. Saeba
for being our bodyguard.
I'd like to invite him to dinner at a
restaurant on a ship just ahead.
My, my.
Well, Mr. Saeba, will you
accept my invitation?
Of course, I'll be happy to accept.
That bastard! He gets to have all the fun!
I'll never accept a female client again!
Mademoiselle Kaori,
I would like to cook some seafood
for you, aboard this vessel.
Will you accept?
Yes! Gladly!
To the future success of the Laetitia.
And to your own new journey.
Looks like she's safe so far.
The question is when will Ryo
reveal his true nature.
It'll be fine.
To think that Ayano invited a man to dinner...
It's nothing to a normal girl, but for her,
it's great progress.
Well, let's leave Ayano to him.
Please try my seafood cooking.
Wow, it looks delicious!
Well, thank you for the food!
A date with a beauty sure gets
the appetite going.
You really seem to enjoy your meals.
Really? Then maybe I'll order
just one more dish.
Yes, please help yourself.
What will I order next?
You had that necklace on at
the pool too, didn't you?
Yes, it's my favorite.
And since I was wearing it
when I first met you...
Shoot! They got there first!
Mr. Saeba!
It's those guys again!
All right! Here we go!
Saeko!
Bastard!
It's all he can do to keep up.
As long as she's with me,
he can't shoot freely.
Mr. Saeba...
Oh, no! Get away!
Ayano!
Ryo! Leave this up to me!
You save Miss Ayano!
Damn it! Take this!
I missed!
Kaori, reload! Reload!
Right!
Mr. Saeba...
Did you see that?!
It takes more than one, two, three, or
four choppers to mess with me!
Well, I guess we'll leave it at that.
Now, how's Ryo doing?
Hey, looks like you're awake.
Mr. Saeba, you were kissing me...
Oh, no, you were unconscious,
so I was performing mouth-to-mouth
resuscitation, you see?
You shameless bastard!
Are you going to tarnish even the
romanticism of the ocean?!
Divine retribution!
You got it all wrong!
They were after the necklace
Miss Ayano is wearing?
Where did you get this?
When we were researching
the Hawaiian Islands,
I accidentally found it in a shipwreck.
You just happened to find something
belonging to an assassinated spy.
The week before you went diving,
a spy stole secrets from an
American bio-company
and his yacht was blown up.
Then, the people who came after her are...
An international criminal organization:
Black Widow.
Look!
It gives me the shivers to think
that Black Widow might have gotten
hold of such information.
So, you were following them all this time and
mistook me for one of them at the hotel.
But I never knew that you were
involved in all of this.
You were watching when they came in
disguised as workers
and attacked the Laetitia.
Oh, you knew that?
It was fun, Mademoiselle Kaori.
Thank you, Mr. Saeba.
Monsieur Saeba, if it were possible,
I'd have liked to trade assistants.
Actually, I was sort of thinking
the same thing.
Ryo!
Papa! How could you?!
I've always told you not to call me that!
Papa?!
I was once known as the
Don Juan of the sea!
I'll never be popular with the women
if it gets to be known that I have
such an old daughter!
I guess it's safe if they're family.
The mystery's finally solved.
Goodbye! Take care!
Goodbye!
Mr. Saeba was such a wonderful person,
and Miss Kaori too.
They were a very refreshing pair.
Next time we come to Japan,
I will make Miss Kaori mine.
Ayano, go capture Monsieur Saeba's heart.
Papa!
There they go.
Say, Kaori?
You'd have been popular too if only
you'd been born in France!
What did you say?!
Stop right there!
Flying through the sunrise
Searching for the sunset
Changing the color of my lipstick
doesn't excite me anymore
Because its color is far from that of dreams
A journey to see a sunrise
like a ball of fire
If I could invite you too
I would take to the sky like a feather
If I can become passionate,
that's all I want
An invisible sun will surely rise in my heart
I want to gaze upon something grand
Even my bit of courage goes barefoot
And runs away
It's quite a feat to hire an assistant
when you don't have a job.
She pushed me into it. Hitomi just
adores detectives.
But that's no reason to make her
wear a miniskirt, Mr. Mokkori.
Actually, she's gotten involved in a case.
So, we should help her out, Kaori Sempai.
Sempai?!
You can count on me!
City Hunter 3:
"Who the Heck is Ryo?
Even the College Girl is Smitten
with the Thrill"
You'll be smitten if you don't watch.