Step on the gas
Soaring too high
Nemurenai gozen niji
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
Nemurenai gozen niji
Iradachi ga doa o tataku
Hashirenai ookamitachi
Yami ni tsume o tate samayotteru
Kimi o saigo ni mita no wa
Hokori no mau zattou no naka
Semeru you na manazashi ga
Tachisaru senaka ni itami nokoshita
Kiri ni tozasareta mootaauei
Ima demo kotae sagashiteru
Tegakari no nai yozora ni
Chiheisen ga yokotawaru
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, seiza no kieta sora
Wow, wow, wow, joushiki no nai michi
Wow, wow, wow, yasashisa tada motome
Wow, wow, wow, yowasa to mukai au
Wow, wow, wow, sonna kimi wa iranai
Looks like you stuck your nose
in too far, Mr. Detective.
You've got nowhere left to run now.
Give it up!
Do you think so?
You bastards think you can hit me?
What?! Finish him!
No way.
Looks like you underestimated me.
He's so cool!
You bastards think you can hit me?
Bang! Bang, bang!
Looks like you underestimated me.
Please! Just a little bit!
No means no!
I just want to examine it a little!
I won't fire it or anything!
You sure as hell won't!
Please! I just want to get one
good look at a real gun!
If you keep at it,
I'll arrest you on the charge of
hindering a public official!
Arrest me?! That's so cool!
Hey, try and arrest me!
Wow, real handcuffs! Lemme see!
Lemme see!
I don't wanna deal with her!
Who the Heck is Ryo?
Even the College Girl is
Smitten with the Thrill
Say, Miss?
Won't you keep me company for
a full course of mokkori?
I'm doing just fine, thank you.
Let's see, my next target will be...
Oh, shoot!
Oh, my, really?
You're so lucky.
Safe... If she finds me, she'll make me
pass out fliers again.
Kaori's walking with a man?!
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, must be my imagination.
Shall we go?
Where is she going?
The way he moves! That look in his eyes!
He's not just anybody!
If you go straight ahead about
three hundred meters,
there's a dark colored building
to your left. That's the one.
Thank you for your trouble.
You've been a great help.
You're welcome.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Giving directions...
I get it. I get it.
Mister, you're a detective, aren't you?
Yeah!
You scared me!
A mokkori gal!
May I help you?
Don't you need to keep tailing that person?
Is there anything that I can help with?
Who are you?
I'm Hitomi Takano, nineteen years of age.
I'm a college student!
A mokkori college student!
My name is Ryo Saeba. I've been
waiting for someone like you.
Please, let me be your assistant!
I just adore detectives!
I'll do anything! Please, Sensei!
Sensei?
All right, I understand.
I don't generally accept assistants,
but I'll make an exception and
take you on as one.
Wow! Thank you very much!
But the training will be tough!
Yes! I'll work hard, Sensei!
To become a detective, you must
first look the part.
I need to wear a skirt this short?
Mr. Saeba, I think miniskirts generally
hinder movement.
My dear Hitomi, that is an
amateur's way of thinking.
The work of a detective involves
a lot of danger.
And in general, the enemy is male.
And the male's weakness is a miniskirt!
What? I don't really understand.
Oh, I see! So this is how you beat
them up. Right, Sensei?
Very good.
Well, is this part of a detective's
costume too?
How strange. You only changed your clothes
and you already look like a
respectable detective.
Awesome!
Now I finally get to do detective work!
Not so fast! There's still the
intensive training left!
What? Intensive training?
Hello.
Welcome.
Has Ryo come by?
I haven't seen him today.
He ran away after all!
Is something wrong?
We were supposed to pass out
fliers this afternoon,
but when I looked around, I couldn't
find him anywhere.
That sounds just like Saeba.
Oh, thank you.
It isn't funny.
I'm always the one that gets stuck
with the hard work.
Where's Umibozu?
He went to a nearby bank
to exchange money.
Wow, I didn't know Umibozu did
things like that for you too.
You'd never know it by looking at him.
Welcome.
Hi!
Could it be? He's a bank robber!
Wait! No!
Someone! It's a bank robber!
Catch him!
No, I just came to exchange money...
No! He's my friend!
What?! He's not a bank robber?!
What'll I do?!
We've got no choice. Last resort plan!
Yes, Sir!
Run!
Damn you! I won't forget this, Ryo!
Sensei, I can't run any further!
What's this?
You'll never be a detective
if you tire so easily.
Physical strength is essential to a detective!
Yes, Sir.
He was with a girl in a miniskirt?!
At that rate, they're probably making out and
getting mokkori in the park right about now.
I'll never forgive that Mr. Mokkori!
I wonder if Saeba will survive?
He brought this down on himself.
Now, intensive training number one!
Let's try sit-ups.
Sensei, you don't have any ulterior
motives to peek, do you?
Of course not! I'll sit with
my back to you, okay?
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
The mokkori's right behind me,
but I'm at a bad angle!
Seven...
The mokkori's right behind me,
but I'm at a bad angle!
Seven...
I can't stand it anymore!
Eight...
Nine...
Woo-hoo!
Are you okay, Sensei?
Your kicking power's not bad.
Intensive training number two!
Mr. Saeba, is it time yet?!
You can do it! Thirty seconds to go!
Those mokkori thighs are very
nice at close range.
Oh, I can't hold on anymore!
If it's too hard, I'll hold you up.
What're you doing, you idiot?!
Scary!
That's it!
Oh, my.
It hurts, but I'm happy.
We don't have any work! You think you
can keep two assistants?!
Well? What do you have to say
for yourself, Ryo?!
Ow, ow, I'm against violence!
It hurts! It hurts! Let go!
Please stop, Sempai!
Sempai?
It hurts! It hurts! Let go!
I'm to blame.
I just adore detectives, so I pushed
Mr. Saeba to let me...
I don't care if I'm an assistant or not,
just please let me make myself useful!
Please, Sempai!
Well... Sempai, you say...
What should I do?
Well, I guess you can stay as an apprentice.
Wow! A real gun!
Quick bastard.
Ryo, who was it meant for?
What?! I get to stay here?!
Right!
Until we know who the culprit is,
we can't let you be by yourself.
And if you're here, I can
protect you properly.
You're going to protect me?
That's right,
because an unexpected evil
might come after you.
Wow, this is so exciting!
Hello.
Oh, welcome, Saeko.
Doing some cleaning?
Ryo's out right now.
I was passing close to here,
so I just dropped by.
Is Ryo out working?
Yeah, sort of.
Did something happen?
It's nothing big, but just now, at the park...
How can it be this much for just
toiletries and clothing?
Well, this conflict might be
prolonged, you know?
I brought ten days' worth of clothing.
Ten days' worth?!
Wait, that means there are ten days'
worth of underwear!
Counting both top and bottom,
there are twenty articles of college girl
underwear in here!
That one has my textbooks and pillow in it.
Bro, let's get this over with already.
No, let's not.
It might get troublesome with
that guy around.
Let's watch how things go for a bit longer.
This is called a Mini Cooper, right?
Yeah, how did you know?
I like cute cars.
The other day, I bought a used Subaru,
but I got into an accident.
What's wrong? Are you worried?
Who are you really, Mr. Saeba?
There's no way a normal detective
would have a gun.
But then, you don't look like a
police detective either.
Maybe I'm a killer for hire.
Yes, you have that dangerous
scent about you.
Do you not like a dangerous scent?
No way! I love it!
And which park is this?
It's the park near Mitsuboshi Bank. Why?
Oh, just wondering.
Well, I think I'll be going home now.
Bye, say hi to Ryo for me.
Okay, bye.
I wonder what she came here for?
Say, is there anything I can do to help?
Don't worry about it.
Oh, could you go get Ryo soon?
I think he's in the basement.
Okay!
That serious expression isn't like the
Mr. Saeba I've known so far.
Hitomi, welcome!
It's his usual expression.
Here.
It's heavy. It really feels solid.
You want to try firing it?
What?! May I?!
All right!
It's saved my life many times over.
But...
But?
I've hurt just as many people with it.
That is the way of guns.
I don't think I can fire it.
Because I don't think I can bear
the weight of the real thing.
I see.
Who's there? Ryo?
Who are you people?!
You stay here!
What?! Mr. Saeba!
Now, stay quiet!
I'll save Miss Kaori!
Mr. Saeba, get in!
Can you do this?
You can count on me!
I did it again.
Now, look here...
We were this close to saving her!
If something happens to Miss Kaori,
it'll be my fault!
There's no need to worry about that.
The one they're after isn't Kaori.
If they were after Kaori from the beginning,
they would have killed her on the spot.
Then, the one they're after is...
You or me, it seems.
Did you see their faces?
It can't be!
Looks like you just remembered something.
But they want to kill me,
just for hitting them?
Hitting them?
Oh, no! I'm sorry!
Damn! Just go!
It was my fault, so I was going
to pay for the damages,
but they drove off in a hurry,
as if they were on the run.
One of the guys who kidnapped
Miss Kaori was the guy I hit.
Speak of the Devil.
That's right.
I want to trade your partner for the girl there.
Don't do anything funny if you
value your partner's life.
Yeah, got it.
The outside's set.
All right, then all we have to do
is lure them inside.
It's an old rule of thumb: Kill all witnesses.
Don't hold it against us.
We went to a lot of trouble to
get hold of a gun.
It'll be pointless if we don't see
a profit from it after all.
You didn't have to go wear Kaori's
battle getup, you know.
Wearing this makes me feel like I can
feel Kaori Sempai's courage.
Because Sempai was kidnapped
in place of me!
I don't really get the reasoning.
Miss Kaori!
Wait! Hitomi!
If we don't hurry up and get out
of here, we're barbeque!
Ryo!
There's just one way.
Hitomi, please. Do this for us.
Please take off your trousers.
Hey! Get serious!
It was a joke!
Did you bring this?
Yes, I brought it along with these clothes.
What is it?
Let's hurry up and get outta here.
What the?
Damn it.
Die!
Bastard!
Damn you!
Hi, Ryo. Long time no see.
Saeko!
This gun was actually stolen from the police.
I'm glad we recovered it before
the media got wind of it.
What's going on here, Saeko?
I heard that you'd been shot at in the park,
so, just to be safe, I checked
the markings of the bullet.
And it turned out that it matched
the stolen gun.
All we had was the getaway vehicle that
had been hit and abandoned,
so I was in a real bind without any
other clues to go on.
The vehicle that had been hit...
I see, so these guys are the perpetrators.
Exactly, and you know the rest.
Wow! Awesome!
Oh, how cool!
Perfect.
Please, would you tell me your name?
I'm Saeko Nogami from police headquarters.
Nice to meet you.
Well, I'm Hitomi Takano,
nineteen years of age.
I've always adored female police detectives!
Please, make me your assistant!
Ryo, are you here?
I've properly taught everything to Miss
Hitomi, so I'll leave the rest to you.
You didn't happen to teach her how to
manipulate men, did you?
Oh, my, I would never.
Then what did you...
Mr. Saeba...
Mokkori thighs!
First lesson in self-defense!
Second lesson!
Take that!
That's dangerous!
That's strange. I was sure
I had aimed to miss.
Flying through the sunrise
That's strange. I was sure
I had aimed to miss.
I guess I need more training.
I'd better work at that!
Searching for the sunset
Mou kuchibeni kaete mo tokimekanai no yo
Yume no iro ni wa toui kara
Hi no tama no you na asahi o mini iku tabi e
Moshi anata mo sasoetara
Hane no you ni maiagaruwa sora e
Atsuku naretara sore de ii
Kono mune ni kitto mienai hi ga noboru
Ookina mono o mitsumetai
Chiiisana tsuyogari mo hadashi no mama
Nigete yuku yo
Oh, rain, rain, come again. Kei will...
Head in the clouds, as always.
Well, the client is a mokkori
weather girl after all!
The ever more popular Miss
Kei Amamiya, right?
I, the greatest sunshine guy in Japan,
will blow away any man who
dares threaten her!
Would you blow away our debts too
while you're at it?
City Hunter 3:
"Love Forecast of Rain, Then Shine!
The Beautiful Newscaster's Umbrella of Love"
You'll get soaking wet if you don't watch.