Step on the gas
Soaring too high
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
Frustration comes knocking on my door
Wolves that can't run
Wander around, clawing at the darkness
The last time I saw you
Was in the dusty crowds
Your accusing gaze
Left an ache in my back as I walked away
The roadway has been blocked by fog
Even now, I'm still looking for the answer
In the clueless night sky
The horizon stretches out
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, a sky
without constellations
Wow, wow, wow, a path
without common sense
Wow, wow, wow, seeking only kindness
Wow, wow, wow, facing loneliness
Wow, wow, wow, I don't need you like that
Another boring day.
The low pressure that developed here
will progress east-northeast, and
will probably advance rapidly.
Weather in the Kantou Region will most
likely gradually go downhill.
Wow! Mokkori weather girl!
Now, we are in the square in front
of Shinjuku Station
Megumi Amamiya
Weather Report
Now, we are in the square in front
of Shinjuku Station
Megumi Amamiya
Weather Report
for our "Everyone's a Weather
Expert" segment.
Today, we'll see if the saying, "It will rain
when a cat washes its face," is true.
Now there's a scene I want
to show that octopus.
Even the chinchillas and the shorthairs
are doing whatever they want.
In other words, a cat's gestures
are not reliable.
This was Kei Amamiya, bringing you
the weather report.
Sorry for the wait, Ryo.
What?
Where'd he go?
Love Forecast of Rain, Then Shine!
The Beautiful Newscaster's Umbrella of Love
Here, Director.
Okay, I'll take care of the rest.
I'll be leaving now.
Good work!
Be careful!
Kei's going home!
Kei!
Miss Kei, please wait!
Miss Kei!
Miss Amamiya!
Kei!
Please sign this!
Doing well as usual. I feel light!
Please excuse me!
A woman with a sheen of sweat is beautiful.
I'm not in the entertainment business,
so I won't sign anything for you.
If it's a sign, I already got one.
The bold XYZ on TV.
Then you're Mr. Saeba?
Yes...
But to hear such cold words from your lips...
Could it be because a cold front is coming?
Cold front?
I, Ryo Saeba, study the relationship between
crime, women and weather.
Well, I suppose you could call it
weather sociology.
A Weather Reader for Even
the Most Amateur
Well, I suppose you could call it
weather sociology.
You're interested in the weather?
Then we have a common interest.
Right, and my accepting your job
is a blessing from Heaven.
No, it could even be divine fate.
I think I could easily talk to you.
Wow! In that case, the sooner the better.
Let's go somewhere we won't be
bothered and discuss the job.
Come on, come on.
Say, Mr. Saeba?
Yes?
The typical winter pressure
pattern is breaking up.
Why don't you have an umbrella with you?
But the weather's so nice.
Look, the barometer's dropping
lower and lower.
Barometer?
It measures pressure.
It's the best way to determine local weather.
Shoot! It wasn't written on the cheat sheet!
No, wait, I am a man of sunshine!
Has it ever rained when I was trying
to capture a beauty?!
Mr. Saeba, could it be that you know
nothing about the weather?
Don't underestimate me!
Weather forecasts started when the
Meteorological Agency
was established in Meiji 3!
It was established on June 1st
of the 8th year.
Right, and ever since Meiji 8,
the accuracy of the forecasts has not
improved much beyond eighty percent!
In other words, weather forecasts are
wrong twenty percent of the time.
Look at that clear sky!
What?
The story of Ryo's experience is that
eighty percent of forecasts come true.
Mr. Saeba, it seems you still have
a lot to learn about the weather.
If I give up now, the name of
Mokkori Ryo will be shamed.
Kei!
I never knew that umbrellas had such a use.
Mr. Saeba!
Wow, what electrifying legs.
Not again.
Here we go. Please come on in.
I'm so sorry that you had to
go through that for me.
Not at all, my job is to protect you
from things like that.
More importantly, it would be awful
if you caught a cold!
Take your clothes off!
What?! Oh, no, thank you.
I think they'll dry soon.
What are you hesitating for?!
It will be disastrous if you can't
appear on TV tomorrow!
Ryo?
What?! Kaori, you're here?!
Well, sorry for being here!
Here I was, wondering where you'd gone
without even eating, you bastard!
No! No! She's a client!
Client?
You're Miss Kei Amamiya! I'm sorry you
had to see that.
Kaori, hurry up and untie me.
Hello? Saeba Firm.
What? Television station?
Oh, yes, Miss Kei's here.
Please wait a moment.
For me?
Television stations know a lot. They learned
where you're staying.
Hello?
You still don't seem to get it.
Hiring a bodyguard won't do you any good.
I know everything.
If you continue to ignore my demands,
I can't guarantee your safety.
Hello? Who in the world are you?!
Why are you...
I've loved telling fortunes to predict
weather since I was little.
I'd roll a geta and predict whether
it would be rain or shine.
My feelings didn't change, even as
I grew into an adult.
That's why I went to work for a private
weather forecasting firm.
When I started reporting the
weather on television,
I introduced regional jinxes and folk-wisdom.
It was well received.
But one day, I got a threatening letter.
"Quit being a newscaster."
"Or else, strange things will begin to
happen around you."
Since then, a light fell on a staff
member during a briefing.
A pachinko ball hit a fan asking
for an autograph.
It's probably all because I won't
do as he demands,
but I love my work.
And that's why you hired us?
A rival colleague or someone envious
of your popularity...
Don't worry. Now that I'm your bodyguard,
you have no need to fear him anymore.
Oh, but instead, you'll teach inept
little me about the weather, okay?
Hey, don't take advantage of her situation!
How wonderful! You'll protect me,
and on top of it, I get to talk about
weather all day long!
Now that it's decided, you better not
go out again today.
I insist that you stay here tonight.
Okay! Thank you for having me!
Really?
Speaking of which, I hired you
because I saw this.
Yes!
The effort of passing out all those
fliers has finally paid off!
Is what's written here true?
Of course, it is.
I think I pass.
SAEBA FIRM
Count on us!!
We will guard your secrets
without fail!
Troubleshooting, bodyguard,
searching for people, etc...
30% off right now!
SAEBA FIRM
Count on us!!
We will guard your secrets
without fail!
Troubleshooting, bodyguard,
searching for people, etc...
30% off right now!
The thirty percent off right now part, right?
SAEBA FIRM
Count on us!!
We will guard your secrets
without fail!
Troubleshooting, bodyguard,
searching for people, etc...
30% off right now!
No, farther down.
I am the President.
Those with bust sizes 88 cm
or above get 100% off!
Ryo
I am the President.
Those with bust sizes 88 cm
or above get 100% off!
Ryo
"Those with bust sizes 88 cm or above
get a hundred percent off..."
I feel bad taking the hundred percent off.
Not at all! For you, I'll include
a special service too!
Special service?
Yup! Mokkori service!
You don't need to include such a service!
I don't need the mokkori service, so
thirty percent off will be fine. Yes!
Oh, why? Sniff...
Can't sleep, Kei?
Mr. Saeba...
I just can't settle down.
When I'm sad or worried about something,
I look at the night sky.
And it gives you a sense of peace.
Yes!
Just do something that won't
let me be at peace,
and you'll get the hundred percent
larger hammer.
The sky gently embraces all sorts of things,
like the sad things and the ugly things
about people.
And above all, it doesn't lie.
How's tomorrow's weather looking?
I won't know for sure without detailed data,
but the moon has a halo and the
breeze is slightly moist.
At times like these, I sometimes decide
by the luster of my hair.
Maybe it'll rain a little around
noon tomorrow too.
Really?
Even with so many stars out?
I guess you really like weather forecasting.
Yes!
In the city or the country, the
world's weather is my friend.
Tokyo Weather
Forecasting
The morning sun stings my eyes.
Ryo needs more sleep.
You have to study accurate data
in the morning
in order to do the weather
forecast at noon.
Really?
I thought only the Meteorological
Agency did things like this.
Even if it's only a couple minutes
of broadcast time,
it's an important thing that we can't
do without in everyday life,
Mr. Saeba, would you wait
around for a while?
Take your time. This place is full
of interesting things!
I'm glad. Now...
Mr. Saeba, please do not bother me.
Oh, did I mess up your concentration?
Then I'll stay quiet back here.
The weather is going downhill.
Please be careful.
Are you supposed to use keyboards like this?
On days like today, do not
forget your umbrella.
I don't think you're using the
umbrella right either.
Ryo can't hold back anymore!
This is the correct use of a hammer!
I'd forgotten.
What's that sound?!
It's time for exercise!
Wow! Could it be that storm of fans?!
I'm from Ueda Pro!
I'm from Suwa Agency!
I'm from Kobayashi Planning!
I've brought a good contract today!
Mr. Saeba, this way!
Right with you!
We won't let you escape today!
What the hell?!
Please do a recording debut with us!
No, please appear in our movie!
Looks like we underestimated her popularity.
Oh, boy!
Is every day this intense for you?
I'm used to it. There's too much
commotion at the office,
so I come here to analyze data and things.
I see.
I never knew the weather forecast
started in a place like this.
What?
She's so immersed in her work that
she doesn't even see me.
Watch out, Kei!
Get down!
That was...
"I've warned you many times before now,"
"but I won't hold back anymore."
"I have reached my limit."
"Announce your retirement
in today's broadcast,"
"or else I have no choice but to kill you."
Why?
The culprit has finally issued
a serious challenge.
It would be rude if we don't
take him seriously.
I'll need you to take some risks too.
Can you do it?
Miss, is it going to keep raining?
Well, a little longer.
But it'll clear up towards the afternoon.
Do you hate rain?
The northern and southern parts
of the Kantou Region,
as well as the northern Izu Islands,
will be going from rain with
a mix of sleet to shine.
Saitama, Kanagawa, Ibaraki,
and Gunma Prefectures
will probably have some clear skies
in the afternoon as well.
Now for "Everyone's a Weather Expert."
The weather is getting better,
but at times like this, please be
careful of car accidents.
According to the Kanagawa
Prefecture Police's data,
not only do accidents occur due to
slippery road conditions
when the air pressure is above ten millibars,
but drivers also have worse judgment.
On days like today, when the air
pressure changes so rapidly,
I feel like something scary might happen.
But tomorrow, we should have
clear weather all day.
I will see you all again tomorrow.
Okay, good!
Mr. Saeba, it's over.
Where did you go?
Mr. Saeba?
Looks like Mr. Bodyguard let his guard down
and went somewhere.
What are you doing?! Let me go!
Quit struggling!
Shut up! Do you see these?!
What's that?!
That can't be!
It's dynamite!
So, you're the one who's been
threatening me all this time?
That's right.
I'm the nice guy who went to all that
trouble just to warn you.
I warned you meticulously, over and over.
Is there a cameraman around?!
Cameraman?!
Yes, Sir, thanks for waiting.
You called for me?
You want me to tape you looking cool
and monopolizing Miss Kei?
Hey, you're pretty perceptive.
I've watched over Kei, ever since she
first appeared on television.
I'm nothing like the bodyguard that
hangs around her these days!
Well, don't get so worked up. You might
want to smile a little.
Like this? Or how about this?
You're just lacking a certain dignity.
Maybe if you stick out your
chest a little more.
How about this?
A little more.
Like this?
Just a little bit more.
Like this?!
Was that broadcast nationwide?
The dynamite you have is of no use
now that its fuse is all wet.
You're the bodyguard!
You underestimate me!
I've got plenty more dynamite!
Oh my, it's raining buckets.
Too bad! And now the criminal
has lost his trump card!
How dare you ridicule me?!
Don't mess with me!
If you do any more funny things to her,
you'll never get to see her
on television again.
Have mercy! I was wrong!
I won't go near her again!
Jeez, there sure are a lot of hopeless
guys out there lately.
Kaori, why are you here?
It's easy to find you when it's been
broadcasting all this time.
Man! The case is solved and the
sky's beginning to clear up.
It's beginning to clear up and what?
Oh, no! It's nothing important.
Mr. Saeba, thank you.
Now, I can continue to do weather
forecasts without any worries.
I'm glad for you, Kei.
Yes, it looks like the afternoon will be nice.
Say, Mr. Saeba?
Would you come with me to search
for rainbows after the rain?
Sure thing! I'll follow you wherever!
Ryo the pervert!
You are passing out fliers, a hundred
percent more than usual today!
But, Kaori!
Don't "but" me! Saeba Firm's motto is,
"Rain, then work."
Let me take a little break.
No!
Oh, Kei! Help me out here!
Flying through the sunrise
Searching for the sunset
Changing the color of my lipstick
doesn't excite me anymore
Because its color is far from that of dreams
A journey to see a sunrise
like a ball of fire
If I could invite you too
I would take to the sky like a feather
If I can become passionate,
that's all I want
An invisible sun will surely rise in my heart
I want to gaze upon something grand
Even my bit of courage goes barefoot
And runs away
Why did you accept a job to split up
a couple that eloped?!
Because if I bring Tsubaki back,
I get to be in the lap of luxury with
parent-authorized mokkori!
It's awful that the parents forced their
disagreement on the kids,
but you're awful too!
Then what am I supposed to do?
Hurry up and bring her back!
What? Then you don't mind if I take the job?
Well, I already used up the
money they paid us.
City Hunter 3:
"A Wedding Dress for Christmas (Part 1)"
You're awful if you don't watch.