Step on the gas
Soaring too high
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
Frustration comes knocking on my door
Wolves that can't run
Wander around, clawing at the darkness
The last time I saw you
Was in the dusty crowds
Your accusing gaze
Left an ache in my back as I walked away
The roadway has been blocked by fog
Even now, I'm still looking for the answer
In the clueless night sky
The horizon stretches out
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, a sky
without constellations
Wow, wow, wow, a path
without common sense
Wow, wow, wow, seeking only kindness
Wow, wow, wow, facing loneliness
Wow, wow, wow, I don't need you like that
Kazuhiko and Tsubaki love each other
so much that they eloped.
And we've been hired to make them split up?
That's terrible!
What in the world happened between the
Yamaoka and Umino families?
Who cares about that?
What's important is that Tsubaki's
father officially recognizes me,
and I'll be in the lap of luxury and mokkori!
Enough already, you mokkori monster!
But Tsubaki is so daring, don't you think?
She ran off with Kazuhiko from the party
at the Umino mansion!
There isn't time to be impressed.
There are suspicious people
following the couple.
What?
A Wedding Dress for Christmas
(Part 2)
Thank you, Sakurai. Take care.
Yes, you take care as well, Miss.
They've switched to a red, two-door Golf.
Roger.
We're following them.
There's something I want to ask you.
Step outside.
You think you have time for that?
What?
Mr. Saeba!
Tsubaki, where are we headed?
Yokohama.
I have reservations on a ship
bound for Europe.
Europe?
I have friends in Switzerland.
They have a big ranch on pastureland
in a green valley.
I don't think even Papa or the others
will follow us overseas.
Are you okay, Tsubaki?!
Yeah...
I never thought she'd go to such
lengths to split us up.
We must have really hit a nerve in Mother.
No, it could be Papa.
Let's not think about that anymore.
Even if it's only us, let's be
joined in such a way
that we do not leave any hatred
behind in this world.
That man...
We'll take care of you first! Go!
Die!
No way!
Impossible! What a bastard.
It's safe now, nothing to
worry about anymore.
Well, thank you very much.
Tsubaki! Hang on!
Hey, me too!
Oh, no...
I thought she was a shrew, but
I guess she's a girl after all.
Make sure you hold onto her tight
and don't let her go.
I will. I'll never let go of her again.
You should hide out at my place for a while.
Oh, but we're...
Nothing will ever be resolved if you
keep running away.
But...
The guys who came after you don't seem
to have been sent
by either the Yamaoka family
or the Umino family.
Mando Nakata
You failed?!
Yes, well...
Their bodyguard is actually
a rather remarkable guy
and he brought down a helicopter
with a gun in one shot.
Shut up!
I'm not paying you vast sums to hear
such ridiculous reports!
We know where those two are staying.
We'll definitely get them within
two or three days! Definitely!
That's enough! Report to me when
you've taken care of those two!
Yes, leave it to us!
Excuse us!
I won't stand for Yamaoka Shipping and
Umino Shipping joining forces!
It was because of the discord between them
that my Nakata Shipping was able
to grow to its current size
by taking advantage of their weaknesses.
No matter what happens, no matter
what I have to do,
I must keep those two from being married!
Mr. Saeba!
Did something happen to those two?!
They're safe. They're staying at my place.
I came tonight because I wanted
to ask you something.
What? Ask me, Sir?
What happened between the Yamaoka and
Umino families twenty-five years ago?
Watching the two of you
just makes me envious.
I wish I could have a life or death
love experience too.
You have someone you care
for too, don't you?
No, I don't. If I did, right now, I'd be...
Everyone has someone whose pinky is tied
with a red thread to another's pinky.
I'm sure someone wonderful will appear
in your life soon enough.
Thanks.
He might actually be quite close by.
Yeah, right.
Hello! Merry Christmas!
Ryo! What's with that getup?
What is it? I'm Santa Claus.
I can see that!
Really, leaving these two behind.
And here I was, wondering
where you'd run off to.
Here, a Christmas present.
Christmas Eve is tomorrow, right?
Never mind that.
What?! What is this?! It's a wedding dress!
It's not that three million yen one, is it?!
And I have a tuxedo over here too!
What is this, Ryo?! What's all this about?!
Wedding garments for Tsubaki and Kazuhiko!
Tomorrow's an auspicious day too.
It's Christmas Eve.
I'm saying, let's have a wedding
with everyone's blessing.
With everyone's blessing? But we're...
Never mind all that.
I've already reserved the church,
and I sent out the invitations.
Everything's ready.
The arrangements are set.
Anyway, let's have a toast!
A pre-celebration!
Sir, last night, Mr. Saeba asked me
to deliver this to you.
From that man?
This is it.
What's this? It's a wedding invitation.
So it appears.
Kazuhiko Umino and Tsubaki Yamaoka?!
Sakurai, what is the meaning of this?!
I don't know. I was only asked to deliver it.
Damn that Saeba! He betrayed me!
He's not fit to be called Mokkori Man!
Unforgivable.
I will never allow the daughter of such
a man to join the Umino family.
You two wait here.
Yes, Ma'am.
Wow! You look very beautiful, Tsubaki.
Thank you, Miss Kaori.
But is it really true?
Do the people who attacked us really have
nothing to do with either of our parents?
If Ryo says so, then it's true.
He might not seem that reliable,
but even so, he's much better at
his work than you'd expect.
Tsubaki, we've entrusted everything
to Mr. Saeba. Let's believe in him.
Yes!
Kazuhiko Umino
Tsubaki Yamaoka
Waiting Room
Mother! You came!
I am sorry, but I did not come
to give you my blessing.
I came to make you cancel this wedding.
You're still saying that...
I'm sorry to hear that, Mother.
Today, we will be formally married.
No matter what opposition we may face.
You do not seem to understand
the nature of the feud
between the Umino and Yamaoka families.
I understand.
Because we understand,
Tsubaki and I want to put an end
to this stupid feud now.
So young...
Yes, just like you when you were young.
They feel just the same as you did
when you almost married Mr. Yamaoka,
twenty-five years ago.
What?! Mother and Tsubaki's father
were almost married?!
They became close to each other so rapidly
that their parents almost didn't realize it.
They were headed for a wedding with
just the two of them there.
They vowed to put a stop to their families'
feud with their generation.
But on the day of the wedding, for some
reason, they canceled it and separated.
Ever since then, the feud between the
two families has worsened,
and it has brought us to
our present situation.
It was Yamaoka, wasn't it? That shameless
Yamaoka told you that story, didn't he?
No.
The one who told me this was
the butler, Mr. Sakurai.
I see, Sakurai did.
Yes, he would know. He was the only one
who was on our side.
But I don't understand why you
suddenly canceled the wedding.
Very well, I will tell you
to make Kazuhiko wake from this dream!
Mother...
So, the Umino hag's here too.
Sir!
It's true. Twenty-five years ago,
Yamaoka and I went as far as holding
a wedding ceremony.
Back then, I believed that Yamaoka's
eyes only saw me.
But that was just an illusion.
On the day of our wedding,
he showed his true colors.
It was when we were exchanging
nuptial cups.
Of all things, right when he
was about to marry me,
he only had eyes for the priestess!
I was young and inexperienced,
but what a fool I'd fallen for.
I regret it even now.
That man got close to me only to make
a laughingstock of my family.
Now, do you see the reason
why I am so stubbornly against
your marriage?
I see.
I never knew Papa did such a
terrible thing to your mother.
Tsubaki, don't let it bother you.
No matter what our parents did,
it has nothing to do with us.
Kazuhiko, are you still saying such things?!
It isn't true!
Papa!
It was a misunderstanding.
I never had eyes for the priestess.
What a transparent lie! What do you
hope to accomplish by this?!
At that time, I was so ecstatic that
I was to be married to you
that my mind was filled with thoughts
of our rosy, married life.
An involuntary smile crept onto my face.
Right then, I may have been facing in
the direction of the priestess,
but I could see nothing but you.
I never even knew that the
priestess was there.
That... That's impossible. I can't believe that!
My lack of discretion is to blame for
such a misunderstanding.
But at least...
Please, Ms. Yuki Umino!
My daughter, Tsubaki, is not
responsible for any of this.
Please acknowledge her marriage
to Kazuhiko. I beg of you.
Papa!
Mother!
Mr. Yamaoka, please get up from there.
Then Tsubaki...
Yes, of course.
I am the one who must apologize.
We have paid far too heavy a price
for the mistake we made.
I would never want our children
to suffer the same.
Yuki...
Tsubaki!
Kazuhiko!
I don't know how to thank you.
Well, I guess I couldn't compete
with Tsubaki's dedication.
What a fool you are. You gave up a
parent-authorized mokkori.
We're both fools.
It's just that you're a fool only when
it comes to your daughter.
I'd like it if you two would attend
my daughter's wedding.
We've still got things to do before that.
We are still missing one guest.
Though the people must be burdened by
the cross due to our sins,
our merciful Lord in Heaven
could not look away
from those who would tie the sacred
bonds of holy matrimony
What's wrong, Kaori?
And He bestows upon us
abundant blessings.
I'm just somehow happy.
And He bestows upon us
abundant blessings.
I'm just somehow happy.
Kazuhiko Umino, do you take
this woman to be your wife
Hey, this is just an act.
Kazuhiko Umino, do you take
this woman to be your wife
I know, but I was thinking how I wished
my brother could have seen this.
And to be bound to her in holy matrimony,
as the Lord decrees?
I know, but I was thinking how I wished
my brother could have seen this.
In times of sickness and in health,
And then suddenly, I...
and when others may abandon her...
They're here!
Yuki, this way!
Let's go, Kaori!
After them! Don't let them get away!
Split up and look for them!
Yes, Sir!
One down.
You think you're hiding? Die!
Damn, it's just the veil.
Over here!
Hi!
Good work.
You aren't Tsubaki Yamaoka. A stand-in?
You've given us a lot of trouble,
but this is it.
Throw down your gun!
Don't do it, Ryo!
I don't care what happens to me,
just get this bastard!
I can't do that.
It'd be awful if that three million yen
dress got a hole in it.
That's true.
It'd be awful if we harmed such
an expensive dress...
What?! That's just great! I'm not even
worth three million yen, am I?!
Hey, stop that!
What?! That's just great! I'm not even
worth three million yen, am I?!
You bastard!
Let go!
Kaori!
Kaori! You okay?!
Ryo, I'm sorry. The dress... The dress...
You idiot! Who gives a damn
about the dress?!
Oh, I'm all right.
I see. I'm so relieved.
Ryo...
Take us to your client.
Mando Nakata
You idiots! You failed again?!
We're quitting this job! We'll give you
back the money, so...
You cowards! Get out of here!
Yes, Sir, you don't need to tell us that.
Damn it. I'll hire someone top notch,
no matter what it costs me!
Hello? This is Nakata.
What?!
Don't mess with Umino Shipping or
Yamaoka Shipping anymore.
That is, if you want to live longer.
What kind of foolishness is this?
Cigars aren't good for you.
What?! Who the hell are you?!
It isn't as if you have long to live.
No need to hurry to your grave.
Wasn't Tsubaki beautiful at her wedding?
I guess by now, they're on an airplane,
headed for Europe.
Snow! It's snow, Ryo!
No wonder it's so cold.
Oh, yeah! There's no present
for you this year!
Thanks to getting that dress full of holes,
we're in debt again!
No, I don't need one. I already
got my present.
Thank you for worrying more
about me than the dress.
No present could have made me happier.
A white Christmas?
Flying through the sunrise
Searching for the sunset
Changing the color of my lipstick
doesn't excite me anymore
Because its color is far from that of dreams
A journey to see a sunrise
like a ball of fire
If I could invite you too
I would take to the sky like a feather
If I can become passionate,
that's all I want
An invisible sun will surely rise in my heart
I want to gaze upon something grand
Even my bit of courage goes barefoot
And runs away
A broker for sweepers came looking for us!
We're so lucky!
If Miss Sophie likes us, we'll never
have to miss another meal!
Something's not right here.
Why does Sophie care about the gun
Robert left when he died?
It just happens to be the day Robert died.
And someone is after Sophie.
It does all seem a little choreographed.
I wonder who she really is?
City Hunter 3:
"Goodbye City - A Farewell Gift (Part 1)"
It'll be goodbye to you if you don't watch.