Step on the gas
Soaring too high
Nemurenai gozen niji
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
Nemurenai gozen niji
Iradachi ga doa o tataku
Hashirenai ookamitachi
Yami ni tsume o tate samayotteru
Kimi o saigo ni mita no wa
Hokori no mau zattou no naka
Semeru you na manazashi ga
Tachisaru senaka ni itami nokoshita
Kiri ni tozasareta mootaauei
Ima demo kotae sagashiteru
Tegakari no nai yozora ni
Chiheisen ga yokotawaru
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, seiza no kieta sora
Wow, wow, wow, joushiki no nai michi
Wow, wow, wow, yasashisa tada motome
Wow, wow, wow, yowasa to mukai au
Wow, wow, wow, sonna kimi wa iranai
Reserved
Give me a shock, for the
satisfaction of the era.
Clumsy tricks will only bring
everyone to grief.
Hey, Ryo, you're drinking too much.
No way! Ryo's not dwunk at all!
Hey, Umi, there're no more drinks!
Miki, Kasumi, c'mon over here!
Jeez...
There we go!
Hey, wait, Umi! It's on me. Drink up.
Oh! Miki, Kasumi, let's have a toast!
Saeba, are you really okay?
I'm okay! I'm okay!
Cheers!
Ryo, that's enough already.
Why?! I was just having fun!
I'm gonna change scenes and
go drink some more!
Hey, Ryo!
Leave him alone.
Today's a special day for him, isn't it?
Goodbye City
A Farewell Gift
(Part 1)
Robert, let's party!
All right, here we go!
I'll be waiting there ahead of you...
Robert!
That's right, today is the day
Robert passed away.
It's not anyone's fault.
It's the result of two pros fighting with
their pride and guts on the line.
But he can't forget his friends.
He's too kind.
Kabuki Town Block 1
All right, let's go to one more bar!
Cabaret
Neko Manma
One, two! One, two! One, two! Mokkori!
One, two, mokkori! Mokkori!
One, two! One, two! One, two,
mokk... mokk...
Ryo...
He's not there!
What's the big idea, ever since yesterday?
I'm in a really bad mood right now.
Let's hear your answer.
What?! You have something against me?!
I think we should first have an
international goodwill mokkori!
We can talk after that.
Damn it! I was worried, and here you are!
American Private Detective Association
general manager, Sophie Silverman.
Nice to meet you.
American Private Detective?
You mean that famous brokerage
firm for sweepers?!
Correct. I accept jobs from clients,
and then I pass them along to the person
best suited for the job.
City Hunter's name is known
in America as well.
I'd love to become his agent in America.
I will, of course, select the jobs carefully.
We did it! We did it, Ryo! Now we can
become world famous too!
We'll never have to worry about
missing another meal!
Hey, it's okay, right? Right?
The way you look at me
just really bothers me.
He's a little out of it right now
with a hangover.
Please don't mind him.
There is one condition regarding
the contract.
Condition?
I'd like to see him work.
Well, of course,
I need to know the performance of
the machine in order to sell it.
See him work? I hope it'll be all right.
If possible, I'd like to be in close
contact for observation.
Close contact?
All right! With that condition, I'll accept!
Let us immediately get into close contact.
Hey!
Come on now, close contact, close contact.
Ah, Ryo!
Don't you leave your partner behind,
you bastard!
This is bad. If she sees his true nature,
we can forget about the contract.
Ryo!
Who are they?
Ryo's Fan Club, I'm practically
an idol in this town.
Okay, if you want my autograph,
line up, line up.
I don't care about your autograph! Pay us!
That's right! We came to collect on
the tabs you've accumulated.
We won't let you get away today!
Pay your tab!
What the heck are you doing?!
That's it, I'm taking the amount we used to
pay the debts from your monthly allowance.
Okay!
The client writes "XYZ" on
this message board.
I check the message and decide whether
to accept the job or not.
In other words, you're his agent.
Well, I guess so.
And what's the relationship
between the two of you?
We're only business partners.
That's right.
Really? You have no romantic
feelings for each other?
Vomit!
Vomit for me too!
The conditions are right though.
The best way for a man and a woman to
get together is to become partners.
More so if the job is dangerous.
Is that speaking from your own experience?
Who's the client?
Let's see, a stranger is stalking her lately,
and she's beginning to feel threatened.
She's a college student who was
chosen to be Miss Body Con.
Who is it?
I told you, Miss Body Con.
Turn that job down right away!
What are you so worked up about?!
You're acting weird. She's just the
type of client you prefer.
A trivial job like that won't show off
my true talent!
That's not true. Every job reveals
a man's true character.
But...
What?
Is there something bad about this?
No, well...
In any case, this is not the time
to be picky about work!
I've already accepted it, so quit complaining!
Yes, Ma'am.
What's with the shades?
Just thought I'd act sort of cool, you know?
Miss Midoriko Sayama?
You're City Hunter?
It was about a week ago when I first noticed.
Everywhere I go, this man appears.
What has he done to you?
He's just really persistent, always
hanging around me.
No!
At this rate, I won't even be able
to sleep without worrying!
Definitely a weirdo.
What are the characteristics of this man?
Well, he's rather tall, about 190 centimeters.
I think he tends to look thinner
when he's dressed,
because he was rather muscular
when I saw him at the pool.
His hair is neither long nor short.
His mouth is always warped into a leer,
and his eyes are those of a pervert.
He wears a sports jacket with
the sleeves rolled up
and a T-shirt on the inside.
Don't worry, I'll subjugate this
weirdo immediately!
Thank you!
Ryo!
Yes?
Hey, where are you going?!
Did that weirdo look like this?
Yes, he did.
Sit down!
I'll have your head!
Wow! You caught him already!
Now I can go on with my life
without worrying anymore.
Thank you very much!
Not at all.
You're welcome.
That's definitely Sophie.
Wait, Serano.
Why?
The President's orders are to kill Sophie
as soon as we find her.
The man with her...
I'm pretty sure that's City Hunter.
What?
Here you go, please make
yourself at home here.
Thank you.
Then, please excuse me, good night.
Why do I have to lower myself like this?!
It's all because of that Mr. Mokkori!
Have mercy!
No, think hard about what you've done!
If a story like that ever gets out,
we'll never get another job again!
I'm sorry! Oh, God! Oh, Buddha!
Oh, Kaori! Please let me down!
Damn you, how many times do we
have to go through this?!
In the end, I can never resist
the temptation of mokkori.
Sophie!
What?
I can't say that I approve of your hobby.
Poking your nose into people's secrets.
Do you have an interest in that gun?
Not particularly, but I do know how to fire it.
You point it at the person you want
to kill and pull the trigger.
Walther P38...
This will be the second time I've seen
its muzzle pointed at me.
What happened to the person who
pointed it at you the first time?
Sorry, but of all these guns, I don't want
this one touched by others.
Ryo?
Yes?
Last night, weren't you supposed to be
on the roof repenting your deeds?
Why are you here?
What? Well, I just went for a late night walk.
Unbelievable! You better not have done
anything weird to Miss Sophie!
I swear to God that I didn't!
Miss Sophie, was everything really all right?
We were alone together in a small room.
Well, that is true, but...
What are your plans for today?
I will observe your work, of course.
I don't see any signs of City Hunter.
All right, let's do it.
Kaori, enough is enough! Untie me!
No, you will stay there and repent
your deeds all day.
What in the world's going on?!
Untie me, Kaori!
What is this?!
Damn!
Die!
Do Not Enter
Are you hurt, Miss Sophie?
I'm all right.
It looks like we lost them somehow, but...
Miss Sophie, do you have any idea
why they would target you?
Here they come.
What a persistent bunch.
Stay here. I'll do something about it.
There are two of them.
I'll be okay.
I think...
You can't use a gun with your
right hand shot up.
Ryo!
Leave this to me. You take care of her.
All right!
Damn!
Gotcha!
You thought I'd fall for a rudimentary
trick like that?
You've seen too many movies,
B-movies at that.
Damn it, I won't forget this!
Miss Sophie?
It's loaded.
What's this about?
This gun has been waiting for me to use it!
To avenge its former owner!
Flying through the sunrise
Searching for the sunset
Mou kuchibeni kaete mo tokimekanai no yo
Yume no iro ni wa toui kara
Hi no tama no you na asahi o mini iku tabi e
Moshi anata mo sasoetara
Hane no you ni maiagaruwa sora e
Atsuku naretara sore de ii
Kono mune ni kitto mienai hi ga noboru
Ookina mono o mitsumetai
Chiiisana tsuyogari mo hadashi no mama
Nigete yuku yo
Sophie was Robert's lover!
But Robert doesn't want his death avenged!
I will accept this challenge,
now that Kaori has been taken as a hostage.
Ryo, you're not going to...
Sophie! I'll fight you as I promised!
No! There's no point in living if Ryo dies!
If you're going to shoot,
shoot us both together!
City Hunter 3:
"Goodbye, City - A Farewell Gift (Part 2)"
If you don't watch, it'll be the last episode!