Step on the gas
Soaring too high
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
One can a day
Careful, don't drink too much!
Hi
At 2 AM on a sleepless night
Frustration comes knocking on my door
Wolves that can't run
Wander around, clawing at the darkness
The last time I saw you
Was in the dusty crowds
Your accusing gaze
Left an ache in my back as I walked away
The roadway has been blocked by fog
Even now, I'm still looking for the answer
In the clueless night sky
The horizon stretches out
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness
Believe me baby
Running to the horizon
Break away from yesterday
Climbing on loneliness, a sky
without constellations
Wow, wow, wow, a path
without common sense
Wow, wow, wow, seeking only kindness
Wow, wow, wow, facing loneliness
Wow, wow, wow, I don't need you like that
We did it, Ryo!
An American broker for sweepers wants to
make a contract with Ryo!
This is our chance to make the
Saeba Firm world-famous!
All right, we have to show off for Miss Sophie
even if it means letting her be in
close contact for observation.
She didn't come here on business.
She came for revenge.
She came to avenge Robert's death.
Goodbye City
A Farewell Gift
(Part 2)
So that was it after all.
You knew?
When you were gazing at Robert's gun,
you looked as though you'd been
reunited with a loved one.
Apparently, the American Private
Detective Association
does not have a manager named
Sophie Silverman.
But I have heard of a female sweeper
named Sophie Silverman,
who goes by the alias of Silver Panther.
You're right. I met Robert on a
particular job we did together.
He had intended to make the
job in Japan his last
and wash his hands of it all afterward.
But he never returned from his final job.
I couldn't believe it.
Because I'd seen with my own eyes
just how good he was.
He was cautious about his work,
almost to the point of cowardice.
He always said that it was the
ironclad rule to survival.
I swore on his grave
that I would go to Japan and,
with my own hands,
I would kill City Hunter, who killed Robert.
I was looking forward to seeing just
how skilled City Hunter was,
but I guess you can't put
your faith in rumors.
I'm disappointed that I slipped
past your guard so easily.
So, those guys were bait
to bring me out here.
No, they're from the Guinness Corporation,
and they're after me.
Guinness Corporation?
The murder agency that does everything
from training terrorists to assassinating VIPs!
The ones who hired Robert for the job in
Japan were the Guinness Corporation.
Of course, when he learned that it was a job
from Guinness, he tried to turn it down.
But the organization learned of my
existence and threatened Robert.
They told him that I would die if he refused.
There shouldn't be any reason for them
to target you anymore.
It's this.
Inside this is what Robert stole from them,
a microfilm of Guinness's
VIP assassination plot.
He obtained it to try and insure my safety.
But Guinness must have decided that
it would be safer for them
to steal the microfilm back
and take my life too.
Now, draw! Just like when you killed him!
I have no intentions of fighting you.
But I do!
I see.
Then I will make you want to fight.
Well? Feel a little more like fighting me now?
Sorry, but I have a policy of not
pointing guns at women.
We'll see how long you can
stick to your policy.
Miss Sophie, are you all right?!
Ryo!
What happened, Ryo?! So much blood!
We have to treat you right away!
Miss Sophie, please help me!
Don't worry, he won't die of
wounds like those.
Why don't you come with me?
What's going on here?
If you don't want Saeba to die right now,
come with me quietly.
Miss Sophie, what in the world...
If you want to get Kaori back unharmed,
come to where the Honboku Base used to be
at 0-hundred hours a week from now.
If you don't come, you will suffer
the same pain that I did.
The pain of being robbed of a loved one.
Now, let's go.
Ryo...
I wonder where Ryo's run off to?
I came all the way here to tell him
some good news.
Oh, well, next time.
Ryo! Don't grab me so suddenly.
I'm not ready to...
Ryo!
You're so coldhearted.
I guess you didn't come to pay up
on the mokkori.
Ryo, what happened to you?
I see, Sophie Silverman challenged
City Hunter to a duel.
That's convenient for us.
We'll take care of both of them
in one fell swoop.
Don't do anything until I get there.
If we send Sophie Silverman to her grave
and kill the City Hunter,
the name of the Guinness Corporation
will resound throughout the world.
I never thought she would act
so favorably for us.
Looks like things worked out in the end.
I wonder if Saeba will be okay?
He doesn't seem to be in danger of dying.
But why did someone as skilled as Ryo...
Sorry for the trouble.
No big deal.
What happened?
Kaori's disappeared,
and I hear you were seen
with Sophie Silverman.
News travels fast.
It's Saeko.
Apparently, people from Guinness
Corporation were acting strange,
so she was investigating the matter.
Why don't you talk?
Sophie Silverman was Robert's lover.
Robert's?
She challenged me to a formal duel.
Kaori's a hostage until then.
So that's it.
What are you going to do?
I have no intention of harming you.
I'm just going to use you
to make Saeba suffer.
Your hate isn't justified!
It's the result of two pros that fought
with everything they had!
Would you believe that, even if
Saeba were killed?
Could you just let it go?
That's...
There's no way you could understand.
You've never lost what you held
dearest in your heart.
I do understand!
You could never understand!
I do understand! I lost my older brother too!
I understand your feelings
of hate towards Ryo.
But please try to understand
how Robert felt too.
Robert...
They were good friends.
Robert and Saeba were?
And they had to fight each other,
because they're both pros.
Because they're both men!
Do you think that Robert hates Ryo?
Miss Sophie!
Robert...
Stop it!
When this job is over, will you
go to the church with me?
This is the last of the dangerous jobs.
When I come back,
I'll become an instructor at a
shooting range or something.
Be careful.
Don't let me become a widow
before the ceremony.
Robert...
How did it go?
Sir, all that's left is to order the dispatch.
Sorry for making you wait, Makimura.
Looks like I'll get to drink
with you again soon.
Don't do it!
That's right! Revenge is such
an outdated concept.
I can't not go.
It's my fault that Kaori was taken hostage.
I'm sorry.
But, Ryo, your wounds haven't healed yet.
No need to worry.
You're going no matter what, aren't you?
But be careful.
Guinness, the president of Guinness Corp,
arrived in Japan today.
Guinness did? I see. I'll be careful.
Get in.
I don't need your concern.
With your wounds, the upshot's going to be
that you'll get into an accident
before you get there.
Well, I'll do as I please.
Come back, all right?
I still owe you lots of mokkori.
Forget about it.
Otherwise, I won't be able to face Makimura.
Ryo, you don't intend to...
Take care of Kaori for me.
Make sure that she wants for nothing.
Got it.
Ryo...
Good, you came.
Looks like you still have a little pride left.
Sorry, but we'll have to postpone our match.
What?! Are you still going to...
Quit hiding like sewer rats and come on out!
I should have expected that of you, Saeba!
I was going to wait until
one of you went down,
but since you've noticed us,
I have no choice.
Guinness! How dare you?!
If we defeat the two of you, nothing could
better advertise the Guinness Corporation.
You could potentially lose all trust in you too.
We'll see how long your big talk will last.
I'll serve you plenty of treats:
Lead bullets.
Damn, what in the world?
Hey, don't leave me out. Serve me too.
Umibozu!
Could that be Falcon?!
Why is he here?
Damn it! Shoot them all full of holes!
Kill them!
After them! Don't let them get away!
Yes, Sir!
You busybody, you should just
quietly play the café boss.
You stay here and rest, so you won't
drag down the rest of us!
Looks like we'll have a truce for a while.
I guess there's no choice.
You'd better not get killed by that rabble.
I'm the one who will kill you.
Are you okay, Ryo?! Your wounds must hurt.
Don't worry. You stay here and hide.
If anything should happen,
use this to defend yourself.
Got it?
Ryo!
Well, don't push yourself.
That's right, I shouldn't stop him.
Because this is Ryo's work.
What the?!
Damn Umibozu, he sure is
going wild over there.
Saeba!
It's all clear up there.
It's gotten quiet. I wonder if it's over?
Kaori!
Ryo!
Ryo, are you okay?!
You're slow.
It looks like the wounds Sophie gave you
are going to cost you your life.
We'll see about that. You never know
until it's all over.
This is the end, Mr. Saeba.
Impossible!
Looks like we swept them.
Now there's nothing to get
in the way of our duel.
As I promised, I'll fight you.
No!
Miss Kaori?!
If you're going to shoot, shoot me!
Get out of the way, Kaori!
No! There's no point in living if you die!
I've had enough of being
left behind to grieve!
My brother was bad enough!
Shoot!
Shoot us both together!
Get out of my way!
I knew from the beginning.
I knew that I couldn't shoot Saeba.
By continuing to hate you,
I felt like I was with him.
Miss Sophie...
Robert, I've lost you all over again.
I'm returning this to you.
I don't want any more sad
memories of Robert.
I think Robert would be happier if you had it.
All right, I'll hold onto it.
Miss Kaori, I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Not at all, take care.
Robert is dead, but from now on,
he'll continue to live on in my heart
through our happy memories.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you.
Say, Falcon, did Saeba really intend to die?
He's a lucky bastard to have survived.
They both fought, intending to die. How sad.
Maybe in the end, we're all just
looking for a place to die.
I'll never forgive you if you die alone, Falcon!
When you die, I'll go with you.
What a public display of affection!
And they're getting into the
mood over there too.
Shall we go drinking, just us
unattached gals?
Of course! The one unattached
the longest gets to pay.
You go on home, okay?
Sister!
Flying through the sunrise
Searching for the sunset
Changing the color of my lipstick
doesn't excite me anymore
Because its color is far from that of dreams
A journey to see a sunrise
like a ball of fire
If I could invite you too
I would take to the sky like a feather
If I can become passionate,
that's all I want
An invisible sun will surely rise in my heart
I want to gaze upon something grand
Even my bit of courage goes barefoot
And runs away