She... she did it!
Inokuwma Yawara wan the world cup!
I like you!
You...
Good job.
You truly are a superstar, Yawara-san.
A thief! Somebody stop him!
Move it! Move it!
Get out of my way!!
Camera. . .
Right:
Amazing!
Te... Terrific...!
I've been following you ever since I was
mesmerized by your flash of talent
Not just me either...
I'm really bored.
Please stop playing around, Miss.
Miss!
P-P'laase forgi...
Were you injured?
You threatened our lives. Who are you?
Did you know that Fm Inokumua Jigoro?
A-Absolutely not. Really, I have no excuse.
I was careless and wasn't keeping
my eyes on the road.
It was fate that the queen of
sports, Sayaka, met Yawara.
Oh, these are splendid trophies.
They were awarded to you, young lady?
This quInik! !!
Junk! Junk!
All j-unxk!
Junk!
Miss, they're comphetely destroyed.
Winning has no value to me.
The issue is how excited they can make me.
Buta I have nothing to get excited about.
Those who are given only one ability by God,
they do not Ulndemtand how baring it is.
I hate that God has given me not
only two, but three abilities.
We-IL judo was not among them?
J udo?
Did I surprise you, Miss?
There will be more suwrp'ises.
I know a girl who is much stranger than
lam. She's the same age as you are.
Eh?
Jignro lnokuma, it's been a month.
WhQn you see the results of my hard training,
you'll tell me the whereabouts of the girl.
Eut I wonder if I've become stronger than her.
I'm late. I'm late.
Ah. Sayaka-san.
I'm sorry. I'm in a hurry.
W'a-iut.
I'm sure you know her too.
What are you taLkixng about?
You know the identity of the
really strung girl, don't you?
Pm reality in a hurry!
I have a test!
I will not let you hide that inlfarmlalzinn from me.
Please release mue!
If you dont tell me, you"l'l get hurt.
You want me to show you the
results of my hard training?
Come of? fit.
l"l.l miss my bus!
You will get hurt unlesa you
are prepared for my attack.
Enough... is... enough!
You will get hurt unless you
are prepared for my attack.
I'm really in a hurry!
That's the gm.
That's the giiri who is extraordinarily strong.
Not only did she beat my perfectly
executed mweV
She also saw me without my fake tooth.
Miss Sayaka became even more
passionate about Judo.
Just you wait!
Why?!
Why don't you debut in the jawdn
world when you are so skilllled?
Why are you trying to hide your talent?
I'll cry out! . l"lll make a big noise!
I became more passionate too.
I'll cry out! - I'El make a big noise!
I beg of you! Please answer me,
even if it's just one word!
I'm betting my career as a reporter on you.
Please leave me alone!
Leave her alone.
Kazama tsuri Shinnosuke, Sayaka's coach.
You have no right to violate her
privacy or to collect material.
Who was that guy?
Is that man a reporter from a photo magazine?
Whautl?
No... I thought you might be a popular idal singer
or something and were being fella-wed.
An idol? Me !?
No, not at all!
I'm also invad-iing your privacy.
That's only because ymu're dazzling!
Because of this perverted stalker,
the situation changed.
No way, a TV aation?
Did y'uu meet anyone famous?
I met and talked with Sugilmura Haruko-san
and Taukamine Misha-sun.
They were more beautifui in person than on TV.
Did you see S'honen-ta-i or Genji Hmkaru?
We no interest in school boy groups;
By the way, why dnl'd you go to the
TV station in the first place?
Prumotjng yonu, of course.
What? Promoting me?!
The best wary to glamorousaly promote
youlr debut is through TV, so...
I can't beHeve it!
But, Osh-iuri TV rejected it.
Hnow coulld they refuse such juicy material?!
Of course!
Please don't do such stupid things anymore!
I have no ilntentian of entering the fuck: world.
I'm finally able to be like a normal girl and...
"A normal girl..." and what, get a guy?
Remember, Yawara, that in any warld, idols
don't get careless and get boyfriends.
Getting the National Achievement Award means
that you'll be the indol fozr adll Japanese citizens.
And so, an idol like that can't possibly
have a boyfriend get in the way.
I diam: want to be everyonek gilrl,
I just need to be one man's gvirl.
No more! Fm never going to dn judo, ever!
Yawara, in your body flows the
blood of a judo athlete...
You can't quit, even if you try!
Hmph, who cares about the blood
of a judo athlete. Not fair!
l was forced to do judo ever
since I coulld remember.
Who's there?
You're the newspaper repartenr agaiin, aren't you!
Okay, that's it! How dare you
invade my home and peep!
iv f n
What's happening, Yawara?
A peeping tom! He was spying on our dojo!
You thug!
Ka-Kazam atwri -san . . .!
in Ka-Kazamaxtsuri -san . . .l
u .,KE-Ka;zgmatmn-san...!
KE-Kazamatsuri-san...!
Ka-Kazamavtsun asanA .
Ka-Kazam'amts:urivszan  . .!
Ka-Kazamatsunvsan. . .!
Ka-Kazamatsuri-san..
Ta-da!
The Daiiy Every Sports' Matsuda Kosaku
has finally captured the decisive scene!
I got great shots, Matsuda-san!
And to throw Sayaka Hon'ami's coach and pin
him with an arm-crushing cross body lock,
it's an overwheLming scoop!
lnokumna Yawara
Super-idol Surfaces!
When is your debut match?
Please get out of my way!
Why were you hiding youself all this time?
Whafs your relationship with Han'ami Sayak'a?
There's none!
What about Shinwnosuke Kazamatsuri?
What's wrong. aren't you gonna eat?
If you don't eat, you wan't become strong!
I don't care about becoming wrung,
When did yuu start doing jludo?
I don't know.
But, I do remember stomach-throwing
my father when I was five years old.
I wanted to be praised by everyone.
Five years old?!
Of course, grandpa was overjoyed,
but at that time, it seemed like my mother
was in the shadows of the dojo, crying.
At that age, I had no idea that I
was different from other kids..
When I got to junior high, I Wnally noticed it.
All of my friends werewt doing
marnilng and night practicas.
Everyone were pretty clothes,
dated bays, and had fun...
While I only... I only...
I don't hate judo.
But, I just want to be a normal girl...
Just a normal girl...
Yawara-savn .
Do a matrh and... LOSE in fmnt of everybody!
You were supposed to lose.
But you...
This is it.
Good bye judo.
Yawara!
How dare you try to lose?!
I won't ever have to throw anybody
with an iippan-zeoi anymore!
with an i-ppan-zeori anymore!
I won't ever have to throw anybody
with an i-ppan-zeoi anymore!
with an i-ppan-zeori anymore!
I won't ever have to throw anybody
with an i-ppan-zeoi anymore!
with an i-ppan-zeori anymore!
I won't ever have to throw anybody
with an ippan-zeoi a'nymnre!
lnokumal!
I'll becam a normal girl so I can... Imn...
I'll became a normal girl so I can... I can...
Elii, how persistent!
You won.
You won against Todo Yuki and your
official debut was decided.
And, as a special featurev we will have
a special guest exhibition prior
to the start of the tournament.
Everyone, please welcome eight-dan
black bet-t, Jigoro Itnokulma.
I'm nine-dam!
Fix it, he's a n-i-ne-dan!
I'm lnnkuma Jigaro, JyaJ
I'm still strong enough to take on you young ones!
Umm, you're a bit too close to the nut...
I'm mll strong enough to take can you young ones!
Although l"rn stilll physically able
to fight in a tournament...
please forgive me for just doing that
exhilbivwhatever for you guys.
Ill'l place of me, my granddaughter, Yawara
lnakuma. will probably astmish you!
Finally, in an official tournament!
In place of me, my granddaughter, Yaw-are
lnokumna, will probably astomish you!
Finally, in an official touwrnamen't!
Everyone. . .
Fight-
oh!
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
Everyone...
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
Fight-
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
oh!
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
Fight-
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
oh!
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
Fight-
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
oh!
That's the time you were coaching
the weak Musashiyama Judo club.
the weak Musashiyama Judo Club
Okay. Let's do three laps of rabeit
hops around the school nrext.
Wham? That's im possible!
Yawara-saun !
rs
Hurry up, the repormrs are
going to mob you soon.
Your en-try into the tournament was confirmed
at the official press canference.
I don't want to be min the tournament!
You're unbelievably strong.
Put that talent to good use!
No! If I do jluudo, I can't wear pretty clothea!
You can wear pretty clothes
after you do an ippon-zeoxi.
I couldn't cook, either.
After winning a national tournament,
all your food can be eaten.
I want to fall in how normally,
and become a bride someday.
Even if you won a gold medal at the Olympics...
you could still have a wonderful love
rife... and be a notmal bride, too.
What would be normal about
a strong bride like that?
Let me off!
Just let me off!
Kidwnapper!
Watch it, watch it... come on!
That's dangerous!
Wow!
Hey, is this someone's extra mansion?
Dont be surprised by that.
Come over here!
Oh yeah! There they are!
There! Look closely, Yaw-ara-san!
Running iIn the sand with steel sandals
and dragging a giant tire...
This is Hnn'ami Sayaka's rignrous training!
Fight, fight!
Fiifty more meters!
Who do you thirmk that fashionable
young lady is doing that for?
Yawara-san, i-t's to fight you!
Sayaska-san!
You don't feel anything after seeing this...?
You don't fee! anything after seeing th.is...?
ways:
?
if
Kazamautsunriwsan. ..
Yawa ra-san . . .
Oh... oh really?
Is the-t so? oh, I see!
I thought so.
Is that so? Oh, I see!
Is that so? Oh, I see-!
Yawara-san feels some-thing for me...
I see!
You're happy about this, aren't you?
D-dnn't kin me!
She's stilil in high school!
Han'ami Sayaka is a high school girl, too.
HIuh?
Don't tell me you think there's something
going on between me and her?
Well, with your reputation, iit's
really hard to think otherwise.
You're only aggressive whh women, right?
If only you could have used that
agressiun xin judo matches.
What do you mean by that?
I'm saying that, hand you used your girlwchasing
energies in judo matches...
You coulnd"ve won the Nationals
a-t leagt. You stage-fright freak!
I don't chase giris...
I'm just attractive, so they come to me.
Hrs the girls who want me,
just like Yawara-san.
Ahh, this is so stupid.
I wan-ted to ask you, but I changed my muinti
It was stupid of me to think
of asking you, anyway.
H...hney wralft!
What were yoru going to asak me to do?
Oh, I know!
Yawara-san wiilll Hsten to what I say...
You wanted me to ask her to fight
in the tournament, right?
l"lil do it!
That's when I started seeing Yawara-san
as a girl and not just as a judo athlete.
IS that. . .
Is that true?
Yes.
Your wait is over.
We have found Mr. Inokuma Kojiro in Seoul.
Very well.
Start the negotiatjans to have him as my coach.
I don"t care how much it casts.
But my daughter will get even stronger, too.
Daughter?!
When Inukuma Koj'i-ro becomes my coach,
l willl throw you beyond the
galaxy, lnukuma Yawara.
She embarrassed me, who is perfect
at everything and what's more,
that cat-thief is trying to steal Kaza'ma-tsuri-san!
She wan against me only once and
now she's avoiding fighting me!
Begin !
Inokuma Yawara won against me
and it was totally an accident.
It was pure luck! One chance in a million.
Finallly .
N.. no way...
That can't be!
You completely won.
But.
Take you? To Setagay-a's an Gym now?
Yes. Please take me.
We won't make it in time.
And your awards ceremony is about to start.
Take me!
You were only concerned about the Musashiyama
High Judo Club's matches.
I'm sorry, Inokuma.
I can't do it anymore.
Hanazono-kun!
arm, I can hear yaw voice in my head...
But, I'm a wimp that gives up easily.
I... I'm IOO years too early and unworthy
to fall in love with you.
Hanaznno-k unn!
Hanazn no-kuln!
Yawaara-savn !
Hanazono-kun, grab the back of his collltatr with
your heft hand! Then, hook youlr left leg into it!
Clamp your legs aruunnd his left arm.
cradle his other arm with your right arm, and
then tighten his collar with your left arm!
Put more pressure in ybwr legs!
Keep going, Hanazono-san.!
He got IR!
End of math.
lInoekuma. . .
I"m. .. here, Hanazono- kun.
Did you win?
Yes.
I... won.
Really? You're so great, lInnonkuma.
You're really great.
ND...
All of you are great.
We all won for the first time. Us!
It's because you taught us judo, YHWElra-SBIL
No, all of you taught me instead.
Doing your beat is. ..
great. isn't it?
Iwill never forget that time...
your smile.
Cd
In retrospect, my youth's been terrible.
In retrospect, my youth: been terrible.
In retrospect, my youthes been terrible.
in retrospect, my youth: been terrible.
lIn retrospect, my youth's been terrible.
In retrospect, my youth's been terrible.
What are you saying?
It's full of greatness!
You'll be happy for the rest uf your
rife, if you do just as I say.
That's how things go from bad to worse.
Next Yawam!
Yawanra has come, seen, and conquered.
he is the world's number one jundo gilrll
If you don't watch it, l"ll do an ude
h-ishigi juji gatame on you.
Winning against Belkens and Teleshikova,
Inokuma Yawara-san became number i .
I will not continue judo anymore.
Because of my jludo, my family is scattered.
Yawara-san, you have decided
to quit judo several times,
but you have always come back.
Yawara lnokurna. I came all this
way from Canada to see you.
Come on, l-et's fight.
For example, Jody Rockwell,
You would have quit judo a long
time ago, if you hadn't met her.
Shes Finally met her match.
Yaw-ara's encountered a strong opponent for
the filrst time, so she's actually enjoying it.
I've got you now!
Are you okay, Jody?
Fm okay.
lfs not good to worry about the apponenlt
dulring a match, Yawara.
Here I come!
Let's atop, Jody.
Your arm is seriously ilnj ured.
No!
Until now, I've never had so much fun doing judo.
Please, fight me, Yawaral
Yawara, please!
Jody. . .
This is the first time I've ever had fun, too.
So, next time...
Next time?
When your arm is headed, let's fight again, mkay?
At a competition somewhere.
R-Really? Yawara?
Yes. I promise.
You went to many competitions
in order to keep that promise.
Ippon.
uncredeb Ie.
She advances to the finals, just like that!
Coach Yuutenj'i. I didn't know she was this great!
President, then we have no problems
with her scholarship appointment?
Not even a problem!
Well! surely win a Barcelona Olympic
gold medal for our school!
My textbooks!
You went through my room again, didn't you?
Gear!
Give them back!
No.
Iit's useless to waste your time studying
all night long without sleeping.
Useless?
What's meless about my exam studies?
You're already set to enroll into Saikai College.
I'm going to Mitsuba Wamen's College!
Listen, I will never let you
go to that Mil-hm college!
l"l.l keep these textbooks.
Give them back to me!
Geez, I have to use up my month's
allowance for these.
And, I'm the one trying to budget
the family expenses, too.
Here he comes again,
that pervert Kazama tsuri.
"But, it is often difficult to distinguish a person:
true feeling," Tam Buchanan said to me.
That's perfect.
You're excellent, Yawaramaa-n.
No, you teach very well, Kazamatsuri-sazn.
No, you're very smart.
You won't have any prublems
getting into Mitsuba College.
I don't know.
But, Kazamartsuri-san, why are
you so good with English?
Once, I was very fascinated by the
works of a certain American poet.
I wanted to read the poems in the original
language, so I really studied English.
Poems?
"We loved with a love that was more than love.
She was a child and I was a child.
In this kingdom by the sea,
But we loved with a low that
was more than haven"
Just a few lines from Edgar
Allen Poe's "Annabel Lee-l"
Like this poem, l"nm probably booking...
for that single, eternal woman to love.
Or something like that.
Was that a Little plretentinus?
Nat real'ly. . .
Geez!
What are they doing?
It's been over   hours now! B hours!
M....Ma-tauda-san, I cant breathe!
Damn, that Kazama-tsuri!
Don't tell me...
Studs are so lucky.
You idiot!
Don't think so nasty!
You were thinking the same
thing as well, Ma:tS'Unda-san..
Yes?
Shin-Chan. It's me!
Holy! bah-Marika!
Last time was so good!
I've been thinking about you ever since then.
I...I'm grateful for an your help!
Can I'?
Oh sure.
Can I come over now?
Oh really?
ND!
T
I... I'm bedridden with a really
bad headache right now.
Maybe next time?
Umm, HI...
Yes?
Make some tea.
Tea, huh?
Oh no!
The cup with the lipstick stain of White Lily
College girl, Megulmi, is still in the kitchen.
Helho? Shin-Chan?
Oh, there's a culp.
Hey, that's okay.
You must be tired from doing
jludo and exam studying.
judo and exam studying
I"m actually very energized. I'm not tired at all.
No, no. Just sit there.
You're very mice, Kazanmavtsulri-san.
Come ocn, let's get back to studying
again, Yawara-sam!
Kazanm'a-tsuxrir-san !
Let's take your friend out to eat with us....
That was divine retribution.
We have much bigger and happier n-ews!
Our only daughter, Sayaka,
and Kazamatxu ri--kun. . .
are now engaged!
What?
W...wa;it.
This is a very happy outcome!
Shinnoswke, now our Kazamatsuxri
Brewery is in wife hands.
Serves you right!
So, that means...
Wait, everyone --
This is Sayaaka.
To be engaged to Kazanmatsuri-san
is the happiast even-t for me.
But, i:n order to have a bILissful
marriage, I mmt do one thing.
That is, to defeat Inokuma Yawara,
and become Number One in Japan!
Bun.
I... I was the only one thinking we had something.
Kazanmavtsulril-san,
Fm... such a fool!
And then, the day of the exam came.
Yau sprained your hand in yesterday's match?
I can't hold a pencil because it hurts so much.
I think I barely made it through
the morning exam,
but the pain numbs my brain...
I dun? think I can make it anymore.
I need to go.
You're going to take ft with that hand?
Yawara-saun .
I studied so hard for this.
Regardless of the result. ! won't give up.
l"ll duo my best until the very end.
But, with that handu.
At worsta rll go to Savikai College.
Matsuda-san, the-t choice will be great
news mantena-l for you, right?
Give me your right hand.
Just give me your right hand.
There was a tennis player who won at Wixmbelsdaon
by tyilng the racket tn her injured hand"
Here you go.
It looks dumb, but it"s better than
not being able to hold a pencil.
Give your all in me Last fro-minute bout.
Umm. . .
Let's see your exam results together.
Good for you.
Yawara, are you not home yet:!?
That girl, breaking curfew again!
Yawara just called earlier.
She's working an a report with her friend.
Are you sure she didn't go to a disco?
NmNn.
I doubt that.
EE: is!
:f. .. bl;-
.JU
Jl- -
Jigoro-san's guess was an the money.
The World Cup was coming up,
The World Cup was coming up;
The World Cup was coming up:
The World Cup was coming Lipi
The World Cup was coming up,
but since Yawara-san became
a college student".
What is that girl doing'n
The one who brought you back to judo is...
What?!
Hue touched yowr bottom!
So I jlust tried to brush him off...
Brush him off?
Jtust brushing cuff caused a person
to fly through the aiur?
It was an accident.
He accidently tripped right then.
IsnT that judo?
Oh, what are you talking about?
What is this jlundn thing?
IInokunma-san, I reaullly think
I have seen you before.
Back then, just after being forced
to give up on being a ballerina,
I was living at my home in Shizuoka without
being able to find any new goals,
and I was just spacing out in front of the TV.
Another llppon-zeai I
She was glowing incredibly.
I didn't know a thing about judo, but I would tell,
that she is a gift who wi-ll become the best in the
world - the very thing I was trying to achieve.
Thank you, lncnkuma-san!
I decided to give my days of youth
a try again because of you.
I realized that I shouldn't just sit there
when I saw you shining so brightly.
I decided to give my best at the entrance exam.
This is so excitilng!
You are that giri!
I have a Friend who will became the wodd's best!
I really wanted to dance for the world.
But you can!
Von can make my unfulfilled dream a reality!
Yawara-san decided to compete
in the World Cup.
M...Ma...Ma...
..Ya...
Ya...
It's not about to stop anytime soon.
YES.
That newspaper reporter.
Yawara, it might get difficult for you, but your
steady boyfriend will help you through it all.
What? You have no one, and yet
you don't want to meet anyone.
You're zs already.
Start thinking about it.
I have someone in mind;
Let me check the weather.
She's going to be in the World cup.
'r
Oh you filrst, Matsuda-san.
Well, I'll be in Seoul tomorrow.
It's finally time.
Huh? Yeah. H! be waiting for
you there, Yawara-san.
YES.
Actua-Illy, my Dad seems to be in Seoul.
Really? I hope you can meet him!
Yawara-savn.
Yes?
After the Worid Cup...
After the Wodd Cup...
Umm. . .
Oh!
Todo-san!
Yawawra-saun !
I"l.l catch up with her. Excuse me.
After the Wodd Cup...?
U'h, well...
I wanted to reserve a special interview...
Ma-tsuda-san, you're always about wark.
Please excuse me.
Todo-san.
After the World Cup...
Fujiikmsan !
Fujiikn-sem. . .
Peace!
You left for Seoul and stepped
out onto the World's Stage.
By the way, Jigoro-san. Is what you
said in the commentator box true?
The reason Yawara-san's father.
ch'iiro-san is missing,
is due to the shock of being thrown
by S-yealr-ohd Yawaravsan.
Dan't tallk about that!
But if that's true, it's so drama-tic.
So I really was the reason.
The reason he's gone...
It was w years ago.
By losing to Yamashfta-kum, I realized
the toughness of judo once again.
And I leamed what I was missing.
It's the natural born talent
And I didn't realizza someone with a natural
born talent was so close to me.
But that day, she wrely performed a throw.
I knew I was thrown.
By my mere five year old daughter!
We heard that story.
From Yarwam-saan. She told
me with such a sad face.
The shock was not from beilng
thrown by Yawara...
By seeing her true talent, I...
I was... truly touched.
And so you left for a journey of training,"
Kojiro-san, where are you?
I took apart your father's judo
gi, and sewed it up again.
I'm glad I cauald finish it before you left.
Dads?
lit was Dads dream to become the
best judo wrestler in the wand.
I wonder if I can see him in Seoul?
rm sure you can.
x: SK
Ky .
Young Lady,
You ruled all other sports, but
you could not rule Judo.
Holding back is not good for you.
Cry to your heart's content.
As inf I wauww cry!
The only time I will cry is when
I beat hnokuma Yawara,
and after becoming the true queen of the world,
I will cry for joy!
How could I dare cry until then? How could I....
Looks like I was right at judging you
as the damned rival of Yawara,
Lady, you will get much stronger!
Read that and study a lot!
And get much, much, very much stronger,
and come back to face Yawawra!
As the strangest rival in exmance.
Wait and see, lnokuma Yawara!
Miss ,
I've brought him.
Please come in.
I've been waiting far you, lnokuma Knjmro-sazn.
Grandpa, Dad heft because of my jundzo.
Stop talking nonsense!
Do you think yau can get a gold medal
at the Olympics with that attitude?
It has nothing to do with me.
We are starting youxr training right now and
we're going to fix your loser attitude.
I don't want to...
Next YHWBII'B, I"'m gaming to quit Judn!
Wh wh wh what?!