Presented by FroZen-EviL!
I've loved him.
daisuki datta no
I've always been waiting.
zutto honto wa mattetanda
I showed off whenever he was around.
seiippai kakko tsukete wa
But I acted cool, like I didn't care.
ki no nai furi shiteta
My career and love life?
shigoto mo ren'ai mo
I do think they're both important.
watashi taisetsu dakedo
But when I see his smile,
aitsu no egao ga yappari
I know it's what I want the most.
saikou no takaramono
He proposed to me; was it real?
omoigakenai puropoozu!
I feel like I'm stuck in a crosswalk.
sukuranburu no domannaka
uso deshou
It's so unbelievable.
I'm frozen and I can't take a step.
tachidomatta mama
My umbrella rolls away like a flower.
korogatte yuku kasa no hana
Horns don't get through my ears.
kurakushon sae kikoenai
I stand there still, in the pouring rain.
zubunure no mama ugokenai
The world is silent and completely still,
sekaijuu iki wo hisomete
As you and I see each other, eye to eye.
ima watashitachi mitsumeteru yo
Kiss! Kiss!
Chu! Chu!
H-Hey, Jody.
What's with the crowd?
Nothing's with the crowd, Yawara!
You were the World Cup's gold medalist.
A little Japanese girl.
Canadians were cheering for you on TV.
B-But...
Yawara!
She is number one judo girl, Yawara!
Number one!
Don't be shy. Wave to the crowd.
But...
Come on!
Yawara!
The Last Ippon Seoinage!?
Here they come!
They're my students from the judo school.
They're so cute.
Yawara!
Oh dear, everyone.
She will have a practice game on our wedding day!
Hm? What did he say?
What was he talking about?
He said that you'll do a match for us at our wedding ceremony.
Miss Rockwell, is that true?
Can we really see a match with Yawara here in Canada?
I can't participate, since I'm still recovering,
but I have the perfect opponent prepared for Yawara.
Jody, I...
Yawara, will you throw an amazing Ippon Seoinage for us?
Yawara!
Sign: All Sports News
Good night.
Man...
This company really works my fingers to the bone...
I haven't gotten much sleep in the past three days.
Wh-What?!
Wh-When did this story come in?
Hm? What's the fuss?
What do you mean, "fuss"?
Yawara-san!
Inokuma Yawara's doing an exhibition match in Canada!
Yes!
Thank you so much, Jody!
This is good.
Yawara will finally return to judo.
What are you looking at, mister?
Excuse me, miss.
Is this the new recruit?
Yes...
U-Um...
Oh, don't point like that.
Call me "Marilyn."
I also...
Anyway, can you make sure that my gi fits my body perfectly?
I need to show off my body, okay?
Sh-Show off your body?
Anyway, I'm only starting judo to protect this body,
so I don't want any scratches or bruises on it.
Come here.
No way.
I thought so.
Judo's not an easy sport.
What on earth can you possibly do with a girl who doesn't want scratches or bruises,
and a girl who's so frail a stiff wind could knock her over?
B-But... I want to improve my health.
Yeah!
What am I supposed to do if I get hurt?
No offense, but just give up.
I won't!
Don't you know it'll be your fault if something happens to me?
This is hopeless.
I can't make a team to bring Inokuma-san back to judo.
Inokuma-san...
I'm sorry.
That makes thirteen of them!
Why?
Why do I have such bad luck?
Men are... Men are...
assholes!
Four more people...
Four more...
They'll come...
Four amazing judoists.
I'm sure of it.
She's...
She's staring at the recruiting poster with such intensity,
I can feel her spirit coming out of her back.
You're the one!
I've been waiting for someone like you!
I swear I'll throw you!
You're in for a surprise if you think I'll go down easy!
I'll teach you not to mess with me!
Sh-She is the one!
Do you want to learn judo?
Hell yeah.
I'll throw down every single man on earth!
That's the spirit!
Hey, do you have any experience?!
Well?!
Experience?
O-Of course I do.
How much?
Hey, how much?
Th-Thirteen...
Thirteen years?
Woohoo!
Hallelujah!
A savior at last!
Hurrah!
Inokuma-san, an amazing judo team is waiting for your return!
Here they come!
Yay!
Jody!
Congratulations, Jody.
Yawara!
You look absolutely beautiful!
Thank you, Yawara.
Is your foot okay?
Oh, this is nothing.
I have him to support me.
You're such a lucky woman.
Make sure you put on a wedding dress yourself and cozy up with Matsuda.
Ma—
A-A dream?
What a beauty she is...
Yawara-san looked gorgeous in her wedding dress.
And I was right next to her.
Then the honeymoon...
Then...
the first night.
I want to see what happens next.
Ah, snap out of it!
This must be happening to me because I've been locked up in this place, living like a priest!
It's before dawn.
The dojo's lights are on.
Sayaka-san, what a busy bee you are.
S-Such intensity...
I'm sure of it.
He must be!
He's Master Inokuma Jigoro's son, and Yawara-san's father:
Master Inokuma Kojiro.
Hey!
It's pointless to try and hide.
I noticed you when you walked in.
I'd like to tell you just one thing.
P-Please tell me anything, Master Inokuma Kojiro.
The egg I have for breakfast...
I'd like the yolk a little softer.
Okay...
What do you think, Yawara?
Isn't it an amazing dojo?
Your opponent is amazing too!
Jody...
She couldn't enter the World Cup because of an injury,
but she's the new hope of Canada!
Jody, please listen to me.
Ladies and gentlemen!
I know we're all having so much fun,
but let's have one of our wonderful guests celebrate René and Jody's marriage.
The World Cup Women's Free-Weight Class Judo Gold Medalist, Yawara Inokuma!
Timing: Juggen         Encoding: Skr
Editing: Yoshu-sama, Collectr
Translation: Urasawa
The World Cup Women's Free-Weight Class Judo Gold Medalist, Yawara Inokuma!
Editing: Yoshu-sama, Collectr
Timing: Juggen         Encoding: Skr
DVD Provider: CP
kokujin-kun, Skr, Juggen, Yoshu-sama
QC Team: tlynnec, Rosti, Mamo-chan, CP,
Translation: Urasawa
Editing: Yoshu-sama, Collectr
Timing: Juggen         Encoding: Skr
QC Team: tlynnec, Rosti, Mamo-chan, CP,
kokujin-kun, Skr, Juggen, Yoshu-sama
DVD Provider: CP
Yawara!
Yay, Yawara!
Yay!
I'm so excited!
Jody...
Hey, come here, Yawara.
Jody, I...
Don't worry about a thing.
Look, she's super strong, you know?
After all, she was supposed to represent Canada for the 72kg competition in the World Cup.
The poor thing dislocated her right shoulder right before the World Cup trial.
She wanted to go to the World Cup,
so I want to give her the chance to fight you, Yawara!
Jody, I've already quit—
Yawara!
Will you please give it your best for her sake?
Jody...
Yawara Inokuma will be facing our very own rising star, Kristin Adams!
Go get her!
So she's Yawara Inokuma.
The Yawara who won the World Cup.
I can finally fight her... the great Yawara!
Jody...
Step forward.
Bow.
Go! Go! Yawara!
Jody, I really can't...
Note: "Hajime" means "Begin." It is used in dojos world-wide.
Hajime!
Let's fight, Yawara!
Jody...
Yawara!
Why do we have to carry these tatami mats?
Fujiko-sama, we need to find more members.
I don't want to build muscles from carrying something so heavy.
Hey, Kyonkyon, are you really doing your part?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm doing my best already.
Excuse me, you... um...
Me?
I'm Yoko.
Minamida Yoko.
Minami as in "South,"
Da as in "paddy fields,"
and Yoko as in "sun."
I see.
Miss Paddy-field.
Don't call me that!
I heard you've been practicing judo for thirteen years.
What's so funny?
It's just...
Fujiko-san told me that you were an amazing person with thirteen years of experience,
but you were just infuriated from being dumped by thirteen men?
If you don't stop laughing, you're really going to pay!
But it's really funny!
They run away because you chase them, you know?
All I have to do is leave them alone, and they come after me.
You'll never know what I went through!
You're just a slut!
Then shall I introduce you to your fourteenth boyfriend?
At least put a shirt on under the gi!
No wonder men come after you!
E-Excuse me.
Let's carry the tatami.
There!
Oh no! I can't believe I did that!
Well, it curved a little.
There's no one good in the recreational tennis club,
nor in the recreational golf club, of course.
Where will I find anyone who can do judo?
Oh, I'm so sorry!
I finally found a person with thirteen years of judo experience,
but with a twig like Kyonkyon and that pervert Marilyn...
It doesn't even make a difference!
Oh, my God!
Where are you throwing?
It's going into the street!
Fight! Fight!
Wow! Kristin's combination moves from the inside to the outside are bringing Yawara to her knees.
She's...
She's also...
strong!
One, two, one, two...
One, two, three, four!
I couldn't possibly find anyone amazing in a jazz dancing group.
I need to make the judo team look more official before Inokuma comes back from Canada.
Just one more...
I just need one more person who might be able to do judo.
No more.
I can't go on a diet. No way.
W-Water...
F-Food...
Parfait, hamburgers, cod roe, spaghetti, daifuku mochi, fried chicken, chicken bowl...
I'm sorry. I can't move.
I look tired, don't I?
This is fine!
Keep me pinned to the ground.
Please... feed me something.
I can't get out.
This is perfect!
Keep me pinned down!
Inokuma-san!
I've found her!
I've found an amazing person!
Anything...
Please, give me food.
I've found one!
Feed me.
Jody...
I'm sorry to spoil your wedding ceremony,
but this match is mine!
Ippon!
That was awesome!
That very last Ippon Seoinage!
It was awesome, Yawara!
Superb!
Number one, Yawara!
Ji-Jigoro-san...
Isn't... Isn't that a gold medal?
My, what's this?
I put it on when I was cleaning, and I forgot to put it away!
Man, it looks amazing whenever I see it.
Right, dear?
Yes, truly.
What an amazing thing.
What are you doing?
Well...
So long.
For goodness' sake.
Could you stop flattering him about that medal?
It puts him on a high horse.
B-But it's not like I have a choice!
H-He doesn't go home until I say something about the medal.
Why does he have to come every day?
The new owner of the dry-cleaning place told me that
he even wears that medal to the next town's marketplace.
What a shameless man...
Hey, it's the medal geezer!
Take that!
Take care, Yawara.
Thank you.
You gave me so many gifts.
Oh, no.
It was a wonderful ceremony, thanks to you.
Give my regards to Master Jigoro.
Yeah.
And let's meet at Barcelona, okay?
What's wrong, Yawara?
I'm sorry, Jody.
That can't be true!
You can't really be quitting judo!
Tell me it's not true!
Sign: The Barcelona Olympics in 523 Days
Yawara!
She's still not home?
That girl better not have lost to a mere bear in Canada and became its meal!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Jody.
Hey, tall girl, I'll train the new judo team you put together.
However, my training is pretty strict.
Grandpa, what are you talking about?
Next time on Yawara:
The weakest Japanese judo team.
The Weakest Japanese Judo Team
Hey, Grandpa, what are you talking about?
At twilight, my heart gently falls into a labyrinth.
tasogare ni maiorita kokoro no labyrinth
Thrills and sorrows swirl around me.
tokimeki to setsunasa ga mawari hajimeteru
We're pushed and shoved as we cross the street.
hitonami no kousaten senaka osarenagara
We climb an endless hill, just you and me.
sakamichi wo doko made mo anata to aruita
I want to say "I love you" to the one I truly want,
naze hoshii mono wo "daisuki" to
But why can I not? I really don't know.
koe ni dashite ienai no?
You're standing here by my side.
ima anata ga iru
That fact alone puts my worries to rest.
tada sore dake de yasuragu kimochi
"Please don't let go of the hand you're holding,"
"tsunaideru sono yubi wo hanasanaide..."
I say as I look for your smile.
egao wo sagashite