This is strange;
This is the college life I've dreamed of,
But...
it's not fun at all.
Grandpa is still being himself."
Attend me World Cup!
And you better become the champion!
Disco?
Yes.
It's another party with thne golf
club from Meihn University.
Huh?
nnokulma-sam
It's disco we are ta-Ilking about!
Don't you want to go?
It's not that."
Curfew again?
Then just tau him that you are
wurkixng on a report with me.
I could.
Dancing is so nice.
Forget about mrything and dance,
and it'll make you feel great!
You can trust that coming
from a former ballerina.
Eu-t, F u'jiiko-san, isn't disco completely
different fmm ballet?
If Grandpa found out that I went to a disco...
A discol?
Disco and ballet are different...
But just obeying grandpa doesn't do any ..
I think I will...
I think   will...
I"Il go to the disco.
Really?
I' ll feel better if you are coming.
But this wilrt be my firQ: disco too.
Let's start with finishing luwnch now.
IOC President Tamaranch i s visiting Japan!?
Yes.
I invited him.
After all, President Tamaranch and my father
Hon'ami Ki.nunosuk,e are very close friends.
He said he would love to toms ta
support me at the World Cup.
Hey, you, would you ask for permission
before you take photos?
If you are shooting from this angle,
wowld you back up a Little?
It"l'l be fine.
My skill allows me to make anything look pretty.
What do you mean anything?
The H un'am.i Group and President Tamaranch's
relationship has become even closer since
the Los Angeles Oiympic Games,
in which corporate sponsorship became popular.
lit's not a sexy shot, so stand normal.
This is normal.
So Hon'ami Group is involved in
the upcoming Worhd Cup too
That's pretty good. Matsuda-san.
So, you do more than chase after gossip.
Only one representative will be chosen from
each country foa' each weight class.
I thought the choics was finalized for the
ItEkg class with the match the other day.
Are you talking about the Japan Cup
that I farfeited, Matsuda-san?
That was purely accidental.
Right, Kazamatmn-san?
Yes, that's right.
If I had attended the final match, I
would have beaten Yawaura easily.
Yes E
Just thmw her away!
My, we agree in this case.
Yes!
Besides, don't you think a World Cup without
me is like breakfast without caviar?
The entire world is waiting
for my wonderful judo.
People will rush to see how I throw away
the enemies from all over the world.
The coltisewm will be in a great heat.
I wonder about that.
WhatE?
Jody Rockwell who fought Yawara to a standstill.
And Anna Teleshiikava who beat Jody.
Will your judo be good enough against them?
Your judo which was beaten in the blink
of an eye by lnokurma Yawara!
You see, this is why you are
stilt! a third-Irate newspaper.
This concludes the interview.
Please come see my matches for the rest,
Tokunaga, the guests are going home.
I 'll see how long you can keep that smile!
Good Luck, Sayaka-san!
Matsuda-san is absolutely right.
There is no time to be laughing, Sayaka-san!
At your current skill, you are...
A II
A LA,
Fujiiko-san.
Fu'jiIko-san!
The sound is very loud.
What?
Rea-Ely .
RteaHysI-wl
Disco is beyontagglief.
Disco is beyond belief.
My ballet is no good here.
Hey gins,
aren't you dancivng?
No, not yet.
ea
.u
No, not yet.
no
;
No, not yet.
Right, Fujilko-savn?
No. I'm building up my arategy.
No. I'm builldiing up my strategy.
Strategy?
Right.
I'm trying to master everyone's steps perfectly.
What are you doing, Yuwkari?
I!
What are you doing, Yukari?
What aiou doing, Yukari?
Aren't you gonna dance?
Q
Aren't yo: gonna dance?
I know!
I'm coming right over, so don't
cheat on me, KumWhixko!
d Ah
I'm coming light ove   so don't
cheat on,me, Kunfhiko!
J
U
Kagihiko?
Kunilka-o?
Did we have him in our circle?
I just picked him up over there.
He's a med student, and owns two beame'rs.
You should come on over too!
sci!
F u'jiiko-san ,
aten't we sort of out of place?
:'
,
w
aren't we so: gtf'gtb'f place?
arenjp-We swig
aren't we sort of out of place?
Yawara!
Yawara, are you not home yet:!?
That girl, breaking curfew again!
Yawara just called earlier.
Yawawra just called eariier.
She: working on a report with her friend.
Are you sure she didn't go to a disco?
No.
I doubt that.
lt'lll be fine.
Shem! be back soon.
By the way, I made the pork
stew you like so much.
This hook, delitinus.
NI-ND!
I'll be waiting in the dnjo!
No!
I dan't want it!
He reallly is mad.
No!
I don't Understand.
lnokuma-san, I'm no good!
Please go dance first!
Fujiko-san, I'm not. . .
Inokummsam
Would you dance with me?
No, no. I'd be better.
But I can't dance.
No prob hem!
I"l'l Shaw you.
I asked her first!
We been checking her out for a whvi'le now'!
"I've Liegen chethgEEFauthWL
I'vepljiiefen checgihhggEEIt-bumm .
:
.ar
I've Ipiefen checkihngFE puLfi-aMWe
I'venEeuen checkihgiEEEaumeWP
We been checking her out for a while new!
I 'll dance too.
;
You ntaigjjggow uwntijlggu try  ;
v
J i
You nWw untilxggu try We;
n.
'n
.sr ,
You nWw wnf-ijggu tryWa
v
J, ---a.
You ne . azaw wnf-ijggu tryWa
You never knmv until you try it.
live only ance.
l"l.l challenge it!
Right?
What is that girl daingl?
Hey, you can dance.
You think so?
Hey, do you wanna come with me after this?
Huh?
I drove today.
What is it?
That's cowl.
Fu'jiiko-san!
You're back. you bad girl!
The heck with the college life-!
You're still only a kid...
tpa.
Hey, this is grown up...
Jeez, ol-d scum!
It's not my fault.
It's your fault for acting Hike a thief.
You touched it far free-I
Who's the thief herel?
You stay quiet!
Even you haven't touched it yet.
Shut up!
So, what happened to Yawara-san?
I know you want to touch it.
What happened to the G o'clock curfew,
and the b hours of training in
the morning and at night?
It is none of your business.
So it's all because she went
to Mitsuba Junior College.
Why did you let her go there?
She was suppased to fail.
She was supposed to f'a-ill the exam
because of the hand iinjlulry.
However. ..
I know why.
It's because Kasaku helped...
Well, it's already done. so we can't help it,
By the way, did you know that President
Tamaravnch of IOC is coming to Japan?
Tama...
Tamarannch . . .
Oh, you perv!
Ta, Ma, Ra, N, Ch!
Hon'amli Sayaka invited him!
Hon'ami Ki rmosuwke and President Tamaranch
are wch close friends that they can go
"Wassup, Kin-Chan?" "Not much. Tammchan."
Isn't that incredible?
KilntE. . .
Is he that great of a guy?
We'll, sure...
He s the greatest of the greats.
Is he so great that he can change the World
Cup however he wants with his order?
Well, he's the executive supervisor of it.
Ma -chan ,
you know how there is no open weight
division in the World Cup?
Yes...
Doni you want see a match between
Yawavra and Jody in the World Cup?
Well. of course.
l"m sad I won't.
I 'II let you see it.
You'll see that big match at the Warhd cup.
No, that's impossible.
There s no... open...
You mean, you're gonna ask
President Tama raunchn
Thafs impossible.
Even if you aak the president, I don't think...
That's so absurd that it's not
worthy of writing it up.
I cant wait for the world cup.
Yes, that's it, Fujiko!
Huh?
Huh? lit became un-iet all of a sudden.
I-t's the cheek time.
Cheek time?
Please don't.
Oh, come on, let's enjoy it.
Piease stop.
Let me go.
WeTe done with the interview now.
Let's go on a date, Kosaku.
Huh I
Sure, it'd be great if there's
an open weight division.
But...
Oh, you're upset because I let
h-im touch me, aren't you?
It's just too impossible to ask for.
But...
When he wants something, there's
no reasoning or whatever.
Oh, you're jealous!
Please don't.
Hey, about the talk earlier.
Let's go down highway E in my car,
and watch the nice View from the Bay Bridge,
Stop it.
and than...
off to a nice hotel by the seaside.
No way...
Oh, no!
We done it again!
I've dnne it again!
Inuk umav-sann! Wait!
Ivnokurmawsan !
Hue touched youxr bottom!
How rude-l
L
So I jlust tried to brush him off...
Brush him off?
That happened just by brushing him off?
Jlust brushing off caused a person
to fly through the air...
It was an accident.
He accidentally trilpped right then.
Isn't that judo?
Oh, what are you talking about?
What is this judo thing?
IlnokuIma-san, I reallly think
I have seen you before.
We only met for the first time
at the entrance carenmany.
Oh, no!
I better get home soon, or grandpa will be mad.
I need to take the New Keio Line.
You're takilng the JR Line, right?
See you
That was bad.
Maybe she noticed.
No girl would throw a guy with an Ippon
Zeoi just by having her bottom touched.
I'm not normal.
My body moves before I think.
I'm a living weapon.
l"m home.
The hall with you're home!
It's way past the six o'clock curfew!
I'm sorry.
I will make them hold the open weight
divisinn competition at the World culp.
Only trailning awaits you, so you better wiwn!
Next Yawara -
An Open Weight Division is
the andy way for Yawam'a.
You bzetner watch it, our l"l.I
give you an O-soto gari!