kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Translator Notes:
Saikai means reunite, so the author might have named the College Yawara was fighting at Saikai College because Yawara is reunited with someone there.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Translator Notes:
Saikai means reunite, so the author might have named the College Yawara was fighting at Saikai College because Yawara is reunited with someone there.
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Hurry up and win it, Yawara.
Okay, do an ippon-zeoi there!
[ippon-zeoi : one arm shoulder throw]
You got it now!
Yuhkoh!
[Yuhkoh : partial 5 points]
Episode 10
"An Ippon Zeoi With My Mom!
The 90's is Yawara's Era! Jya!"
Out of bounds! Halt!
What's that?
Five seconds and she's down
by a yuhkoh already.
Isn't there too much of
a weight difference?
Weight difference is not the problem.
She's just nervous, being in
her first match and all.
Her true strength will soon be revealed.
Right, Sayaka-san?
When it's about Yawara Inokuma,
you seem so excited.
W... well, that's because the more her
strength is appealed to the world, when you
do beat her, it'll be more glorious for you!
Hey, hey, Kazamatsuri-san, what
just happened right now?
Did Yawara lose just now?
No, no, she's only behind by a yuhkoh.
[yuhkoh : partial 5 points]
If the match is dragged to the final decision,
it's disadvantageous, but with Yawara-san,
there won't be any final decisions.
No way! It continues?
I feel sorry for her.
Just cry, Yawara!
What's with this girl?
I thought she might've been tough,
but she's unbelievably weak!
Why do I have to go against
such a neophyte? Geez!
Begin!
This person... this Yuki Tohdoh is...
...weak!
Out of bounds! Halt!
Eii! What's wrong with you, Yawara?
I didn't teach you that kind of judo!
What's up? She's being pushed around.
She's not even trying to attack.
Th... this looks bad.
Yawara-san, make a move!
Just try to attack her!
That's why you say, but she's really weak!
If I even try to make a move...
Begin!
Aah, this is irritating!
What's wrong with Inokuma-sempai?
That person isn't strong enough for Yawara-san, right, Hanazono-san?
She's just testing the water.
You're... Ganryuji High's Sasaki!
Her strength isn't what you see there.
Only people who've went against her know that.
In other words, my body
knows her the most.
You! Don't say it so suggestively!
Well, don't think so suggestively, then!
What should I do? I can't just
keep running away.
Hey, you! Stop squirming away
and attack me, for once!
Refrain from personal comments.
Inokuma, be a little more aggressive.
Y... yes, sir.
What a tasteless match.
Is it gonna end like this?
That Daily Every must have been
blowing hot air all along.
No! It will not end like this!
You're Saikai College's Judo Team Coach,
Mr. Gohzoh Yuutenji!
That Yawara Inokuma's method of stance...
has no openings whatsoever.
It's not often that you see
such a controlled stance.
Is that really what it is?
Then, you're saying that she's faking it,
despite her true strength...
Jigoro Inokuma-sensei is truly amazing.
Such excellent guidance!
Hey, she's actually strong or something.
Really?
That's what Coach Yuutenji said, so...
Matsuda-san, it's getting worse, isn't it?
If this goes on, they'll know she's faking.
Attack, Yawara-san! Attack her!
But.. but if I try...!
Eii, Yawara! Why are you taking so long?
There! Do a counter attack!
Argh! Cut the crap, Yawara!
Attack, Yawara-san!
I'll win a move from you soon!
There, Yawara!
Do a move, Yawara-san!
Well, maybe just a bit, then...
She's got her!
No, don't get it!
Yuhkoh!
[Yuhkoh: partial 5 points]
What was that just now?
Why didn't you get it with that?
I thought she got it, but...
...maybe she didn't get it, on purpose?
I can't believe her! Couldn't
she even dodge that?
I almost scored an ippon just now.
[ippon : full 10 points]
I guess I slacked a bit too much,
since she's so weak.
I won't make any more mistakes!
Yawara Inokuma. If this is her level, then I
was fired up for nothing, Kazamatsuri-sa..
Yawara threw her, so why didn't she win?
Well that's because...
Hey, you people, that's enough.
Stay away from Kazamatsuri-san!
What's with her?
Seems pretty anal.
I told you to stay away!
Well, she did score a yuhkoh...
It's almost time...
Almost time to lose?
Oh man. I can't bear to watch it!
Matsuda-san.
What are you doing, Yawara?
Hah! Yawara, you..!
Yawara! Don't tell me you're trying to...!
This doggone match is over!
Yawara! You big, fat idiot!
I know your scheme! You're trying
to LOSE, aren't you?
Oh no. Grandpa found out!
Inokuma-san, you can't get inside.
Please calm down!
Eii! Let go of me!
Don't pull any stupid tricks, Yawara!
I'd better hurry up and lose!
Inokuma-sensei, why is
Yawara-san trying to lose?
Oh, Hanazono-kun!
Listen carefully, you too, reporters.
This isn't a match!
Not a match? What's tha...
Eii, shut your trap and just listen!
Yawara has attained terrifying strength
from my superb teachings.
But that child, for some ridiculous reason, doesn't want to do judo! Weird child, she is!
But, out of the blue, Yawara said
that she's going to do a match.
I thought something smelled, and I was right!
She'll lose on purpose to show that she's weak, and disprove all the media hype.
That's what she's trying to do!
What?
What the heck is this
gramps babbling about?
You're saying that just to
cover up her weakness.
That's not it, you retards!
She's trying to be a normal girl!
Nonetheless, this kind of
match isn't newsworthy.
What a load of crap!
How dare you be so rude and
call her a load of crap!
That's right! Inokuma-sempai
is really strong!
It was close, but everyone is starting
to think that Yawara-san is weak.
Reporters, if it's about her, just ask me.
Sasaki.
These guys act like they know her,
but my body knows her the most...
I told you not to say it so suggestively!
Waza-ari!
[Waza-ari: Semi 7 points]
Y... Yawara-san!
Out of bounds! Halt!
Dammit!
Geez! Why can't you get
an ippon with that?
[ippon: full 10 points]
Yawara Inokuma! I'm ashamed to
have regarded you as a rival!
Is it still going?
Just cry, Yawara!
Butt out! Go home!
I can't watch this anymore.
Matsuda-san...
All right, then! I'll just have
to end this match by force!
What are you thinking?
Stop this old man!
Eii, let go! You want me to place painful
moves on you? Let go! Just let go!
Hey, what are you trying
to do to Inokuma-sensei!
Hold them back!
These guys are trying to ruin the match to cover the fact that Yawara Inokuma is weak!
Th... that's not it!
Inokuma! Show us your...
Show us your true strength!
Yawara! Yawara-san! Yawara-sempai!
Everyone... I'm sorry.
Begin!
Dosu-koi!
[Dosu-koi: sumo grunt]
I'm... going to lose now!
And now, everything will end.
The star that was supposed to
shine for Japan's Judo World and
Japan's Sports World will now...
..fall from the sky.
Yawara-san, please obtain
your normal happiness!
Uhm..
Is this the way to the judo hall?
Y... yes! Th... there was dust in my eyes!
Thank you very much.
Uhm..
Let me say this...
This match isn't too fun to watch.
Even that housewife is Yawara-san's fan.
She was really supposed to
become every citizen's idol.
It's almost over! Please score
a clean ippon from me, okay?
Yawara!
Goodbye to early morning
and night practices!
I won't ever have to throw anybody
with an ippon zeoi anymore!
Inokuma!
I'll become a normal girl so I can... I can...
Eii, how persistent!
M... mom?
Mom!
No! No, no, no!
That didn't happen! Referee,
let's just forget this!
I'm sorry! I didn't do anything!
I...
No, don't!
I... IPPON!
[ippon: full 10 points]
The star... has fallen.
Everything is over.
Yawara-san, it was brief, but thanks
for letting me see a good dream.
Resignation
I guess I'll go back to Yamagata and
take over the family hostel.
Chopping firewood and fishing
can't be all that bad.
Cheer up, Kosaku Matsuda!
Crying's no fun, let's just laugh!
Y... Yawara-san?
Matsuda-san!
W... what's happening, Yawara-san?
What's going on? What just
happened, Yawara-san?
I...
... WON!
What?
I... I got it!
I got it perfectly, Matsuda-san!
But, why... why did she win?
Taxi!
Hurry! Hurry in!
Matsuda-san!
Don't worry. Just leave the rest to me!
But what did she mean that she won?
Hey, Daily Every! Why'd you let her get away?
U... uhh, wait. I don't know what's
going on here. What happened?
Yeah right, quit fooling!
Didn't you see that 70kg-plus heavyweight,
Yuki Tohdoh, flown in an instant?
Oh man!
Terrifying!
It's unfortunate for Yuki Tohdoh not to
have taken her seriously, but to have
been thrown with such sharpness...
...you'd forget to do ukemi and pass out.
[ukemi: falling technique]
Coach Yuutenji, so the winning move was Yawara Inokuma's ippon zeoi?
[ippon zeoi : one arm shoulder throw]
It all happened so fast that it was
hard to figure anything out.
Yeah, as soon as we saw Inokuma
move into the opponent's space...
..the next moment, Tohdoh's
massive body was in mid-air.
Just thinking of it makes me have goosebumps. Just like this, see?
What speed!
Truly the epitome of
"Softness yields even strength!"
That's only the tip of the iceberg.
If you're blown away with just that, then your heart won't be able to handle what's to come.
Inokuma-sensei!
I am very deeply moved right now!
You have developed your
granddaughter so... so well!
Then stop having such a large face and
go develop an athlete to rival Yawara.
I shall!
Sensei!
Inokuma-sensei!
Please let us be your students!
Just as much as Yawara-san's
fingernail crumbs' worth of training
will do! Please instruct us!
That's rude! Yawara-san does NOT
have any fingernail crumbs!
Kids, become stronger then.
Because, I don't teach wimps!
That was an excellent debut.
This is why I abandoned everything
to devote myself to judo.
Right, Kazamatsuri-sa...
Kazamatsuri-san, does that mean
Yawara won that match?
What just happened in there?
Okay then! Let me explain the
judo rules over some tea!
Th... this is preposterous!
Matsuda-kun! Our company's star!
You did it! That was great!
Kamoda! Is it developed?
Matsuda-san! Where'd you go? I got it!
If you tell me you missed it, I'll slice
up that pineapple head of yours!
Y... you...!
I... is there a problem?
You're Japan's Number 1!
This is awesome!
The cheering's back. The cheering
of the large crowds again!
Yawara Inokuma, you're one of
those athletes that either appear
or not in decades... a superstar!
But, why did Yawara-san win a match
she was supposed to lose?
Yeah! Why? Huh? Why?
U...uhm...
Well.. she yelled this right before she
threw the ippon zeoi.. "Mom!"
"Mom"?
Geez, Mom, you appeared out of nowhere.
I was so surprised that I threw
her with an ippon zeoi!
[ippon zeoi : one arm shoulder throw]
So, you were trying to lose that match?
I'm so sorry.
Well, it's not your fault, really.
But, why did you want to lose?
I wanted to quit judo.
It'll take forever for a strong girl
like me to find a boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
You are of that age already, aren't you?
I am a high school senior, you know.
But, Yawara...
You may be strong in judo, but
that's nothing compared to me.
Mom... strong?
Uh-huh. I had you and raised
you up to this day.
That's true, since you did it
all alone without dad.
Women get stronger and stronger,
regardless of any help!
You'll understand this someday...
...of what it means to be truly strong.
Whether you quit or go on
with judo is up to you.
But, if a boy looks at you strangely just
because you do judo, then that's when
you SHOULD do an ippon zeoi on them!
Mom!
The key is to not lose
your femininity, Yawara!
Am I feminine now?
You're a very attractive girl!
Just like me when I was young!
Really? Am I really feminine?
Yawara! What the heck was today's match!!
Grandpa!
I never taught you that kind of judo!
How dare you scheme of losing on purpose!
Welcome home, Father.
T... Tamao-san, you're back?
I apologize for leaving the
house for such a long time.
Dinner's ready, but would you
like to take a bath first?
It's not your fault, Tamao-san,
but I don't need dinner.
I'm so upset that I can't eat, all
because of a stupid girl!
Who are you calling a stupid girl!?
I made your favorite, hijiki no gomokuni.
Stop it!
I don't need dinner.. dinner.. dinner...
Seconds, please.
Tamao-san's cooking is always the best.
Yawara's cooking is too foreign! Judo athlete's food should be native dishes!
Whatever! I'll never cook for you again!
All you make is that "strong combo"
beef bowl anyway!
Beef stroganoff!
Oh yes. The reason I went to Hida
Takayama is because of a rumor...
...that somebody took a picture
of a Kojiro-san like person.
Dad?
Isn't this an abominable snowman?
Is this really Dad?
As soon as he sensed people, he ran away. This is a picture of the footprints.
These are wood slippers. I see,
it's very Kojiro-like to wear those.
Wearing wood slippers
in snow... seems cold!
Dad should end his training and
just come back already!
You don't need to worry about that.
You made your debut today.
You need to start practicing more
to get the gold medal and the
National Achievement Award.
Grandpa, I...
If you ever pull a stunt like that again,
you'll be banished from this family!
I will not be manipulated by you, Grandpa!
You're ippon zeoi is nothing yet!
I'm going to make you stronger
with more and more discipline!
Grandpa!
Oh my!
A cha-bashira, look!
[cha-bashira : vertical tea stem]
That's a wonderfully good omen! Gold medal and the National Achievement Award is
going to become a reality, then! Right?
Grandpa...
950 Days to Barcelona Olympics
Debut match and first victory!
The first step to the gold medal and
the National Achievement Award.
Grandpa! I had no intention
of making a debut.
Even if you didn't, the rest of
the world think otherwise.
Just look at your school.
What? No way! The whole
school's riled up!
Causing a ruckus is an idol's destiny.
Next time, on "Yawara" ...
"Big Panic at High School
With The Yawara Fame!"
I'll do a kesa-gatame on
those who don't watch!
[kesa-gatame : scarf hold]
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Kyonen wa anata to
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Eigakande miteta hazu
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Soba ni ite ne
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Ano koro no youni
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Kata o daitene
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Otana ni naranaide