From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Mom!
Episode 11
Big Panic at High School
With the Yawara Fame!
Congratulations, Yawara Inokuma!
Nippon, cha-cha-cha!
Fure, fure, Ya-wa-ra! Sore!
[typical Japanese cheer]
Congratulations, Yawara Inokuma!
I saw it on the sports news!
I was delighted. Your ippon zeoi
is Musashiyama High's pride,
hope, and shining star!
And so! How about making
a female judo club?
Female judo club?
If you perform well, our school's name will reach every household nationwide.
Right, Kaizuka-sensei?
W... well, that's true.
That's too much for me!
I want to go to college!
No problem!
I'm sure athletic colleges will come to
recruit you, so you don't need to worry.
I want to go to an all-female 2-year
college as a housekeeping major!
If it's housekeeping, then
the athletic colleges...
Wha... what did you just say?
I want to go to an all-female 2-year
college as a housekeeping major!
What? H... ho... housekeeping?
A... are you sure about this? Even if you're strong in judo, you can't just get in so easily.
You need to study for the entrance exam,
and what'll happen if you fail?
That's why I don't have
time to do any clubs.
Excuse me.
Yawara-kun.
Inokuma.
Kaizuka-kun!
Yes?
Why'd she choose housekeeping?
Don't "heh?" me! You don't get
a chance like this that often!
Is there any way you could convince
her to change her mind?
Kaizuka-sensei!
Yes, sir.
There! Keep Going!
Go, go! Almost!
Wimp.
That's 10 losses in a row!
Shut up.
But, if Hanazono-san saw us
like this, he'll cry again.
That's okay. Hanazono-san said he's
not coming. He's out college-hunting.
I see. Once Hanazono-san graduates though, it'll be the end for this judo club.
We're just too weak to train
any new members.
We're so pathetically weak.
Loser judo club.
The disgrace of high school judo.
Clumsy, let me try.
Hold on, just one more time.
You'll lose again anyway. Let me try.
No! This time I'll win.
Yeah right.
Ah!
Quit faking me out again.
N... no. Look!
Wha... what's up?
They're laughing!
They probably came to mock us,
the loser judo club!
Is Inokuma-sempai here?
What?
Yawara-san is in this judo club, right?
Huh?
We're interested in joining
Yawara-san's judo club!
Doom.
What's wrong?
Just thinking about studying for the college entrance exam is making me depressed.
That's true.
Talk about a small-scale study war!
But you're lucky, Yawara.
Huh? Why?
Aren't you going to continue on with judo?
What? Of course not!
I want to be a normal
female college student!
Oh really.
Come on, let's go eat
something to feel better!
Right on! Let's go!
Yawara-san!
What? You didn't intend to win?
Yeah.. I just kind of threw her.
Just kind of threw her..?
You weren't finally serious
about doing judo?
You didn't decide to continue doing judo?
Th... the cheering of the large crowds
has once again faded away.
M... Matsuda-san, get a hold of yourself!
Hey, what are you going to do now?
You won, you know!
You can't run away anymore.
It's all because my mom came
back from nowhere.
Mom?
So, your mother came back home?!
She found your estranged father,
Kojiro Inokuma, didn't she?
That's a scoop!
And so, what was he doing all this time?
Does he have any intentions of
returning to the judo world?
Come on, tell me! Why was
he away for so long?
That has nothing to do with you!
No, it does! I need to know
everything about you!
Leave me alone!
Hey, wait! Yawara-san!
Geez!
Oh my...
E... excuse me!
What's up?
Hanazono-san is still out,
visiting some athletic college.
What about Yawara-san?
She's already gone home.
What should we do?
Yawara-san has nothing to
do with this anyway.
Should we tell them?
We have no choice.
But if we do that, everyone will leave!
What else can we do, then?
Wha... what the hell?
Hey, sempai dudes, is Yawara-chan here?
I came here to join the club
to see Yawara-chan.
Well, is Yawara-chan here or not?
Which is it?
W... well, Yawara-san's not
coming today. Right?
Y... yeah, today is college
hunting day for seniors.
Damn, she's really not here?
Oh well, I'll be back.
I came all the way here to see her,
but what a waste of effort!
Next time, make it so that I can tell
whether or not Yawara-chan is here
from the outside, will you?
H... hey, you!
I think it's not respectful to call
a sempai, "Yawara-CHAN."
Oh, then, if "Yawara-CHAN" isn't good,
then maybe I should say "Yawa-PEE."
Right, sempai dude!
H... how dare you!
Don't you... casually... touch
my shoulder... like that!
No good...
She's late!
Isn't Yawara back yet?
I wonder where she is.
That child! She just had her debut
and already she's skipping practice.
Maybe she's overwhelmed from
suddenly becoming so popular.
It reminds me of the time when
Kojiro-san had his debut, too.
Father and daughter both wandering about... those greenhorns!
Ah... Isn't there a guy out there that can
get rid of these heavy feelings?
Kazamatsuri-san?
Yeah right!
He's a judo coach, and so cool, a total stud!
He whispered in my ear, "You have
such beautiful hair, Kyoko-san!
You have a hidden, alluring
quality about you."
Me too!
He said, "It's the first time I've seen anyone with such beautiful completion!
If you diet, you'll probably make
many men go stir-crazy for you!"
You guys were told, too?!
He said, "Kazumi-san, you're hiding such special things behind those glasses.
Don't keep it to yourself;
take off your glasses!"
What is he, anyway?
But, Kazamatsuri-san cares about you.
Yup. He said to please take
care of Yawara-san.
He said that you're his special person,
so please stay good friends with her.
R... really?
Oh, look at you, being all happy!
I'm jealous!
Hey girls!
You seem to be having fun.
Can we join in?
Let's do something, baby-baby, okay?
That's pathetic.
Was that you're pick-up line or something?
That's right.
Come on, let's go out, huh?
Hold on...
Country boy.
How dare you!
Wait up!
Are you okay?
That was slick!
Even though he's not my type.
Hope you didn't get hurt.
Th... thank you. We weren't hurt at all.
No problem at all.
What do you think you're doing!
I touched Yawara-chan!
Who are you?
I'm Yawara-chan's fan club member
number 1, freshmen C class, Sudoh.
Nice to meet you!
Don't give me that! Don't call yourself
a fan after touching someone's butt!
Hey, hey. Just don't do an
ippon zeoi on me, okay?
Wait just a second!
Your aggressiveness turns me on even more!
Yawara!
Oh! Ever since I saw you on the sports news, my heart went pitter-patter!
Sign my boxers next time! See ya!
What was that all about?
Unbelievable.
Pervert!
What's with him?
Uhh, those wishing to join, please write
your name and class on this sheet.
Wh. what did you say? So, you let yourself
get thrown by a freshmen yesterday?
Y... yes.
And you just let him go after that?
Y... yes, but he was really strong in judo...
And he was a bit scary-looking. Right?
Y... yeah.
What a shame! The first disgrace of our judo club ever since it's establishment!
A total shame!
I was momentarily happy to see
the crowd wishing to join, but...
Is that Sudoh guy in there?
No, it doesn't seem like he's here yet.
All right then! I'll go nab
him and pound him up!
Wait a minute! He's really strong!
What if something happens to you, Hanazono-san?
Are you saying that I'll lose?
We're not saying that. But even
with that, Hanazono-san...
You can't do much with that injury.
Darnit! Why'd I have to break
my leg at a time like this!
Really.
How did you break it?
It was a highly honorable wound.
Honorable..
..wound?
It was on the way back from visiting
Dameda College yesterday...
[Dameda College : literally, No Good College]
A little kitty stepped onto the road,
about to get run over by a large truck!
"Watch out, kitty!"
So that's how you hurt it.
You're so kind, Hanazono-san.
I'm not done with the story yet.
I let the kitty go at a safe place and said, "Take care! Don't get onto the road again!"
I waved at it for a long time,
and right after that...
A ditch!
It hurts bad! And, it's deep, too!
So what part of that was honorable?
Anyways! Bring that Sudoh guy over here!
He'll come here eventually...
Since his objective is Yawara-san.
What!? Yawara-san!?
Y... yes. Sudoh said he came to join
because of Yawara-san.
Wha... what a half-hearted reason!
But he's not the only one. All of them
are joining for the same reason, too.
H... how putrid!
What do they of Yawara-san?
Those people!
Those with such thoughts need not join!
Hanazono-san!
They want to join, you know.
Let me go! Don't stop me!
Even without my leg, I'll use my right
hand to pound and crush them!
You're gonna crush what?
I'm gonna pound and crush him..
and in the name of our Musashi...
And? How are you gonna pound me?
It's Sudoh!
What? You're Sudoh?
The one who raided our dojo and
insulted the innocent Yawara-san?
Who the hell are you, getting all hot? You,
nor the judo club, owns Yawara-chan.
She's everyone's idol!
Get the facts straight, mohawk dude!
Don't mess with me!
You're too ugly to mess with anyways.
Why you..!
Ha... Hanazono-san!
By the way, she's late, isn't she?
I wonder if she's coming today?
Oh well. Whatever.
Please, isn't there any way you can?
There were over a 100 students wishing to join, too, and I was in a dilemma... so... please?
W... well, you know, they wanted
to join just to be with you.
You're asking for too much.
I... I know.. but wouldn't you want to show
off your talents before you graduate?
Wouldn't you like to lead the judo
club to victory and change your
choice to an athletic college?
Never!
Coach!
What? Hanazono-kun was
taken down by a freshmen?
He was ruthless! He kicked
the injured leg...
... and kept stepping on it
when he was down.
Yawara-san, please help us!
What?
Eventually, he'll surely
destroy our judo club.
That Sudoh's still roaming about,
demanding to see you.
S... Sudoh?
Freshmen C class, Sudoh.
Nice to meet you!
Sign my boxers next time!
Only you can go up against him, Yawara-san!
I know our judo club sucks, but to have a punk like him destroy it breaks my heart.
I'd want to... I'd want to...
Why? Why do I have to fight him?
Why?
Yawara-san!
Inokuma.
Why?
Why do I have to lead the judo team?
And, why do I have to fight
with a bad boy like him?
Impressive!
Are these what established you
as the Queen of athletics?
Oh, it's not much, really.
I got rid of most of the items last year,
but I regained all those this year.
Impressive!
Not only have you climbed to the top, but you've defended the status consistently!
Serve the guest the cookies
imported from Denmark.
Yes, Miss.
You are definitely Japan's
home grown sports genius!
Serve the French import, maron glase.
Even that Florence Joyner pales
in comparison to you!
Make sure to add lots of gold
sprinkles to that maron glase.
Yes, Miss.
As I've stated, I'd really like to
have you join our judo club!
What do you think, Kazamatsuri-san?
The Saikai College Judo Club's track
record and staff are top notch...
... so it would be one of the best places
to further improve your skills.
If Kazamatsuri-san says so, then...
I am very pleased. If you join my club,
then we will be invincible!
Now, if Yawara-san joins us, too,
everything will be perfect!
What did you say?
Coach Yuutenji, are you going
to go recruit Yawara-san?
What? Oh yes! She doesn't have
enough official records for me to
recommend her for a scholarship...
...but I'm hoping that she'll be in
a special tournament soon!
I see. Yawara-san might go to
Saikai College, huh?
Don't kid me!
Take back the maron glase!
Yes, Miss.
Coach Yuutenji!
I refuse your offer!
Kamata! Kamata, are you there?
You called, Miss?
The guest is now leaving.
Personally drag him out.
Gotcha, Miss.
This is not funny! How dare he two-time
me with Inokuma Yawara!
Kazamatsuri-san!
Y... yes?
I'm going to Paris right now!
To P... Paris?
At my extra mansion in Paris,
I'll train for the next tournament.
Next tournament?
I will not let her get a scholarship so easily!
Kazamatsuri-san, you'll come
with me, won't you?
Yawara?
Yes?
The bath is ready.
Okay.
Yawara-chan's nude!
Intruder!
Wait you little punk! Wait, I say!
Yawara-chan, please forgive my lust for you! My body just guided me here!
Ouch!
Him again!
See ya!
What a fast rat bastard! If he ever comes again, I'll treat him with my special moves!
What a well-built man!
Wait for me, won't you?
What is this?
Hello, Inokuma residence.
It's me!
I'm so excited to talk with you, Yawara-chan!
It was nice seeing you just now. Oh yeah, I joined that wimpy judo club just to see you.
So come on, let's do some ne
waza practices, won't you?
[ne waza : pin down]
C'mon, Yawara-chan. Are you listening...
Yawara, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Scumbag!
Miss, the meal is served in the lounge.
There's no time.
Huh?
Tell the pilot to hurry it up.
Y... yes, Miss.
Oh geez, I hate being stalked by that weirdo! That's why I didn't want to debut!
Yawara-chan.
You again!
You can't do an ippon zeoi
in this cramped crowd.
Geez!
So, come on, let's get to know each other!
If you try anything to me, I'll scream!
Don't be so tense, Yawara-chan!
You gotta take care of your fans,
right Yawara-chan?
Right, Yawara-chan!
Yawara?
Yawara? The one that threw Yuki Tohdoh?
That ippon zeoi girl, Yawara Inokuma?
That's right!
Everyone, she is Yawara Inokuma!
Geez!
That's it! Now I'm mad!
What are you doing?
Please don't get so violent!
I am not being violent!
Hurry up and change into your dogis!
[dogis : judo uniforms]
Y... yes, ma'am!
You'd better watch out, Sudoh!
929 Days to Barcelona Olympics!
He will not get away with this!
What's that?
Training starts tomorrow! Oh yeah, we should do early morning sessions, too!
Yawara! What's with you, Yawara?
Sudoh, you'll be pounded to pulp and...
Pounded to pulp?
... will be unable to move...
Unable to move?
... until you squeal!
Squeal?
Watch out, Sudoh!
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
Coach Yawara's Extracurricular Lesson!
Those who don't watch it
will get a kata-ha-jime!
[kata-ha-jime! : single wing lock]
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
I watched the video through the night.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stay right here next to me,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
I don't want you to grow up yet.