From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Yawara!
How long are you going to keep
meddling with them, you big fool!
You have a big tournament awaiting you!
Inokuma-san, what did you just say?
Yawara will be in a big tournament real soon.
And prove that she's number one in Japan!
I'm not going to be in that tournament.
See? Now there's no problems!
Yawara-san, will you really do it?
To be our coach?
What?
You want me to be the judo club's coach?
Episode 13
Yawara's Heart Shook in Hayama!
U.. unbelievable! This is supposed
to be the first-class meal?
This poverish thing?
W... well, I think this is about the best you'll get.
See, there's even caviar.
This sad caviar wouldn't even be
touched by my dog, Charles.
Tokunaga! Don't touch it!
To have a Hon'ami servant eat such crud would bring shame to every generation!
O... of course, Miss.
That's why I hate to utilize
the commercial airlines.
I can't believe that my personal jet broke
down right when I wanted to fly home.
When I get home, I'm going to ask my
daddy to buy me a new plane.
Don't anybody move!
I'll kill anyone that moves!
D.nn don't tell me it's a hijacker!
Oh yes! I should get a Concord this time,
huh, Kazamatsuri-san?
I'll throw Inokuma Yawara in
the next tournament,
... and in the Concord, I'll go around the world!
Of course, you'll come with me, Kazamatsuri-san!
S... Sayaka-san, be quiet!
What's wrong?
Don't move. You don't wanna die, right?
Who is this grubby man?
Be quite, Sayaka-san!
So, you wanna die, eh?
What a mean looking pistol.
Sayaka-san!
It has to be a toy, for sure.
Victim number one!
Sayaka-san!
Hey!
What a pathetic hijacker!
Well, it could be that I was
just too strong, though!
Bravo!
Amazing! What sharp skills!
Maybe in the upcoming tournament..?
You threw a hijacker, right, Sayaka-san?
One comment, please!
Weren't you scared?
Kazamatsuri-sama, aren't you coming?
Are you watching, Yawara-san?
Next time, it'll be you!
I am not my old self anymore.
I'll throw you so far into the air so
I won't have to see you anymore.
I... I can't believe it!
Are you ready, Yawara-san?
That Miss Sayaka sure is good
at being flashy, as usual.
This is not even funny!
She's getting on my nerves!
Oh come on, this is how it's
supposed to be, Yawara.
Use that anger in the upcoming tournament!
I told you, I'm not gonna be in that!
You can't fool my eyes, Yawara!
Despite what you say, your eyes tell me
that you're burning up inside.
I'm just mad.. at people like Sayaka-san
and you, trying to make me do judo!
Seconds of kimpira goboh, please!
Sure.
Hey, are you listening?
Grandpa!
Another bowl of nameko miso-soup!
And so, the place will be the National
Martial Arts Hall, with national TV
coverage provided by Oshiuri TV.
And so, the place will be the National
Martial Arts Hall, with national TV
coverage provided by Oshiuri TV.
The First Oshiuri TV Cup Judo Tournament
Official Press Conference
I am extremely delighted to
announce this glorious event!
That was the tournament board president, Coach Yuutenji's comments.
And, as a feature, we will have a special
guest perform a model demonstration
before the start of the tournament.
Everyone, please welcome Inokuma Jigoro,
8th degree black belt!
I'm 9th degree!
That attention-hog gramps!
Uhh, uhh, testing..
Fix it, he's 9th degree!
I'm Inokuma Jigoro, Jya! I'm still strong enough to take on you young ones!
Umm, you're a bit too close to the mike...
Although I'm still physically able
to do a tournament...
... please forgive me for just doing that exhibi-whatever for you guys.
In place of me, my granddaughter, Inokuma Yawara, will probably astonish you!
So, she is going to be there!
Finally, in an official tournament!
Yawara will surely win!
With all ippon victories, too!
Umm, master, we were going to announce entrants right after you...
Coach Yuutenji! There's a rumor that Hon'ami Sayaka is signed up for this tournament, too..?
It's true.
Thought so!
You, too? The whole program's out of whack!
Her determination to be in this
tournament is awe-inspiring.
She's already in Hayama, training in preparation for this event!
Inokuma 9th degree, is there anything
special about Yawara-san's training?
My training is special every day.
Special every day? What type of training is it?
That is..
That is..?
A secret, Jya!
W... well, I shall announce the entrants now...
Okay, now we need to go interview
Inokuma Yawara in person!
Hurry!
Matsuda-san, we should hurry and
go to Yawara-san's place, too...
Matsuda-san? Matsuda-san!
Umm, the entrants are...
Hurry! Hurry!
If Yawara-san is surrounded by the media again, she'll probably refuse to participate!
I won't let that happen!
Yawara-san, this time,
you'll have to get serious!
Everyone, fight --
Oh!
Fight --
B... beautiful!
The sunshine, glistening your beads of sweat!
Your beautiful voice, echoing in
the school grounds!
Even if we forced you into it, I never
thought that you'd be our coach!
Had I not broken my leg, I would've
run with you and trained with you!
You fell in love with her, too, huh?
Y... you're that, Daily Every Sports'...
Matsuda.
Sorry, but she can't waste her
time doing this petty thing.
Petty thing? She's our official judo club coach!
That's why it's a petty thing.
H... hey, wait, you!
Okay. Let's do 3 laps of rabbit hops
around the school next!
What? That's impossible!
Yawara-san!
Hurry up, the reporters will mob you soon.
Reporters?
At the official press conference, your entry
into the tournament was confirmed.
Tournament?
At the official press conference, your entry
into the tournament was confirmed.
What?
Come on, let's go!
Hey, what are you doing?
Y... Yawara-san!
Th... that jerk! What are you
gonna do with Yawara-san?
Hold it!
Ha... Hanazono-san!
You mustn't chase her!
But, Yawara-san said she wasn't
going to be in the tournament...
Idiot!
B... but..
Bear with it. You must bear it.
Yawara-san isn't ours. She is a person destined to shine in Japan's judo world!
Quit acting cool, you dork!
With Yawara-san gone, what'll happen
to this wimpy judo club, huh!
Let me off! Let me off!
I don't want to be in the tournament!
Nope. You'll have to fight this one.
No way! I won't!
Listen up! You are the savior
of Japan's sports world!
You just made it that way!
Be more aware of your situation.
You're unbelievably strong.
Put that talent to good use!
No! If I do judo, I can't wear pretty clothes!
You can wear pretty clothes
after you do an ippon zeoi.
Cooking, too!
After winning a national tournament,
all your food can be eaten.
Who said anything about eating?
What? What did you say?
I want to learn how to cook!
Anyway, I want to fall in love normally,
and become a bride someday.
Even if you get a gold medal in the Olympics...
... you can still have a wonderful love life...
and be a normal bride, too.
What will be so normal about
a strong bride like that?
Let me off! Just let me off!
Kidnapper!
Watch it, watch it.. c'mon, it's dangerous!
Stop.. it!
All right then.. if you're gonna be that stubborn, let me show you something!
What? Where are we going?
To Hayama!
What?
Thank you very much.
Is she done yet?
How is the waist?
It fits just fine.
Oh, it looks wonderful!
Can I get this?
Sure, whatever.
How much is it, miss?
Okay. Thank you very much.
Oh man, geez. And it's before my next pay, too.
I'm so jealous! You're giving her a present! You're so lucky to be with such a nice boyfriend!
Wha.. that's not it.. we're not like that!
Huh?
W... well, I guess we are, huh?
Not at all!
Wow! Hey, is this someone's extra mansion?
Don't be surprised with that. Over here!
Wow, there's even a pool in the inner garden!
Oh yeah! There they are!
There! Look closely, Yawara-san!
Running in the sand with steel sandals...
... and dragging a giant tire..
This is Hon'ami Sayaka's rigorous training!
Fight, fight!
50 more meters!
Who do you think that fashionable
miss is doing that for?
Yawara-san, it's to fight you!
That's it, Sayaka-san!
Sayaka-san!
You don't feel anything after seeing this..?
Kazamatsuri-san..
Wha..?
Yawara-san, hey.. what's wrong?
You've been so quiet.
Yawara-san..
Yawara-san.. you're thinking
of Kazamatsuri, aren't you?
H... hey, don't ride the bus!
I'll take you home on my bike!
Yawara-san! Yawara-san!
H... hey! Do you have any money?
Darnit, geez, take my wallet!
Heh.. it's none of my business.
She's just news material.
And, she's only in high school..
she's 7 years younger than me.
She's still a kid.. a kid!
It's none of my business who
she likes and stuff.
I just want her to perform
well in judo.. that's all..
It it's an interview, please leave.
I'm not gonna interview, looking like this.
Could I borrow some money?
My bike died on me, and I can't get home.
Wha... what is this?
Oh, please don't get near this thing.
Don't talk to her like I'm a germ!
My gosh, does your newspaper not give
you any money for interviewing?
Excuse me. I lost my wallet for some reason.
Here, this should be enough, right?
Please leave immediately.
I'm really sorry.. to borrow
your shower and clothes.
And on top of that, some money, too.
I'll return it to you ASAP.
There's no need for you to return it.
Just don't come before us again.
No, I will definitely return what I borrowed.
Well, excuse me.
Oh yeah, Inokuma Yawara might
not be in the next tournament.
What?
Wha.. what did you say?
She had no intention of fighting
in the first place.
Even in the last practice match,
I practically forced her into doing it.
That's preposterous! Then what
is all our training for?
Well, there is a way to convince her to fight...
What should be done?
Oww..
It's Kazamatsuri Coach.
What about Kazamatsuri-san?
There's someone attracted
to Kazamatsuri Coach...
Don't say that in front of Sayaka-san!
Who is attracted to Kazamatsuri Coach?
Him! He likes me!
Hey, let's talk outside, alone.
Oh.. oh really? Is that so? Oh, I see!
I thought so.
Yawara-san feels for me.. I see!
Aren't you happy.
D... don't kid me! She's still in high school!
Hon'ami Sayaka is a high school girl also.
Huh? Don't tell me you think there's something going on between me and her?
Well, with your reputation, it's harder
to think that nothing's going on.
You're only aggressive with women, right?
Only if you could've used that
aggressiveness in judo matches!
What do you mean by that?
I'm saying that, had you used your
girl-chasing energies in judo matches...
You could've won at least the Nationals,
you nervous freak!
I don't chase girls.. they just become
attracted and come to me.
It's the girls that want me, just like Yawara-san.
Ahh, this is so stupid!
I wanted to ask you, but I changed my mind.
It was stupid of me to think
of asking you anyway.
H... hey wait! What were you
going to ask me to do?
Jesus! How could Yawara-san
fall for such a jerk!
Oh, I know!
Yawara-san will listen to what I say..
You wanted me to ask her to be
in the tournament, right?
I'll do it!
No! Don't get near her!
Don't worry, I can do it!
Inokuma Yawara!
That model demonstration for that tournament.
Should I go with this?
That was excellent, Father.
Tamao-san, you're here?
That was wonderful. I can watch it
for hours without getting bored.
Right, right?
Maybe I should prolong my demonstration time.
The audience would be so happy, they'll be moved with tears in their eyes!
Of course! If you do great, it'll encourage Yawara to do even better!
But, where is Yawara? Where is she...
Skipping practice, that delinquent girl!
It's Yawara.
That stupid child!
Yawara! What's wrong, Yawara?
We waited for you to eat dinner together.
I made your favorite -- doria!
Eii, Yawara! The tournament date's real close!
Hurry up and change into your judo outfit.
Today's doria has some tasty shrimps in it!
It's shrimps, Yawara! Shrimps!
Today's practice is uchi mata sukashi!
uchi mata sukashi -- inner thigh reaping throw slip
The uchi mata sukashi, Jya!
The uchi mata sukashi!
uchi mata sukashi -- inner thigh reaping throw slip
Kazamatsuri-san..
915 days to the Barcelona Olympics
Yawara, why are you spacing out?
Practice, child, it's time for practice!
What? Kazamatsuri-san has
something to tell me?
Why in the world..?
Eii, Yawara! You're still
mumbling over that guy?
But, Kazamatsuri-san is with Sayaka-san..
But.. but when he looks into my eyes, I..
I won't allow it!
I won't allow it, Yawara!
Next time, on "Yawara!" ...
Yawara's Date Has So Much Surveillance!
Those who don't watch will get my hiza-guruma!
hiza-guruma -- knee wheel
This episode was sponsored by:
David Seid
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental