kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Yawara-san!
At the official press conference, your entry
into the tournament was confirmed.
Tournament?
The place of event is the
National Martial Arts Hall.
National Martial Arts Hall?
The Oshiuri TV Cup!
What?
Fight, fight!
50 more meters!
Who do you think that fashionable
miss is doing that for?
Yawara-san, it's to fight you!
Sayaka-san!
Kazamatsuri-san..
Wha..?
Episode 14
Yawara's Date Has So Much Surveillance!
Can you hear me?
Right now, Yawara-san is at the Kichi-jyoji's Sun Road Cafe with her classmates.
I'll leave the rest.. to you!
Yawara, you're gonna get fat.
Something happened, didn't it?
Like, getting dumped or something..?
Thought so.
Was it perhaps Kazamatsuri-san?
That's sad.
I see.. you were dumped by
Kazamatsuri-san, huh?
Hey, Kyoko, you seem happy.
Are you interested in him?
O... of course not. No, no, no, no!
That's a shock. Kazamatsuri-san
was such a wonderful man.
B... but, you'll meet a more
wonderful person, Yawara.
Really? You don't meet such a great
person like that too often...
Wha.. geez!
But, you can't argue with genetics.
What do you mean by that?
We ate dinner at Yawara's house
a while back, right?
Well, she's eating exactly like the
way her grandfather ate.
Oh, that's true.
Y... Yawara, come on, cheer up!
I'm so sorry! I didn't mean to insult you!
Yawara..
Okay, next is Tokoro-ten!
You're gonna eat some more?
You're really gonna get fat.
But you do seem a little happier.
Eating made me happier. It's true
that "nothing beats appetite."
You guys are not going anywhere
until I'm finished.
What?
Come to think of it, it's not worth worrying
over a person or two like Kazamatsuri-san.
She's acting tough.
So it's reckless bingeing.
They say that lonely women get fat, right?
I was the only one thinking
it was a relationship.
From the beginning, Kazamatsuri-san must have only thought of Sayaka-san...
Ahh! Yawara! Red! The light's red! Red!
K.. Ka.. Ka..
Kazamatsuri-san!
I've been looking for you, Yawara-san!
W... well, we'll go on home, okay, Yawara?
Kazamatsuri-san, good afternoon!
Hey now, let's go!
You needed to talk to me?
I just wanted to see you, Yawara-san.
Oh? Isn't there someone else you
want to see, instead of me?
Oh geez, you're not your usual self, Yawara-san! Hahahaha!
You don't have time to laugh! Stop small talking and get to the core of the plan!
I didn't ask for you to go on a date with her!
I just asked you to urge Yawara-san
to be in the tournament!
Quit grinning like that! Hey,
don't get so close to her!
Why am I so irritated?
Oww! What was that for?
Sniffing around again? You hyena guy!
Inokuma-san. Why are you here?
I'm here to take my practice-skipping, delinquent girl home.
N... no, you can't go there!
Let me go, you..!
With an important tournament coming
up, she doesn't have time to fool
around with that glitzy guy.
They're at a critical point for
that important tournament.
What's that?
I'm having that guy urge her
to be in the tournament.
I don't need his help! I'll just drag
her into the tournament.
No, you can't do that!
Kazamatsuri-san, you..!
I thought it was strange for
you to cancel practice.
I just knew you went to see
that Inokuma Yawara!
You were wonderful in that match the other day.
You threw that massive giant,
Tohdoh Yuki, with an ippon zeoi.
ippon zeoi -- one arm shoulder throw
That has to be none other than a fine art!
You took a martial art like judo and
took it to the height of fine art.
Umm..
Won't you show me once more..
your ippon zeoi? Please?
That jerk!
Take it easy. Relax!
Why don't you have Sayaka-san show it to you?
Sayaka-san does judo more seriously than me...
She's more beautiful than me,
has a better figure, and...
Don't think like that. She doesn't
even come close to your beauty.
That's why she used her money
to hire me as her coach.
Gosh, that's not like you, Yawara-san.
I'm coaching for the sake of business.
If you didn't have Jigoro-sensei as your coach, I would have definitely chosen to coach you.
You seem down. We should
go to a different place.
Come on, let's go.
H... hey, those two are leaving!
All righty then, I'll conk his head with this!
Leave that piece of junk here!
Make sure they don't know that
they're being followed, okay?
Hmph! Why do I need to be sneaky, too?
Yawara! Go home and practice!
Yawara!
Practice!
Stop it! Every time you do that, Yawara-san refuses to be in matches!
Shut up! That guy is Hon'ami Sayaka's coach!
U... uhh, excuse us!
Y... you're..
Hon'ami Sayaka!
I... I just came to do some shopping.
Hey, wait!
It's your fault, Daily Every!
Inokuma-san! Had you stayed quiet,
it wouldn't have turned out this way!
This is a godsend!
I don't have any coins!
Sayaka-san.. you?
Excuse me, you're in the way
so please be seated.
Hmph! I can't sit in such a dirty seat!
Grandpa, if you'd like, have my seat.
I am NOT frail enough to
need to be offered a seat!
This is like a tortoise and a hare.
Can't you go faster? Didn't we tip
you more than enough?
Huh? Who told you to stop!
It's a bus stop.
My, that's a pain!
Well then, I'll just rent this bus.
Okay, no more complaints, right? Let me drive!
Oh, hey!
You're being reckless, Inokuma-san!
First of all, do you have a license?
I'm 8th degree black belt in judo!
Left! Go left!
Gotcha.
Where do you think you're going?
It's a bus-jack! Help!
It's a red light!
Ta.. take off, Jya!
When people see the ocean, for
some reason, they feel peaceful.
Do you know why Yawara-san?
In French, the word "ocean" is feminine..
as in "motherly ocean."
But, the ocean isn't just beauty.
It has the immeasurable ability to carve the continents and to change the shape of the world.
Just like you.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Have you ever thought of this, Yawara-san..
Your judo conquers the world, and the
world cheers you on with praise.
Yawara-san, I can clearly hear the large crowds joyfully cheering you on.
I never thought of something so grand.
You have no ambition. You can do it, you know. You need to live life more boldly.
I have a more.. local problem.
Geez, how much longer do
I need to sneak around?
Shh! Be quiet.
And what is this local problem, Yawara-san?
For example..
For example?
For example, I like this person,
but this person likes someone else.
And is always with this certain woman.
Nope. I think that's just your misunderstanding.
That person must be with this certain
woman for business purposes only.
Eii! What are they doing?
Just a little more!
I cannot stand to watch this any longer!
Man, you too?! Darnit, I can't
stand to watch this either!
Yawara-san, you will be in the
next tournament, right?
What are they...!
Stop it, you delinquent girl!
That jerk!
I cannot forgive them!
How bad does she intend to be?
Please let me think it over.
Yawara-san! You shine most
brilliantly when you do judo!
When I do judo, I..?
Who asked you to do THAT?
C... calm down now. What did I do?
Just because Yawara-san has feelings for you..
I just did what you asked for, which was
to urge her to be in the tournament.
I... Inokuma-sensei!
How dare you fool around with my granddaughter, you playboy!
No, you misunderstand!
I never, r... really..
Kazamatsuri-san.
Sayaka-san.
You, of all people.. YOU, of all people..!
Sayaka-san!
You made the situation more complicated!
You reap what you sow.
What?
Both of you.. don't you ever get near Yawara.
If something like this ever happens
again, I'll attend to you!
You'll be in the next tournament, right?
You shine most brilliantly when you do judo!
Ah, Yawara-san!
Everyone in the judo club..
Yawara-san, umm..
Why aren't you coaching us?
Even I have other things that keep me busy.
Yeah! You were probably dating some guy anyway! Despite having a man like me...
E... even he's frustrated.. since the summer tournament preliminaries are coming up.
But, Hanazono-san can't participate
because of his leg fracture..
And without your guidance, our team will surely lose in the first round again.
I was just forced into coaching by everyone.
I never agreed to be the coach.
Th... that's true.
And, you do have your own tournament
to prepare for, right?
Those guys! I told them not to
pressure Inokuma, but..!
I'm sorry. Well, goodbye.
Yawara-chan!
Please! Share just a piece of your strength!
Sudoh..
To tell you the truth, I don't care
about the judo club.
However, these upperclassmen
guys are just so pathetic!
I know that to you, Yawara-chan,
this is all a pain.
That's why we're begging you!
At least for once, I wanna.. I wanna..
Shine brilliantly!
S... S... Sudoh!
Hey, you guys, stop standing
there and beg, too!
Please!
Don't do such an embarrassing
thing in front of my house!
Please go home!
Yawara-san! Please!
Everyone.. and their selfish agendas!
I'm home.
Oh, Yawara.
Mom, I need some advice..
Great news! I got a new lead about
your father's whereabouts!
Really? Where?
At Shikoku, a person doing the hachi-jyu-hachi kasho meguri saw someone!
hachi-jyu-hachi kasho meguri --pilgrimage to the 88 holy spots.
A man in a judo outfit!
Really?
It has to be your father!
I'm leaving for a while again, but,
Yawara, you'll be okay, right?
S... sure.
Oh, what about my advice?
No. Nothing.
Well, I'm going. And, I already made dinner.
Mom..
Is this family split up because of judo?
It's because of judo that this household
is torn apart, isn't it?
Oh my, what are you saying, Yawara?
Because!
Yawara, it's totally the opposite.
Had it not been for judo, your father
and I would never have met.
He was so wonderful! Your father shone
most brilliantly when he did judo!
Shone.. most brilliantly?
Uh-huh. That's why I'm still out looking for him.
Oops, am I lusting?
Oh, it's already this late! Well then.
Take care of Grandfather, okay?
I'll call as soon as I find your father.
Mom...
Oh!
Are you Yawara's friends?
Yes, but I'd like to be more than just friends...
H... h...hey!
Yawara! Your friends are
waiting for you out here!
Well, I do need to go, so...
Yes, please excuse us!
Your father shone most brilliantly
when he did judo.
Had it not been for judo, your father
and I never would have met.
You shine most brilliantly when you do judo!
You will be in the next tournament, right?
Kazamatsuri Coach. Because you
tried to do that to Yawara-san...
... it's such a traffic jam, plus it's raining cats and dogs, and on top of that, we got a flat tire.
Don't blame me for everything!
I just did what you asked me to...
I didn't ask you to KISS Yawara-san!
Inokuma-san! It might help if you came
out to give us a hand, you know.
It's poison for senior citizens
like me to get wet from the rain.
At least for once.. I wanna.. shine brilliantly!
What? No way!
You're all crazy. Here's some towels!
Use this umbrella, too!
Inokuma!
For God's sake..!
Yawara-san!
Oh, Yawara-san! Yawara-san!
Please, Yawara-san!
Tomorrow.. let's meet at the
school dojo at 6am, okay?
I... Inokuma!
All right!
Tamao-san, could you get me a towel, please?
Because of that stupid girl, I'm all drenched!
Th... this is..?
Finally.. she's finally willing to do it, eh?
908 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
You're finally willing to do it, Yawara!
I'm shining brilliantly? Me?
I shine most brilliantly when I do judo?
Finally, the duel between you and
Miss Sayaka will happen, Yawara!
Is it true, Kazamatsuri-san?
Oh yeah, you need a black belt!
It's not cool to have on a
white belt, right Yawara?
I want to know.. I really want to find out!
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
A Challenge to Yawara Over Love!
Those who don't watch it will
get my oo-uchi gari!
oo-uchi gari -- large inner reap
This episode was sponsored by:
Julie Divola
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Kyonen wa anata to
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Eigakande miteta hazu
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Soba ni ite ne
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Ano koro no youni
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Otana ni naranaide