From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Yawara-san, you will be in the
next tournament, right?
What are they...?
Stop it, you delinquent girl!
You're all crazy. Here's some towels!
Use this umbrella, too!
Inokuma!
For God's sake..!
Yawara-san!
Oh, Yawara-san! Yawara-san!
Please, Yawara-san!
Tomorrow.. let's meet at the
school dojo at 5am, okay?
Episode 15
A Challenge to Yawara Over Love!
Musashiyama High School
So, this is the Musashiyama High School that Inokuma YOKOREMBO Yawara goes to, correct?
YOKOREMBO -- illicit love
Yes indeed, Miss.
I... Inokuma DOROBO-NEKO Yawara!
DOROBO-NEKO -- cat thief
I will teach you once and for all..
that's what's mine is mine!
Err, this is Inokuma Yawara-san, our official coach for our judo club from today.
Wow, Yawara-san!
She's cute!
Gorgeous!
..and sharpen our skills, and sweat together..
What the heck are you doing?
Well, I was thinking of putting a picture
of Yawara-san in my wallet.
How dare you..!
What in the world are you thinking...
Yawara-san! Yawara-san!
U... umm, could I have your autograph?
Hey guys, don't be so pushy.
Hey! W... what did you join the judo club for?
Well, obviously, because..
We wanted to spend our youth
with Yawara-sempai! Please!
This school is rather dirty.
Well, Miss, compared to your school,
Seishin Jyo-Gakukan..
And, it kind of smells, too.
Well, compared to Seishin Jyo-Gakukan..
Oh my gosh, it's co-ed!
All the guys look like such losers.
Hey look, a real babe!
That uniform is Seishin Jyo-Gakukan!
Err, the judo club dojo is at..
Let's finish up the matter quickly
so we can go home, Miss..
Miss... Ahh!
Hey girl! Won't you have some tea with us?
Oh, Miss!
Nice timing. Do you people know
where the judo club dojo is?
We know, we know!
It's that shack behind the gym.
Forget that. Let's go eat some oshiruko.
oshiruko -- cold sweet bean soup with
rice cake dumplings
Come on!
No! Stay away!
What are you trying to do to her!
Who's this old geezer?
M... Miss, let's go home!
That's why I hesitated to bring
you to a place like this!
Whaddya mean by "a place like this"?
C'mon, let's go eat some oshiruko!
O... okay then!
If you must then I shall go eat
oshiruko with you!
Y... yeah right! Why do we have
to eat oshiruko with you!
Let's be friends...
Miss!
To be friends with me, you're 10..
no a 100 years too early!
Th... this is supposed to be the judo hall?
Even my beloved dog, Charles,
wouldn't live in such a dump!
Yes indeed.
Oh well. I need to have a word
with Inokuma Yawara.
O... oh, Miss, please keep it peaceful!
Tokunaga, open it. Even the doorknob is dirty.
Yes.
We'll die if we do anything more!
We quit the club!
To... Tokunaga, what was that?
Wait!
I'm sorry! I'll make it easier,
so please come back!
Let them go, Inokuma! We don't need
anybody that can't handle your training.
That's right, Yawara-san.
The summer tournament preliminaries
are coming up, so please don't
worry and train us harder.
But, over a hundred people joined,
and they all quit.
The only new member that stayed is Sudoh-kun.
100 pushups, 100 bridge pushups..
and 1000 mock throwing..
Those softie Yawara-chan followers
can't handle that.
You need to be a hard-core fan like me to...
Don't act so cool while you're barfing!
Hanazono-kun!
To break my leg at a time like this,
Inokuma, and not train with you,
makes me feel so ashamed.
Sayaka-san!
What are you trying to do
with those sweaty boys?
W... why?
I've come here today to speak
to you about something.
Matsuda-san, how do you plan to pull Yawara-san into the tournament?
How should I know!
It's all Kazamatsuri, that pervert's fault!
Because he tried to do something to Yawara-san, everything's down the drain!
But, who knew that Yawara-san
had a crush on Kazamatsuri!
Good looking guys are so lucky. We should
be jealous, huh, Matsuda-san?
Kamoda! You're pretty persistent.
Why should I be jealous, huh?
I don't have any special feelings toward her!
She's just...
News material, right?
Th... that's right. That's exactly right.
But, you know..
But what?
Ever since you found out abouther feelings toward Kazamatsuri, you seem a bit irritated..
W... what part of me is irritated?
She's just a high schooler.
Why do I have to get irritated over such a kid?!
Wha... what is it?
Look at that!
Hon'ami Sayaka!
What is she here for?
Seems like something might happen.
What is it that you wanted to talk about?
Don't give me that attitude, especially since you're trying to steal what's mine.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'm talking about Kazamatsuri-san.
From now on, please stop enticing him.
I have not done that!
What's wrong, Inokuma?
Hey, what a pretty chick.
Oh look, you have so many
wonderful boyfriends.
You have an Easter Island
Stone Face big man and..
A street gangster.. what a perfect match!
You're a street gangster!
You're a Stone Face!
What the heck is that?!
Hold it!
Sayaka-san, what are you trying to say?
Stop trying to allure Kazamatsuri-san.
I never tried to allure him.
This is more intense than a judo match!
An extremely volatile confrontation
between love-rivals!
Dammit, why is a pervert like
Kazamatsuri so popular, eh?
See, you're irritated ... Oww!
H... Hi, Daily Every reporters!
Sayaka-san didn't happen to
come by here, did she?
I heard that she wanted to come
here to speak to Yawara-san..
Heheh, that's exactly what's happening.
They're throwing sparks over you as I speak.
There, take a closer look, you perv!
There, there!
Hmph. You probably have no intention of being in the next tournament anyway.
Acting as if you're going to be
in the tournament, just to get Kazamatsuri-san's attention.
My, what a kniving scheme!
Kazamatsuri?
But, it won't be like that anymore.
I've always gotten what I've wanted.
And I always will.. forever!
Do you understand, Kazamatsuri-san is mine!
Do... you... understand?
So, stop getting attention by playing around on your decision of being in the tournament or not.
If you don't want to be in it, fine. Don't.
It's already a fact that I'm Number 1
in Japan for judo.
It's because I have Kazamatsuri-san
as my strong ally.
Hey, hey. Don't give us your selfish crap.
The Number 1 in Japan is
Yawara-chan, you dork!
A street gangster like you has
no right calling me a dork.
Inokuma Yawara! If you so desire, we can settle this right here, right now!
Screw you! Yawara-san doesn't
need to fight you.
I'll bust that snobby nose of yours...
Hey, Sudoh! Straighten up! You OK?
So.. Do you now know how strong I am?
Well, let's go home, Tokunaga.
If we stay at this dirty place any longer,
we might get sick.
Y... yes, Miss.
Tokunaga, when we get home,
disinfect all of our clothes.
Yes.
Wait.
I haven't played around with
my feelings for attention.
And.. I've already decided..
I will.. be in.. the next tournament!
I want to find out if I shine
brilliantly when I do judo.
Just this time.. I'll do it.
Hmph, then I can soon make it clear
that I'm Number 1 in Japan..
... in front of everyone in Japan..
..in two weeks, at the National Martial Arts Hall!
Prepare yourself for this fight.
D... did you hear that, huh?
M... Matsuda-san, you're shaking the camera.
Hmm. It seems as if my date worked, after all.
Why are you looking like that?
Aren't you supposed to be a bit more grateful?
You're jealous, aren't you, Matsuda-san?
Oww, oww, oww!
Soon To Confront!!
Hon'ami vs Inokuma!!
Both throwing sparks at Musashiyama High Judo Hall
The One Showing Weakness Shall Lose
Soon To Confront!!
Hon'ami vs Inokuma!!
Both throwing sparks at Musashiyama High Judo Hall
The One Showing Weakness Shall Lose
Everything is going as calculated.
Soon To Confront!!
Hon'ami vs Inokuma!!
Both throwing sparks at Musashiyama High Judo Hall
The One Showing Weakness Shall Lose
To sharpen one's skills by fighting rivals opens up the path to the gold medal
and National Achievement Award.
That Kaza-midori or Kaza-matsuri or whatever..
Yawara must have finally discovered that
she can't waste time on a guy anymore.
Kazamatsuri-san!
Fifteen years since I've started judo...
I finally have to tie on a black belt...
Begin!
..since Grandpa said that it wouldn't be cool to wear a white belt at the National Martial Arts Hall.
Ippon!
Ippon -- a win, full 10 points
That's Inokuma Yawara?
I... Incredible!
Don't go wild over just a first degree black belt.
Yawara's ability is 4th degree, no, 5th degree..
Heck, she's already 6th degree!
That's not true! I'm not that strong, really.
Don't be so modest, Yawara.
One of you must be 4th degree or 5th degree.
Just throw them and show your true strength.
Grandpa!
Hey wait, we shouldn't waste time
earning one rank at a time.
Let's jump straight to 6th degree and go home.
Won't somebody fight Yawara?
Grandpa, that's enough!
Ranking exams need to be
passed for each rank up...
... and I can only get up to 2nd degree
until I'm 20 years old.
Eii! Everyone here is so spineless!
Quiet down over there!
Oh, it was you, Inokuma-sensei?
What degree are you?
I'm 5th degree, but..?
Great! Then you go against Yawara!
Grandpa!
I'm sorry, he's just blabbing nonsense.
Yawara, don't apologize. You really
are 6th degree or more.
Grandpa!
Hurry up and change into your judo outfit!
Geez, Grandpa!
Recently, I feel like Grandpa's pawn.
But..
You shine most brilliantly when you do judo.
Kazamatsuri-san!
Yawara-chan!
Oh, you finished changing already?
Inokuma..
We missed it, Hanazono-san.
Eh? That's not what I came for!
By the way, Inokuma, the date for the
summer tournament preliminaries is set.
The first round is next Sunday, against Todoroki-dai Kita High School.
Is that a strong team?
Compared to our pathetic team,
any team is stronger...
We are no longer our old selves.
Because of Inokuma, we all became stronger!
Oh.. really...?
Don't laugh weakly! Be more confident!
But, you know, we never won
any official games yet, so..
It'll be okay. You've all worked so hard.
All of you should be really strong now.
Th... that's true.
We endured all of Yawara-san's training..
..and, we just need to follow Yawara-san's instructions during the match.
You'll come right, Yawara-san?
Of course! I don't know if I can help you,
but I'll be there to cheer you on!
Definitely, on next Sunday -- ah?
Next Sunday?!
O.oh yeah! The same day as YOUR tournament!
What time is your match?
It's an afternoon match, so it's from 3pm.
The Martial Arts Hall matches start from 12pm, and the number of matches are..
It's okay, I think I can make it.
Don't push it, Inokuma! You should just concentrate on your matches!
But, if Yawara-san isn't there..
Don't depend on her. Just leave it to me!
Heh! What can a fractured gorilla like you do?
Say what? It's your fault that
my leg hasn't healed yet!
It's your fault for being such an idiot!
What did you say?!
This is not the time to fight
amongst yourselves!
Anyway, I'll come as soon as
I finish my matches, okay?
So, to prepare for the matches,
let's do the last bit of fine tuning.
Let's drive on, okay!
..o.ohh..
I can't hear you!
OHH!
OHH -- yeah
Next person, come on!
It's almost perfect.
My coaching is excellent, but Sayaka-san's ability to absorb all of it amazing too.
I'm not exaggerating to say that both
of our extreme talents came together
in her to produce such results.
I guess this explains why Sayaka-san's
father took a liking to me.
Nowadays, my Sayaka seems so lively. Especially since she usually
gets bored so easily.
But this time, this judo, is different.
It seems that your coaching and your
presence has affected her greatly.
I'm humbled.
Look out this window.
Ferrari's new model. It's not sold in
Japan yet, but just take it.
It's your bonus.
Th... that's.. for me?
Is it not enough?
N... no, it's more than enough!
Thank you very much!
By the way, how's this..
Won't you permanently stay
in the Hon'ami Group?
You're graduating college this year, right?
Yes..
Eventually, I'd like you to take
on an important position..
..since I'm sold on your skills
of developing Sayaka well.
I'm honored.
And, this is also an eventual thing, but..
Yes?
Won't you please guide my Sayaka forever?
Forever... meaning?
Well, I'm asking if you could keep that intention in mind when you keep her company.
Unless, you have a person like that already?
N... no, not at all!
Well then, that's wonderful. My Hon'ami Group's future is in safe hands then.
Oh yes, I'll give you another bonus next month. How would you like a cruise ship?
Cruise ship? That's great!
Kazamatsuri-san!
Something wrong?
N... no.. nothing, really.
I'm done with randori.
randori -- free sparring
How did I do?
It's perfect.. almost.
Almost? I threw all the men skill fully,
but it's still "almost"?
I think it's absolutely perfect!
If it's a regular opponent, that is.
But, your opponent in three days
will be that Inokuma Yawara.
Oh, that's right. It's that girl you
tried to kiss, Inokuma Yawara...
As I said before! That was just to
convince her to be in the tournament..
Oh well, I settled that matter
with her the other day.
Anyway, I will defeat Inokuma Yawara
and become Number 1 in Japan..
..since, there's nothing I cannot get a hold of!
Ahh, that's it!
What?
N... no..
Well, it's time for some tea.
Tokunaga, prepare some tea.
Yes, Miss Sayaka.
There's nothing that she can't get a hold of.. she must have asked her father to get me.
Hon'ami Group's important position..
is a pretty good offer.
But, what is this nagging feeling in my heart?
Matsuda! What is this wimpy article?
Your enthusiasm over Inokuma Yawara used to pour out from between the lines!
Are you slacking off, huh?
In your case, you need to indulge yourself into liking the news material more and more and more-
Chief..
Matsuda-san got dumped by Yawara-san..
I know that, Chief! You don't
have to tell me twice!
I still like Inokuma Yawara.. the judo athlete!
Ever since I first saw you,
my enthusiasm hasn't changed.
Ever since I.. first saw you.
Ka... Kamoda!
G... gotcha!
But.. another feeling has mixed
into that enthusiasm.
That's what made my article so wimpy.
Yawara-san! You can't stay
where I can reach you.
You need to go farther away.
Yeah, to a really faraway place.
But, that'll happen real soon.
You'll definitely become an
almost unreachable person.
Tomorrow, at this National Martial Arts Hall.
901 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
What? Sudoh-kun got hurt?
Finally.. finally, your debut at the
National Martial Arts Hall, Yawara!
Hey, Yawara!
But if Sudoh-kun can't do it, then there's not enough people to do the team match!
You don't have time to be
involved with that bunch!
Why can't you show your good face to the audience in the National Martial Arts Hall?
But, but..!
Yawara! Are you listening, Yawara?
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
Yawara's National Martial Arts Hall Debut!
If you don't watch it, I'll do
a ko-uchi gari on you!
ko-uchi gari -- small inner reap
This episode was sponsored by:
Julie Divola
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
I watched the video through the night.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Stay right here next to me,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
I don't want you to grow up yet.