kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
I will.. be in.. the next tournament!
I want to find out if I shine
brilliantly when I do judo.
Just this time.. I'll do it.
Hmph, then I can soon make it clear
that I'm Number 1 in Japan..
... in front of everyone in Japan..
..in two weeks, at the National Martial Arts Hall!
Episode 16
Yawara's National Martial Arts Hall Debut!
The First Women's Judo Oshiuri Cup
How long is this going to last?
Hurry up and start the matches!
Dammit, the model demonstration is
supposed to be only for 5 minutes!
It's already over 30 minutes now!
I... Inokuma-sensei, your time's up!
Please stick to the schedule!
Who's the fool that got the gramps
to do the opening ceremony?
Splendid! He did it!
Ah, screw it! Forget him.
We'll edit him out later,
so don't tape him anymore.
Isn't Inokuma Yawara here yet?
It's almost time, too.
Yawara-san.. isn't ditching
this tournament, is she?
Players' Waiting Room
Wh... what? Inokuma Yawara isn't here yet?
I entered this tournament to fight her.
I will beat her this time!
Next!
Judo is power and intensity! Which is why I gained 10 more kilos [22.5 lbs].
It's so noisy! That's why I hate shared rooms.
M... Miss, please bear with it
just a little while longer.
Tokunaga, go find another waiting room.
I don't want to be with a she-gorilla.
What did you say?
Who are you calling a she-gorilla?
Oh my, what a large face.
What did you say?!
You're saying gibberish about
fighting Inokuma Yawara...
... but you won't be able to do that.
Do you understand, TODO-san?
TODO -- sea cow
It's Tohdoh!
No matter how much you win, you're
going to fight me in the semi-finals.
So why won't I be able to
fight Inokuma Yawara?
You're dumb, aren't you?
In the semi-finals, I'm going to defeat you.
I will fight Inokuma Yawara in the finals.
How dare you brag!
Oh, it's the truth.
Tokunaga, the coat's dirty.
Give me another.
Y... yes!
Is this.. no.. this.
Don't you forget about me!
I won't forget, TODO-san.
TODO -- sea cow
It's Tohdoh! I'll crush that
snobby face of yours!
With an already crushed-up face like yours,
I guess you have no worries.
What did you say?
What are you doing, Yawara-san?
Listen, Hatakeyama-kun, your left arm
pull is rather weak, so be careful.
National High School Tournament, Tokyo District Preliminaries
Listen, Hatakeyama-kun, your left arm
pull is rather weak, so be careful.
Tomioka-kun, don't get intimidated.
You need to glare back at them, too.
That's good enough, Inokuma. Now go
to the National Martial Arts Hall.
Y... yeah. If you don't hurry, it's gonna start.
But..
Don't worry. They absorbed everything
you've taught. Right?
Oh!
Oh -- yeah
I... Inokuma.. I.. I'm extremely delighted!
The reason why these guys have such
brave voices is because you gave
them the confidence they needed!
It's not all my doing.
The limo has arrived! Yawara-chan,
hop on! I'll take you to the station.
Well then.. I'll go.
Yeah. Do your best, Inokuma.
You'll surely become Number 1 in Japan.
Fight, Yawara-san!
Do your best!
And win!
You guys do your best, too. You'll surely win.
As soon as I finish my matches,
I'll come back. See you!
Hang on tight. I'll go full throttle!
Everyone, do your best, okay!
Inokuma.
You'll.. you'll definitely win.
And.. you'll become an unreachable superstar.
That's good. It has to be that way.
Inokuma!
Sudoh-kun, listen. Since Hanazono-kun
has a broken leg...
...everyone is depending on you today.
I know. Anyway, hang on tighter.
Okay.
Yahoo!
Geez! Don't be so reckless!
Y... yes.
But.. I think of you differently now, Sudoh-kun.
I never thought you'd do judo so seriously.
W... well, that's because you're the coach.
Hey, Sudoh-kun, promise me.. that you
won't use judo in fights anymore.
Of course not! How could I ever use the judo that you taught me, Yawara-chan, in fights!
Promise me!
I already did!
Hey.. that's Sudoh.
Heheh! Found something fun!
Well, Yawara-chan, do it right!
Long time no see, eh, Sudoh?
O... oh, hi.
Riding a bike with a girl.. ahh, youth!
I... I'm in a hurry, so..
Don't ignore us!
W... what are you doing?
Why you..! Don't act like you
didn't do those things!
Wha... what things?
Doing those things to Yoshikawa-san's
girl, Shimazaki's girl, and even my girl!
And still you deny it, huh?
Wh... what are you saying?
I didn't do anything! I didn't!
Quit lying!
Players' entrance!
It's Inokuma Yawara!
Inokuma came!
She came!
She has come!
Excuse me, please let me through.
I need to change.
Umm, the locker room is..
Over here!
A spectacular show! It's nice and dramatic
to have the big player come last.
G... Grandpa.
So, shall we go get it.. the status
of being Number 1 in Japan!
Y... You jerks!
How dare you take advantage of me..
because I don't fight back!
Don't use it for fights, okay?
Yawara-chan.
What's wrong? Weren't you gonna throw me?
You guys aren't worth it.
What?
Hey, Sudoh..
You really want to..
DIE, don't you?
Hanazono-san, what happened to Sudoh?
Players' Waiting Room
That idiot is probably trying to pick
up on some girls somewhere.
Sudoh!
As promised, I didn't use judo for fights.
Sudoh, what's wrong? Hey, get up! Hey!
The first round has begun.
What? What did you say?
Yuhkoh!
Yuhkoh -- partial 5 points
Calm down and explain it slowly.
What happened to Sudoh?
W... well, Sudoh was battered by his
old sempai or whatever.. and...
Hanazono-san and Kohno took him
to the doctor's office now, but..
But, if Sudoh-kun doesn't fight, you guys
can't do the 5-on-5 team matches!
You guys will lose by default!
Wh... what should we do, Yawara-san?
There's nothing I can do..
Doctor's office
I can't do anything about it.
So, he can't do any judo matches now?
Are you kidding? He needs to be
stabilized for quite a while.
He fractured his left arm, chipped 3 teeth,
and has a severe concussion.
You big, fat, lumbering idiot!
H... hold it!
Y... Yawara-chan..
The fourth match is between Fujisawa Kumi, 2nd degree, and Inokuma Yawara, 1st degree.
Yawara-san, where did you go?
Geez, she's such a pain in the butt!
Okay, calm down. I'll go there as
soon as I'm through here.
What are you doing?
Wh... wha..?
You're up next! The match!
Y... Yawara-san? Yawara-san?
This is not the time to do such things!
You don't have time to be
on the phone right now.
But..
But, schmut! You have a match to do!
But, it's a serious situation now!
It's serious over here, too.
Now go!
I'm doing a match in this.. big place?
Come to think of it, this IS the
National Martial Arts Hall.
I came here for concerts before, but..
But, I never imagined that I'd be standing here!
She's finally come to fight me!
She has finally come.. to fight me!
You're gonna lose to me in
the semi-finals and cry!
Oh-hohohoh! It's you that's going to cry.
Though your crying face wouldn't
be too cute anyway.
You gotta stay calm, Yawara-san.
Main table, main table.
I'm going to get comments from
Inokuma Jigoro-sensei about his granddaughter's first official match.
One comment, please.
Don't get riled up just over this.
Don't get so excited over
this cheap, little match.
Yawara has the gold medal and the National Achievement Award waiting for her, you...
Th... that's it for now! Back to you, main table!
Stay calm, Yawara-san!
Just do as you always do!
That's true. I can't waste time here.
I need to hurry back to the judo team.
Inokuma's opponent is the 52-kg
weight class All-Japan champ...
Fujisawa Kumi, 2nd degree.
Bow!
What intensity! Maybe I should lose.. then
I could go to everyone's place quicker..
You shine most brilliantly when you do judo.
Okay.
Begin!
I.ippon!
Ippon -- full 10 points, a win
A... awesome!
How strong! Inokuma Yawara
is truly invincible!
She got an ippon victory in
less than 2 seconds flat!
Coach Yuutenji, what are your comments.. about this genius judo girl?
Genius? That's not enough to describe her!
Her strength is from an accumulation
of effort upon effort!
That razor-sharp execution
comes from pure devotion!
I'm astonished at the level of jujitsu perfection!
I want to applaud not only to Yawara-san,
but also to her excellent master,
Inokuma Jigoro-sensei!
Main table, I'd like to get a happy comment from that master, Inokuma Jigoro-sensei.
One comment, please.
I told you not to get riled up over just this.
Yawara has the gold medal and the National Achievement Award waiting for...
Tha... that's it for now! Main table, main table!
That was the greatest, Yawara-san!
Wha.. what can I say.. this feeling..
Move it, move it! I need to make a phone call!
Phone call? Again?
Where have you been calling?
Setagaya's 12th Gym.
Setagaya's 12th?
Isn't that where the High School National Preliminaries are being held?
The Musashiyama Judo team
is in serious trouble.
What? Hanazono-kun is going
to be in the match?
Y... yes. Hanazono-san is taking off the cast..
Please don't!
W... wait a minute!
Even if the cast is off, he can't
fight with that leg!
Ah! Hanazono-san!
He's taking the cast off by himself.
Wha.. how reckless!
Inokuma? Hey, Inokuma!
Hanazono-kun? A... are you okay?
No problem! It was getting itchy,
so it was about time.
Listen, Inokuma. You just concentrate
on becoming Number 1 in Japan!
We will win, too.
We'll win!
Yup!
How about your leg? Doesn't it hurt?
This leg is just fine.
Hanazono-kun? Hanazono-kun?
Wha... wha... wha... what happened?
Yawara-san, it's no good after all.
Wh... what should we do?
NO! It's okay! We're not going to waste Inokuma's efforts of coaching this team!
Ha... Hanazono-kun..
Ippon!
Hon'ami Sayaka has won the
first 2 rounds with ease.
Sayaka! Sayaka!
A Job well done.
Whoa! She's blowing kisses!
The fans are going wild!
Hmph! Getting all snotty!
It's just fan service.
Those punks will cry over your
defeat in the semi-finals.
Nobody will cry over your defeat.
My, how pitiful!
Okay, next up is a seed player, Tohdoh Yuki.
Uh.. what an intensely frightful look!
Inokuma! We need to go soon.
You do your best, too.
You can't, Hanazono-kun!
I'll be looking forward to the news
of you becoming Number 1!
Hanazono-kun..
Hello? Hello? Hello... He hung up.
I want to go advise them.. Hanazono-kun
and everyone else, too.
Don't be stupid!
But, everyone worked so hard every day!
Yet, at this rate, they might lose
in the first round again!
Ippon!
Ippon -- full 10 points, a win
Don't think about anything right now.
You need to go again soon.
B... but..
All right, say your advice in this!
What?
I'll be your messenger!
Ma... Matsuda-san!
Hanazono-san, let's quit! Come on, let's quit!
I'm okay. You guys straighten up, too.
We need to live up to Inokuma's coaching. Right?
Y... yeah..
Ah, don't get so intimidated over
Todoroki-dai Kita High!
We'll just flip'em around like pancakes!
Who are you gonna flip around like pancakes?
To... Todoroki-dai Kita High..
It's no good, is it?
Hang on, Musashiyama Judo team!
I'll deliver Yawara-san's voice to you!
Yawara-san.. you better win!
Ippon!
Ippon -- full 10 points, a win
Th... the invincible Inokuma Yawara!
Both matches were won in a total
of less than 5 seconds combined...
...with all ippon zeois,
she's made it to the finals!
ippon zeoi -- one arm shoulder throw
It's almost time for her to fight me!
It's almost the time for her to fight me!
U... umm..
Yawara has the Olympic...
Th... that's all for now! Main table!
Those were such glamorous victories.
Sayaka-san.
You're next, right, Sayaka-san?
Please do your best.
I don't need that from you!
Right, Kazamatsuri-san?
Huh? Well, you know..
Excuse me.
Sa... Sayaka-san!
Yawara-san..
Okay, the next match is between
Hon'ami Sayaka and Tohdoh Yuki.
Which one will fight Inokuma in the final round?
It's me.
It has to be me, of course.
No, ME!
No, ME.
894 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Everyone, do your best!
As long as you do your thing, you'll win.
Yawara! Come on, look at it!
Miss Sayaka and Tohdoh Yuki's
match is about to start.
All of you practiced so hard. You'll do fine.
Those two are really determined to fight you.
This is gonna be fun!
I want to go.. now, to everyone's place!
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
Yawara's Love Message
One more ika-chinmi, Jya!
This episode was sponsored by:
Tom Smith
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Soba ni ite ne
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Otana ni naranaide