From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Hon'ami Sayaka, Tohdoh Yuki,
and Inokuma Yawara.
Each has won past the second round.
This women's judo tournament is
about to get more interesting.
Bow!
Hanazono-kun.
Yawara-san, it's no good after all.
What should we do?
NO! It's okay! We're not going to waste Inokuma's efforts of coaching this team!
Ippon!
She did it!
Inokuma Yawara, with an ippon zeoi,
has easily made it to the final round.
And, in the second semi-finals match,
we have the intense rivalry between
Hon'ami Sayaka and Tohdoh Yuki.
Who is going to fight the extremely
strong Inokuma Yawara?
Episode 17
Yawara's Love Message
Yes... that's right.
I would like to speak to a Musashiyama
High team member, please.
They've already entered the arena.
Is there any way to speak to them?
They're in a match already, so...
I see. Sorry to bother you.
That was very wonderful!
Wonderful, absolutely wonderful!
Yawara-san, with your expert techniques, nobody can stop you!
Kazamatsuri-san.
You are shining... very brilliantly!
The semi-final match between Sayaka-san
and Tohdoh Yuki is about to begin.
This may sound bad, being Sayaka-san's coach, but neither of them will be able to beat you...
... because you shine so brilliantly.
Kazamatsuri-san, I..
What's wrong? Let's go watch
the semi-finals together.
Everyone, cheer up! It's okay.
Every one of you has the power to win.
I.. Inokuma.
I.. It's Yawara-san's voice!
Everyone, listen carefully...
Yawara-san!
Hey! Stop caressing the tape player!
It's all your fault this happened
in the first place!
But Yawara-san is more worried about
your matches than hers.
Don't you guys understand her feelings and want to win one for her, like a man?
Inokuma! She cares so much about us!
She's so... she's so..
Idiots! If you wanna be a man, don't cry
like that! Yawara-san is trying hard,
so follow her example!
How are Inokuma's matches going?
Don't worry about her. She should have made her way to the finals with all ippon victories.
This tape player has crucial advice
for you guys on how to win.
Especially for you and your injured leg, Hanazono-kun!
Take her feelings and words
to heart and win for her!
If you lose, I'll get on your case!
We will now begin the seventh preliminary match between Musashiyama High
and Todorokidai Kita High.
Okay, that fired me up!
Let's go get 'em, everyone!
Ei, ei, oh! Ei, ei, oh!
[Ei, ei, oh! -- group pep cheer]
Your long, shabby hair is in the way.
Can't you do something about it?
What's more in the way is your huge potbelly.
What did you say? Are you taking
judo seriously at all?
Hey! Refrain from personal comments!
And you have makeup on!
My dogi will get dirty!
It's a cheap one anyway. If you need it cleaned, just hand it over to Tokunaga.
Shut up, you stupid woman!
Calm down now!
S.. such intensity! These two are ready
and fired up to start the match!
I will fight Inokuma Yawara!
I will.
Me!
Me.
I'm telling you, it's me!
No, me.
I hope everyone's okay.
See, Yawara-san?
The two of them are getting excited
over you. It's so exhilarating!
Begin!
Whoa! Tohdoh boldly charges!
Unfortunately for you, I'll win this match.
I should say the same to you.
To prove my supremacy in judo and to show that Kazamatsuri-san is mine, I need to...
Oh wow! This is the first time since her debut that Hon'ami Sayaka was taken down!
The giant Tohdoh Yuki is pinning her
with a reverse kesa gatame!
[kesa gatame -- scarf hold]
Hon'ami's in a pinch!
I'll make you cry really.. really hard!
I.. Inokuma Yawara! Enjoy your moment
next to Kazamatsuri-san, but not for long!
I will not lose!
Whoa! Hon'ami is dragging the
giant Tohdoh to escape!
I will not lose!
I will not lose! Inokuma Yawara!
Halt!
Out of bounds!
That was close for Hon'ami! She escaped
the hold by going out of bounds.
Dammit!
I will not lose against her! Not until
I fight Inokuma Yawara!
Dosu-koi!
[Dosu-koi --sumo grunt]
Please, end it soon! It doesn't matter...
please, just end it soon!
Dammit! What's going on?
The match is gonna end!
Hanazono-san!
I'm scared!
Stupid, don't squirm! Th.. th. that's
the most intimidated loses!
Musashiyama High pointman, Hatakeyama-kun.
Y.. yes!
Y.. Yawara-san!
Hatakeyama, go for it!
Do it right!
Drive on!
Hatakeyama! Remember what Yawara-san said!
You'll do fine, Hatakeyama-kun.
You've completely mastered
the okuri ashi barai...
[okuri ashi barai -- trailing foot sweep]
... so just wait for the moment the
opponent shifts to the side.
Don't ever step in forward. Don't worry,
you can do it, Hatakeyama-kun..
Todorokidai Kita High pointman, Yasuhashi-kun.
Yes.
Uhh, to do the okuri ashi barai, force the opponent to shift to the sides and not the front..
What's with him? What's he babbling about?
Begin!
Wait for the side.. side shift timing..
The side.. the side...
Oh no, Yawara-san, he's not shifting sideways!
Oh no!
Ippon!
Dammit! If I can't write the article because I missed the finals match, I'll get fired for sure!
Hon'ami vs. Tohdoh. Neither is budging
and it's dragging into a long stretch.
Which one will make it to the finals?
Tohdoh Yuki, or Hon'ami Sayaka?
Me!
Hurry, hurry up and end it! Please!
The semi-final between Hon'ami and Tohdoh. It's a great rivalry, as expected.
But neither of them show any hint of movement.
I wonder why?
They're not moving because they can't move.
This is turning out to be a great battle!
No, they just suck.
Geez, what are they doing?
The Musashiyama match will be over.
But, this isn't going anywhere. If only
they'd be more aggressive..
No, that's too risky. They're at equal levels,
so they can't risk a move.
Each is waiting for the other
to initiate something.
This match will probably drag
on for a long time.
Oh... Oh no.
Wait, Hanazono-kun. Where are you going?
What are you two doing? I don't care who wins. Let's get on to the finals match!
Y.. Yawara-san!
Th.. this is an unexpected outburst from Inokuma! She's boldly challenging
Hon'ami and Tohdoh!
N.. no, that's not what I meant!
Yawara sure knows how to get to them!
Whoa! It prompted Hon'ami to charge!
Inokuma Yawara! How dare you
stand out more than me!
I was waiting for you to move, Missy!
Tohdoh! Going for a planned uchi mata!
[uchi mata -- inner thigh reap]
Hon'ami! Grabbed the hooking leg and...!
Koka!
[Koka -- Partial 3 points!]
Almost! Hon'ami's sukui nage
wasn't complete, unfortunately.
[sukui nage -- scooping throw]
Attempting to pin her down, but is it possible?
I'm very sorry!
Don't cry, Hatakeyama. It's only the first match.
That's right. We'll just win
4 in row from here on.
But, I went against Yawara-san's advice
and charged in from the front.
Everyone, cheer up! It's okay. Every one
of you has the power to win.
Okay, Yawara-san's voice charged me up!
Hatakeyama, I'll win this one for you!
Musashiyama High second pointman, Kohno-kun.
Oh yeah!!
Because of Yawara-san, he became
really tough, huh?
Yeah.
All right! I'm ready for anything!
Sure.
As I said, I forgot my helmet
because I was in a hurry!
So you're saying that you don't need
a helmet if you're hurrying?
No, that's why I apologized several times!
The finals match at the National Martial
Arts Hall will be over soon!
Oh that. I wanted to see that, too.
Yawara-chan, right? I bought the ticket,
but I had to work today.
That was a real bummer.
Quit babbling and just write the ticket, dammit!
Despite Tohdoh's weight difference,
Hon'ami is faring well.
But, can she actually move this giant?
I.. Inokuma Yawara!
I've always got what I wanted.
But, ever since you appeared,
things have been going astray.
But, that will be the last of it!
There isn't anything in this world
that won't go my way!
Wha-?!
What?!
Sayaka-san!
Whoa!
There isn't anything in this world
that won't go my way!
Th.. this can't be!
I will be the Japanese judo champion
and have Kazamatsuri-san, too!
Amazing! Hon'ami flipped
Tohdoh's massive body!
Tohdoh is struggling to break free.
Can Hon'ami pin her for 30 seconds?
20, 19, 18, 17..!
And, Sayaka's supporters are counting down! Tohdoh is inching towards the boundaries!
I will be the one to fight Inokuma Yawara!
I will be the one to fight
Inokuma Yawara, TODO-san!
[TODO -- sea cow]
I am...!
I am... not a TODO!
[TODO -- sea cow]
Ippon!
Sayaka-san!
She did it! Hon'ami Sayaka has
made it to the finals!
She'll go against Inokuma Yawara!
Despite having a weight disadvantage,
she overcame it with strength and
willpower and won an ippon victory!
Well, it seems that I underestimated
Hon'ami Sayaka's abilities!
Even though she may have conquered
other sports, I doubted she'd pull
it off so easily with judo, but...
It seems that Inokuma Yawara sparked her.
To have a rival to sharpen each other's skills against and become stronger... that's judo!
The outcome of the finals is now unpredictable.
What's there to figure out?
Inokuma Jigoro sensei!
It's going exactly as I planned.
I'm the one who saw judo potential in
Hon'ami Sayaka and dragged her into it.
I also set her up as Yawara's rival to have them sharpen each other's skills to get stronger.
S.. so you're saying that the outcome of the finals will go along with your plan, too?
Absolutely.
Look, they're already throwing sparks
at each other with this rivalry.
Congratulations, Sayaka-san. Umm,
I don't know what to say, but..
I'll want to receive words of praise
from you after I beat you.
Well, regardless, that was really great!
I can't wait to see the two of you fight! Really!
Kazamatsuri-san.
Let's discuss our strategy for the
finals at the waiting room. Alone.
Uh, sure.
I'll teach you in the finals
that what's mine is mine.
Uhh, w.. wait!
Yuko!
[Yuko --Partial 5 points!]
Kohno is behind by two yukos, but he's
still hanging in there, huh?
Kohno, remember what Yawara-san said!
Kohno-kun, remember... the stance
with one knee bent, with your feet
3 and a half footlengths apart.
That's right. I practiced this
move day in and day out!
Yeah, you can do it, Kohno-kun!
Hah! This timing!
Now, Kohno-kun!
Ippon!
All right!
I did it!
Musashiyama High, Kohno-kun, tai otoshi ippon. The score is now 1-1.
[tai otoshi -- body drop]
There, Tomioka!
Pin him down!
Don't let go!
Tomioka-kun, your body weight becomes a powerful weapon for the tate shihoh gatame.
[tate shihoh gatame -- vertical 4 corner hold]
If you put all your weight
on him, you'll beat him.
Go, Tomioka! Hang in there! Go!
Out of bounds! Halt!
Oh, almost!
This is like a dream. These guys are fighting on the same level as Todorokidai Kita High.
These guys...! Inokuma, I owe it all to you! You are absolutely wonderful!
Please! At least take it to 2-2 until my round!
I have to win, even if my leg gets chopped off!
Inokuma, just for you!
Yes, the Musashiyama High match.
Yes.
Yawara.
I'll praise you for making it so far.
Grandpa.
But, Yawara, don't brush off that Miss so easily.
If it was only on strength, you'd surely beat her.
But, that Miss is fired up! She has such
an intense desire to defeat you!
She really is a fearful rival!
Yeah, she sure is a fearful love rival.
What's that?
N.. nothing, really.
Well, I'm in a hurry, so..
Wait, Yawara! Beware, and don't
brush it off so easily!
C'mon, I'd better make it on time!
Shortcut, shortcut!
Oh damn!
That was nothing!
Go, Tomioka! Hang on! There!
End of match!
Final decision!
Tomioka had the advantage, right?
Yeah.
Of course, Tomioka was so persistent!
Todorikidai Kita High, Iwamoto-kun.
Advantage victory!
Tomioka, good job!
Yeah, nice guts!
B.. but..
Y.. yeah, you fought hard to the end. Don't cry.
We'll take it from here, right, Yasui?
Yasui? Yasui?
Yasui! Go for it!
Oh no, he's not listening!
He's shaking!
Wh.. what?
It's 2-1. No turning back.
If I lose... If I lose, then Musashiyama
will lose, Yawara-san!
Ma'am, give me the ikataro and
the mamekichi-kun, please.
Well, I'd better hurry, before the match starts.
That back is...!
C.. could it be..?
I should've known. I didn't
expect him to come here.
That runaway son of mine, Kojiro!
Here comes Inokuma Yawara!
Such thunderous cheering!
Despite many exciting concerts held here...
... it has been a while since this National Martial Arts hall filled with such excitement over a martial arts event, like its namesake.
Discovered by a newspaper scoop a year ago...
... Inokuma Yawara has displayed her formidable strength from 15 years of
obscurity and intense training.
And, also a year ago, after defeating the
tennis queen, Navratilova, Hon'ami Sayaka suddenly switched over to judo.
And she conquered the judo world like a lightning -- that's Hon'ami Sayaka!
Inokuma-san, as soon as I defeat you and settle everything, I'll retire from judo.
Be honored to be the final person that proves Hon'ami Sayaka's utter supremacy.
Everyone, hang in there. I'll be there soon.
I'd better make it on time!
Begin!
887 Days until the Barcelona Olympics
Finally the finals match!
The fight against Miss Sayaka!
Hanazono-kun, hang on!
Everyone, I'll be there soon!
Yawara, don't take her too easily.
That Miss is really intense.
Hurry, I need to finish this match quickly!
Next time on "Yawara!" --
"The Decisive Battle! Yawara vs. Sayaka"
Watch it, or I'll do an uchi mata!
[uchi mata -- inner thigh reap]
This episode was sponsored by:
Christopher Dewane
Julie Divola
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental