kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Episode 18
The Decisive Battle! Yawara vs. Sayaka
The Oshiuri TV Cup.
Women's Judo Tournament.
Inokuma Yawara vs. Hon'ami Sayaka.
The final round of these two destined
rivals is just about to begin.
Bow!
Th.. this piece of junk.. the brakes doesn't work!
Inokuma Yawara-san.
Once I defeat you and end this rivalry,
I'll retire from judo.
I'll teach you in the finals that
what's mine is mine.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Listen, Inokuma. You just concentrate
on becoming Number 1 in Japan!
We will win, too.
We'll win!
Hanazono-kun... Everyone...
I won't allow any miserable fights.
Not for my beautiful perfection's sake.
Begin!
Phew, it's finally over.
Oh, now I need to go see
the Musashiyama team.
I.. Ippon!
[Ippon -- Win, full 10 points]
Sayaka-san, your false tooth fell off.
Here.
N.. no.
That can't be!
I.. I.. I apologize.
I neglected to announce this
instantaneous incident.
Perhaps all of you TV viewers are confused
as to what just happened.
Anyway, Inokuma Yawara won an
ippon victory with an ippon zeoi,
and has won the tournament.
Awesome. Awesome. Awesome!
You're awesome, Yawara-san!
I'm going to interview her first
in the locker room!
Matsuda-san!
Yawara-san?
Yasui!
Don't let him take your collar!
Don't just stand there, Yasui!
Out of bounds! Halt!
Your chance is when the opponent
lays down his left foot.
It's okay.
You blew out 3 candles with the wind
caused by your free foot. Yasui-kun!
Yawara-san.
I.. I can win, right?
Take you? To Setagaya's 12th Gym now?
Yes. Please take me.
We won't make it in time.
And your awards ceremony is about to start.
Take me!
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Win, full 10 points]
Ya.. Yawara-san. I did it!
All right!
Hanazono-san.
D.. don't worry.
Just leave the rest.. leave the rest to me..!
Quit screaming! You're the
one making me hurry!
I asked for you to hurry, but
don't be so reckless!
We might go to heaven before we
reach Setagaya's 12th Gym!
There's a reason why I can't drive safely.
The ------ on this bike are broken!
What? What did you just say?
The brakes are broken!
Musashiyama High Captain, Hanazono-kun.
Hanazono-kun. Don't let the opponent
know about your injured right leg.
That's right, Inokuma.
You're absolutely right.
Todorokidai Kita High Captain, Manjoume-kun.
Showing your weakness is the worst.
The opponent will mercilessly
attack that weak spot.
Hanazono-san...
I hope he's okay...
What's wrong, eh? Sweating up a storm?
Are you scared?
Don't kid me. What have you been looking at?
Inokuma Yawara threw me
before "Begin" was called!
M.. Miss..
If not...
If not, I couldn't have been thrown so easily.
Right? That has to be it!
No. Inokuma Yawara threw you
right after the "Begin" call.
To prove that, look.
The timer stopped at 2 seconds, see?
You're telling me to believe that
cheap, domestic clock?
Call the timekeepers over here right now.
Oh yeah, that timer's definitely wrong.
It's not two seconds after the
start of the match, but...
...rather, one second, see?
Tokunaga!
Y.. yes?
Bring the car out. We're leaving immediately.
M.. Miss!
I can't hang around too long in such
a ridiculous tournament.
My, how ridiculous!
Miss..
Kazamatsuri-san, we'll practice
as soon as we return home.
I can't just back away now.
B.. but, Sayaka-san. The awards ceremony...
..you're the runner-up... Sayaka-san...
Hon'ami Sayaka has given up the appeal.
It seems like she's accepted the final ruling.
But, Coach Yuutenji, wasn't Inokuma Yawara's ippon zeoi truly astonishing?
Yes, absolutely.
It was an absolute masterpiece of an awesome display of razor sharp skills!
Oh, the playback is on.
At the call of "Begin", Hon'ami
Sayaka first moves in.
Inokuma Yawara is already in position
for an ippon zeoi and..
...in one moment, she gets into
Hon'ami's space, and..
...in the next moment... A.. amazing!
She threw, using just the timing and natural body flexion with no strength at all!
Utterly amazing.
This is the true image of judo
that I have been striving for.
Not even close.
Inokuma Jigoro-sensei.
There, her left arm pull is still weak.
It'll be difficult for her to conquer the world,
or even Japan, at just that level.
World? Is the ultimate
objective the world then?
She'll get the Olympic gold medal, then
the National Achievement Award!
Out of bounds!
Halt!
We're going to lose.
Hanazono-san, let's quit.
I see. His right leg is hurt.
Our judo club has gotten stronger
with Inokuma's coaching.
I can't let this injury make us... make us... lose!
Wait for me Hanazono-kun! Everyone!
I'll be there soon!
What?
Inokuma Yawara and Hon'ami
Sayaka are gone?
With no champ and runner-up, how are we gonna do the awards ceremony?
Just find them!
Matsuda-san, where'd you go?
Hey, aren't we there yet?
Quit complaining!
Tokunaga, hurry up and start the car.
Y.. yes.
You're Hon'ami Sayaka, right?
See, the reporters are already
here because you're so slow.
I saw the match.
You will become even stronger.
Of course I will.
Tokunaga, hurry up and start the car.
But my daughter will get even stronger, too.
Daughter?!
We're here!
Now let's see if this bike's brakes work...
A.. awesome!
Dammit, he keeps going for my right leg!
Hanazono-kun. Hanazono-kun. Hanazono-kun!
I'm sorry, Inokuma.
I'm can't do it anymore.
I.. I'm starting to hear things.
Yuko!
[Yuko -- partial 5 points]
Osae-komi!
[Osae-komi --Hold-down!]
Hanazono-kun!
I'm s.. sorry, Inokuma. I'm at my limit.
My right leg isn't listening to me anymore..
Hanazono-kun! Hanazono-kun!
Ohh, I can hear your voice in my head..
Hanazono-kun!
But, I'm a wimp that gives up easily.
I.. I'm 100 years too early and unworthy
to fall in love with you.
Hang in there, Hanazono-kun!
Sorry. Forgive me, Inokuma!
Hanazono-kun!
I.. Inokuma!
Yawara-san!
Hanazono-kun, grab the back of
his collar with your left hand!
And then, hook your left leg into it!
Hurry! Hurry, or he's gonna
score an ippon on you!
Oh..!
Hurry! Take his back collar!
G.. gotcha!
Clamp your legs around his left arm, cradle
his other arm with your right arm...
...and then tighten his collar with your left arm!
Th.. this is..
..Jigoku Zeme!
[Jigoku Zeme -- Hell Attack]
We will now begin the First Oshiuri TV Cup Women's Judo Tournament Awards Ceremony.
Third place, Tohdoh Yuki, 4th degree.
Runner-up, Hon'ami Sayaka, 1st degree.
Err, due to unforeseen circumstances,
1st degree Hon'ami cannot make this ceremony. Please bear with us.
And finally, the champion,
Inokuma Yawara, 1st degree.
Err, also due to unforeseen circumstances,
1st degree Inokuma cannot make
this ceremony either.
As her representative, Inokuma Jigoro, 7th degree, a close kin, will substitute her.
I'm 8th degree, Jya!
But my daughter will get even stronger, too.
Miss, I found out.
And, what did you find?
Oh, yes.
Inokuma Yawara's father, Inokuma
Kojiro, is also a judo expert.
According to the records, in 1974, he appeared like a comet and won the Judo Nationals.
W.. won?
It's like what Yawara-san just did!
But, within the year of debut,
he disappeared from all records.
Wh.. why?
He ran away.
Ran away? Why?
I see. Being Inokuma-sensei's son and Inokuma Yawara's dad makes him a judo expert.
Inokuma Kojiro.
He knows every detail of the Inokuma's judo.
Tokunaga.
Yes?
Find this Inokuma Kojiro immediately.
No budget limits, either.
Utilize the Hon'ami family's vast wealth and information network to find him.
Yes, Miss.
And.. and, we'll completely analyze
Inokuma Yawara's judo secrets.
His leg.. his right leg is loosening!
Hanazono-kun!
That's it. Don't loosen the grip!
You've gotta score soon or
you'll run out of time!
I won't let go, even if I die.
Inokuma, for you, I'll... win!
Inokuma-san, Yawara-san is
invincible, isn't she?
Of course.
But, her skills aren't sharp enough yet.
She's still a diamond in the rough.
She seems so strong, yet you're saying
that she can be stronger?
Without shedding more tears and
sweat to sharpen her skills...
...there's no way she can aim for the world!
Whoa!
No! Don't let go!
You'll win with just a little more!
Put more pressure in your legs!
Keep going, Hanazono-san!
He got it!
End of match!
I w.. won.
Hanazono-san.
Inokuma...
I'm.. here, Hanazono-kun.
Did you win your tournament at the
National Martial Arts Hall?
Yes.
I.. won.
Really? You're so great, Inokuma.
You're really great.
No, all of you are great.
We all won for the first time. Us!
It's because you taught us judo, Yawara-san.
No, all of you taught me instead.
Doing your best is.. great, isn't it?
Ya.. Yawara-san!
The... the Camera...
Oh, hey.. wait... umm..
The next day, all of the sports newspapers
put the photo of Yawara-san's victory at the National Martial Arts Hall on the front page.
Ippon Zeoi
Japan's No. 1
Ma'am, a sweet bean roll, a coffee milk,
and a Daily Every Sports, please.
Yawara! Absolute Domination
Ma'am, a sweet bean roll, a coffee milk,
and a Daily Every Sports, please.
Here's 730 yen in change.
Thanks.
But, our Daily Every Sports splashed its front page with a close-up of Yawara-san's tears of joy from seeing her first judo victory.
880 days to the Barcelona Olympics
That's my Yawara.
She easily became Japan's Number One.
But, this is all because of my
excellence in coaching her.
And so, because of an overwhelming amount of requests, we've decided to share the
stories of my youth to everyone...
Who requested it?
Eii, shut your trap!
Next time on "Yawara!" --
Jigoro, His Love and Youth's Raging Storms
With this, the ratings will skyrocket!
This episode was sponsored by:
Julie Divola
Christopher Dewane
Erik Schweitzer
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Kyonen wa anata to
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Eigakande miteta hazu
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Soba ni ite ne
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Otana ni naranaide