From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
My dearly beloved Kaneko.
Ever since you passed away 15 years ago,
our runaway son, Kojiro, is still missing,
but Yawara is doing great.
Under my personal care, the day that she'll
get the gold medal at the Olympics...
... and the National Achievement Award
won't be too far down the road.
I'm home!
Grandpa?
Grandpa --
Eii, you're late! You're late, Yawara!
Today is the 15th anniversary of Kaneko's death, so with who, where, and what were you doing?
Well, I went to buy the cherry
rice cakes that you asked for.
It was Grandma's favorite, right?
Here's the cherry rice cakes.
Oh, that's right!
Tea! Get some tea, Yawara!
Kaneko loved to eat these while
sipping coarse tea.
You're beginning to look like Kaneko
more and more, Yawara.
No way? Like Grandma?
When I met Kaneko, she was as
beautiful as any heavenly being.
And I was a brash young lad, ready
to move up in the ranks.
We had met during the rough times
revolving around the 2.26 incident.
G.. Grandpa, I know.
I've heard that story so many times..
During those times, there was pure love.
And pure vegetables, and rice.
Grandpa...
Those were the times.
But, it sure brings back memories.
Episode 19
Jigoro, His Love and
Youth's Raging Storms
Showa 9 Nen [1934]
So this is Tokyo? Is this it?
The ground here is so hard. You can't
have a farm on these hard grounds.
Oh my gosh, what's that?
Oh gosh, it's a country boy. A country boy.
No, don't look at him.
Hey you, what are you doing?
Oh man, geez, I can't think of anything.
Am I at the peak of my talents?
Is my dream of becoming
a novelist just a fantasy?
H.. how dare you!
Wh.. what's up?
He's going up against a cop!
What? No way!
Why, I don't need charity from a g.. guy like you!
Don't say that and just eat it.
It's the authentic Shonai rice from Yamagata.
It's delicious.
I.. I'm telling you not to eat your lunch
here, don't you understand!?
Then, what about some kimpira gobou?
[kimpira gobou - shredded burdock]
Come here, you're under arrest!
How dare you waste food!
What? You're resisting arrest?
Amazing!
I won't forgive people who waste food.
I, Inokuma Jigoro --
Let go! I'm still eating my lunch!
You don't have time for that.
There'll be more after you because
you just threw a cop.
This is delicious!
Th.. that's great. The steak bowl
here is one of the best.
And your throw was one of the best, too.
You said you were Inokuma Jigoro, right?
I'm a novelist-to-be, and I had a writer's block, but I was refreshed by your throw!
You're a novelist?
Some day, soon.
To draw a moving novel,
and be a famous novelist.
Then why don't you use me as
a model for your next story?
I came to Tokyo today from Yamagata.
To become Japan's greatest judo athlete.
Put all my daily struggles and glorious moments I achieve until I reach the
ultimate goal together into a book.
It'll surely sell.
Wow, you're so sure of yourself.
What's your judo record like?
230 victories in a row.
W.. well I'll be..
And my opponent was a KUMA.
[KUMA -- bear]
I threw a total of 230 KUMA.
[KUMA -- bears]
KUMA? The comedian, KUMA-san?
Groowwl!
Kind of bear!
A r.. real bear?
A.. an eat and run thief!
Hey, wait up!
Wait! Wait up, you!
Wait!
I'm sorry!
A man.. that steals food! How pathetic!
Way to go, Jigoro-kun! Great job!
Th.. thank you very much.
How can I repay you?
Don't worry about it.
I just can't stand people who
are twisted in their ways.
U.. umm, you haven't paid your bill yet.
U.. uhh...
Thanks for treating me, Mr. Novelist.
H.. hey, I'm a poor writer.
I don't have any money.
Weren't you going to pay for me?
I'm penniless.
Eii, don't urban people have any compassion?
I nabbed a thief for them,
so why do I have to do this?
They sure used us like slaves.
It's a lot easier throwing bears.
I don't know how legitimate he is,
but he has a strange charm.
For a change, I'm getting
the urge to write again!
Hey, Mr. Novelist, thanks for guiding me.
This must be the dojo I've been looking for.
You came all the way from Yamagata
to learn at this run-down dojo?
Kyudou-kan Dojo
It may look run-down, but it's beautiful in spirit.
The master of this dojo is none other than the master I adore, Ushio Umanosuke-sensei.
Patience
D.. died?
Y.. yes.
Patience
Even the invincible master, Ushio-sensei, couldn't defeat an illness.
Now there's only two students left.
Patience
And this is the state of this dojo...
Ushio-sensei p.. passed away?!
The Ushio-sensei that I adored and idolized ever since my childhood..
Sensei's only daughter, Miss Kaneko,
has been running around trying to
re-establish this dojo, but in vain..
J.. Jigoro-kun.
Ah, Miss.
Oh? A visitor?
I am Kaneko.
I.. Ino.. ku.. J.. Ji..
This apricot-like and baker's garlic-like bittersweet feeling...
..I'm in love!
If this isn't love, then what is love?
We're just dropping by again, Miss.
I.. it's the guys from the
Goudou-kan Dojo again.
Our important sign... H.. how could you?
You won't need it anymore, since this
place'll be torn down soon.
Now Miss, we need you to move out.
The due date for the debt is long overdue.
Or, have you thought about
our president's offer?
A beautiful lady like you doesn't need to
stay couped up in this dusty place.
Don't you touch Miss Kaneko!
Who the hell are you?
I am Inokuma Jigoro, jya!
Eii, a thug like you deserves to be
thrown by me to the pits of hell!
Q.. quit it!
You're outnumbered!
Let go!
If I win, then your novel will
become more interesting.
I.. If you lose now, then it won't even be
long enough to be a short story!
What are you all blabbing about?
I'll rip you apart.
Stop it, everyone.
President!
Sa.. Saimonji-san.
I'm sorry, Kaneko-san.
My men don't know how to treat
a proper lady with manners.
Is he Japanese?
Y.. yeah.
By the way, I'm came to get
a reply for my PROPOSAL.
What's a FURO-BOUZU?
[FURO-BOUZU -- bathing bald guy]
PROPOSAL. A request for a hand in marriage.
Wh.. what?!
I thought that I had given
you an answer already.
Kaneko-san, you're so untouchable.
I know that the first few no's mean yes, anyway.
Besides, if you agree, this proof
of debt will be nullified.
You can continue this dojo, not only that,
you'll get all the money you want.
To make this dojo as big as you want.
You're always so beautiful.
Your existence itself is like a SHI.
[SHI -- poetry]
JI? You call her a JI?
[JI -- hemorrhoids]
What a rude thing to say!
W.. who are you?
I mean SHI... as in poetry, or POESIE.
POE-JI? There's no such JI!
[JI -- word]
That's why I hate country boys.
I'll come again, Kaneko-san.
I look forward to a good reply next time.
H.. hey, wait up, you! Wait up, you rude jerk!
That Miss sure is stubborn.
Ah, she'll fall soon. Just like
a ripe fruit falls from a tree.
But that guy...
..he's in the way.
Th.. then it's a scam!
Yes.
The money we borrowed during my
father's illness gradually increased
by two fold, and three-fold.
Saimonji hired men from the Goudou-kan
dojo to help with the eviction.
And, to stop this harassment,
he asked me to marry him.
That's unforgivable!
That Saimonji!
Miss Kaneko, leave it to me.
I'll protect you with my power and revive
this Kyudou-kan Dojo once again.
I'm beat.
Eii, straighten up!
That's why you get picked on by
those Goudou-kan Dojo jerks.
Stand up! Stand up!
We're going to do uchi-komi 10,000 times!
[uchi-komi -- repeat throw practice]
10,000 times?
H.. help!
Hey wait! Wait!
Sigh.
Instead of reviving the dojo,
you lost your last 2 students.
It's better that they're not here, anyway.
Umm.
Please, the breakfast is ready.
This is delicious!
You're a great cook, Miss Kaneko.
Right?
Y.. yeah.
Seconds, please.
Oh, yes.
A boiled egg-like warmth from her hands.
It's love... definitely love. A burning love!
Umm, Jigoro-san.
Please promise me one thing.
H.. huh?
Even if the Goudou-kan Dojo men come,
please don't fight them.
I don't want to use judo for such fights.
My father's... judo was a very pure one.
O.. of course!
I'm not so small as to care about those guys!
I, Inokuma Jigoro, going up against a 570 bears, have purified my body and soul! Yes!
Didn't you say 230 bears?
I was modest with my figures then.
The best! Miss Kaneko is the best!
You guys...!
Shove off.
Wh.. what do you want?
Well, since we heard you're the only one left...
We decided to be your practice buddies.
As a samurai's generosity.
Don't play with me!
I'm serious. Now, let's practice.
Please promise me.. not to fight them.
What the heck. Let's take him all at once!
J.. Jigoro-kun, wake up! Jigoro-kun!
Jigoro-san.
The Goudou-kan guys did it.
Jigoro-san!
I.. I'm alright.
I'm the g.. guy that fought 890 bears...
J.. Jigoro-kun!
Jigoro-san!
I'm sorry, Jigoro-san.
All this, for me...
Saimonji-san.
I heard, Kaneko-san, about that
country boy getting roughed up.
The Goudou-kan guys have good hearts,
but are out of my control.
By the way, did you rethink
your reply to my offer?
Oh yes, I saw a strange dream.
The Kyudou-kan Dojo got torn down,
and that country boy gets hurt more.
Oh, I wish it doesn't become true at all.
Wh.. what, you're m.. marrying Saimonji?!
N.. No way! No! No! Don't get under his thumb!
Yeah, Kaneko-san. You've got
to think of yourself more.
No.
I can't trouble all of you anymore.
You're not troubling me at all.
And, I don't want to lose this dojo.
Because my father protected it with his life.
And, there's so many fond memories
of my father in every corner.
In every column, and in every tatami mat.
I.. I'll do something about it, jya!
You can't.
I'm tired of it all.
No way!
No way...
Did you hear?
Kaneko-san finally agreed to marry Saimonji.
He's scarred really deep.
Please hurry, Miss.
The President awaits you.
Are you sure this is right, Kaneko-san?
And, where is Jigoro-kun anyway?
Jigoro-san..
Ka.. Kaneko-san!
Kaneko-san!
Are you okay, Jigoro-kun?
I've had it. I've reached my limit!
Why that Saimonji!
Kaneko-san!
Marvelous! Kaneko-san!
You are the peak of beauty!
The ceremony is about to begin.
Well, my relatives will definitely
be amazed and shocked.
Brother, it's almost time for the ceremony.
Uh, let me introduce her to you.
My sister, Saeko.
My!
I wondered what type of girl you
were chasing but.. my!
What a wonderful country girl!
Shu.. shut up!
Kaneko-san!
I'm sorry. I.. I just can't...
I won't let you go! Kaneko-san!
Jigoro-san, don't!
Don't fight!
Eii, feel at least a hundredth of
Kaneko-san's pain and suffering!
Jigoro-san!
Miss Kaneko!
Kaneko-san!
My father's judo isn't for fighting.
No way!
I didn't know that Kaneko-san was that strong.
I.. I'm sorry!
The proof of debt!
The man that threw a bear was
defeated by a w.. woman?
I was fooled!
The man's name was Yoshinokawa Eiichi.
He soon published the classic tale, Miyamoto Musashi, and became famous.
That's a lie!
What's a lie?
Because.
If I wasn't thrown by Kaneko, the classic
tale would've been, Inokuma Jigoro,
not Miyamoto Musashi.
The last time you told it, weren't you
two supposed to be models...
... for Kawabata Nariyasu's classic, Yuki Guni?
[Yuki Guni -- Snow Country]
H.. huh, uhh, well...
Kaneko was strong, so very strong.
Well, next is a new story arc for Yawara!
What new story arc?
Of course, after taking Japan, next is the world!
There are strong opponents
all over the world.
Geez, I'm busy with entrance exam studies.
Studies? You don't need to study
for global competitions.
Not for judo, I mean for college entrance exams.
Next time, on "Yawara!" --
The Big Guest For Yawara.
If you don't watch it, I'll give
you a kami shihoh gatame.
[kami shihoh gatame -- upper four corner hold]
This episode was sponsored by:
Christopher Dewane
Erik Schweitzer
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
I watched the video through the night.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Stay right here next to me,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
I don't want you to grow up yet.