Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 10
Things Are Not Turning Out Well...
Senkawa High School
Where's the manager ?
She went to greet him.
Greet ? Who ?
You know, what's his name, the chairman of the PTA.
Oh.
Do you really think he can persuade that principal ?
Who knows ?
Oh, my.
You've become so beautiful.
They say that girls grow up fast, but after not seeing you for a while, I really feel that way.
Oh, you're such a sweet talker.
It's not just talk.
What do you mean ?
Let's see. I should probably divorce my wife and propose to you soon.
What ?
I'll leave it to you then.
Sure, you can count on me.
I'll definitely make it
an official baseball club.
Oh, that face.
You're worried ?
You can tell ?
You can rest assured.
I'm the PTA chairman after all.
All right.
How about this ?
Thank you for doing this.
Sure.
Principal's Office
Until you say yes, I won't leave.
Then how about this ?
The Final is Set
Meiwa Ichi vs Shinkawa
Face-off tomorrow !!
What about Meiwa-Ichi and Shinkawa ?
Girls' Dressing Room
How about this ?
You could catch that one !
Yeah !
Sorry I'm late !
Does it look like it will go okay ?
Mr. Takemura said, "Leave it to me."
You said he was the president of a construction company.
What kind of person is he ?
Despite how he looks,
he can be scatter-brained.
And he gets carried away easily.
Principal's Office
He talks big, but later plays dumb.
Even then, no one dislikes him.
He really has an advantageous character.
Maybe we should plan our next move...
The Final is Set
Meiwa Ichi vs Shinkawa
Hey, Haruka. Are you going to accept my proposal ?
Again...
So how did it go ?
Yeah, about turning the baseball fan club into an official club.
Of course he approved it.
Really ?
I told you to leave it to me, didn't I ?
Um...
What is it ?
How did that stubborn
principal approve it so easily ?
No, it wasn't easy.
You mean...?
The principal set an
outrageous condition.
Condition ?
Yeah. The condition is...
...that you play a practice game against this year's champion.
If you win, the club can
become an official one.
No way. That's absurd.
Don't worry.
Of course, I said no.
"Stop this nonsense !" I said.
It goes without saying.
There's no way that a school
that's advancing to the Koushien...
...would have time to
play a practice game.
You're right.
So if anything, you'll play against the runner-up.
...?
Huh ?
Now, which one of you is Kunimi ?
I'm...
That's me.
Oh, it's you.
Haruka told me about you.
You throw amazing pitches, I hear.
Oh.
Once this becomes an
official baseball club...
...there's no doubt that it will go to the Koushien, right ?
No, it's more than that.
I hear that it isn't a pipe-dream for the
team to win the national championship.
You can easily beat the runner-up from the regional tournament...
...and leave that principal speechless.
Now, guys, good luck to you.
Oh, yes.
It's probably a needless worry...
...but if you lose, the fan club will be abolished, so don't go easy on the opponent.
Who's going to win the
national championship ?
What ?
I guess that dude isn't the only one who talks big and gets carried away easily.
Now, let's practice !
If we lose, we'll be disbanded.
Now, fight, fight !
The sky is blue !
Is that true ?
That's so funny !
Hey, guys !
I have some big news for you !
What is it, Captain ?
Listen and be shocked.
That baseball fan club will be upgraded to an official club.
What ?
On the condition that
they win a practice game...
...against the runner-up in tomorrow's game between Meiwa-Shinkawa.
What if they lose ?
They're abolished.
That principal must
really hate baseball.
If they win, they'll be an official club...
What are you thinking ?
The only decent players
they have are the battery.
There's no way they can win with
such a porous defense behind them.
Oh, that's right.
What am I worried about ?
It'll be abolished !
This is such a downer.
Why is Meiwa even in the discussion ?
Maybe he feels some kind of rivalry against them ?
Well, our opponent will
probably be Shinkawa.
You never know. But of course,
I want Hideo to go to the Koushien.
Are you worried ?
Of course I am.
Don't worry.
Meiwa will definitely win.
That's not what I'm worried about.
Whether we can defeat the
runner-up or not is the issue.
Oh, that's right.
Shinkawa couldn't have advanced to the finals just by pure luck.
Right.
EYECATCH
Hm.
When it comes to the
night before the final...
...even you feel nervous.
Not really.
If the opposing pitcher were Hiro...
...I might be, though.
You're coming tomorrow, right ?
Actually...
I can't come.
The archery club has a
preliminary tournament next week.
You have practice, then ?
Our coach is really fired up.
Oh.
To make up for it, I'll definitely
come see you at the Koushien.
What's wrong ?
No, it's nothing.
The Final Match !! Meiwa Ichi High School x Shinkawa High School
Out.
"The national championship is no pipe-dream once we're an official club," huh ?
As I was describing you to them, I just got carried away...
Are you mad at me ?
No, it's actually funny.
If you were talking about someone else, that is.
Maybe I got too excited ?
Well, it's fine. Managers
need to think big, after all.
Just pray that Meiwa
doesn't lose this game.
But honestly, what a joke of a principal.
Top of the first inning, despite worries about Shinkawa's pitcher, Koyama...
...he retires the side with just three batters against Meiwa's high-power offense.
Yanagi
The final match in which the
winner goes to the Koushien...
...is between Meiwa Daiichi High
School and Shinkawa High School.
Bottom of the first,
Shinkawa is on offense.
What's going on ?
You're watching high school baseball.
Top of the second,
Meiwa is on offense.
Leading off this inning is the third
baseman, batting fourth, Tachibana.
Did you find anyone cute ?
I can't find...
You're aiming too high, maybe ?
...Hikari.
...?
Oh ? Where is Amamiya ?
We're not sure.
Homerun !
It's a homerun !
First year, Tachibana hits a monstrous homerun right to the center field display !
Meiwa 1-0 Shinkawa
All right !
What are you doing here, Amamiya ?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Meiwa Ichi
Shinkawa
There's no way we could hit that.
That pitcher played center field until last year, right ?
Oh, really ?
In the tournament last year, he threw out three runners at home plate with his strong arm.
I'm impressed. You've really been a high school baseball nerd since junior high.
I see. No wonder he doesn't
look comfortable on the mound.
He doesn't look comfortable ?
How ?
Strike ! Batter out !
But honestly, those pitches from a lefthander must be difficult to hit.
No, we can do it.
Do you think so ?
We don't know yet if we'll be playing against Shinkawa.
Don't say such an ominous thing.
Whoever the opponent is,
it's still ominous.
Shoot !
Hey, Nabe !
What kind of a shot was that ?
What are you doing there ?
Akagi !
Yeah, how is it going ?
After five innings, Meiwa is up 1-0.
Just as I figured.
That first year cleanup
batter hit another homerun.
Tachibana, huh ?
He really is amazing.
Tachibana...
Tachibana Hideo...!
If you insist on letting Tachibana
hit fourth, I'll quit the Hakusan Angels.
Are you okay about losing your ace pitcher, Coach ?
Are you going to choose me,
or Tachibana ? Let's settle it here.
...!
Damn him...!
If only he...
If only he hadn't come along...!
Goal !
You should wipe your bloody nose.
All right !
Just as expected of Meiwa.
One more hit and
it'll be double-digits.
But they've scored only one run, from Hideo's homerun.
Well, they hit into three
double-plays, after all.
Out !
But fairly well-hit balls
are all ending up like that.
It must be luck.
It feels ominous.
It'll be fine. They won't be able to score runs off that Meiwa pitcher.
I hope so, too.
Thank you.
...
Eighth inning.
All right !
I have a bad feeling about this.
What are you talking about ?
There's one out in the ninth, and the
pitcher has only yielded three separate hits.
Just two more outs.
It's probably going to end here.
It's a cakewalk.
The ace pitcher got injured.
The reserve pitcher lacks experience.
He's fatigued from all the
games up to the final.
Bottom of the ninth,
up by one run.
If he shuts down the opponent this inning, it will be the Koushien.
You're such a worrywart.
Ball. Ball four.
Things aren't turning out well...
It'll be fine.
Safe !
After bunt attacks, Shinkawa has the winning run on base.
We're not sure how the game will unfold from here.
Out.
Two outs with runners on second and third in the ninth inning. What would you do ?
Walk the batter and load the bases.
The way the pitcher is pitching right now, a bases loaded walk is a real concern.
Hm.
The count is full.
What would you make him pitch ?
Close your eyes and throw one right down the middle.
I guess.
Now, we know our opponent !
Meiwa Ichi
Don't make faces like that.
What kind of a face are we supposed to make ?
Smile ! Smile !
Now, let's go home and practice !
Let's give it our best !
Things aren't turning out well...
See ?
Meiwa Ichi
Shinkawa
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Takemura:
Akagi :
Yanagi:
Arikawa:
Yamaguchi:
Nemoto:
Archery Coach:
Fanclub Member:
Head Umpire:
Komura Tetsuo
Nojima Akio
Ugaki Shuusei
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Yanagisawa Eiji
Takemasa Hiroko
Konishi Hiroko
Takagi Wataru
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
"kotatsu" is a table over an electric heater with a hanging quilt that retains heat, which Japanese people often use in the winter.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Do you have the lineup finally set for the game against us ?
If only we could set a solid line up the middle, we could put up a good fight.
So do you have any prospects ?
I have a second baseman in mind. The issue is the center fielder.
The ideal would be someone who runs fast, has a strong arm...
...and knows how to play baseball.
You mean someone who's an overconfident, selfish show-off, on top of all that ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"Defeat Meiwa Daiichi."
Next episode of H2 is
Defeat Meiwa Daiichi !
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?