Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 11
Defeat Meiwa Daiichi !
Ball four !
Bottom of the ninth, Shinkawa gets a runner on board with one out to sustain their hopes.
What happens from here is the problem.
Yeah.
The pitcher throws his first pitch.
Oh, it's a bunt !
He's not very good at fielding.
He's a reserve pitcher, after all.
Safe !
He didn't have to press.
All he needed to do was to
make sure that he got an out.
But he pressed to protect the lead.
After that, they do a sacrifice bunt...
...and move the runners over to second and third with two outs.
Will this be the final pitch ?
It's popped up !
That was poorly hit.
Oh, it fell in ! It fell in !
It's a walkoff ! It's a walkoff hit !
With two outs, the runners are moving on contact...
...so the second base
runner also scored easily.
Shinkawa gains the ticket to the Koushien !
2-1, a come from
behind walkoff victory.
Goodbye to the Koushien.
Oh, well.
Shut up.
Aren't you supposed to be my friends ?
Why don't you try to be considerate to me and say something to console me or something ?
You shut up.
We're the ones who are
really depressed about this.
That's right.
Huh ?
Oh, I didn't know that you were pulling for me so earnestly.
I've never cheered for someone
else's team as much as I did this time.
I definitely wanted you
to go to the Koushien.
You guys...
You really are my best friends...
I mean, I'd get it if Shinkawa
were overwhelmingly superior.
Huh ?
But that was an opponent you could win seven out of ten games from.
What ?
Bungler.
It couldn't be helped.
You only get one shot.
Oh well, what are we
going to do about it ?
That's right.
What're you talking about ?
Shut up.
The batting lineup is still on a roll.
That second year pitcher will probably learn from this loss and grow.
It's going to be a problem.
It's going to be a problem ?
For whom ?
For us, that's who !
Huh ?
What're you talking about ?
Shut up, blockhead !
What's wrong with you ?
I said you're a blockhead
because you are !
That's right.
What ? What's that about ?
His club becomes official if they win against our club, and abolished if they lose ?
That principal is so terrible !
That condition is
nothing short of malicious.
I don't know about that.
What do you mean ?
You saw them play against the soccer club sometime ago, didn't you ?
There's no way they'll win.
But this time, Hiro is the starter.
Baseball is played by nine people.
We have eighty members, though.
I don't know what they're thinking.
Hey, why don't you lose to them ?
It's just a practice game.
For us, it is.
But for them, it's not.
They'll be serious.
They'll be playing really hard.
It'd be disrespectful for us to go easy on such an opponent.
You don't want Hiro to play baseball ?
I don't want him to, since we want to go to the Koushien next year.
Hide-chan !
It's Meiwa, isn't it ?
Yeah.
If we lose, we won't even be able to play catch.
That's right.
What are we going to do ?
It's easy.
Huh ?
We just need to win.
Can we win ?
Hey.
You heard about it
from your father, right ?
It sounds like you're in trouble.
The game is ten days from now. At Meiwa's field. Okay ?
But I...
At least once !
At least once in your lifetime, you
should rebel against your parents.
A filial tie isn't supposed to be one-way.
Isn't that right ?
As it is, your father will never
understand your true feelings.
And you won't understand the real
reason that your father dislikes baseball.
Adults are like that.
His real reason ?
Yeah.
Adults are fixated on saving face.
It might just be that he
hasn't had the opportunity...
...to take down the billboard that says "I dislike high school baseball,"...
...which is affirmed by both
himself and the people around him.
Really, whether it's baseball or something else...
...it's strange to say that he
dislikes people who work hard.
Anyway, what's clear is that, in order to show your father a good game...
...we desperately need you to play second base.
But I...
We'll keep second
base open for you.
See you.
Kunimi.
The tie will loosen if you don't
tighten it from both sides, Yanagi !
How did I do ?
I think it was kind of persuasive.
The part about "filial tie" may have been a little too corny.
No, that was just about right for him.
I wonder if he'll come.
It's all a gamble.
Recruiting him to be the second baseman, or defeating Meiwa.
A gamble...
Hey, Fan Club guys.
Are you discussing what to do
after your fan club gets abolished ?
Yeah. We're playing
against Meiwa, after all.
And Hideo.
Well, Koga won't have to worry.
Our soccer club will
responsibly take her.
You seem to have lots of free time.
What happened to the
Inter-High Tournament ?
The real soccer season
starts on New Year's Day.
You should sit at your kotatsu eating your mikan, and watch my great performance on TV.
It'll be abolished ! Abolished !
The Fan Club will be disbanded !
Hooray !
What happened to the Inter-High ?
The first baseman will be Hironaga.
The shortstop will be Arikawa, even
though he doesn't have a strong arm.
The right fielder will be Nemoto, for the time being.
So the left fielder will be Yamaguchi ?
Wait.
If that's the case,
who will play third base ?
Hmm...
We need at least one more player !
If we don't have at least one more
decent player, it won't even be a game !
Man, we're in trouble.
Hey, whatever the case, isn't it unusual to discuss strategies at your opponent's house ?
Shut up.
You should give us something cold to drink, instead of just drinking by yourself.
You have plenty to sell, right ?
That's right.
There's a vending machine outside.
Hideo, you jerk !
You can't drink alcohol until you're twenty.
EYECATCH
Amamiya
This air-conditioning is kind of weak.
Hey, just because
it's summer break...
...does that mean you can take it easy and look at those things ?
Huh ?
If you lose the game
against our school...
...you won't be able to play baseball for all three years of high school, right ?
Hideo told you ?
That's right.
What's going on with you ?
You don't have time to be
doing stuff like this, do you ?
Shut up. You don't need to tell me; I already know.
But you look calm and composed.
I'm going to practice shortly.
Oh, I see. I appreciate your effort in this hot weather.
Honestly.
Okay.
I will give you permission to use
the field until the day of the game.
The time you will be allowed to use the
field is, let's see, between 11 and 2 o'clock.
The principal really is thoughtful.
He chose the hottest
time of day on purpose.
That's fine, isn't it ?
You'll get to practice and also
develop your mental toughness.
You should show a little empathy.
You should realize
that winning takes effort.
After all, our school is
extraordinarily strong.
Whatever.
Thanks for the advice.
You're welcome.
Well, good luck.
All you have is baseball, anyway.
Crud.
You can give Hideo
food poisoning, if you want.
I give you the permission to do so.
I'll think about it.
Oh, yes.
What happened to you, with the
Archery Club's regional tournament ?
Eh ?
Don't just stick out your glove.
You could have fielded
it in front of your body.
Even if you can't catch it, you can do something with it if you keep it in front of you.
Yeah !
Here ! One more !
Did you decide on the starting lineup ?
It doesn't matter what I decide. We have just enough members to play the game.
Here.
Thanks.
Don't make a face like that.
They really love baseball.
Dammit !
I know.
Eight days left.
If we could at least solidify the middle, we could put up a good fight.
Noda is the catcher.
Kunimi is the pitcher.
Let's hope that Yanagi will be the second baseman.
The problem is center field.
Yeah, we want someone who runs fast, has a strong arm, and knows how to play baseball.
And someone who's overconfident,
selfish, disagreeable, and a showoff...?
I refuse.
Why ?
You said you were going to cooperate
with us if we'd bow and ask for your help.
Right.
That's why you should
have bought me then.
The value of a person goes up and down.
For a game that decides
the fate of the Fan Club...
...I can't sell myself so cheaply.
How much has it gone up ?
Let's see.
A day-long date with Koga.
Including a kiss.
No way !
Damn. I wish you'd think for a while before you answer.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you sure ?
If you need me,
now is your chance !
The closer it gets to the game, the higher my price goes !
A day-long date with a kiss won't be enough then !
It's going to be an overnight date. And it includes...
Goal !
Should I have thought
about it a little more ?
There's no reason for you to waste the precious time of your youth.
But you need him, right ?
What I need is someone who runs fast, has a strong arm, and knows how to play baseball...
...and who's overconfident, selfish, disagreeable, and a showoff. That's all.
I don't need someone who's so mean as to take advantage of other people's misery.
Don't worry.
As long as I don't give up any hits to the outfield, it should be fine.
But honestly,
it's not looking good.
Kine is out, and
Yanagi is questionable.
It looks grim.
Griping won't do anything.
The two of us will have to make up for what we don't have.
I'm counting on you, Sir.
Me, too.
Homerun
We told you to get in front of the ball.
One more time !
Let's go !
Okay, let's switch.
Arikawa, go ahead !
Okay, let's go !
All right, one more !
Okay, there !
You can catch that one, too !
Yeah !
Okay, good job.
Okay now !
All right, next !
Well, you caught us.
You always practice here ?
Yeah.
Why didn't you tell us ?
Well, we thought you two might be tired for a lot of reasons.
You practice pitching after you coach us.
Besides, we're lousy.
We have to try to catch up to you as much as we can before the game.
We don't want to drag you down.
There's a chance that we might play baseball as an official club because you two joined us.
If we don't work
hard now, when will we ?
Nice catch !
Next, fly ball !
Okay, this way !
I got it ! I got it ! I got it !
One more !
Man, I'm exhausted !
Tastes great !
I'm so looking forward to the game !
You seem to be having fun.
So your lineup is set ?
Can you afford to take it easy and read a magazine ?
Well, it's a piece of cake for us.
Oh.
All right.
Hmm.
Let's see.
Wow.
What did you do now ?
Defeat Meiwa Ichi !
"Defeat Meiwa Ichi !" ?
It sounds great.
Morons ! Why are you
putting this up in my room ?
It's okay.
What's wrong ?
It's not okay !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Yanagi:
Hironaga:
Yamaguchi:
Arikawa:
Satou:
Komura Tetsuo
Izaki Hisayoshi
Takagi Wataru
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
"Kotatsu" is a table over an electric heater with a hanging
quilt that retains heat, which Japanese people often
use in winter.
"Mikan" is a type of Japanese orange.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hiro, I'll be waiting for you at the pool. You should take a break.
I'm tired of looking at you in a swimsuit by now.
Even if you say so, you
actually want to see it.
I have a place to go.
Where ?
A great curry restaurant.
Curry restaurant ?
Who are you going with ?
Who knows ?
You're acting suspicious.
Next episode of H2 is, "Maybe I Don't Have Much Luck With the Lottery."
Next episode of H2 is
Maybe I Don't Have Much Luck With the Lottery
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?