Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 12
Maybe I Don't Have Much Luck With The Lottery
Let's go...
I'm not done yet...
Let's do it, let's do it...
Fight ! Fight !
Guys, give it all you've got !
How is it ?
The effective temperature seems to be about 43 degrees(110F).
We first have to battle this heat before we play against Meiwa, I suppose.
I'm going to change my undershirt.
Um, I'll go buy some sports drinks.
At this rate, you'll all be dehydrated.
True.
I'll get going !
She's full of energy.
Here we go !
You're working hard in this heat.
Don't say things that are obvious.
Just think about the
predicament we're in.
The game against our school
is next week, after all.
What brought you here, anyway ?
Your practice will be over soon, right ?
We still have one full
hour before 2 o'clock.
Water, water...
Oh, the water is out.
What ?
I'm going to the city pool.
Why don't we go swimming
when you're done with practice ?
Swimming pool ?
You should go with Hideo.
Of course Hide-chan is coming, too.
Noda, come with us, too.
He's not coming.
There are lots of girls
with high-cut swimsuits.
High-cut...
Girls...
You changed your mind, right ?
I said no.
See you.
Hey.
It's no good.
What's no good ?
If we go to the pool now, we can see that girl in her swimsuit ?
Will she be wearing a
high-cut swimsuit, too ?
Everyone's thinking about Hikari's swimsuit now.
Well, this practice is useless, anyway.
But...
Hm ?
They're going to the swimming pool together. Why would she invite intruders ?
Honestly.
Come to think of it, you were
often invited to join their dates.
Hideo wasn't comfortable around girls.
Despite the fact that he asked me to introduce him to her...
...he didn't even speak a word when I first set those two up.
He'd only whisper in a quiet voice.
If I weren't there as an interpreter, they wouldn't have been able to communicate.
It took almost a year for them to speak with each other by themselves, I think.
That's how advanced
he was at that age.
On the other hand...
...we entered junior high while we were still kids, so we didn't think about boy-girl stuff.
In particular, I grew up slowly.
You were so small.
You definitely looked like
an elementary school kid.
Leave me alone.
Bear with it. After all, you did become popular with girls in junior high.
On the Valentine's Day before graduation, you received more chocolates than Hideo.
It really went slowly.
Are Hiro and the others coming ?
He didn't say. But there's no use practicing in this heat.
Right about now, he's probably griping as he heads home to get his swimsuit.
Really ?
To the swimming pool !
But really, we finished junior high.
Things shouldn't stay the way they were.
Well, it's all right. She probably asked us out so that we could take a break.
I'm going to show you the splendid butterfly style of a former swimming club member.
Did you know ?
The "butterfly style" takes its name from a butterfly, Mr. Mothra.
Who're you calling Mothra ?
So I'll see you at the
city swimming pool.
Okay.
Oh, no.
It's taking her too long.
We're leaving second
base open for you.
Big Brother Yanagi !
Oh, hello.
Great timing.
Can you coach
these kids for a bit ?
There'll be an inter-town match
the day after tomorrow.
In any case, catching the ball in front of you is fundamental.
Use the resilience of your
knees, and stay low.
Until you actually catch the ball, don't worry about the runner or think about the throw.
It's easiest to catch when the
ball is about to hit the ground.
The next easiest is when
the ball is on a short hop.
And then when the ball
is at the top of a hop.
Other than those, the ball often changes course, so be alert.
Oh, sorry.
Wow. You're as good as always.
You really are a
fine second baseman.
We're keeping second
base open for you.
Noda !
Where's Hiro ?
He's coming later !
She's late.
I wonder what she's doing.
I doubt that's what it is, but...
...I guess...
...it's possible.
Kunimi !
This way !
Koga, practice is over.
Oh, I messed up again ?
Let's go back to the school.
Okay.
Wait, Haruka. Why don't
you introduce me to him ?
Who is he ?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruka's ex-boyfriend.
That's a strange name.
Who's my ex-boyfriend ? Don't say weird things !
When she was in the first year of junior high, I received a love letter from her.
So we went out for a while.
It wasn't a love letter !
She's a jealous girl, you know.
If I even had a brief chat with another girl, she'd get angry, and it would become trouble.
What's your point ?
Oh, don't worry. We didn't have a really deep relationship.
Not that deep.
You're not popular, are you ?
I'm not popular with girls ?
Haruka, you should tell him how many love letters I received in junior high.
With guys, I mean.
I asked if you were
not popular with guys.
What's the point of being
popular with such things ?
Just as I thought.
Kunimi, let's go.
Are you really fine with that, Haruka ?
You'll regret it. It's rare for
me to ask out a girl myself.
Next time you ask her out, you should get my permission first.
Are you sure you want
to talk to me like that ?
I know a lot of bad boys around here.
Hey, if isn't Hiro !
Long time no see.
I heard about it.
Your elbow wasn't
broken after all, huh ?
I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
Are you in trouble or something ?
Not really. I bought too
many drinks, so I'm in a bind.
And this guy says he doesn't want one.
Can you drink some ?
Oh, thanks.
If you're in any trouble,
just let us know.
I'll lend you a hand any time.
See ya.
Get out of the way !
Your girl is waiting for you. You should go to her...
Have a nice trip !
I'm not going anywhere.
If you like, would you like to
go eat some curry and rice ?
Sure.
I know a great curry restaurant.
But before that...
If you have other
things to do, it's fine.
Well, we have to go
back before that.
We left our bags there.
Oh, that's right. You're right.
You're not going to
swim anymore, Hikari ?
It's getting cold.
In the end, he didn't come.
I guess things have
changed since junior high.
I was sure it was
somewhere around here.
Is there actually a restaurant
in a residential area like this ?
Good restaurants are often
found in unexpected places.
Oh, I know !
It's in this alley !
I don't mind if we
go some other time.
No. Definitely no.
Huh ?
You don't have to be so stubborn.
No, I really want you to eat it.
Right, it must be past the station !
Honestly, you really saved me.
That person won't take me seriously, no matter how many times I say no.
He's unbelievably conceited.
Shop Conceited
Original
Triumphant
Face
And who sent a love
letter to a guy like that ?
As I said, it wasn't
anything like a love letter.
It was just...
It was just...?
More like I wrote something saying that I wanted to be a friend of his.
That's kind of how it
is at that age, right ?
How so ?
In the first year of junior high, girls just create idealistic fantasies from how someone looks...
...and falls in love with love,
rather than with the boy himself.
Oh, is that how it is ?
Tachibana is cool.
Tachibana is a good guy.
Maybe I don't have much
luck with the lottery.
All the guys I thought could be
nice have mostly been misses...
...when I look back and
with a calmer mind.
You should change this
careless aspect of yours first.
You draw a "miss" because you hastily grab one.
I'm sorry.
Hey, have you ever found a "hit" ?
In my case, there were
no more tickets left.
What ?
I'll show you my junior high
photo sometime. You'll laugh.
Until the second year of junior high, I was a snot-nosed midget.
Finally, my height caught up, and I started to think about maybe looking for a girlfriend...
...but by then, girls that interested me were all in the midst of their first love.
Seriously ?
What's the point of lying about this sort of thing ?
See you.
Yeah.
Well, do you want to get
some tea or something ?
It's okay.
I want to take a
bath now, anyway.
I see.
Bye.
Bye, Hikari.
Huh ?
On a second thought,
let's have some tea.
Huh ?
Okay ?
But you're popular with girls now.
Huh ?
I mean, you're definitely cool,
when you're pitching on the mound.
I don't know if I should be happy to hear it from someone who tends to draw a miss.
I'm serious.
Oh well, you're capricious.
Now, never mind that.
Hm ?
What would you like to order ?
It's on me today.
Oh, lucky me.
So what would you like, Hide-chan ?
I'm convinced.
It's definitely this alley.
I've heard you say that so many times. My hunger is at its limit now.
I found it !
Look, this is the place !
Phew.
This one is a "hit."
Bottom of the ninth, a bases
loaded homerun for a walkoff win !
Right !
Hey, Kunimi !
Look ! They gave me this !
She's having fun...
Oh, it's going out.
It's gone...
It was pretty.
Yeah.
I hope we'll get our second baseman.
What happened to your face ?
Oh, I ran into a telephone pole.
I see.
Dad, I...
It was a good bath.
I can go from here.
Okay.
Before you draw a "hit,"
don't get hit by a car.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow, at the field.
Good night !
Thanks for today !
The fireworks were beautiful, Kunimi.
What happened to you yesterday ?
We were waiting for you.
It's my life.
I didn't say I'd come.
Oh, okay.
I was going to show you the
swimsuit figure of the grown-up Hikari.
How are you grown up ?
The swimsuit itself is different from what I had in junior high.
It's a high-cut lewd
kind of swimsuit.
You're lying.
Even if you say so, you
actually regret it, don't you ?
Yeah, right !
I don't even need to see it.
With my talent, I can totally see you naked in my imagination, even when you're dressed.
Really ? So what's the color of my underwear today ?
Pink with a polka dot pattern.
That's what you're wearing.
Stop talking rubbish.
Just go to your practice.
Okay.
Hiro.
I'll cheer for you for now, until your club becomes official.
Can you break Hideo's arm
when you get a chance, then ?
You moron !
Give me the apple back !
It's in my stomach already.
Geez. He really is still a brat.
Don't take unnecessary risks and charge.
Make sure to keep
the ball in front of you.
You're going to throw, right ?
Is this okay ?
Yeah.
I mean, you're definitely cool,
when you're pitching on the mound.
One more !
Yahoo !
There !
How about it, Kunimi ?
Right now, I can settle for two
dates with Koga, including a kiss.
The price will definitely rise. If you're going to buy, now is the chance.
For inquiry, contact the soccer club.
Guys who approach
you are all like that ?
Honestly.
Even though I graduated from junior high,
my luck with the draw hasn't changed, huh ?
In any case, one more
week until the fateful game.
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Yanagi:
Hironaga:
Yamaguchi:
Arikawa:
Delinquent:
Coach:
Man:
Catcher Boy:
Komura Tetsuo
Izaki Hisayoshi
Takagi Wataru
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Sugawara Junichi
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Hiro talking to the tree: A willow tree is called "Yanagi."
Conceited Joke: This is another one of those homophone puns. The word that was used for "a conceited person" is "unubore-ya," and "-ya" also means the same thing as "shop," e.g. "vegetable shop" = "yao-ya,"
"fish store" = "sakana-ya." Kunimi is imagining a store named "unubore-ya," where "triumphant face" and such are sold.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Even if you're pitching, our lineup will definitely hit it to the outfield.
I know. I've done my research.
See ? So you need a good centerfielder.
Really, he's the one.
Here, you need Hide-chan's help.
What's Hide going to do ?
That's a secret.
Next episode of H2 is,
"You'll Understand if You're My Friend."
Next episode of H2 is
You'll Understand if You're My Friend
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?