Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 13
You'll Understand If You're My Friend
Huh ?
What are you doing here ?
What do you mean ?
This is my room.
Meiwa doesn't have practice today ?
People were saying that there was no
doubt that Meiwa would go to the Koushien...
...but it ended up losing
the final on a walkoff.
And we, the Fan Club, will become an official club if we defeat this prestigious Meiwa Daiichi...
...or be disbanded if we lose.
So you're going
to go easy on us ?
Sorry, no.
All the other guys
are practicing as usual.
Then why ?
I have to go to the
doctor now, so I left early.
Are you injured ?
Are you ill ?
I'm just going to the dentist.
I wouldn't want it to start hurting before an important game.
You should have four
or five teeth extracted !
Shut up.
Your dentist is lousy !
Oh, well.
All Meiwa baseball club
members should get food poisoning.
I guess that won't happen.
Um, well...
...as long as no balls are hit to the outfield, we should be fine.
The issue is how
to solidify the middle.
Someone who runs well, has a
strong arm, knows baseball well...
There is someone who is an overconfident, selfish, disagreeable show-off.
If only we could find Meiwa's weakness...
If I recall, he has two sets
of practice uniforms, right ?
Yeah.
There's a set here, too.
Meiwa's baseball club
has 80 members. Right ?
Hide-chan.
Oh ? Your archery club's
practice starts now ?
Yeah.
You're going to the dentist ?
Yeah, in preparation for the game against Senkawa.
Loads of over 2 tons
prohibited 60 meters
from this point
You don't have any thoughts of losing the game against Senkawa for their sake ?
No. It's going to
be a serious match.
You're stubborn.
Yeah, I'm stubborn.
Get set, go !
Let's see who's faster !
Whoever loses owes the other a drink !
All right !
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Good job.
Speak up !
Dammit.
The legs are too long, but it's tight around the waist.
Hey, you there.
What year are you ?
Hey, Suzuki !
Help me out here !
Okay.
Don't act nervous.
It makes you seem more suspicious.
There are a lot people here.
If you wear a cap and act
normal, no one will notice.
Yeah.
If only that idiot had shut them
down in the bottom of the ninth...
...we wouldn't have had to go through this much trouble.
What are his pitches like ?
I can't really tell unless
I catch for them myself.
All right, one more !
Excuse me, Saitou.
I'm Tamura.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Tamura. Tamura.
Tamura from the baseball club.
You have a phone call from home.
Please report to
the office right away.
A call from home ?
Oh, shall I fill in for you ?
Yeah, thanks.
When Tamura takes the phone, you're in charge, nyakay ?
Um, excuse me.
Tachibana went to the dentist today.
Today's loser is tomorrow's winner.
Just kidding.
One sitting mat.
Hm ?
How could they lose with this pitcher...?
Hey, are you a first year ?
Um, well, yes.
What's your name ?
Um, I'm Suzuki.
You're easy to pitch to, with both your body shape and the way you set up.
You're promising, so work hard.
Thank you.
They're hitting squarely back to center field.
Hey, you there !
Don't just stand there ! Go out there and pick up the balls !
Yes, sir.
The starters' hits carry far.
This lineup plus Hideo, huh ?
No matter how you look at it,
they're going to hit it to the outfield.
Right now, I'll settle for two dates with Koga, with a bonus kiss.
I mean, you definitely look cool
when you're pitching on the mound !
Moron...!
Throw the ball back !
What...?
So what are your thoughts ?
If that lefty pitches, our fan club guys won't stand a chance.
They'll just have to put on a bunt attack, and hope that our opponent makes a mistake.
And us, too. If we look to hit a
big one, we'll fall into their trap.
I see.
How are their hitters ?
They're better than I thought.
If they had gone to the Koushien, the newspapers would have rated them as "A."
Any strategies ?
Trust the fielders and go
full-strength after the hitters.
In that case, we'll need Kine.
Right now, I'll settle for a kiss...
We can't agree to
his conditions, though.
More importantly, there's Yanagi.
If we don't have him at
second base, it's all over.
I see.
Well, that was productive.
It's great that we took the
trouble to go spy on them.
We still have one week, after all.
That's right !
Yeah, it was so useful !
It was.
Sorry !
It reminds you of our days with
the Hakusan Angels, doesn't it ?
Right, Fune ?
Namihei...
Strike !
I hear that you told the coach that you'd quit the Hakusan Angels if I was the cleanup hitter.
That coach had no eye for talent.
Before you came along, they used to win with scores like 3-2, 3-1...
...but with you, the team
became capable of scoring 5 runs.
But in exchange, you couldn't be sure
how many runs the team would give up.
Back then, you weren't
what the team needed.
It was me.
It really was me !
It's not that the coach didn't have an eye for talent.
What ?
I'm the one who kicked you out.
By making you out to
be a suspicious person.
Strike !
Fortunately, no one on the team spoke up on your behalf, so it was easy.
What are you talking about ?
Well, all I did was put the
coach's wallet in your bag...
...in a way that it would
be easily noticeable.
Twice.
Strike ! Batter out !
Well, that's in the past.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks to being the cleanup
batter for the Hakusan Angels...
...my baseball career got on an elite
track, from junior high to high school.
Of course, it was a track that I could run because of how good I am.
My one miscalculation was
that Hiro resumed baseball.
I was glad when he went to a high school without a baseball club.
Can it be that the lousy doctor who misdiagnosed Kunimi's elbow is...?
Of course I introduced
him to that doctor.
Oh well, he's in a fan club that will be disbanded next week without a doubt.
Weren't you friends ?
We are friends.
When we're not playing baseball, that is.
All stones on my rail will be
kicked out to the soccer club.
I don't care if baseball loses popularity or if it hurts the caliber of play.
As long as my contract money
increases, that's all that matters.
You were smart to give up on baseball so quickly.
I think we can be friends.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, can you give us the ball ?
That bastard !
I'm not going to let
you get your way !
Is he simple, or just honest ?
Thanks.
He's joining the
Baseball Fan Club ?
With no conditions attached ?
Maybe he ate something bad ?
No ! Our earnest feelings must have reached God !
God, huh ?
Hey, Kunimi !
We've got to win
the upcoming game !
We're not going to let
Tachibana get his way !
By Tachibana, you mean the first year who hits cleanup for the prestigious Meiwa...
...and who is from the food and
liquor store, Tachibana Store.
That's the Tachibana Hideo
I'm talking about !
What do you think he said ?
You and I are all rails on a rock !
You mean, rocks on a rail ?
Um, yeah, that's it !
All the geniuses like me that are going to get in his way...
...he said he'd crush, kick around, clobber, and throw them to the nether reaches !
Hideo said that ?
He says he and you are friends as long as you don't play baseball !
He says he's going to kick
you over to the soccer club !
Fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh, fight, oh...
All he cares about is himself. He doesn't care about you.
He introduced you to a quack !
And he turned me into a wallet thief !
It was all for his own sake !
That guy is a demon !
A devil !
Hideo, you bastard !
Who's a rock on a rail ?!
We're friends as long as
I'm not playing baseball ?
You're going to kick me
back to the soccer club ?
How dare you say that !
Is he simple, or just honest ?
You mean stupid.
He hid the coach's wallet and blamed it on someone else ?
You're stupid.
Are you actually his friend ?
You don't even know if Hide-chan is the kind of person who'd do that ?
I don't know what he
was like in grade school.
He introduced you to a quack so that you'd quit baseball ?
Moron.
It's cold.
When Noda hurt his
back for the first time...
...who took him to Uetake's clinic,
saying that he put his full trust in him ?
It was this guy.
Huh ?
Moron.
Don't keep calling me moron.
I knew something was a little weird.
A little weird ?
It was all weird.
You should have realized right away.
You should know why Hide-chan
would act like a bad guy.
If you're his friend, that is.
Realized !
So is Kine playing in the game ?
Yeah, he's really into it,
saying that he won't forgive you.
Thanks for that. I'll be sure to resolve the misunderstanding after the game.
That's okay.
Regardless of the reason, it doesn't change the fact that he quit baseball because of me.
Defeat Meiwa Ichi !
I'm happy if we can play
to the best of our abilities.
If you're my friend,
you should hold back a little.
Because I'm your friend,
I'm not going to hold back.
Anyway, all that's left is Yanagi.
Yeah.
Yanagi ?
Yeah, don't you remember ?
The guy who played second
base for Kita Junior High ?
That Yanagi is at your school ?
Yeah.
I hadn't heard that.
Of course not. I didn't tell you.
Right ?
Right.
Why would Yanagi go to Senkawa, of all places ?
His father is a bit of an issue.
And he is the principal of our school.
You know about the team that lost a no-hitter with the score of 0-30 at the Koushien...
...Sousei High School, right ?
He's a graduate of that school.
Ever since then, all he hears about is that game, so he's totally bummed.
He says he hates high school baseball, and won't let Yanagi play.
I didn't know that your school had not only Kine, but Yanagi, too.
Huh ?
Hide, having played the role of the
bad guy already, can you call Yanagi...
...and threaten him by saying you'll set
off a bomb at his house or something...
...if he doesn't play in the game ?
What ?
Moron !
One out with runners on first and second. Now batting is the fifth hitter, Tanaka.
It's a chance to drive in runs.
Well, the Koushien has finally begun.
Momiji Bank,
Branch Manager,
Oomori Yoshio
When the Koushien
starts, I feel all jittery.
Which high school did
you graduate from ?
Sousei.
Sousei !
Sousei High School.
Oh, that 0-30...
0-30 what ?
Um, well, nothing.
Now, about that certificate
of deposit that has matured.
I'm withdrawing it.
Huh ?
I'm withdrawing it, of course.
There !
Yes ! I've got
the go-ahead run !
Damn !
We should have gone with the disappearing pitch.
What's wrong, Hiro ?
You've been cornered.
God must be hasty. He didn't have to arrange their showdown this soon.
Oh well, I guess it's over.
What ? It's not over yet !
There's still the bottom of the ninth !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Oomori:
Meiwa's Coach:
Umpire:
Tamura:
Girl's Voice:
First Year Member:
Club Member:
Child:
Komura Tetsuo
Kitagawa Takurou
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Aizawa Masaki
Neya Michiko
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Hiro solidifying the middle: He's talking about the fielding positions of catcher,  second base, short-stop, through
center field.
Another homophone joke: Dentist, "haisha," has the same sound as loser, "haisha." In stand-up comedy, one would throw a sitting mat for jokes that are either funny or not funny - I forget which.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Finally, the day of destiny.
The game is starting, right, Hiro ?
But, oh well,
they're underestimating us.
What is it ? You're playing
against their second-string team ?
It gives us a better
chance of winning, though.
That's not good. Just give them a
rude awakening with your pitching.
You want me to drag their
first-string into the game ?
Fans across the nation are waiting
for your showdown with Hide-chan.
Next episode of H2 is,
"The Second-String is Playing."
Next episode of H2 is
The Second-String is Playing
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?