Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 14
The Second-String is Playing
Let's have a family outing !
Outdoor vacation
The Forest House Lodge
Travel Friend' Extra Issue
Don't act tough just
because you're big !
Soon, I'll be as big as you !
Hey, don't laugh, Hikari !
Oh, come on.
What could Mother be doing ?
This is the day of destiny, where
Senkawa High School's Baseball Fan Club...
...will play a game that decides whether it
will become an official club or be disbanded.
Meiwa Daiichi High School
He's his usual self, it seems.
Hey, Fune.
Did you see my wallet
somewhere around here ?
You little...
I steal bases,
I don't steal wallets.
That's great and all.
Hey, Kunimi !
Fune ?
Don't you dare give
up any hits to him !
We have to win this game no matter what kind of hand we're dealt !
Got that ?
But I can only deal
with this hand of mine.
Hey, Hiro !
Is Yanagi here yet ?
It doesn't look like it.
What do you mean,
"It doesn't look like it" ?
What're we going to
do if he doesn't come ?
Who's going to play second base ?
Shut up.
That's the same line I've been
repeating in my head for a while now.
Just as I feared, he just can't disobey his father.
So, who do we have available ?
Let's see...
Satou, Tanaka, Sasaki, Nakamura, and...
Oh, did you catch a cold ?
The guy with a cold.
Huh ?
Amamiya
I'm home.
So, Hikari, which one
are you pulling for ?
It goes without saying.
I'll get going.
It goes without saying ?
Hm ?
They're underestimating us.
They're playing the second-string.
That's great for us.
Just as Kine says, what's important in this game isn't how we play.
What's important is that we win, no matter what tactics we use.
Bow !
Pleased to play with you !
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
They let us take the field first, even though we're the visitor.
It's all great for us.
I thought I asked you
not to hold back on us.
Well, it's way too cruel to play
the first-string from the start.
It would be a problem if you lose to us.
Oh, stop kidding. They aren't
your usual second-string players.
They're second-string on Meiwa's team,
which is famed for its deep roster.
They're all good enough to be
first-string players at other schools.
If they were to lose...
...I'd shave my head.
Hey, there's no way you'll be playing in this game.
Take it easy and
watch from the dugout.
Senior, you might want to warm up, too.
Oh, well.
Give them a rude awakening, Hiro.
And drag Meiwa's regular lineup,
and me, out onto the field.
Oh !
Hey !
He's very aggressive
from the first pitch.
Safe !
Don't worry. Don't worry.
See ?
If we were to lose,
I'd shave my head.
This is really a drag.
Why do we have to
play a team like this ?
It can't be helped.
After all, Senkawa's principal is the
boss of all the principals around here.
I wonder what that dude is thinking.
He told us not to hold back
against these silly fan club guys.
Anyway, let's finish this off quickly and get back to real practice.
Yeah. If we score like twenty runs in three innings, they'll give up.
Damn right !
Runners on the
corners with no outs.
Out !
Huh ?
Oh my.
I'm surprised that no runs were scored with runners on first and third with no outs.
Your guys are putting up a good fight.
As I said, it will be a
problem if you lose to us.
Oh, please.
It was just dumb luck.
What's going on ?
The second-string is playing ?
Yeah.
I thought I'd be able to see Hiro's silly max-effort pitch for the first time in a while.
I'm a little disappointed.
You'll be able to see it.
Really ?
Meiwa Baseball Club is not that soft, including the second-string.
Anyway, I'm going to be
pulling for Hiro for this game.
Is that okay ?
It's just today, right ?
Of course.
Then it's okay.
Strike ! Batter out !
Man, he doesn't throw like any second or third-string player I've ever seen.
Geez, I have to pitch to a
sick person ? I can't take this.
Yeah, he's good !
The fielder is good, too...
Safe !
Yeah !
A perfectly laid-down bunt
just barely makes it...?
He runs really fast !
Um...
Who is he ?
Hey, Noda ?
He's hittable ! He's hittable !
Okay, okay.
His batting form looks
good for a lousy hitter.
EYECATCH
Out !
Damn.
Impressive, third batter.
That was a great at-bat
to advance the runner.
Shut up. More importantly, you should be careful.
That pitcher's fastball moves a bit.
Who are you talking to ?
Don't you know what
I used to be called ?
Of course not.
"Dr. Baseball."
In terms of knowledge
and analysis, I'm a genius.
If I see three pitches...
...that's enough for me to figure out a pitcher's velocity, power, quirks, and everything.
Huh ? Noda, you're
not the cleanup batter ?
I mean, he made so much noise...
...about how he wouldn't be able to get the bat on the ball if I didn't hit fourth.
Strike !
Just watch, Kunimi.
I'll show you a model example of how to capture a pitcher based on baseball theories.
Sure thing, I'm watching you.
He sure talks tough.
Wait on the ball, swing from the waist without opening up the upper body...
...and...
Huh ?
Do you understand, Kunimi ?
It's all about willpower !
That's the fundamental
of baseball mangas !
Hahaha !
And I'm someone who doesn't steal wallets, but steals second base instead.
Huh ?
Out.
I sure saw that.
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
Hm ?
It'll be a problem if your team loses.
Oh, stop that.
The game is just beginning.
Nice job covering, shortstop.
That's right.
The game is just beginning.
You're pitching like a slacker out there.
Huh ?
You should say that I'm pitching like a tactician.
I thought hard about what
I should do in order to win.
More importantly, Hikari.
You're pulling for us today, right ?
Just for today, yeah.
What did Hideo say ?
"Just for today," he said.
He let us have the goddess of victory on our side.
Just for today.
Then we'll invite you to our dugout.
You can sit and watch comfortably.
Thanks for that.
Now, I'll get going.
Foul !
Out !
Oh, well. Can't you do anything about your slow-footedness ?
Try not to screw up.
B: Hmm...
We're getting the ball right on the barrel of the bat.
Why aren't we scoring any runs ?
Geez, this game feels like a set-up.
Oh, come on.
In a game like this,
once we score one run...
...the next runs will come to us like a crumbling sand castle.
That's right.
We'll get more runs than
we could ever want.
You guys should stay
second-string forever.
Huh ?
Alright, you got it !
Out !
He almost got it !
It would've been an infield hit, if only
our Yamaguchi were their third baseman !
Hey...
It's still just one out !
Arikawa, narrow down the target and chop it down from the top !
And don't swing at high pitches !
Yeah !
Avoid popping up, no matter what !
Keep the swing compact !
That's the way !
Oh, that was close !
If you keep the swing a little more compact, you'll get it !
He hasn't changed in this regard.
Yeah.
You don't have to be a stranger.
Okay then.
There's no need to go for a big hit !
Just slap it ! Slap !
It feels like the old days, doesn't it ?
It does.
Your elbow will break
down in three months ?
You're not going to say that you're quitting, are you ?
If you take baseball away from
you, there'll be nothing left.
If you're a man, you should follow
the path you've chosen to the end.
Don't turn your back midway through your journey.
When you go down, you go head-first.
You should cure your elbow pain with your willpower.
Moron, it's just a sport.
Sports are things that are
supposed to strengthen your body.
What kind of morons are out there
playing sports to ruin their bodies ?
After all, good health is the most
important thing for human beings.
Yeah.
What kind of an old man are you ?
You're so gutless !
Say whatever you want.
Nowadays, self-destructive heroes aren't in vogue.
This is my retirement pitch.
You should watch it, since you've known me since the first time I played catch.
Here I go !
Go on.
Clap, clap, clap, clap.
Well, good work.
Ouch.
Why are you just standing there blankly ? You should catch it.
It's your retirement memorial ball.
Moron. With these things, you have to
wait and feel the afterglow, you know ?
Ouch...
You shouldn't cry.
You're so dramatic.
It really hurt !
Oh, you mean your elbow, not your head ?
Moron...
Would you like a drink ?
...?
Barley tea.
Thanks.
Out !
That was close !
He would've been totally safe if only
that first baseman were our Hironaga !
Hey...
It's only the third inning !
Let's go for it !
Of course ! Let's go for it !
Yeah !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Hikari's Mom:
Hironaga:
Yanagi:
Yamaguchi:
Arikawa:
Ichinose:
Nemoto:
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Ikemoto Sayuri
Takagi Wataru
Izaki Hisayoshi
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Ishino Ryuuji
Yanagisawa Eiji
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Meiwa Principal saying he'd shave his head: "Shaving head" is a gesture of becoming a monk, i.e. abandoning the worldly ambitions and going into the path of religion.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hiro, you won't be able to get through this lineup with your dodgy pitching now.
Damn. I wish I could get through the lineup one more time with this stuff.
Hide-chan is going to get
two plate appearances.
You came here to pull for me, right ?
Of course.
Just for today, though.
Then cheer for me with
everything you've got !
You should pitch with
everything you've got, too !
Okay.
Next episode of H2 is,
"I Look Kind of Cool, Right ?"
Are you having a refreshing workout ?
Next episode of H2 is
I Look Kind of Cool, Right ?
Look forward to it !