Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 15
I Look Kind of Cool, Right ?
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
All right ! Let's crush
them in one blow !
Let's destroy the sand castle now !
We should cheer, too !
Well, that was the
eighth hit given up already.
What're you talking about ?!
We're winning right now !
But I mean, it feels like
we're just getting lucky.
For some reason, when runners are in scoring position, the ball goes right to the fielders.
How faint-hearted ! This is how good we actually are !
You should have faith
in your ace pitcher !
That's right. Two perfect games, five no-hitters.
If we include unofficial practice games, we don't even know how many records he has.
But that was when he
was in junior high, right ?
That's true.
We should cheer ! Okay ?!
Okay...
Give me the scorebook.
Damn ! That guy again ?
When we have scoring opportunities, the balls go right at the fielders.
Most of our outs are being made by their
second baseman and center fielder.
All right ! Go ! Go !
Out ! Change !
I feel like I've seen
that pitcher somewhere.
Hey, good job !
Shut up !
How much longer are you
going to pitch like a slacker ?
I joined you to beat
Tachibana, you know ?
Settle down.
Even if they're second-string...
...if they lose to an ordinary fan club, both Meiwa and Hideo will lose face.
Shut up !
I pitch better than
you're pitching right now !
Listen ! You should drag
him into the game already !
Otherwise, I'm going to...
Great job, Kine !
Nice throw back to home plate !
I'm going to work hard, Koga.
"Otherwise, I'm going to..." what ?
Meiwa sure is impressive. They have a deep roster.
Yeah. In spite of it all,
they're hitting the ball well.
The way it's going, you won't be able to deceive them for much longer.
Well, let's take it as far as we can.
It's a pretty good team.
It'll be a problem if you lose, Mr. Meiwa.
Oh ?
Nice batting !
Let's push them here !
Huh ? What is it ?
Nothing.
This is just a show of courtesy.
I got it !
Strike ! Batter out !
Oh ?
You've been spared this time.
The opponent's pitcher is a finesse guy who pitches to the corners.
If we look for the right pitch and hit for contact, we can get him.
Let's finish him off this inning !
Yeah !
You don't have to get so worked up...
Well, let's see how far I can go.
Oh ?
Pitch inside.
Throw a curveball that drops from a
hittable spot, and it'll be a fly ball to center.
I got it ! I got it !
Nice job covering !
Shut up ! Pitch seriously !
I am.
Nice job, second baseman.
Now then...
He wanted an out on a fly ball to center,
but it was single to right-center field.
He wanted a double-play on a grounder to second, but it was nearly a single to center.
Now, is he going to go for a double-play with the second baseman again ?
Out !
Dammit !
Phew ! That was close.
It looks like they're
finally getting serious.
After all, it was unreasonable to
think that I could deceive them...
...by spotting the pitches with ordinary fastballs.
Top of fifth, runners on
second and third with two outs.
If we make a mistake here, it'll hurt.
I agree.
Are you going to be okay ?
Hm ?
I mean, we're totally relying on you.
That puts a lot of
pressure on you, doesn't it ?
We started this game without too much hope anyway.
Let's take it easy.
We've come this far. You've done plenty good already.
Don't you want to win ?
Eh ?!
You want to win, right ?
Yeah, but...
Then let's win !
Hang in there, Kunimi !
Strike !
Strike two !
Strike ! Batter out !
Yay ! I struck out a
batter for the first time !
Hooray !
I struck out a Meiwa hitter !
I'm so happy !
It's embarrassing. Stop it.
It's too late now.
What's with that pitcher ?
I don't know.
I don't have any interest,
so I have no idea what his name is.
Really ?
It'll be a problem if you lose to us.
Oh, please.
Who do you think we are ?
We are the prestigious Meiwa team.
There's no way we're going to lose.
I hope that's the case.
What is our principal doing ?
Who knows ?
Regulars
need
to
play.
That was impressive !
This is the first time I've
seen a pitch as fast as that !
You're exaggerating.
I mean, really.
We can win this thing.
We can do it.
We definitely can.
I'm getting fired up !
The opponent's dugout has a serious look now.
They must have put in some
colored contact lens or something.
Colored contact lens, huh ?
What ? That pitch was
right down the pipe.
Three outs ! Change !
They're getting the timing right.
Our seniors are actually doing great.
Yeah. We have to make sure this club becomes an official one.
Where's my glove...?
Is this it ?
Yeah, that's it. Thanks.
Was that a new fan of mine ?
She's pretty good-looking.
But I feel like I've seen
her somewhere before.
All right, I'm on a roll now !
Let's go after them !
The keys to their defense are the
second baseman and the center fielder.
And the pitcher has a great command of his pitches and an unexpectedly live fastball.
That's fine.
That's all they have.
There's no way a nameless
first year pitcher can keep going...
...because high school baseball, no, Meiwa baseball is too tough.
Kunimi !
Hang in there !
Leave it to me !
Ouch...
Hey, be serious, Hiro !
Okay.
Hiro...?
Kunimi...Hiro...?
T...timeout !
Meiwa's starters are in now.
Ah, we might be done for.
I thought we might win...
Hey, famous guy.
I was hoping that they might wait for another inning.
We've got four innings left.
Unless you pitch a no-hitter, you'll face Hideo twice.
That puts some pressure on us.
Yeah.
But this is why we can't quit baseball.
Right ?
Play !
Strike !
I thought he injured his elbow and quit.
Lots of things happened.
Strike.
Strike ! Batter out !
All right.
One out ! One out !
Wow ! The guy was
definitely late with his swing.
We can pull this off !
We can do it !
This is how he should
have thrown from the start.
It's fast.
I can tell from just watching.
Faster than it looks, I mean.
Strike !
I see.
In that case...
He couldn't deaden the ball.
But it flew into a good spot.
Out !
Nice job, second baseman.
Batter out !
Yeah !
Shall I be honest with you, Tachibana ?
When I saw Seinan Junior High play, I wanted him more than you.
More than you, who hits fourth as a first year on the prestigious Meiwa team.
I'm not surprised at all.
You say you don't want us to lose, but in actuality, you came here to win, didn't you ?
If you make it an official club after defeating us...
...it would be great
publicity for your new team.
I have no interest in gaining publicity through baseball.
Well, sorry. We gain publicity through our powerhouse high school baseball team.
I don't want them to be an official club.
You don't have to worry.
We are going to win. We're a
prestigious baseball school, after all.
I'm counting on you.
What is it ?
Huh ?
I'm making a facial expression to
show that I'm surprised once again.
When I'm playing baseball, I look kind of cool, right ?
Yeah.
You sure seem fired up.
Our opponent is worth it, after all.
She's cute.
Hey, who's that girl ?
Oh, you don't know her.
She's Hideo's girlfriend.
What ? Why is Tachibana's
girl in our dugout ?
It's fine.
She's supporting us for today.
Huh ? What's going on ?
She's Hiro's childhood friend.
We've known her
longer than Hideo has.
Oh.
What's this ?
You're so pathetic.
You let Tachibana take this beauty away
from you, even though he had a later start ?
What a moron.
You're annoying. Just go away.
Ah, how pathetic !
Hey, have you ever found a "hit" ?
In my case, there were
no more tickets left.
I'll show you my junior high
photo sometime. You'll laugh.
Until the second year of junior high, I was a snot-nosed midget.
Finally, my height caught up, and I started to think about maybe looking for a girlfriend...
Strike ! Batter out !
Damn !
Three up and three strikeouts.
Their first stringers sure are good.
This is it.
This is baseball.
Well, it's getting interesting.
Yeah.
Good luck.
Are you sure about that ?
The lead-off batter this inning is Hideo.
I'm cheering for Hiro, for today.
Finally, my height caught up, and I started to think about maybe looking for a girlfriend...
...but all the girls that interested me
were in the midst of their first love.
Seriously ?
What's the point of lying about this sort of thing ?
Let's pull ourselves together here !
Three more innings, let's do it !
Let's go ! Let's go !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Meiwa's Coach:
Hironaga:
Yanagi:
Sato:
Arikawa:
Ichinose:
Tanaka:
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Izaki Hisayoshi
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Ishino Ryuuji
Yanagisawa Eiji
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
We've all been waiting for it.
Hide-chan and Hiro finally face off.
Well, if you can hit it, go right ahead !
Tachibana is a great guy.
Haruka ?
In my case, the guys who seemed nice turned out to be superficial; they were total misses.
Really ? But this time, you'll...
What are you two talking about ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"This Time, It's Not a Miss."
Next episode of H2 is
This Time, It's Not a Miss
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?