Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 16
This Time, It's Not a Miss
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
Play !
I'm counting on you...
...my best friend.
Thank you.
Dang. I feel humble.
The Hakusan Angels'
cleanup hitter is impressive.
There sure are talented
players in this world.
Oh, gosh.
Talented players, huh ?
You don't have to be disappointed.
It's totally understandable that you feel uneasy...
...when a lousy pitcher like that is the ace pitcher.
You don't have to worry. He was the ace pitcher until yesterday.
I'm the new ace pitcher, Kunimi Hiro.
Nice to meet you.
Ouch.
You just thought, "What kind of rubbish
is this midget talking about ?" didn't you ?
You can't be a first-rate hitter while
people can still read your mind so easily.
You just thought,
"What a noisy midget," didn't you ?
You just thought, "You bastard, I'm going to beat you up !" didn't you ?
If you face the two of us,
we can easily outwit you.
You're not the only one who's been given a gift from heaven, Tachibana Hideo.
I always hit the ball that I'm going for, no matter how fooled I am.
Remember that, you midget.
You just thought,
"He one-upped me." didn't you ?
You just thought, "Ah, how
nice it is to vent !" didn't you ?
Huh...?
Foul !
This is the first time.
What ?
A real face-off between
Hiro and Hide-chan.
You're putting on such a
powerful swing, best friend.
As always, you're stubborn.
Here.
I feel like this game is why
I've been playing baseball.
You must be imagining things.
This is just a worthless practice game, so let's settle down, okay ?
You rascal !
Foul !
Hey now. What are you
aiming for with that swing ?
With that swing, you mean to say that you won't be happy with just getting a hit ?
If I just aim for a single, I feel like I'll be late on the swing.
Oh, come on now.
Moron ! Don't call
for such a stupid pitch !
Just set up right down the middle !
Crap.
That's right. He has his strikeout pitch, the 140 km forkball.
That moron. The count is 0-2, with no runners on.
With nothing to lose, it would
have been an interesting pitch.
Here it comes, Hideo !
Hit it if you can !
Oh, crap !
The 140 km forkball ! Damn him !
If it's a single, I'll take it.
You won't make it, Kine !
Don't dive !
Shut up ! I'm going to catch
that guy's hit even if it kills me !
Oh ?
On this field, if it goes over the
fielder's head, it usually ends up as...
...an inside-the-park homerun.
The score is finally tied !
You shouldn't be happy with a tie.
Ball.
He'll be fine.
Is he fine ?
Ball.
Losing command of his pitches after an error ?
I suppose he still has some growing up to do.
He's not that delicate.
Timeout.
Hey, what were those pitches about ?
It's strange. It made the perfect dive when I pitched it to Hideo.
Right ?
It's not "right ?" Just forget about your fluky forkball !
The score is tied now !
And you have to face Hideo again !
This is no time to
be fooling around !
If we lose this game, we won't even be able to play catch at Senkawa !
You're right.
Three outs ! Change !
Good job keeping it to one run.
Well, don't worry. If you give up a run, we just need to score a run.
Now, the cleanup is
coming up this inning.
Let's get fired up !
I see.
If we give up a run,
we just need to score a run.
Safe.
All right !
This world is made perfect !
Stars always get a chance to shine !
Don't overswing, Kine.
Come on !
He's not listening.
Strike.
Strike two.
Damn...
Just as I thought,
he didn't listen to me.
Dammit...
Oh.
He pulled off a sacrifice bunt.
What is it ?
I just haven't had
enough batting practice.
If not for the hiatus, I would've
had no trouble with those pitches.
Leave the rest to me, Kine.
I'm not counting on it.
Even if we don't score here, this will give Hiro another at-bat in the ninth.
Yes.
Hide-chan says that he had more homeruns and a higher batting average in junior high...
...but in terms of walkoff hits, Hiro had more.
In the ninth inning, Hiro is the
most dependable player, he says.
All right !
Uh-oh.
A double play. No runners left.
That means...
...what it means.
Hey, Hide !
It's okay to play hard, but you
should show some humanity here.
No one would complain if
you couldn't catch that ball !
You know better than me
how dutiful Hiro is, don't you ?
I shouldn't do him any favors here...
...if we're to play a fair and even game that decides who will go to the Koushien in the future.
Oh, well.
More importantly...
Is it really just today that
you're going to root for Hiro ?
You're so obnoxious.
Sorry.
He's such a great guy.
What ?
Tachibana, I mean.
Oh.
He's a little stubborn, though.
How long have you been
going out with him ?
Let's see.
We got introduced to one another
by Hiro in our first year of junior high.
After that, we started to go watch movies
and have a cup of tea together on off-days.
Since your first year of junior high...
Hide-chan was already popular then.
He was athletically talented, and he looked cool.
Here.
And as you started to go out with him, you found that his merits went beyond his looks.
Right.
You have good luck with the lottery.
In my case...
...guys who looked cool all turned out to be blanks with nothing beyond good looks.
I've never drawn a hit.
First you need to correct
your careless personality.
You grab one in haste, and that's how you draw a miss.
Kunimi, have you drawn a "hit" ?
In my case, the tickets were sold out.
This time, you probably didn't draw a miss.
Huh ?
A love letter to Hiro ?
Are you serious ?
Hiro.
Wait, Hikari.
Look, I've caught up with you in height.
Told you so !
There's no need to rush !
Just be steady !
Out !
Good job !
All right !
He was short...
Until the second year of junior high, I was a snot-nosed midget.
Finally, my height caught up, and I started to think about maybe looking for a girlfriend...
...but all the girls that interested me were in the midst of their first love.
What is it ?
Um, well, nothing.
All right ! Go !
Out !
Do you really want
to disband this team ?
I made this promise
to make that happen.
It's hot.
It's summer.
Strike ! Batter out !
All right !
All that's left is the ninth inning !
Now, it's getting interesting, Koga !
Team
Meiwa-Ichi
Senkawa
It'll be a problem if your team loses.
If we win, we'll be a baseball club. If we lose, we'll be disbanded.
So what happens if it's a tie ?
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Meiwa's Coach:
Umpire:
Yanagi:
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Izaki Hisayoshi
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
It's a tie game after the eighth inning.
Meiwa will come after you with all they've got.
It's my second match-up against Hideo. If only I can get him out...
Overconfidence can be very dangerous. Hide-chan isn't your only opponent.
See ? A hard-hit ball hits Hiro's leg.
That scared me. I thought for a moment that it hit Kunimi's leg.
It did.
What ? That's not good !
This isn't a big deal.
Next episode of H2 is "Hiro is Injured ?!
What Will the Baseball Fan Club Do ?"
Next episode of H2 is
Hiro is Injured !?
What Will the Baseball Fan Club Do ?
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?