Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 17
Hiro is Injured !?
What Will the Baseball Fan Club Do ?
All right, go !
Out !
Do you really want
to disband this team ?
I made this promise
to make that happen.
It's hot.
It's summer.
Strike ! Batter out !
All right !
All that's left is the ninth inning !
Now, it's getting interesting, Koga !
...!
If we win, we'll be a baseball club. If we lose, we'll be disbanded.
Hm ?
I made this promise
to make that happen.
Team
Meiwa-Ichi
Senkawa
So what happens if it's a tie ?
It's already the ninth inning.
Well, it has become
such an interesting game.
Would you like some barley tea ?
No, thank you.
Okay.
Honestly, it's quite impressive that your
team is keeping our first-string to one run.
Come to think of it, what will
happen if the game ends in a tie ?
My thinking was the game would end in such a way...
...that the loss would result in the dissolution of the club.
Well, of course...
There are no extra innings in this practice game.
If you don't score this inning, we won't win.
And this is a game between the
prestigious Meiwa and a nameless fan club.
Given your talent and training, you won't embarrass yourselves no matter where you are.
...there's no way you'll
embarrass yourselves.
Now that you've put a lot of pressure on yourselves, I want to see what you're made of.
Yeah !
What do you think, Kunimi ?
Don't form a circle in a
game against a fan club.
Well, that aside, we're going to have to face Hideo this inning.
I know.
Then, that's that.
Yeah.
Now, it's the last inning !
Everyone, hang in there !
The final inning...
If we keep them scoreless here...
We might have a walkoff win...
Hey ! How much longer are
you going to make us wait ?!
Just start it already !
All right, let's pull ourselves together !
Yeah !
Team
Meiwa-Ichi
Senkawa
Tachibana will have one more at-bat.
They'll be fine.
He's going to hold him down.
That's right.
The two hitter.
The three hitter.
And...
...the four hitter.
Play !
In any case, I can't allow a
runner before Hideo's at-bat.
Strike !
Watch out.
I know.
Foul !
This will make it a
three-pitch strikeout !
Don't underestimate me !
Ball.
Huh ?
Meiwa is impressive.
The second time through the lineup,
they're definitely seeing the ball better.
All right !
Right at the shortstop !
All right ! Good job !
Tachibana, how strong
is that catcher's arm ?
He wouldn't embarrass himself no matter where he is, either.
I see.
Hikari.
Yes ?
Do you know the
next hitter's weakness ?
I don't know.
I see.
That's unfortunate.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Don't touch it !
Safe ! Safe !
All right. Runners are on
first and second with no outs.
This is how it should be.
In this situation, even
a single could be fatal.
You're right.
What are we going to do ?
Should we walk him ?
Hey ! You guys aren't thinking about walking him, are you ?!
Maybe walking him is our only option ?
Surely, loading the bases would make it easier on the defense.
Right...
Switch with me !
Team
Meiwa-Ichi
Senkawa
But we really have played a good game.
That's right.
Yeah.
Of course, we want to pitch to him.
I might get hit.
If it happens, it happens.
Since we're totally relying on you,
it's not really our place to say, but...
...after coming this far,
we want to settle the score !
But if we lose, the
club will be disbanded.
Even if they take the lead here, we still
have our at-bat in the bottom of the inning.
That's how we feel,
but what do you think ?
I'll do my best.
Then let's pull ourselves together !
Yeah !
The momentum has totally gone to the other side.
Don't worry.
They only get lucky twice.
We wouldn't have to worry if the upcoming batter was someone who got hits with luck.
We're going to strike him out.
You know who the next
batter is, don't you ?
It's the liquor store's son, right ?
Huh ?
All right.
Kunimi, hang in there !
Strike !
You can do it ! The batter
was totally late with the swing !
Yes ! The count is 0-2 !
Strike him out with
three pitches, Kunimi !
This is the first time I've seen
Tachibana swing and miss twice in a row.
Man, that's fast.
The 140-km forkball is coming next.
Yeah, I know.
0-2.
If you're playing by the book, you're supposed to throw a ball here, Hiro.
Hiro focuses more on command when he throws off the plate.
The location might be difficult,
but the velocity is a different story.
Don't go for such a pitch !
On this field, a ball that goes
over an outfielder will usually be...
I won't make it !
Nice play, Kine.
EYECATCH
I get it.
You saved us, genius.
I get it. Just get back
to your position already.
Runners on first and second with one out.
Um, I hate to pester you, but what are
we going to do in the case of a tie ?
The prestigious Meiwa's baseball club
plays a tie game against a puny fan club ?
You don't have any confidence that you're going to win ?
Of course we do.
It will be a problem if it
becomes an actual club.
That was close...
But the team is still in a tight spot.
It'll be fine, now that the
most detestable hitter is out !
...!
Note: -san, chan, kun. Our group only uses them for pet names.
Um, Tachibana is such a great guy...
I mean, Mr. Tachibana.
He's a little inflexible, though.
Right, he doesn't back down.
Oh, you can just call him Tachibana.
Hm ?
One out ! One out !
Yeah !
Complacency is the greatest enemy, Hiro.
We're counting on you, Tamura !
Yeah !
Strike !
All right !
Two more outs.
I'll shut them down and then turn it over
to our offense in the bottom of the inning.
...!
Out !
Damn ! If it hadn't hit the mound,
it would've gone through to center !
What bad luck !
Nice job, second baseman !
Okay, two outs ! Two outs !
I'm relieved.
For a moment,
I thought it hit Kunimi's leg.
It did.
Huh ?
Strike !
But it doesn't seem
to have affected him.
Hiro...
...makes a big fuss
when it's not a big deal.
But when it really hurts him...
All right ! It went through ! We're in luck !
Safe !
When it really...
When it really hurts,
Hiro won't tell anyone.
Even a good pitcher will have trouble keeping Meiwa's lineup scoreless the second time through.
It was a meatball right down the pipe.
Well, the Meiwa lineup
doesn't miss mistake pitches.
Mistake pitch, huh ?
Moron !
What're you doing ?!
What are you going to do
about my super fine play ?!
Hmm...
Meiwa is in luck, I guess.
Then I guess we'll
have to rely on the sun.
Nice play, second baseman.
Thanks.
I'm glad you showed up, Yanagi.
Thanks to you, we were
able to play a good game.
Are you going to give up ?
If I could give up so easily, I wouldn't play a game like this to begin with.
You probably shouldn't
talk to him about the leg.
Huh ?
It would be useless to say anything to him until the game is over.
That's how he always is. He never gets treatment.
He gets stubborn for silly reasons.
I see.
Yes, so...
But I can't do that !
What ?
I'm the manager !
Kunimi, come over here !
Oh, what is it, Manager ?
Just get over here.
Okay...
Now, it's just two runs !
Get runners on base !
It's a tie game if we get a
runner on and hit a homerun !
We can tie up the game
with one scoring chance !
Whatever you do,
just get me an at-bat !
If we score three runs,
we win in a walk-off !
We don't need four runs !
No, I'm going to hit the
bases loaded walk-off homerun !
Kine !
Koga ?
You're the first base coach !
Oh, of course, of course.
First base, first base.
Let's go ! Leading off is the left fielder, hitting ninth, Moriya !
Yeah !
It's such a transparent cheer.
Hmm ?
What is it ?
You've grown up a
fair amount, it seems.
Shut up.
She's the best manager.
Foul !
But really, we're in a tight spot.
It's just two runs.
Strike !
Strike ! Batter out !
We can tie it with one scoring chance.
Don't worry ! Don't worry !
We're counting on you, Ari !
Yeah !
Safe !
Out !
It's not over yet !
Things are just starting !
In baseball, things
start from two outs !
Of course.
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Meiwa's Coach:
Hironaga:
Sato:
Yanagi:
Arikawa:
Nakajima:
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Yamazaki Takumi
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Ishino Ryuuji
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Honorifics: We don't use them. This is an English translation.
They are levels of familiarity among people or status. Examples of what we would use in the translation -
San = Mr/Mrs.  Sama = Lord/Lady/Sire
As for "chan" and "kun" you could consider them as
using someone's last name with out the "Mr."
Example: "Hey, Smith, come here."
Our group only uses them for pet names.  Hikari is an example of using a pet name for Hideo. She calls him "Hide-chan."  And remember the Japanese rarely use given names with each other unless they are close friends or going out.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
Noda on luck and the sun: This is another one of the homophone puns. Luck, or "tsuki," is a homophone of
"moon" ["tsuki"]. So since the moon is on Meiwa's side,
Noda says they have to rely on the sun to be on their side.
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Down by two runs, Senkawa has its last turn in the bottom of the ninth.
We can't go down like this. If we win, we'll be an actual baseball club.
Your leg hurts, right ?
It doesn't matter when we've come this far.
We'll have to put our hopes on Hiro's batting in the bottom of the ninth.
All right, Yanagi, get on base !
Then I, Kine Ryutarou, will
decide the game in the end !
Next episode of H2 is"A Heated Game in the Bottom of the Ninth ! The Batter Is Kunimi..."
Next episode of H2 is
A Heated Game in the Bottom of
the Ninth ! The Batter Is Kunimi...
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?