Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 18
A Heated Game in the Bottom of
the Ninth ! The Batter is Kunimi...
The air-conditioners are operating at max.
The road is full of outbound and inbound traffic.
At the Koushien, high school baseball players are playing heated games.
But...
It's hot.
It's summer.
A heated game no one knows about is being played here in the ballpark at Meiwa Daiichi.
They're underestimating us.
They're playing the second-string.
That's great for us.
The objective of this game is just to win, no matter what the means.
The objective is not to play a good game, it's just to win, in any way we can.
Yes, we, the Senkawa Baseball Fan Club, have a goal: to win at all costs.
We scored the first run of the game
on a lucky hit by "Dr. Baseball," Kine.
Do you get it, Kunimi ?
It's all about willpower !
Somehow, someway,
we got closer to our goal.
When we have scoring opportunities, the balls go right at the fielders.
Most of our outs are being made by their
second baseman and center fielder.
Out !
Hey, good job.
Shut up !
How much longer are you
going to pitch like a slacker ?
I joined you to beat
Tachibana, you know ?
If they lose to an ordinary fan club,
both Meiwa and Hideo will lose face.
You should drag him
into the game already !
Otherwise, I'm going to...
This is just a show of courtesy.
0:00:50.00 0:00:51.00
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
It will be a problem if you lose.
Out.
That was close.
They're becoming serious.
Meiwa isn't so weak as to lose
to a nameless first year pitcher.
Hang in there, Kunimi !
Hey, get serious, Hiro !
Hiro ?
Kunimi Hiro ?
Timeout !
I was hoping that they might wait for another inning.
I thought he injured his elbow and quit.
Lots of things happened.
Yeah !
Shall I be honest with you, Tachibana ?
When I saw Seinan Junior High play, I wanted him more than you.
More than you, who hits fourth as a first year on the prestigious Meiwa team.
I'm not surprised at all.
I'm counting on you...
...my best friend.
Foul !
You're putting on such a
powerful swing, best friend.
As always, you're stubborn.
Here.
I feel like this game is why
I've been playing baseball.
You must be imagining things.
This is just a worthless practice game, so let's settle down, okay ?
You rascal !
Foul !
Hey now. What are you
aiming for with that swing ?
With that swing, you mean to say that you won't be happy with just getting a hit ?
If I just aim for a single, I feel like I'll be late on the swing.
Oh, come on now.
Moron ! Don't call
for such a stupid pitch !
Just set up right down the middle !
Crap.
That's right. He has his strikeout pitch, the 140 km forkball.
Here it comes, Hideo !
That moron. The count is 0-2, with no runners on.
With nothing to lose, it would
have been an interesting pitch.
Hit it if you can !
It fell. The pitch
Hiro threw definitely fell.
The 140-km forkball ! Damn him !
But Hideo successfully hit it.
If it's a single, I'll take it.
I'm going to catch that
guy's hit even if it kills me !
Kine was going to catch it even if it killed him, but...
...he lay on the field.
Top of the seventh,
Meiwa scored its first run.
The score is finally tied !
You shouldn't be happy with a tie.
Team
Meiwa Ichi
Senkawa
If we win, we'll be a baseball club. If we lose, we'll be disbanded.
So what happens if it's a tie ?
There are no extra innings in this game.
Top of the ninth, we're facing Meiwa's cleanup hitter, Tachibana Hideo.
Don't go for such a pitch !
When he said he'd catch
Hideo's hit even if it kills him...
...Kine wasn't lying.
Nice play, Kine.
But then...
For a moment,
I thought it hit Kunimi's leg.
It did.
He makes a big fuss
when it's not a big deal.
When it really hurts,
he won't tell anyone.
Safe !
Meiwa is in luck, I guess.
Then I guess we'll
have to rely on the sun.
Nice play, second baseman.
I'm glad you showed up, Yanagi.
Thanks to you, we were
able to play a good game.
Are you going to give up ?
If I could give up so easily, I wouldn't play a game like this to begin with.
Down by two runs,
we have one inning left.
Strike ! Batter out !
Two more outs left.
Safe !
Out !
No, just one.
In this game, which stakes the promotion of this fan club to an actual club...
...we're down by two runs.
In the batter's box is
a guy who caught a cold.
Is the fan club going to be
able to make a comeback ?!
What're you being a commentator for ?
Foul !
One more out.
Or rather, one more pitch, now that the count is 1-2.
1-2...
It's not over yet.
In terms of a pitcher's psychology,
he's definitely going for a strikeout.
Foul !
Ball !
This is where you show your
specialty, guy who a caught cold.
Meiwa's ace pitcher, you won't be able to strike this batter out.
He's peerless in his
ability to foul off pitches.
Foul !
We'll leave the second base open.
You should go against
your parent for once.
A filial bond shouldn't
be a one-way street.
It won't be a good tie if it
isn't pulled from both sides.
How many pitches are left now ?
It's the next pitch.
Ball four.
All right !
Kunimi in the ninth inning, the most dependable hitter, gets his at-bat !
If not for the leg injury...
I guess he was injured.
Kunimi ! Hit a homerun !
If you hit a homerun,
you won't have to run !
It's probably impossible to hit it over the fence, since there are two fields in one here.
Kunimi, just think about getting on base. Okay ?
I'm the featured actor !
I don't have such a margin for error that lets me give up the lead role.
EYECATCH
Oh, did you know ?
Our school doesn't have a baseball club, but it has a baseball fan club.
Oh, I see.
I love high school baseball, so I'm
working as their manager starting today.
What're you gonna do ?
About what ?
It goes without saying.
Let's make the history of this
school's baseball club ourselves.
The Koushien doesn't matter.
We can play baseball again.
You and me, the golden battery.
I don't have any complaints.
Let's surprise those
powerhouse baseball schools !
All right, let's do it.
Strike !
You were totally fooled
by a breaking pitch.
That battery must have
thought the same, too.
All right, the same pitch !
Foul !
That was close.
That was a homerun.
It had the distance.
In a normal ballpark, it would've
been on the fair side of the pole...
...and into the stands, before it hooked into foul territory.
Now that he's our opponent, he teaches me all over again just how scary a hitter he is.
Dammit. I was
gambling on that one pitch.
If you take away baseball, you've got nothing left.
If you're a man, you should stick to the path you've determined for yourself.
Hey...
Don't turn your back midway through your journey.
When you go down, you go head-first.
You should cure your elbow pain with your willpower.
Don't look at me with
such a scary expression.
So you're going to get me out
with that pitch no matter what ?
I like that personality.
That's how an ace pitcher should be.
Get through !
Safe !
Runners on first and third with two outs.
Batting fourth, center fielder, Kine.
We're sending Satou as a
pinch-runner for the first base runner.
Star players get a great stage.
Of course.
Kine, do your best !
Listen, if you hit a homerun, we'll have a walkoff win !
If I hit a homerun...
...you're going on a date with me !
Okay, sure.
Anyway, we're counting on you, Kine !
What ? What ?
Including a kiss !
Of course ! Of course !
What ? What ?
You can have my kiss, too !
Just do something !
It's a promise, Koga !
Ugh ! Okay then !
We're leaving it to you !
Count on me !
What's wrong ?
This definitely isn't it.
This isn't it !
Huh ?
Remember how I used to swing !
Just because I had a long hiatus, this isn't how it should be !
Just remember !
Batter up !
Wait a sec !
I thought you used to hit lefty when you were with the Hakusan Angels.
Moron. I was...
...a big fan of Kakefu...
See, this is the sound !
You can't see a sound.
Batter !
Yeah !
He might actually hit it.
There won't be many
homeruns on this field.
I think...
There's an inside-the-park homerun, though.
But I might want to give him a kiss if he
hits a come-from-behind walkoff homerun.
I'm Kakefu !
Strike !
Watch the ball, will you ?
Hey, Kakefu !
Even if your swing is sharp, you
won't get a hit if your timing is off !
That's what the
battery will think, too.
Moron !
Strike two !
You bait him to throw the same pitch, but
you swing and miss that pitch ? That's silly.
It looks like he's going to swing and miss again.
That's what the
battery will think, too.
Don't underestimate me !
Crap, it's a fastball...
Go !
It's gone through !
The guy with a cold scores. The lead is down to one.
Runners on second and third.
He did it.
Even though it didn't result in a date...
Right.
What a game...!
Yeah. I'm gonna kiss him.
I'm glad I kept playing baseball for three years of high school.
It's not over yet, Seniors.
If they intentionally walk Noda, it'll be your turn.
Huh ?
What...?
How many more pitches to go ?
Two outs ! Two outs !
Batting fifth is the catcher, Noda,
who should actually be hitting fourth.
Noda.
When the club gets funding, we should buy a helmet for left-handed hitters.
And catcher's gear, too.
First base is open, Coach.
Nice game.
Play !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Meiwa's Coach:
Hironaga:
Sato:
Yanagi:
Arikawa:
Tanaka:
Ichinose:
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Yamazaki Takumi
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Ishino Ryuuji
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Noda on Luck and the Sun: This is another one of the homophone puns. Luck, or "tsuki," is a homophone of
"moon" ["tsuki"], so since the moon is on Meiwa's side,
Noda says they have to rely on the sun to be on their side.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
Kakefu was the famous cleanup hitter for the Hanshin Tigers
in the 80's, back when the Tigers won the championship.
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Is he going to become the last batter ?
Noda, the game is
approaching its finale.
Until the very end, we won't let up !
That's right. We shouldn't give up until the last out.
But what if the umpire
makes a bad call ?
What ? What do you mean ?
People with discerning
eyes do watch closely.
What do you mean ?
Next episode of H2 is, "A Come-From-Behind Win ! The Senkawa Baseball Club Is Born ?"
Next episode of H2 is
A Come-From-Behind Win !
The Senkawa Baseball Club Is Born ?
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?