Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
Episode 19
A Come-From-Behind Win !
The Senkawa Baseball Club Is Born ?
Fair !
Hey, best friend !
Out !
Yes...!
We did it ! We did it !
Three outs !
Game set !
Nice game.
Team
Meiwa-Ichi
Senkawa
With the score of 3-2,
Meiwa High School wins.
Thank you.
It was a great game.
Guys, you did great.
Dammit...
We were just a step short...
If we play again, we won't lose...
That's right. We want
to win next time, right ?
I'm going to negotiate with
the principal one more time.
Okay ?
Yeah !
I vote for Koga.
Damn that Tachibana...
I'm going to leave
him speechless next time.
Manager...
A promise is a promise.
True.
Then, if the "fan club" gets dissolved,
how about creating a "fan association" ?
Isn't that a great idea ?
Hey...!
Hey, wait ! Wait !
Wait up !
I'm foolish, aren't I ?
I say all kinds of unnecessary things.
Would you like to go and eat some ice cream ?
Um, thank you.
But I have to clean up.
She's the best manager.
Well, that last play was a close call.
Honestly.
It was an out.
Hey, no one's
complaining about your call.
Yeah. Just by a hair.
The out was definitely a fair call.
If only the foot wasn't
off the bag, that is.
Huh ?
But it's okay.
Whether it's boxing or soccer...
...when you're playing on the road, you
have to expect calls to go the other way.
Is that true ?
But we had a narrow escape.
Even though it was
just a practice game...
...it would be a huge problem if our
first-string were to lose to a puny fan club.
That's right.
Good call.
Yeah.
See you.
Okay.
Ugh !
W...who did that ?!
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Baseball Club Camp Hall
This is a prestigious high school baseball school...
Oh, you were in the restroom ?
Would you like something cold to drink inside ?
There's a hornet's nest on top of that school building.
Oh, let's take a look.
Oh, it's true.
I'm surprised that
you can see that far.
Yes, I'm fortunate to have good eyes.
So if the fan club isn't okay,
what about a secret society ?
It's a great idea, isn't it ?
Is your leg okay ?
Yeah.
Welcome home.
Is your cold better ?
Sousei High School Graduation Commemoration
Aren't you going to ask why
I hate high school baseball ?
No. It's probably a
silly reason, anyway.
You came close, Kunimi.
Ouch...
You should really have
a doctor take a look at it.
It would be bad if you
have a bone fracture.
It's no trouble at all.
I'll be hospitalized or
do whatever they want.
I have nothing to do
from now on, anyway.
What are you sulking for ?
It was a ridiculous condition to begin with,
so there's no reason to adhere to it anyway.
Easy for you to say.
"A promise is a promise" ?
It almost made me laugh.
I can't believe you'd
say something like that.
What ?
Ah, damn...
You guys came close.
If it had gone through, it would have
been a come-from-behind walkoff win.
Tachibana, I'm moved by your fair play.
Thanks.
Hey, transfer to our school.
Let's play baseball together again.
It's too late for that.
I've learned how fun it is
to pitch against you.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Hey, you're trying
to look cool again !
It's too early to give up, Noda.
Huh ?
It was a ridiculous condition to begin with,
so there's no reason to adhere to it anyway.
Who said that ?
Anyway, let's find another way.
Then, why don't you dissolve the
fan club and start a fan association ?
Your brain is on the
same level as Kine's.
Don't compare me to that guy !
You don't have any other ideas ?
To refresh our mind, let's watch a wonderful video !
Hey...
Um, I mean, we should rest our overworked brains.
Hm ?
Yanagi...
Eyecatch
Wow, you're impressive, Mo-kkun.
I love baseball !
The high school I graduated from is going to the Koushien. Isn't that amazing, Mo-kkun ?
Yeah, that's amazing !
Let's go watch together.
Yeah !
Yay, the Koushien ! The Koushien !
Sousei
I have a great idea !
Well ? Don't you think it's a good idea ?
I see.
So up until ten years ago, your
father played catch with you.
Yeah.
So he changed after the lopsided loss
of his alma mater, Sousei High School.
That he showed his son
such an embarrassing game...
...also contributed to
his hatred of baseball ?
Hey...
He's a proud man, after all.
Hey, are you listening
to what I'm saying ?
Shut up. If you want
to do it, just do it.
Yanagi, just give him your home phone number.
I'm surprised that he was a Giants fan.
Geez.
He especially liked Egawa.
Yes, Yanagi speaking.
Don't say anything.
Just do what I tell you.
We have your treasured son.
If you want him back safely, create a
baseball club at Senkawa High School.
Maybe if we get Egawa to ask him, your father might say yes.
How are we going to ask Egawa to ask his father ?
Um...
Got that ?
So all I have to do is
create a baseball club ?
That's right.
See ?
It's amazing, isn't it, Mo-kkun ?
Yeah ! It's amazing !
Got that ?
I got it. I'll do as you say.
I have an autographed ball from Mr. Hara.
Mr. Hara...
Are you satisfied ?
It was a waste of time,
so think more seriously.
He says he'll create it.
Create what ?
Senkawa High School's baseball club.
Ten years...
It must be a silly reason, anyway.
He may be right.
Noda ! If you're joking,
I won't forgive you !
He wouldn't joke.
My father.
Then hurry.
That's right. You should go home
before he changes his mind, Hostage.
Hiro, you should hurry, too.
Me ?
There's someone who's waiting anxiously for this news more than anyone.
Yeah, there is !
Noda, you should call everyone
in the fan club and let them know.
Okay...
Hey, don't boss us around.
Just go !
Okay...
Crud, a phone call should be enough.
Why should I go through all
this trouble to go there myself ?
I'm injured, you know ?
I thought she lived around here...
Koga
I guess I'll call instead.
...!
Oh, no.
Hey, be quiet !
Sorry, Third.
I forgot to feed you...
...?
Hey, Manager !
Kunimi ?
What brings you here so late ?
Well, I wasn't eager to do it, either.
But I have something
I need to report to you.
Report ?
Um, I'm sorry. I've been
preoccupied with my own issues.
Does your leg hurt ?
Was it a bad injury ?
No, that's not it.
I'm thinking about transferring.
To a school that has a baseball club.
I see.
It's Senkawa High School Baseball Club.
You should definitely continue playing baseball, Kunimi.
What ?
I'll cheer for you even if
you play for another school.
Even if I can't be the manager.
Um, it's Senkawa's baseball club.
Well, I don't know
Senkawa's baseball club, but...
What ? Senkawa ?
The principal says he'll create one.
What ? What ?
This is it !
This is how it should feel !
Dammit !
I finally...
...regained...
...my...
Iguchi Batting Center
200 yen per game
25 pitches
...batting swing !
You're in a baseball
club somewhere ?
I'm in the soccer club !
What ? Soccer club ?
Mister !
I need some change !
We're going to hit a lot !
Oh, it's Kine !
Whaddya know.
You're here, too ?
You guys are in
the soccer club, too ?
No...
...the baseball club !
Right ?
Huh ?
The demand that the guys
who kidnapped you made...
...was just to create
a baseball club, right ?
Um, yeah.
I wasn't told that I had
to let you play baseball.
What're you going to do ?
Do you want to be kidnapped again ?
I'll demand it myself.
Please let me play baseball.
I love baseball.
As much as you do, Father.
There is one condition.
Wash my back.
I'll get to play him again.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Is that really true ?
It really is genuinely true.
Is that really genuinely honestly true ?
It really is genuinely...
Anyway, it is true.
Then I can rejoice ?
Yes, you can.
I can really rejoice...?
Manager !
Yes ! I'm Koga Haruka, the manager of Senkawa High School's baseball club !
Kunimi Hiro:
Tachibana Hideo:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjiro
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Principal Yanagi:
Meiwa's Principal:
Meiwa's Coach:
Hironaga:
Yanagi:
Yamaguchi:
Arikawa:
Yanagi (child):
Komura Tetsuo
Ogata Kenichi
Naka Hiroshi
Takagi Wataru
Izaki Hisayoshi
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Konishi Hiroko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Yanagi's first name is "Morimichi." "Mo-kkun" is a short name that combines "Mo" and the address, "kun."
Egawa and Hara were two of the major players on the Giants squad in the 80's.
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hiro, you should go see a doctor.
You should have your
leg properly looked at.
Even though the baseball club is created, maybe I have a leg made of glass ?
Hey, don't make such a bad joke. People are worried about you.
Hikari, please scold him hard. He won't listen to me.
Hey, why are you two pressuring me from both sides ?
Don't run away, Kunimi Hiro !
Prepare yourself !
Next episode of H2 is,
"Pursuit ! Hiro vs. Haruka"
Next episode of H2 is
Pursuit ! Hiro vs. Haruka
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?