Got it.
The dead body was gone?
Yes. Since then
There are other students saw it too.
They locked that place later on.
The forbidden biology room.
It was the old schoolhouse.
The seven mysteries.
Academy's Seven Mysteries
Murder Case File 1
The forbidden biology room?
You don't know?
The seven mysteries.
So...
There're 6 more murders
in the old schoolhouse?
Yes.
The second one was the chopped-off
hand in the printing room.
The third one was the bloody well.
Everybody knows about the six cases.
The seventh case remains a mystery.
They said if you
discover the seventh case,
you will be killed by
the after-school magician.
After-school magician?
Yeah. But nobody has seen him.
But rumor says that he's
at the old schoolhouse.
No way.
Blood!
It's not. Look.
Ketchup?
I'm full!
Now that I know you're here
whenever you skip class.
Miyuki, the omelet was really delicious.
Thanks!
Huh? This is my...
Miyuki, remember to bring more tomorrow.
My ankle!
I can't stand this.
Kindaichi Hajime, you're really
the trash of human beings.
I heard you got zero in math again.
It's hard to believe
you're the childhood
friend of Miyuki, the
best student in school.
Hajime-chan, here you go. Huh?
You already finished my homework
I asked for this morning?
Please do your own homework. Huh?
If I continue doing this,
it won't help you at all.
So, please do it yourself.
You're stingy!
I remember you were a
lot nicer in kindergarten.
No means no.
Come on, please?
No!
Just as usual, Kindaichi.
Sakuragi-senpai?
Leave her alone.
This childhood friend of
yours is really an idiot.
Huh? An idiot?
I'm the only one who
understands your potential.
Excuse me...
Are you asking me?
I'm Sakuragi Ruiko, the chairman
of Mystery Research Club.
Leave this to me.
Are you going to do it for me, Senpai?
I need a favor from you as well.
Kindaichi.
I hope you can solve it.
The seven mysteries of Fudoh Academy.
The seven mysteries?
This is the first time I've
visited the Mystery Research Club.
Why are you here, Miyuki?
Who knows what you'd do, Hajime-chan!
I'm here to watch over you.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I'm Kindaichi, Sakuragi
senpai told me to come here.
I thought Sakuragi has
brought a smart person here.
But you don't look anything
close to "detective smart" to me.
I thought so!
If I'm not mistaken, you're Makabe
Makoto-san who was on
the newspaper, right?
You've won a prize in the
mystery novel competition.
"The story of a dead body"
It's second on the best sellers list.
Makabe-kun is the
star in mass media now.
He's nicknamed the "Genius
Highschooler Novelist".
Someone's story didn't
pass even the preliminary.
No wonder Matoba-sensei
put up the poster there,
Onoue, how good would it
be if you have one too.
What are you doing there?
Nothing.
Go on.
How annoying.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Are those gloves used for operations?
Let me tell you, she's
unusually clean against germs.
Looks I'm at the wrong place...
This is troublesome.
What's the matter?
No one can read this.
The secret signs left
by Sakuragi-senpai.
She said, if we can't solve it,
we can't take part in the camp.
It's more like she did
this at her own pleasure.
This is just nonsense for sure.
This is the club camp schedule.
Look, this is calendar
for the Golden Week.
He's right.
The club camp is held on Golden Week.
You're amazing, Hajime-chan!
I never thought you can
solve such a difficult puzzle.
It's easy!
Good job, Kindaichi-kun.
That was just by luck.
Let me tell you, he's the grandson of
the famous detective, Kindaichi Kousuke.
Well,
He's a genius with an IQ of 180.
An IQ of 180? This fellow?!
Let's start the meeting now.
Today's agenda is the rumor in
Fudoh Academy's old schoolhouse,
the seven myteries. The seven mysteries?
You mean the one that once you know,
you'll be killed by the
after-school magician?
The after-school magician.
Sent a threat letter to the Principal.
The after-school magician
sent a threat letter?
Maybe it's because of the plan
to tear down the old schoolhouse.
It says if the old
schoolhouse is demolished,
the seventh mystery will occur.
If the old schoolhouse is
demolished... What will happen?
Why is there a threat letter?
I'm planning to use this as our them
in our upcoming school anniversary.
Our Mystery Research Club
will solve all the problems.
Of course, we'll uncover
the seventh mystery as well.
As a guidance teacher in
the Mystery Research Club,
I'd like to say something.
Yes, Matoba-sensei.
A long time ago,
there was a student trying
to investigate the mystery,
but he went missing till now.
If anything happens to you...
That doesn't sound
like words coming from
the physics teacher who pursue science.
But... If anything happens... You mean,
you'll be responsible for anything.
Aren't you?
No... I'm not...
Don't worry. We'll proceed with caution.
Is that clear, everyone?
Look.
It's the meeting minutes of
Mystery Research Club 10 years ago.
I found it in the cabinet.
There might be a key in these.
You're brave, Sakuragi-senpai.
I expect the most out of your
capability, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able
to solve this mystery.
I'm counting on you.
Just as I thought, the key
to solve the mystery is here.
It seems you're doing well
in solving the mystery.
Makabe-kun, you're still here?
You're cold just as usual.
I only like smart guys. Beside you.
I am the genius highschooler novelist.
I see.
If that was really your work,
it'd be wonderful.
Damn it, that woman!
Hi, as promised.
What if someone sees this?!
Don't you know if someone finds
out, that'd be the end of my fame?!
If my deduction is correct, it'd be...
Earthquake?
It finally stopped.
This building is really unstable.
This is...
That's right.
I got it, the seventh mystery...
Hajime-chan,
what do you want for
tomorrow's lunchbox?
Sakuragi-senpai...
why are you being so nice to me?
By any chance, am I being too popular?
Geez.
Phone call.
This is Kindaichi.
Sakuragi-senpai?
Kindaichi-kun, the last of seven
mysteries, I finally get it.
Really?
Please come here right now.
I'd like to show you
something interesting.
Everything's just like my deduction.
I never thought it'd be
such a scary secret...
He'll be shocked.
The last of the seven mysteries?
Will it be alright?
The rumor says you'll be killed by the
afterschool magician
if you find that out.
That's made-up.
This place looks creepy at night.
Is it?
Ah, this is the place.
It was the printing room back then.
It's the second of seven mysteries.
A male student chopped his hand off
with the cutting machine
in this printing room.
He died due to loss of blood.
After that, no matter
how hard everyone looked,
they couldn't find his severed hand.
Ever since,
the sound of the hand creeping
around was heard at night.
It was really scary!
What's wrong, Hajime-chan?
I heard something just now.
No... No way.
Behind you!
Just kidding.
You're too mean! Hajime-chan!
It's dark here.
You guys are here too?
You received the call as well?
You scared me.
I'm sorry. I wanted to
switch on the lights,
but I saw you guys coming in, so...
I'm sorry. I wanted to
switch on the lights,
but I saw you guys coming in, so...
You are all here by
Sakuragi-senpai's call?
Mine was a male voice.
He said there will be a
death ritual at 10 o'clock.
Death ritual?
Hey, what are you guys doing here?!
You were called here by a phone call?
Hey, where's Sakuragi-senpai?
It's almost 10 o'clock now.
The time for a death ritual...
Don't say anything scary.
I'll go to have a look around.
You guys, go home.
Can I go with you?
Hajime-chan!
I have a weird premonition.
Everyone please wait here.
It's not here.
How about we go and have a
look at the old schoolhouse?
I feel like something might happen...
If you are worried,
you can see the old schoolhouse
from this new building.
If you look carefully,
the building is really old.
It'll be torn down soon.
There's light over there.
That's strange. How come there's
light from the forbidden biology room?
No one should be able to enter.
The forbidden biology room?
That's?!
That's... Sakuragi-senpai!
What's... that?!
Senpai!
It's the biology room for sure!
It's locked! Where's the key?!
It's without the key! That's why it's
called the forbidden biology room!
Damn it!
It's without the key! That's why it's
called the forbidden biology room!
Damn it!
What's going on?
Makabe-senpai!
Sakuragi-senpai is hanged inside!
It's the after-school magician!
The after-school magician?
What's going on?
Hajime-chan, what's wrong?
Saki, you should help us too!
No way, can't you see I'm busy?
It's gone.
The body and the candles are gone.
That's impossible. I
saw it with my own eyes.
Everything is locked.
There's no way he got
out through the windows.
That said...
There's no way he got
out through the windows.
That said...
The thing we saw just now...
What's wrong with everyone?
Doesn't this resemble
the seven mysteries?
The disapperance of a hanged body
from the forbiden biology room...
Don't say stuff like that.
Hey, Hajime-chan, I finally have the
answer for what happened last night.
It must be a prank by Sakuragi-senpai.
Didn't she say she would show us
something interesting when she called?
It'd be great if that's the case.
Something happened over there.
Miyuki!
Miyuki! Miyuki!
This is bad! What's wrong?
Inside the forbidden biology room...
Return to your classroom now.
Do not come near.
Go back! The class will start soon!
Excuse me!
Hey... What are you doing?!
This can't be... Sakuragi-senpai...
Go back to your classroom.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
I expect the most out of your
capabilities, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able
to solve this mystery.
I'm counting on you.
The after-school magician.
Is this your doing?
I'll definitely solve this case.
In the name of the famous detective...
my grandfather!
Sakuragi-senpai is killed.
The death ritual we saw
that night was not a dream.
The clues left by
senpai before she died,
must have something to do
with the after-school magician.
The shadow that attacked from behind.
And the second murder case.
Huh? Miyuki is missing?!
Miyuki, where are you?!
Please watch again next episode.
Kindaichi Shounen no Jikenbo.
Academy's Seven Mysteries
Murder Case File 2
Can you solve the mystery?
The killer is among them!