FroZen-Evil Presents
Yes, of course. That's why I'd be grateful if you could give me a few comments.
Yes, yes. O-Of course!
That's why I'm calling you.
Yes.
No! That's not it.
You're the clean-up hitter for the Tokyo Mets,
so you need to make a statement about this scandal.
One word. Just one word!
What is your relationship with the woman who came out of your apartment?
Ah, screw you!
You think I want to deal with this crap?!
Sheesh! I'm a sports reporter, but all they want me to do is work scandals!
A purse snatcher! Somebody stop him!
Move it! Move it!
Outta my way!
Kamoda!
Right!
T-Tell me you got that.
I... I... did...
A... Ama...
Amazing!
Watching the skillful Tomoe Nage that took down the purse snatcher, ++
this reporter sensed that this girl was destined to shoulder the future of judo. ++
This paper will do its best to locate the mysterious young girl... ++
This sucks! It sucks!
Such stiff writing won't do.
We need a full-page spread on her panties! Think panties!
It's such a pity. I wish her
face was in the photo.
What kind of girl was she?
Unfortunately, from where we were, all we could see were her panties.
You're missing the point!
The public is yearning for the birth of an athletic superstar!
This girl has a lot of talent!
I can spot talent when it comes to judo.
As you know, Japan has not been successful in the World Cup or at Wimbledon!
However, I know this girl will conquer the world.
We can't waste our time
chasing sports scandals.
Do you feel better now, Matsuda?
Well, make sure you play up the panty angle.
Play up her panties? It's an insult to call this photo a mere panty-shot.
Show her panties?
I'd better make a few extra copies.
What's wrong, Yawara?
You're not concentrating at all!
B-But, Grandpa, I've done 100 pushups, harabai, gyaku-ebi, and kata-ashitobi.
And on top of all that, randori as well!
You fool!
Yawara, sit down for a minute.
I'm already sitting!
What's the meaning of this?
I'm shocked. Is this what you do when you're playing hooky from practice?!
Did you forget that I've decreed you can't engage in outside matches?
Grandpa, this wasn't a match.
I just subdued a purse snatcher.
Snatcher, schmatcher!
It's all the same to me!
Yawara, listen to me. The future of judo rests on your shoulders.
However, this fact is the greatest of all secrets.
At the 1992 Barcelona Olympics, I foresee that women's judo will be a medal sport.
And that is where you'll make your sensational debut.
This is my master plan!
Listen carefully, Yawara. Win the Olympic gold medal, and then win the...
National Achievement Award!
That's why you shouldn't be infatuated with men like these!
Grandpa, you searched my room again, didn't you?
"I'm writing this letter in my room and drinking black tea."
"I wonder what you're doing at this moment."
Your handwriting is so curly and cutesy I can hardly read it!
That's cruel.
You're my grandpa, and I respect you, but you shouldn't read my letters.
Did you make it to first or second base with that boy?
You didn't go all the way home, did you?
Don't be ridiculous!
Wait a minute, Yawara.
If you win an Olympic gold medal and the Achievement Award,
then wonderful men will pursue you.
Stop it! Who cares about the National
Achievement Award or an Olympic gold medal?
In 1992, I'll be 20 years old!
Until then, what kind of youth will I have?
A worthwhile one.
Since I was a child, you've been training me,
but I won't be misled any longer.
I want to be a normal girl.
I want to fall in love like other girls.
And another thing. Don't you ever barge into my room again!
You're soft! Soft and squishy, Yawara. ++
And speaking of squishy, there should be a box of yokan jelly left in the cupboard. ++
Give me a break! How dare he make decisions about my life.
I'm leaving now.
I'm certain that this is
the same school uniform.
Are you sure we should be
doing this, Matsuda-san?
If the chief finds out what we're up to, he'll have our butts.
Idiot! How can we endure spending every day looking for scandals?!
We're on the verge of discovering the superstar of the next generation.
Soon, the day will come when the chief will shed tears of joy.
I-I hope you're right.
My love is fine the way it is.
She told me that as she left.
Nishikimori-san is totally owning the school festival.
I heard that a scout from the Journey Talent Agency came here.
When he graduates, he'll finally
make his big debut.
He looked this way! He looked this way!
Nishikimori-kun!
What's with this Nishikimori-kun?
Hey, aren't you mortified that someone like him gets all the girls?
We're disgusted!
I'm also mortified.
Who cares about good looks?!
A man's virtue comes from the inside. We compete with what's inside!
And if that's true, then I'm also beautiful.
Right?
Y-Yes...
Run 100 laps around the school grounds!
Forgive me.
In any case, I don't like him.
Should we stomp him?
Go ahead, stomp him!
Wh-Who the hell are you, old man?
That evil Nishikimori!
My granddaughter is in the clutches of his poisonous claws.
His poisonous claws?
Really, old man?
He has attacked my innocent
granddaughter many, many times.
What?!
She now drowns her misery by wearing make-up,
as well as flashy clothes, and by frequenting that den of iniquity called the “desco”!
Going to discos?!
And then, she got involved with a gangster at the desco.
He forced her to work in a sleazy business to make money for him!
I've been rather weak lately, and this situation has aggravated my illness.
Are you all right, old man?
Nishikimori! This is unforgivable!
Here she is. The girl we're looking for.
Second year, class B: Inokuma Yawara.
Th-This girl may be...
Look! She lives at the same address as the famous Inokuma Jigoro!
Inokuma Jigoro. I've heard that name somewhere before.
Inokuma is the only man ever to win five straight victories in the All-Japan Judo Championship.
He's a judo genius!
I suspect that Inokuma Yawara is his granddaughter.
What's wrong, Yawara?
The competition is very stiff.
You've gotta be more aggressive.
One per person, one per person...
I-I can't do it today.
Hey, Yawara!
Alas, poor Yawara. You've fallen in love with a playboy.
Timing: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: Live-Evil & AnimEigo
Encoding: Skr
QC Team: CP, Juggen
Typesetting: kokujin-kun
Timing: Skr
Editing: Collectr
Translation: Live-Evil & AnimEigo
Typesetting: kokujin-kun
QC Team: CP, Juggen
Encoding: Skr
I'm home.
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
Grandpa... huh?
You can do it, Yawara!
Yes, Nishikimori speaking.
Hello? Hello?
Um...
Hello? Who's there?
Hello?
I'm sorry. Wrong number!
Challenge!
Who is it? Can't you ring the doorbell?
So we have a masked wrestler!
Don't be silly. It's a face mask.
I don't know what you're doing, but it's strange.
Anyway, what do you want? I'm not paying the NHK fee.
Wait!
What is it?
The reason I came to see you is this.
Please do not make advances toward my granddaughter.
Your granddaughter? Who's she?
I'm talking about Inokuma Yawara.
Inokuma?
I don't think I know her.
As you might know, I have many fans. I can't remember every face or name.
Consider this a warning from the referee!
Don't you have the sincerity to devote yourself entirely to just one girl?!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but I've been advised by
my agent to act prudently.
Since I'm an idol, I don't go out with one specific girl. Well, then...
Wait! Listen carefully!
If you make further advances toward Yawara, I will use my "deathblow techniques."
Don't force me to use them for
something insignificant like this!
Hey! Do you understand?
Please leave and take these.
Oh, and buy my records and CDs too.
Wh-What are these?
My autograph and picture.
What lousy handwriting.
I'll correct it.
Moron!
Well, it should be around here.
Should we really be doing-
This way. Let's go!
Hey, okay!
What?!
Y-You went to see Nishikimori-san?
Delicious. These strawberry-filled rice cakes are exquisite.
I'm too ashamed to see him. This is the end.
Yawara, don't you want one?
Grandpa, you idiot!
You don't want to eat these delicious sweets?
I wonder if Yawara is perhaps feeling ill.
Delicious!
Hello?
Yawara study judo?
Have some homemade radish pickles.
Yes. Thank you.
Well, I can understand how
you got the wrong idea.
After all, I am the judo genius who won
the All-Japan Judo Championship five times in a row.
Y-Yes...
But that was more than 30 years ago.
I'm retired and don't practice judo anymore.
These days, I make a living doing bone setting.
Why, the very idea of me teaching her judo is silly, quite silly...
Yes.
Here.
Oh, sorry.
By the way, 6-dan Master Inokuma...
I'm a 7-dan!
Ah, that's right, 7-dan Master Inokuma, can we see your dojo?
If I can see the dojo, I can tell whether or not they’ve been practicing. ++
Good plan! ++
If you wish.
As you can see,
my dojo, which was a place of blood, sweat, and tears, is now used to race slot cars.
This Ferrari is very fast.
Well, won't you have a race or two?
S-Sorry for bothering you.
Me too. Sorry for bothering you!
Well, when you feel like racing,
please come again.
Thank you. Well, please excuse us.
It's already this late?
Matsuda-san, we're in trouble!
Mission accomplished.
I'll never allow a third-rate
newspaper to get this scoop.
Yawara must make a sensational debut.
See you, Yawara.
See you!
That must be Inokuma Yawara.
Do we follow her?
Judging from the old man, I don't think she has anything to do with judo.
I've got a hunch that the old geezer is hiding something.
Are you sure?
Let's go.
Y-Yes.
Nishikimori-san, please don't forget us after you make your formal debut.
Please buy my records.
Of course. We will follow you
wherever you go, Nishikimori-san!
Buy my CDs too!
Of course.
As I thought, he hasn't mended his ways.
He may still make advances toward Yawara.
Time to give him a real attitude adjustment.
Wh-Who are you?
Nishikimori! You bastard, I heard that you seduced a young girl...
and on top of that, you forced her into a sleazy business!
What?
Now receive our Iron Fists of Justice!
W-Wait for me!
Wait!
Help!
Get him!
What?! Only a total cad shows his back to the enemy!
Help!
Nishikimori!
Wait!
Help!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Chastise him to your heart's content!
Nishikimori!
What did I do?
Don't! Pretend! To! Be! Innocent!
Yawara...
As things were going dark, this reporter witnessed... ++
a performance that one day would be re-enacted before the entire world... ++
one day... for sure. ++
Do you see, Yawara? This is his true spirit.
Now throw that man on his back, hard!
Nishikimori-san...
Y-Yes?
If you need help, call me.
I'll protect you.
Since then, whenever he
sees me, Nishikimori-san... ++
flees in abject terror. ++
I will never, ever practice judo again!
G-Grandpa...
Listen, Yawara. Your youth belongs to judo! ++
Win the People's Honor Award and become Japan's shining star! ++
PHONE APPT.
TOKYO METS (SHINOTA)
WOMAN?
RETRIEVE
INSERT CARD
Aim for Barcelona! The Girl Who Should Win the People's Honor Award!!
ALL SPORTS NEWS
INOKUMA
THE GENTLE WAY WASN'T BUILT IN A DAY
MUSASHIYAMA HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
NOTES
NAME
ADDRESS
AOKI KATSUMI
INOKUMA YAWARA
IWASE NOE
UEHARA MAKI
URAHATA SATOKO
OGATA MISATO
SUGINAMI-KU HAMA
SETAGAYA-KU HIGASHI
SUGINAMI-KU IZUMI 2
SETAGAYA-KU MATSUHARA
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
Yamada's
Nikuman and Anman
Dumplings
A
NISHIKIMORI
THE ROAD RACE ISN'T WON IN A DAY
Coffee Shop Guatemala