From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
It's a queen!
What does it mean?
Be quiet!
Yawara Inokuma, you will meet a
gorgeous man within 24 hours.
She said within 24 hours.
No way! Yawara will find a boyfriend
before me!? No way! No way! No way!
I beg you, read my fortune next.
Mine, mine!
You did it!
It's amazing, Yawara.
Now way. No way. No way.
Let's go.
Oops, I made a mistake! There are
two cards sticking together.
No way!
Episode 3
Enter Kazamatsuri. What a shame
that she is infatuated with love.
See ya, Yawara.
I hope you'll do well in the
English test tomorrow.
Yawara, if you meet the gorgeous
man, be sure to tell us.
It's been a long time,
Miss Yawara Inokuma.
Wh... Who are you?
Oh yes. I've never introduced myself to you.
I'm Matsuda from Every Sports Daily.
Y... You are?
Yes... I'm Matsuda who reported your great tomoenage and showed your panties.
Also, I was saved by you when I was almost smashed by a group of delinquent boys.
In other words, I know you better
than anyone else in mass media.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come, come. You're pretending
that you don't know!
I'm trying to memorize English
vocabularies. Please be quiet!
Even if you pretend, I have proof.
You must be on special judo training
by the 7th dan master, Inokuma,
ever since you were young.
Unrelated - nothing to do with!
False charge - an unjust accusation!
Why!? Why don't you make a debut in
the judo world when you are so skilled?
Why are you trying to hide your talent?
I'll cry out! - I'll make a big noise!
I beg of you! Please answer me,
even if it's just one word!
I'm betting my "reporter's life" on you.
Please leave me alone!
What's this? Kyoko's prediction is off the mark.
That's enough, you molester. Leave her alone.
I'm just gathering data on her.
You have no right to violate her
privacy and to collect material.
It's OK now. You don't
need to worry anymore.
Yes.
He's so cool. Kyoko's prediction
may be on the mark.
Who is that man?
Really, thank you very much.
Don't mention it. By the way,
are you feeling better now?
Yes!
Wow! This is the first time
I'm in a cafe with a man.
Waiter. A cake for her. How about
Charlotte Bois and tea?
I'll get it immediately, sir.
Is that man a reporter from a photo magazine?
What!?
No... I thought you may be a popular idol singer or something that was being followed.
An idol? Me!? No, not at all!
I'm also invading your privacy.
That's only because you're dazzling!
I... I... I am!?
Yes. You have something special.
You have some kind of magnetic
power that pulls people to you,
like the gravitational force of stars.
I've never gotten this kind of
compliment from men.
He said I'm dazzling.
I have something special.
I'm home.
Uncle Uomata, what's the matter with you?
Yawara, help me.
He has a minor disc problem.
Stop being a cry baby.
You're a grown-up man.
What are you watching?
We should start our lesson.
Change your clothes and
wait for me in the drill hall.
Yes.
Oh, oh, did I do too much?
Yawara, why are you in a daze?
How many times do I have to tell you that an unguarded moment may cost you your life?
But, grandpa...
There are no but's or anything!
Your eyes tell me that you are in love again.
If you have time to think about a
worthless fellow, polish your skills.
If you do, you can get everything.
The Gold Medal, the National Achievement Award, and even men.
Get?
We're not talking about things.
Love should be pure.
You can't have love in such
a calculating manner.
You've become argumentative.
I, too, tasted the sweets and bitters of life.
When I met Kaneko, it was just before the 2.26 incident. It was a very unsettling time.
In those days, all young men
were sincere. Not like today!
It was a time when true love existed.
I... I know. Once you start the story,
it takes more than two to three hours...
I was a handsome and bright young man who wanted to be number one in judo in Japan.
I... I understand. Let's start our lesson.
Kaneko and I fell in love at first sight...
Each other at first sight...
Each other...
Will I meet him again?
Kazamatsuri. This is Yurie. You're always out.
The next time I see you, I'll pinch you.
Shinnosuke. It's me. Akina.
I've reserved a room in the hotel we
stayed at last time. Call me.
I'm your Maiko. If you don't call me, I'll have
an affair with someone. It's a lie!
This is Minako. Don't you like me anymore?
I'll kill myself. I'll kill myself. I'll kill myself.
Shin-chan. This is Shizuka. You were great the other day. Let's do it again soon.
Why is the big city lonely in the night time?
Sayaka, how confident are you?
Is your objective to win the title?
Why judo now?
Please give me your answer.
One word will do. One word.
With a full-fledged technique...
I plan to win the championship with
full-fledged points all the way.
She's making a big splash again.
Hey, Yawara, it's about to begin.
What will start?
Didn't you read the newspaper? Sayaka Honami will make a debut in judo.
Is that so?
What are you saying? Your
rival is on television.
Grandpa, you made her my rival for your
own accord without my consent.
Why are you hiding your happiness?
I'm not hiding anything.
I know how you must feel.
You must be irritated because your
rival made her debut before you.
You still don't understand.
A 48 kilo or less class title
match is about to start.
The topic of this match is how
skillful Sayaka Honami will be.
The sports genius who has conquered almost all types of sports will now take on judo.
She's really ostentatious.
Your debut must be better than hers.
Before the match starts,
here is an announcement.
Rapidly developing Honami Group.
The Honami Group is for the 21st Century.
Incredible! They are taking
advantage of each other.
The first opponent for Honami Sayaka is Nagasaki Hisako, who was the runner-up
at the last All Japan Championship.
I did not take up judo
to fight with small fry.
Start!
I want to beat you, Yawara Inokuma.
OK, I decided. Beef Stroganoff. Let's go with it.
Hey, Yawara! Where are you going?
To the kitchen.
To the kitchen?
Haraigoshi for Sayaka Honami.
She started the first match with an easy victory against a strong opponent. Sayaka is strong!
Did you see that, Yawara Inokuma?
This is the result of my hard training.
Tokunaga...
My judo suit has some wrinkles.
I want to change into a fresh one.
Please get it ready.
Yes!
I need to make some preparation.
Some pepper on the beef...
After all, a girl has to learn to cook, right?
Because you're dazzling...
... you have something special...
I'll definitely make a delicious dish.
Fierce ashibarai, continue!
Watch me with your...
Oosotogari. Honami shaky.
Tomoenage.
Without a doubt. Sayaka Honami
won the second match easily.
Are you surprised, Yawara Inokuma?
You must be shocked by my powers.
Tokunaga, I perspired a little.
I want to change into a new suit.
Get it ready immediately!
Yes.
Yawara Inokuma. If you feel chagrin, come out.
Ippon!
She won.
She won the championship in the
48 kilo or less class match.
She's quite proficient. I'm convinced
that she has an excellent coach.
I must compliment myself. I made a
delicious Beef Stroganoff dish.
I wish I could serve this dish to him,
but I didn't even ask him his name.
This is the announcer.
Everyone is chanting Sayaka here!
Now I would like to get a victorious comment from the winner, Sayaka Honami.
Congratulations.
Some comments...
Some comments, please.
This is an empty victory.
Ah, surely it isn't...
You have taken the judo championship.
You would not win and then retire, would you?
Usually I would do that...
... but this is not a real victory.
This is not a real victory!?
No, I have not fought with a
truly strong opponent.
But you beat last year's winner,
Kaoru Yamada, today.
You're irritating me. Let me use your microphone. I don't need you.
Please...
Camera one, and camera two.
Close in on me.
That's good.
Take a good shot of me.
Are you watching Yawara-san?
I just won the judo tournament!
You're suffering, aren't you, Yawara?
Yawara, if you're regretting what you have seen, come out soon. I will not dodge.
I decided to take up judo to
fight only with you because...
... I want to knock you down.
This is something.
I can't believe it.
Yawara, it's a great challenge from her.
What are you going to do?
You're not joking! She has no right to mention my name on television without my consent.
Honami-san, who is Yawara?
Is she stronger than you?
If you are in the mass media business,
you should find the person by yourself.
Now excuse me, everyone.
Sayaka-san became strong.
Do you recall the man who was
accompanying her during the match?
He's the one who helped her win.
That handsome guy?
That's him. He's the one who
threw me out of the bus.
I checked his background carefully.
His name is Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke.
He became her coach.
Sayaka-san gave us the slip...
Let's get the coach...
Is he a great coach?
I've never heard of his name before.
He's one of the best in Japan...
... but he has never won in a real match.
Not even one victory? Why is that?
Is it delicious?
Jeez, if you have time to cook this beef-over-rice dish, then why
don't you practice judo?
It's not a beef-over-rice dish.
It is called Beef Stroganoff.
What's shironge pongo?
Jeez! How does it taste?
While your rival hired an excellent
coach and won the championship,
you are leisurely cooking.
If you're only going to complain,
you don't have to eat it.
Wait! I'm still eating! Hey... Hey...
I didn't make this for you.
What! The coach has disappeared too!
Look for him! Look for him! Damn!
I can't handle it...
The press interviews...
Nervousness?
In front of people, he becomes
completely different.
When it comes to an actual match, he cannot demonstrate his real strength.
I can't believe it. Something is wrong.
As you see, he's trying to
hide from the reporters.
I guess you're right.
This should be destroyed this way!
Th... th... this way!
Tokunaga, clean up this mess.
Miss, the well-deserved trophy...
This is junk!
Without beating Yawara Inokuma, how can I treat this as the trophy for the victory for me?
Why are you so irritated, Sayaka?
When it comes to Yawara Inokuma,
you lose control completely.
You have demonstrated the ability to beat
the winner of All Japan Championship
Match under my guidance.
I think you are invincible.
You're not serious.
It's like eating yokan while
sipping redbean soup.
You can say that since you don't know
how strong Yawara Inokuma is.
Sayaka-san, I heard that you've actually
seen her strength only twice.
How can you conclude
that she's so strong?
It's my intuition.
The perception that is felt only
between two strong opponents.
I see... I think I know how you feel.
The other day I sensed a similar
feeling with someone.
I would very much like to meet
Yawara Inokuma.
It's no use. Usually, she does
not show her ability.
You're not jealous of Yawara because
I want to meet her, are you?
N.. no way! What are you talking about?
Tokunaga, give him her address.
Yes!
He was not on the bus today!
I didn't get his name nor his
telephone number. I'm helpless.
I must be out of practice of this kind because my grandpa forces me to practice judo.
That's right. Grandpa is to be blamed.
Ah! I'm sorry!
It's dangerous. Don't do that.
What a coincidence. I thought
I might meet you again.
What are you doing around here?
Err... Some errand.
If you like, would you like to come
to my house for a cup of tea?
You saved me from the newspaper
reporter the other day and today
I kicked a can at you... and...
Oh, I haven't introduced myself yet.
My name is Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri.
Kazamatsuri-san?
Ahh, this is my house.
This is a lovely house. Oh.. Inokuma?
I am Inokuma. Please come in.
Yawara, are you home?
Ah, grandpa.
Yawara? This is Yawara Inokuma!?
Grandpa, we have a guest.
A guest?
This old man is...?
I am Jigoro Inokuma. How do you do?
Ah! Inokuma-san!
I need to excuse myself today.
Oh, yes! Let's meet Saturday at 3 o'clock
at the shop we went to the other day.
That's better. Let's do that.
Kazamatsuri-san.
See ya!
How odd, I've seen that face somewhere.
Grandpa, you should not display
thing like that in front of him.
I finally meet the master, Jigoro Inokuma.
When I was young, I decided to dedicate
myself to judo after I read this book.
Even now, I always keep this book
with me, Judo is not build in a day.
I got nervous. Damn!
I now know why Sayaka Honami wants
to make the girl and the 7th dan master
Jigoro Inokuma as her opponents.
I'm the 8th dan master.
999 more days till the Olympics in Barcelona
I'm in high spirits. I have a date tomorrow.
Yawara, why are you so excited?
NO! Grandpa, you're a pervert. You are
the lowest to peep into a bathroom.
She hasn't learned from past lessons
and is meeting a man again.
Grandpa, you are not
scheming again, are you?
On the next Yawara.
The strategy to make Yawara participate in a real match. This is my strategy. Don't miss it.
Translated by:
Hiroko Hatanaka-Sukoenig
Songs translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Script by NYTP-XF Projects
Revised by Michael Studte
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
I watched the video through the night.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Stay right here next to me,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
I don't want you to grow up yet.