kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Not good enough. Not good enough.
Stand up, Sayaka-san.
Let's rest a while. How about some tea?
You are taking it too easy. It is like eating
a Marron glace together with anmitsu.
Do you think you can beat
Yawara Inokuma this way?
Kazamatsuri-san, ever since you met
Yawara Inokuma, you've become
a completely different person.
That's right!
Your opponent is the grand-daughter
of Master Jigoro Inokuma.
Master Inokuma is the author of my favorite book, Judo is not build in a day.
In addition, he won the All Japan Championships five times.
Yawara Inokuma is the person to
whom he taught his splendid art.
I want to see it. I want to see her skills.
No good! Such a half-hearted
lesson is not good enough.
You're right. They must be practicing
judo until they shed blood.
My elbows are bleeding since he forced
me to practice harabai so many times.
harabai--move on one's stomach.
Tighten your sides, Yawara.
Put everything into it, Yawara.
Yawara.
Yawara!
Yawara...
Yawara, how could you sneak out
of the lesson to take a bath?
Because my elbow got all
scraped up and it's painful.
You're trying to stay away from the
lesson for one reason or another.
I have a date with Kazamatsuri-san tomorrow.
I have no time to practice.
Here! Use my special lizard
oil for scraped skin.
Aaaa! Pervert!
Even if you are my grand-father, you're
not allowed to peep into the bathroom.
I wish you would exhibit the
same spirit towards judo.
I wonder when she grew up so much.
Even though she's my grand-daughter,
it was a bit too stimulating.
Episode 4
This is my strategy to make Yawara
take part in a real match.
The smell of tea, a delicious cake,
and a wonderful man.
I'm so happy to be able to have this
dream-like Saturday afternoon.
It was indeed wonderful, that Osotogari.
Oh, you didn't watch Sayaka Honami's tournament on television, the other day?
Sorry, I'm not interested in judo.
Is that so?
Sayaka-san is right. She hardly
shows any interest in judo.
But today is the last day you
can pretend to be innocent.
I'll reveal your true power today.
Err...
Please.
You go first, Inokuma-san.
No, Err... Well... ummm...
That's right! Tell me all about your secret.
Well...
You always dress so well.
I get them during bargain sales. All of this.
That's wonderful. I, too, buy only at
bargain sales. Do you stand in line?
Pardon?
When you go to a bargain sale.
Of course I stand in line. Usually,
I stand in line all night long.
Amazing!
That's not it! I didn't come here
to talk about this with her.
Chief, look at all the commotion made
by the mass media about Yawara.
Ever since Sayaka Honami challenged
Yawara on television, there has been
this "Yawara Fever" everywhere.
Ever since Sayaka Honami challenged
Yawara on television, there has been
this "Yawara Fever" everywhere.
Challenge to Yawara.
Find who Yawara is.
Yawara is the girl whom I'm trying to locate.
Please. Let me print this picture again.
Only we have the proof.
This does not serve as a proof.
Bring proof that she is the real Yawara to me.
If I could, I would have brought
it to you a long time ago.
If you can't get it, then stop it!
We can't have you wasting all your time working on this pointless "pan-chira" girl.
Pointless "pan-chira" girl?
Understood! I'll definitely bring one.
Proof that will knock your socks off.
Let's go, Kameda.
Okay!
Listen, chief!
I'm going to get the scoop.
Soon will be the day when the pointless "pan-chira" girl will become the
idol to 120 million people.
You again?
Until you tell me the truth, I'll
come back again and again.
Have some home-made dried persimmons.
Thank you. Here.
You can't bribe me with
a dried persimmon.
I'm determined to get Master Inokuma's acknowledgment today.
This old man does not have any recollection that I was to be called master by you.
Stop playing these monkey games with me...
You have no right to call me a monkey.
Look at these newspapers.
Who is the real Yawara?
All of them are making a
great uproar over Yawara.
All of them are talking about your grand-daughter, right?
That's right.
So, you finally admit it?
That girl is my grand-daughter, Yawara.
I beg you.
Please give us the scoop.
No! I will not!
Since Sayaka Honami made her
debut in a grand style, Yawara's
debut must be better than hers.
Well. Our paper will push Yawara
staking the future of our company.
Please leave. I will not permit a third
class newspaper to have the scoop.
Yawara must make a debut
according to my plan.
It's already developed in my head.
The 7th dan Master Inokuma.
I have the 8th dan.
The time is ripe.
So, Miss Inokuma, you like cooking?
Yes. I cook Beef Stroganoff very well.
Beef Stroganoff? I would
like to try it sometime.
Really!? I'll make the best one for you.
I'll look forward to your Beef Stroganoff.
I'm embarrassed.
Ouch, that hurts!
The way she fell did not give any indication
that she had any knowledge of judo.
Is she really practicing judo?
I have to be careful. I almost used ukemi.
ukemi--a special judo technique to prepare
the body to accept some blow.
Are you alright?
Yes.
You were a bit careless.
This scraped skin. This is the result
of practicing forward harabai.
I'm ashamed.
My arms have scars from scraped
skin. Perhaps, this girl...
Now is my opportunity.
Let me challenge her.
She's thoroughly on guard. If I try to
attack her, what will happen to me?
Throw me. I'm ready.
This can't be happening! What
should I do? What should I do!?
Finally, I will get my first kiss.
She's defenseless! This girl can't
be a genius in judo. She can't be!
Yawara Inokuma...
A date?
You must be joking, little girl.
Tell us what kind of a man he is.
Well... He's tall, handsome, and the sporty type.
How dare you!
... and how far did you go with him?
We went to a cafe and to the park.
Don't play dumb. You know, A, B, or C...
To tell you the truth...
He tried to kiss you!?
He was just about to.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Sorry. Please forgive me.
It must be true love!
That's right. If he really likes
you, he's unable to do it.
Do you think so?
I hate you!
I'm sorry. Are you alright?
I'm fine. Oh, no.
Do you belong to the Judo Club?
Yes. I must wash them again.
Give them to me. I'll wash them for you.
I cannot accept your offer. I'm not
good at judo, so I have to at least
do some work to compensate.
Don't worry. I'm the one
who caused all this.
No...
Yawara, he's saying it's O.K.
Don't worry. I'm used to washing judo suits.
What!?
Oh, nothing. BY the way, when do
I have to return them to you?
Let's see. We have extra judo suits,
so you don't need to rush.
Good. I'll also mend the ripped areas.
No... that's too much...
You won't be strong if you
continue to wash judo suits.
No, one lesson... No, two lesson...
Since you insist, I'll leave them to you.
How did you feel at that time?
Are you still asking that silly question?
She's a typical female high school student.
No. Soon she will show her true color.
By the way, Yawara.
Yes.
There's a big bargain sale in Shibuya tomorrow. Do you want to go?
A bargain? I'll come. I'll come.
I'll definitely come.
Alright. Then, let's meet in front of
the Hachiko statue at 3:00 pm.
Yes.
A bargain sale? I want to go, too!
I'll go anywhere she goes...
... and, we'll take the photo... Only one is needed, to capture her real power.
Judo Club.
I wish you would stop folk-dancing.
Are you going to disgrace yourselves
again at the tournament with
Ganryuji High School tomorrow?
Judo is a sport to throw your
opponent like this to win.
Please win at least once.
I'll be a senior soon and before I graduate,
I want us to win at least once.
Hanazono-san is crying again.
Our captain cries easily.
Don't stand around...Continue free practice.
This is not good.
I wanted Yawara to have a real fighting experience before she makes her debut.
They are no match for her. I thought
there was hope in the big captain,
but he's just a mad gorilla.
He uses only his physical power
and is far from skillful.
I heard you over the window.
Excuse me. Oh my!
It's been a long time since I
enjoyed seeing children play.
Damn you, you mustached old man!
Wait, I will not permit an outsider
to say such slander about us.
Who are you?
I'm an amateur judo lover
who's just passing by.
I see you have not won any
tournament this year.
I'm ashamed.
Long time ago, our club competed
at the National Tournament.
However, nowadays, since I became
captain of the club, I am the only senior,
and the rest are just 4 freshmen.
We may not be able to participate
in the group tournament tomorrow
if we miss even one member.
Is tomorrow's opponent, the
Ganryuji High School, strong?
Yes. Frankly speaking, we
were equally competitive.
During our past regional tournaments,
we always tried to surpass each other
and exhibited great matches.
... but now the difference is so obvious.
They cast their pitiful eyes on us.
I told the team that I don't expect them to
win the tournament, but they shouldn't disgrace themselves, either.
There's no sense in losing a fight.
In any battle, there is only
one way to spell victory.
But...
Leave it to me.
I'll make sure you win.
Master.
Master? It's music to my ears.
There is a big rip.
Grandpa!
You are washing judo suits.
I'm impressed. But, why so many?
They belong to the judo club of my school.
What? They belong to the judo
club of your school? Is that so?
What is it? You're acting strangely.
The Ganryuji High School
Don't act intimidated.
Okay!
There are only 5 club members.
Sasaki.
Hanazono, I guess your club is strong
even though there are few members.
Um... I am very delighted that the four time
All Japan champion, Mr. Inokuma, is volunteering as the adviser to our school.
I won 5 times.
The captain, Hanazono, hinted to me that you have some strategy for today's tournament.
Wait and see.
Come here. I will give you special instructions.
Since I have to be at Shibuya at 3 o'clock.
I had better get ready soon.
Yes, this is Inokuma. What!?
I'm sorry, Miss Inokuma. We cannot start
the tournament without the suits.
Don't you have extra suits?
B... but. A... anyway, please bring
them here immediately. Please.!
You're so selfish!
He said anytime. Kaori and the gang
are waiting for me at Shibuya.
What if I miss the bargain sale?
Gym closet.
Be good. It won't be too long.
What? Kawada is gone?
I think the judo club of the Musashiyama High School has fallen to the bottom of the barrel.
Running away before the tournament
is the lowest act of all!
I hate judo!
I ask you to leave. We do not wish to have a tournament with the team whose members disappear when facing the opponent.
Please reconsider. I propose to have the tournament between 5 members vs. 4.
Have a sense of shame, a sense of shame.
The 7th dan master Inokuma,
we have a terrible situation.
I have the 8th dan.
Should I put a judo suit on
and be a member?
Wait for awhile. Soon she will
come. The Goddess of Victory.
Damn... Where is the judo hall?
I better hurry up or I'll
miss the bargain sale.
What is everyone looking at?
Ahh... Here's the judo uniforms.
You are Inokuma from Junior B class.
Hanazono-kun.
Why are you here? It doesn't matter.
Ehh, everyone has a judo suit on.
Never mind. Well, see ya.
What is it? Let me go.
Everyone. All the members are here.
She's a member of the Musashiyama
High School Judo Club.
Don't make fun of us. Do you expect
us to fight with a woman?
I know I'm making an
unreasonable request.
In addition, I want to request
that we change the rules.
The rules of the tournament?
I request that we do not use the
usual senposen or taishosen.
Instead, I wish to propose kachinukisen.
Hanazono-kun...
Listen Inokuma, you'll be
the head of the team...
The head?
I will be the vice captain...
I will never let you fight.
I don't understand what you are talking about. I'm going to a bargain sale.
Please, Inokuma. All you have to do is
to wear a judo suit and to sit with us.
Wait a minute. A girl? A girl?
We can legally tackle a girl!
A Kachinukisen tournament would give everyone a chance to touch a girl!
Let go of me. I must go.
Please, Inokuma.
Hanazono, we will be generous
like samurai should. We accept all
of your requests. Right, everyone?
I'm really grateful.
Wait a minute. Why do I have to
participate in the tournament?
We will win so that you will not have
to be in it. Please, Inokuma.
Hanazono-kun...
I really have to go to Shibuya.
Please finish as soon as possible.
Ahh, it will be over soon.
Just leave it to me.
Grandpa! Why, why is he here?
Change Room.
I wanted to press him for an answer, but if
they discover that I'm his grand-daughter,
it might cause even more trouble.
I don't have a T-shirt.
Inokuma, are you ready?
Pervert!
What am I going to do? If I fight without a T-shirt, I'll never be able to get married.
Ready, Yawara? This is
your first real fight.
992 days till the Olympics in Barcelona
A girl... A girl... A girl... This is the
first time we fought with a girl.
Idiots and perverts. This is a judo tournament. What are they thinking about?
This is the harsh reality of a real fight.
On the next Yawara.
The moment of a real match has arrived. The road to "Judo Yawara" is not built in a day.
Watch. My Ippon zuyoi will explode.
No. You perverts! Don't look!
Translated by:
Hiroko Hatanaka-Sukoenig
Songs translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Script by NYTP-XF Projects
Revised by Michael Studte
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Soba ni ite ne
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Otana ni naranaide
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental