From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
What? Let me go!
Everyone, we have all our members now. She is a member of our Musashiyama High Judo Club.
Don't belittle us! You expect us to fight a girl?
I know it's a bit unreasonable.
And in addition, I'd like to request
to change the format of the match.
The match format?
Instead of the game, pointman vs. pointman, captain vs. captain...
I'd like to make it kachinukisen. Please!
[kachinukisen--single elimination to the top]
Hanazono-kun!
Inokuma, I beg you. I'll make you the captain!
Captain?
I'll be the vice captain and you
won't ever have to you fight.
What are you talking about?
I need to go to the bargain sale...
Wait a minute. A girl. A girl!
We can legally tackle a girl!
If it's a kachinukisen, then everyone
has a chance to touch a girl!
I get to touch a girl!
Please, Inokuma!
Hanazono, we'll give you a samurai's generosity. We'll accept all your terms.
Right, everyone?
Y... yeah!
Really? How grateful!
Now just a minute! Why do I
have to be in the match?
We'll win all the way so
you won't have to fight.
Please, Inokuma!
Hanazono-kun...
I really need to go to Shibuya...
Get this over quickly, okay?
Ahh, it'll end quickly. Just leave it to me.
Grandpa!
Why, why is he here?
Yawara! Episode 5
Finally the Real Fight! The Path of
Judo Is Not Paved In One Day, Jya!
A girl. A girl!
N... newaza it is!
[Newaza--groundwork]
With newaza, I'll do this and that...
Kubi shihoh gatame might be good...
[Kubi shihoh gatame--Neck all-direction hold]
Damn, I hope she reaches me!
Zowa Zowa Zowaa--Chills down her spine.
Inokuma, don't worry. I'll make sure
that no one lays a finger on you.
We will begin the practice match between Ganryuji High and Musashiyama High. Bow!
Yes!
Matsuda-san, it was worth following
her all this time, after all.
Yeah. This is going to be interesting!
Both pointman, step forward.
Do it right, Ueda! Go man!
If I beat 4 guys, it's the girl!
Bow!
Begin!
Ippon!
[Ippon--full 10 points, a win]
One!
Damn, don't try too hard.
Give us a chance, too.
Not yet, not yet!
Musashiyama High 2nd pointman, Tomioka-kun.
Ippon!
Two!
Not yet...
Musashiyama High center, Yasui-kun.
Ippon!
Three guys!
Musashiyama High vice captain, Hanazono-kun.
Hanazono-kun!
It's okay. All you need to do is just sit there. I'll take down the 5 guys somehow.
I'm counting on you, Hanazono-kun.
If I just...
If I just beat him, it's the girl!
Bow!
Begin!
Girl, girl!
What? Girl?
Ippon!
All right!
Way to go, captain!
All right! All right!!
Ganryuji High 2nd pointman, Kuramochi-kun.
Darn!
How shameful for you to get
distracted by a girl and lose!
In a man's fight, of course you'd
lose with such evil thoughts!
Be ashamed of yourself!
Begin!
Hanazono-san!...
...Captain, drive on!
Ippon!
All right! The girl! Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai! I can do it with
the girl! Banzai! Banza...
Talk about evil thoughts!
How vulgar!
The worst kind of man!
So what now?
I... I'm sorry, Inokuma.
What are you gonna do about it?
Musashiyama High captain, Inokuma-kun.
Inokuma? I wonder...
Kamoda!
Gotcha.
Oh well, I'll just go and lose quickly,
Since there's not enough time,
and I don't have a T-shirt on...
I have no honor...
Inokuma, step forward!
I know, sir.
Inokuma.
A girl! A girl! A girl!
This is the first time I get to touch a... girl!
Zowa Zowa Zowaa--chills down her spine
I'm definitely going to lose so I can get away!
Begin!
Itadakimasu!
[Itadakimasu--Thank you for this meal!
Usually a pre-meal greeting]
Ecchi!
Oh no, I did it!
I... Ippon!
All right!
Even if it was pure luck, good job!
Kuramochi, hey wake up! Kuramochi!
Captain, he's out cold.
He was taken by surprise
and forgot his ukemi.
[Ukemi--landing technique]
His pervertedness still shows on his face.
Hey, carry him out.
To get fooled by a girl's beauty and lose...
... is the ultimate embarrassment since
the founding of our school's judo team.
Captain Sasaki, I won't pull
any stupid things like that.
Of course not!
But before that, do something
about your lust-filled face!
Inokuma, you've done enough. I'm
very satisfied with just one win!
I was already going to go
lose the next one anyway.
I won't make it to the bargain
sale in Shibuya on time.
Everyone is waiting for me....
Sorry. If you don't make it to the sale on time, I'll buy you a dress or anything else.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, you set it up, didn't you?
Ganryuji High center, Makita-kun.
Newaza. It's gotta be newaza!
Maybe kami shihoh gatame?
[Kami shihoh gatame--top four-corner hold]
Or maybe yoko shihoh gatame?
[Yoko shihoh gatame--side all-direction hold]
Tate shihoh gatame might be swell too!
[Tate shihoh gatame--vertical all-direction hold]
He must be thinking dirty again!
Begin!
I should lose before he does something weird!
Hurry up and throw me!
What's wrong, I'm being defenseless for him...
No!
He's taking it to newaza!
I'm jealous!
Inokuma, sorry! At least keep your chastity!
Tomoe nage ippon!
[Tomoe nage ippon--stomach
throw full 10 points]
Ecchi!
Even center Makita-san, too.
Is she lucky twice?
What is it anyway?
Who is that girl?
It's gotta be luck. Kuramochi and Makita
must have fallen down by themselves!
Nope! This is the true ability
of Inokuma Yawara!
Kamoda, did you get that one on camera...
Oww..
I don't get it.
I don't get the girl, Inokuma Yawara, even more.
Why is she so defenseless?
If she is a judo athlete, there should
have been some kind of response.
Is she really strong?
I finished the circuit training...
Kazamatsuri Coach!
You're thinking about Inokuma
Yawara again, aren't you?
Yes.
I've seen it...
You were approaching Yawara for a kiss!
I need to see her one more time to check,
To see if she's as strong as you say she is.
Oww!
Why did you do that, all of a sudden?
Why... why am I so irritated?
Inokuma Yawara!
Inokuma, great job!
[Rokudan--sixth degree black belt]
You, are you perhaps related
to that Inokuma Rokudan?
The master?
Oh yeah, it is the same surname!
No wonder she's so strong!
N... no way! That baboon grandpa
has no relation to me whatsoever.
Grmphh! Help! Grunt!
By the way, teacher, what time is it?
Oh uhm, it's 3:15pm, but..
Whoa, the match, the match!
What should I do? I won't make it
to the bargain sale in time anymore!
Please, teacher, could you
let me lose by default...
Ganryuji High vice captain, Oomori-kun.
Oomori! I don't think you need to be warned but, don't make her lucky 3 times.
Sasaki, I won't let her get to you.
I'll be the last one to do it with the girl then.
All right. Let's go!
Darnit!
Bow! Begin!
Oh, I was going to buy that one-piece miniskirt,
... and a jacket, too.
Everyone's probably mad by
now, since I ditched them...
Hey, look at this one-piece!
And the price, too!
My next date outfit is set!
But where is Yawara? I called
but she wasn't home.
Yeah. She was looking forward to this, too.
Th... this is!
No, enough!
All right!
Out of bounds!
Both of you, fix your sash.
What are you doing, idiot!
Do it seriously!
She's for real.
She's really strong.
You're kidding, right?
Oomori is using everything against her.
Oww!
Yuhkoh!
[Yuhkoh--partial 5 points]
Osae komi. Return to the center.
[Osae komi--hold-down]
Dammit!
Inokuma, straighten up!
That's unfair, aiming just for her leg!
Inokuma-san!
That one-piece's probably sold already.
I really, really wanted that, too.
How is it, Yawara? This is a real fight.
If you can't even get over this,
the gold medal and the National
Achievement Award are unreachable.
I quit already!
Why do I have to be treated
like this over judo?
Teacher, I can't do this anym...
INOKUMA!! How brave of you to
stand up! I'm very deeply moved!
This is exactly what I've been searching
for in Musahiyama High Judo Club...
The ideal spirit!!
Stay with it, Inokuma-san!
Just throw that jerk!
Enough already!
Inokuma! Inokuma! Inokuma!
This is all Grandpa's fault!
Geez!
Inokuma! Inokuma! Inokuma!
Hajime!
Out of bound!
You can mess with me now,
but you'll only get hurt more!
I don't like judo anymore!
Everyone is probably having fun shopping...
I found this first!
This is mine!
No, it's mine! Let go! Grrr!
Inokuma!
Lose!
All right, I got...
Yuhkoh!
[Yuhkoh--partial 5 points]
That's the... Ude hishiji jyuji gatame!
[Ude hishiji jyuji gatame--arm
crushing cross bodylock]
O... Oomori!
M... Maitta!
[Maitta--I give up]
Ippon! That's all!
All right!
Banzai! Banzai!
No way!
Sasaki!
I went against strong guys in
the nationals many times...
...but I never went against such...
such a strong opponent before!
How can you spout such wimpy comments!
Getting confused by that cheap, little girl?
Dammit!
I'll take care of this!
I am the nation's third-best, Sasaki!
Finally came out, eh?
Are you okay, Inokuma?
Hey, you, with that stone face!
Come, come.
Yes, master?
Don't get that face near me!
Let me borrow your ear.
This is an important message, a very important message, so tell it to Yawara word-for-word.
Inokuma, I've got an important
message for you from the master.
Important message?
"That Captain, Sasaki, from
seeing his randori...
[Randori--judo sparring]
... is an immeasurable opponent when compared to the others so far, Jya!"
Stop it with that "Jya!"
[Jya--"Jya" is Jigoro and other old geezers' speech habit of ending sentences]
"With an overblown ego like his, it's
not good to go against him head on.
On top of that, you're leg is injured.
So, if you don't do exactly as
I say, you'll surely lose."
Therefore, for you to win,
Yawara, you must...
Oh yeah. Maybe Kazumi will
buy that one-piece for me.
... so that's it. Got it, Inokuma?
With just this taping, the pain
probably won't go away.
But one more, just one more person and
our judo club can finally win for once!
We need you to try hard, Inokuma-san.
Okay, just one more guy!
Yeah, just one more!
One more guy!
Just one more, just one more!
How low of them to depend on a girl!
And because of a girl, our
pace was screwed up!
We should end this ridiculous
match immediately!
Girl, girl! Don't make fun of girls!
Normal girls don't usually fight judo
with guys on a weekend afternoon.
You should be downtown, wearing
pretty clothes and dating!
If I had that choice...
I'd LOVE to do that!
Begin!
That's it, Sasaki!
Nobody has ever escaped from his Kesa gatame to Yoko shihoh gatame combo yet!
[Kesa gatame--scarf hold]
[Yoko shihoh gatame--side all-direction hold]
Inokuma-san really can't use
her leg strength much.
This is looking bad!
"I never went against such a strong
opponent before", yeah, right!
I just need one finger to
defeat this little girl.
N... no way!
A girl can't possibly hold down a guy!
Her breasts! How soft!
It's a waste to break from the hold so soon.
Let me savor it a while longer!
5 seconds past.
What's wrong, Sasaki, hurry
up and break away!
Hah! Maybe he's doing it on purpose!
Sasaki! You dirty rat!
And you call yourself a captain?!
Don't sweat it!
I guess I should break...
I can't break it!
Sasaki!
What are you doing?
Hurry and break the hold!
20 seconds.
N... no way!
I'm... I'm the nation's third-best, Sasaki!
Excellent, Yawara!
But the path to the National Achievement Award has only just begun!
985 days until the Olympics!
Oh no, no...!
I didn't know that Kazamatsuri-san
is Sayaka-san's coach!
Eeei, Yawara!
Who cares about that glitzy guy!
You're going to have an
earth-shattering debut!
Kazamatsuri-san, I want to
know your true feelings!
Next time on "Yawara!" ...
"Finally Pictured! The Big Scoop of the Century That Will Bring On a Storm, Jya!"
If you don't watch it, I'll give
you one hell of an attack!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
I watched the video through the night.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Stay right here next to me,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
I don't want you to grow up yet.