kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
"I never went against such a strong
opponent before" yeah, right.
I just need one finger for this girl...
U... unbelievable!
Her breasts!
How soft! It's a waste to break from the hold just yet, let me savor it a while longer.
What's wrong, Sasaki, hurry and break free!
M... maybe he's doing it on purpose?
Sasaki! You dirty rat!
And you call yourself a captain?
Don't sweat it. I guess I should break...
I... I can't break loose!
Yawara! Episode 6
Finally pictured! The Big Scoop of the Century That Will Bring On a Storm, Jya!!
Thi... this can't be!
I can't be pinned down by a little girl!
I'm the nation's third-best, Sasaki!
10 seconds.
Sasaki!
Why, why can't I break loose?
It's as if a large rock is on me.
I've done judo for 10 years now.
If I stay pinned by a girl like her,
then what was my 10 years for?
15 seconds.
There's no use in looking at the time.
The holding techniques that I've taught
her won't be broken by some luck.
You can't even break loose even after an hour!
The teacher's instruction?
20 seconds.
10 more seconds.
9 seconds.
8 seconds.
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Ippon!
[Ippon--Full 10 points, a win]
Musashiyama High team victory!
It's finally over.
All right! We won! Time to
group-toss the victor!
Hold it!
Hold off on the group-toss... for now.
All of you have probably guessed
by now, this is my granddaughter.
Grandpa!
I thought so.
Ever since she was little, my
Yawara personally learned my
judo and is a judo genius.
And so, Sasaki Captain, there's no
need to suffer from this loss.
Y... yes sir.
I, the 5-time national champ and 8th
degree black belt, have personally
trained her for all these years.
A 10-year punk like you can't possibly
be on the same level as her!
Y... yes.
By the way, I'd like today's
match to be our secret.
A secret?
You Ganryuji kids wouldn't like the rumor
of losing to a girl to be spread, right?
T... true.
You Musashiyama kids would benefit
from pretending to have won with
your own powers, right?
Wh... why so?
Inokuma sacrificed her leg to fight on for us, didn't go to the bargain sale she wanted
to go to, and brought victory to us!
Yeah, why do we have to keep
such a great story under wraps?
Rather, we should hail Inokuma-san's
great accomplishment!
You can take this great
accomplishment and shove it!
Get this... This girl will have an ultimate accomplishment of getting...
...the Olympic gold medal and the National Achievement Award waiting for her!
G... gold medal... Olympics...
In the near future, Yawara will have
a sensational debut, so this was
just her practice round.
So, no need for a group-toss for
a practice round. Okay?
And so, please keep today's
incident just between us.
Well, excuse us.
Even so, she's too strong.
Yeah. Gold medal and the National Achievement Award..
It's not an unreachable
dream... for her, that is.
Inokuma.
I'm okay, so let me down.
Your leg is precious, don't strain it.
I'll put my special medicine
on it when we get home.
It it's that crushed up viper
stuff, I don't want it.
Well now, the real match was
pretty tough, wasn't it?
Because of it, I had to ditch my
friends at the bargain sale!
But, the real judo is nothing like that.
That kind of judo was no fun at all.
JUDO
One day, there'll come a time for you
to go against that Hon'ami Sayaka.
JUDO
You and that girl will make the
future of judo very interesting!
On the contrary, that will be no fun at all!
Anyway, how could you have
pulled me into today's match?
Ah, well...
What's wrong?
I completely forgot about those
three in the storage room!
Someone! Someone!
Kazamatsuri-san, could I come to
your room next time?
I'll be waiting for your call.
Shinnosuke-sama, this is Yoko.
If you don't call me soon, I'll die!
This is Minako. I have tickets to the piano concert. On Sunday, let's meet at...
Hi, this is Kazamatsuri, the charming...
Why am I so popular?
Oh well, no girl so far has made me hot. Right now, I'm only interested in one particular girl.
You're thinking about Inokuma
Yawara, aren't you?
Sa... Sayaka-san!
Whatever you think about is up to you.
But, don't ever forget that you are
Hon'ami Sayaka's coach!
Understood?
Sayaka-san, then, as your coach,
I need to check one thing..
Inokuma Yawara's strength.
Grandpa, the phone!
I'm tied up right now. Grandpa!
Shut up. I'm busy right now.
Darnit.
Yes, this is the Inokuma residence.
Kazamatsuri-san!
No, I have no plans for...
Yes, then... on Sunday!
All right!
What happened, Yawara,
at yesterday's bargain sale?
Yeah, we waited a long time for you!
Well, I had something come up...
Yeah sure, it was probably that guy...
on a date... or something!
Oh wow, Yawara, really?
No, no. We're going to date on Sunday...
Ahh, we heard that!
Your boyfriend is so fast and aggressive!
He's not my boyfriend yet...
It's not good to be so timid!
Yeah, you should be more aggressive, too.
Should I?
What's wrong, Yawara?
What's up?
Enough already!
H... hi!
Don't say "hi" after following me since morning!
I'll keep following you until
I uncover your secret.
What was that?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Geez, he's so persistent!
Our judo team beat Ganryuji High? Cool!
Is it true, Hanazono?
And you won with that sorry lineup?
W... well, yeah.
Uhh, move over...
Hey!
Inokuma!
Ah, Hanazono-kun, good morning.
U.umm, I bought you this cuz I thought
it might look good on you.
And, and, could you umm,
please read this, too?
envelope -- Inokuma Yawara-sama
Uhh.
Actually, I thought Kazumi bought
that one-piece for me.
Sorry.
Inokuma.
It's complete!
This came out to be an excellent piece.
Yawara's shocking and graceful debut
plan has gone into Phase 2.
None of these grab me.
Oh, if I went to the bargain sale,
I could've bought a new piece.
Yawara!
Geez, knock before you come in, Grandpa!
I'll be out today for an important engagement.
I'll probably be late, taken to a settai at
some restaurant, so plan accordingly.
settai--reception
Okay, whatever.
By the way, why are you trying
to be all dressed up for?
None of your business.
It better not be a date or something.
I won't allow it! If some flashy chump dirties you, then what will happen with obtaining
the National Achievement Award?
Hurry up and leave already.
It's an important engagement, right?
Hey Yawara! Men are forbidden!
Bleah! Unfortunately, Kazamatsuri-san
isn't that kind of man!
Ahh, it's already time!
I'm going to be late!
Today will be different from last time,
I will uncover Inokuma Yawara's secret.
And, she is late...
Kazamatsuri-san!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting so long.
C... cute!
N... no, I just got here also.
Shall we go then?
Okay!
This park... is the place we came last time.
Maybe Kazamatsuri-san is
thinking of it again...
That's Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke.
Hon'ami Sayaka's coach is with Yawara-san...
There must be something going on.
Inokuma-san, I wanted to meet with you
again to relax and talk about things.
M... me too.
Ever since I met you, I've been thinking about you and I wanted to know more about you.
I'd like you to tell me about yourself.
M... me?
Yes, I want to know everything about you.
U... uhm... Well, I...
Yeah, say it, say your secret.
Actually I...
Go ahead, say it!
I gained 2 kilos [4.5 lbs.] this month!
Hah?
I'm trying to be careful, but after school on
the way home, I stop by for ice cream and...
No, not that kind of story, the other kind!
Other kind?
Yeah, what I want to ask you is your...
My...?
Your...
Minako!
Oh yeah, I'm ditching her date!
Th... this is so nostalgic!
I was a fan of this as a child!
Let's go now, Inokuma-san! Let's go!
Come, come.
Hey, pay for it! Un?
Hmm, so you missed the bargain.
Uh-huh. I was looking forward to it but...
That was unfortunate.
We can't be talking about this stuff forever.
Anyway, Inokuma-san, I'd like to hear
the continuation of the previous story.
You should have something
to tell me. Please talk.
I need to tell you something?
Kazamatsuri-san is trying to check my feelings. Maybe he also feels the same about me as...
Come on, tell me your secret this time!
Okay.
Kazamatsuri-san, I, I think...
Don't cry.
Y... Yoko!
Just forget about that guy. He
was probably just playing.
Liar! Shinnosuke-sama isn't
that kind of person!
U... uhm, it's gotten kind of chilly all of a
sudden. Let's hurry back to shore.
I wouldn't want you to catch
a cold, Inokuma-san.
I'm not gonna lose you guys!
Matsuda-san! Something's up!
Oww... Hey Kamoda, on top of being
late, what's up with this?
Forget this, the Inokuma Gramps
went to the TV station...
What? Oh damn!
Grandpa, you are persistent!
No matter how stubborn you are, it's no use.
Whoever this genius judo girl is, it would've been better to have her come instead of you
If you agree to do Yawara's special TV program, I'll let you meet my grand-daughter.
Anyway, I want you to read the plan I devised over consecutive all-nighters.
Plan?
Heh, a 3 hour special? You expect
us to use 3 hours of slot time?
Even that was trimmed down.
And the first hour block is "This Is
Inokuma Yawara's Everything, Jya"?
Yes.
I want Yawara's adorable qualities
appealed to everyone.
And the next hour block is "The Hot Battle! Inokuma Yawara's Shocking Debut Match"?
She'll do a match against one
of the nation's best three.
The place is the National Martial Arts Hall.
And, what is this last hour block
"This Is Inokuma Jigoro, Jya" ?
My obstacle-filled life will be captured
through photo clips and reenactments.
The program will end amidst a
storm of moving emotions.
Have him removed.
Yes, sir.
You're satisfied now, aren't you?
What are you doing, you disrespectful moron!
I'm trying to give you my
grand-daughter's sensational debut!
There he is, Matsuda-san.
OK. Gimme a hand.
There you are Grand-dad!
I'm sorry sir!
He's senile beyond recognition,
so just ignore whatever he said.
What? I am NOT senile!
Come on Grandpa, let's go home.
Hey, let go of me, let go of me!
Eiii, what part of "let go of me"
don't you get!
That was close! God knows what would happen if you laid hands on us!
You cowards! If you get in my way
anymore, I'll have to hurt you!
Yeah, but we're putting our lives on the line
to get Yawara-san's exclusive scoop!
I won't dare let a TV station swipe it from us!
That's right. We're staying close
until we get Yawara-san's scoop!
Idiots! I won't let you guys do that!
Not to a third-rate newspaper like you all!
Inokuma-san, let's have some tea.
I know a good cafe close by.
S... sure.
And, as we drink some hot tea,
I want to know more about you.
O... okay.
This is it. Isn't it nice?
Tokunaga, hurry it up!
Y... yes, ma'am!
Sa... Sayaka-san!
This is not my day!
What's wrong?
Ahh, n... nothing really!
Inokuma-san, I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Let's meet again real soon. Goodbye!
Kazamatsuri-san. Kazamatsuri-san.
Please wait, ma'am!
Kazamatsuri-san asked for my feeling
so persistently, but I couldn't
even say the word "like"...
"Let's meet again real soon. Goodbye!"
Oh well, I can try again real soon!
Huh? Grandpa?
You're back early. Weren't you supposed to
be at a restaurant settai or something?
settai--reception
It didn't happen.
I went to the Oshiuri TV station but...
No way, a TV station? Did you
meet anyone famous?
I met and talked with Sugimura Haruko-san
and Takamine Mieko-san.
They were more beautiful
in person than on TV.
Did you see Shonentai and Hikaru Genji?
I've no interest in school-boy groups.
By the way, why did you go to the
TV station in the first place?
Promoting you, of course.
What? Promoting me?
The best way to glamorously promote
your debut is through the TV, so...
I can't believe it!
But, Oshiuri TV rejected it. How could
they refuse such juicy material!
Of course not!
Please don't do such stupid things anymore!
I have no intention of entering the judo world.
I'm finally able to be like a normal girl and...
"A normal girl..." and what, hook a guy?
gulp!
Remember, Yawara, that in any world, idols don't get careless and make boyfriends.
Getting the National Achievement
Award means that you'll be the
idol for all Japanese citizens.
And so, an idol like that can't possibly
have a boyfriend get in the way.
I don't want to be everyone's girl,
I just need to be one man's girl.
No more! I'm never going to do judo... ever!
Yawara, in you body flow the
blood of a judo athlete...
You can't quit, even if you try.
Hmph, who cares about the blood
of a judo athlete. Not fair!
I was forced to do judo ever
since I could remember.
Who's there?
You're that newspaper reporter
again, aren't you!
Okay, that's it! How dare you come
invade my house and peep!
What's happening, Yawara?
A peeping tom! He was spying on our dojo!
You thug!
Ka... Kazamatsuri-san!
There's another one there!
Show yourselves!
Ta-dahh! The Daily Every Sports' Matsuda Kosaku has finally captured the decisive scene!
I got great shots, Matsuda-san!
And, to throw Hon'ami Sayaka's coach
and pin him with an arm-crushing cross
body lock, an overwhelming scoop!
Sayaka-san's coach?
Kazamatsuri-san is...?
Well then! Please look forward to
tomorrow's The Daily Every Sports!
Wait, you're not getting away with this!
I didn't mean to hide it from you. I didn't approach you for spying, either.
Well, I'll see you...
What fast, sneaky slimeballs!
I must somehow get them
and tear them to pieces!
All right!
We finally did it, huh, Matsuda-san!
Yeah, sure did! From this one picture,
Japan's superstar is born!
You better see tomorrow's Daily Every Sports!
Kazamatsuri-san is Sayaka-san's coach?
Kazamatsuri-san is...?
978 days to the Barcelona Olympics!
Geez, everything is screwed up!
Because of that newspaper reporter,
Matsuda, my identity is revealed!
Yawara-san, you need to be
Japan's shining star!
A superstar!
Please, leave me alone!
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
Hohohoh! The Yawara Boom
That Shakes Japan, Jya!
Please watch it, okay?
A second helping of tofu-miso soup, please!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Kyonen wa anata to
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Eigakande miteta hazu
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Soba ni ite ne
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Ano koro no youni
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Kata o daitene
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Otana ni naranaide