From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Superidol Surfaces!
Hon'ami Sayaka's coach ippon-zeoi.
ippon-zeoi--one arm shoulder flip
Yawara
Inokuma Yawara (17 years old)
Yawara-san, when did you first begin judo?
What are your 3 sizes? [bust, waist, hip]
And do you sleep in pajamas or-- ?
Please! Let me through!
You've learned judo from your grandfather,
so what do the practices consist of?
Like, playing the piano with
your toes or something?
Please get out of my way!
Look this way!
Get the hell out of here, you scumbags!
If you lay even one finger on
this child, I will get you!
Yawara, go!
Ya... Yawara-san!
Ahh, oh well. Then please say
something, grandfather.
When is she doing an official match?
What are Yawara-san's practices like?
It's... LOVE!
Hah?
Education is when the teacher and the learner both value and respect each other. It's only natural to have sympathy rub off.
And so, this is one form of...
LOVE!
Hah?
The way Kaneko and I united
was because of true love.
It was during the depressing times
right before the 2.26 incident, jyatta.
...jyatta... eh?
I was a young martial arts lad trying to
be Japan's best and Kaneko was also...
Hey wait up, gramps!
Don't try to fake us out!
Yeah, yeah!
We were both attracted to each other...
Come on, gramps!
Ka... Kaneko!
It turned out to be one heck of
a mob, huh, Matsuda-san?
Yeah.
If the media is stirring it up this much,
they can't keep it a secret anymore.
Yawara! Episode 7
Hohohoh! The Yawara Boom
That Shakes Japan, Jya!
Inokuma, you're so cool!
I'm surprised you're so strong!
Hey, famous person!
Try a throw for us!
It's not true!
Nope, it's definitely you!
Yeah!
Quit lying, even your full name
and school is mentioned here.
Stop it. Yawara can't possibly do such a thing!
Y... yeah. And she has a
smaller arm than me!
Then, let's try and test her here!
Lay off!
If you mess with Yawara, I will get you!
Dammit! Hey, let's everyone get her!
Yeah!
That's enough!
Hanazono-kun.
You guys! How could you guys
gang up on a helpless girl?
This is... this is not what a
fellow student should do!
I am extremely saddened by this fact!
If you say anything more
stupid, I'll attend to you!
We were only kidding!
Y... yeah, you don't need to cry over it!
Get the hell out of here!
Hanazono-kun.
W... well, you know...
I... Inokuma, if you ever need
anything, just call me.
Well then...
My life is so screwed up!
Ahh! Him!
Yeah, that's right, it's all that newspaper reporter, Matsuda's fault!
Ever since he appeared,
nothing has gone right.
Hey! Don't space out during class!
I'm sorry, sir.
I... Inokuma!
Oh, it was you, Inokuma.
I hit you without knowing.
My bad, my bad, Hahahah!
U...uhm, my home loan's been
only paid half a year now and...
What page do I need to read, sir?
Ahh! I'm sorry, I have a wife and kids!
Don't kill me with an ippon-zeoi!
Please! Please! Please!
ippon-zeoi--one arm shoulder throw
Hey, why did things turn out like this? There's no way Yawara can do judo, you know.
Yeah.. but the more I look at it,
she really looks like Yawara.
Eh?
But, it could just be a stranger really closely resembling you, so cheer up, Yawara!
It's okay, I'm fine. I'm fine.
The media really likes these kinds of things!
"The Hidden Abilities of Today's
High-school Gals!"
That's perverted!
What's going to happen to me now?
But, but Kazamatsuri-san...
why were you with me?
Is it really for spying on me?
Or is it...?
Don't kid me!
Today's lunch menu is ocean
turtle soup, lamb steak...
But, isn't this Yawara-san a
very formidable opponent?
Uhm... fois de gras caviar...
I'm sick of fois de gras, discard it.
Yes, ma'am.
Inokuma Yawara has no status now, so
the story won't be exciting unless she's handled extravagantly by the media.
For dessert, we have foreign
pear sherbert cake..
So, this is all your doing, Sayaka-san?
Of course!
From your previous TV
comments to this incident?
All according to my plans.
The more the public fevers over her,
the more it's worth throwing her!
I see! But don't worry, everyone in the
public is on your side, Sayaka-san!
Compared to that disgustingly
LOW-LEVEL character throwing
the opponent's coach, that is!
My! Oh-hohohohoh!
Inokuma Yawara!
Matsuda-chan, you're great!
I like you, I really like you!
Because of your scoop, Matsuda-chan,
our newspaper is the talk of town
and our sales are through the roof!
I believed that Matsuda-chan, you
would definitely... definitely
accomplish great things for us!
Hey, someone... someone get
some tea for Matsuda-chan!
I've been waiting a long time for this moment! Today's such a wonderful day!
If it's a dream, I don't ever want to wake up.
The tea's going to get cold...
Ohh, we're going to Takotsubo-ten tonight!
Is it your tab, sir?
Of course!
All right!
Kazamatsuri-san, I want to see you...
See you and know your true feelings...
You're Yawara-san, right?
Excuse me! Yawara-san!
When is your debut match?
Please get out of my way!
Why were you hiding yourself all this time?
What's your relationship with Hon'ami Sayaka?
Nothing!
What about Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke?
Geez!
Hey! Don't touch Inokuma!
Help me! Help me!
Yawara-san, get on, quick!
Hurry!
Kazamatsuri-san!
Oh no! Inokuma Yawara has
been kidnapped! Chase her!
Don't kid me! Why do I have
to do a press interview?
Tokunaga, have them vacate the premise.
Yes, ma'am!
You can't go out in public after
having this embarrassing photo,
right, Kazamatsuri-san?
Exactly!
I was thrown so well to the
point of embarrassment.
That shows how sharp and
precise her technique was.
A very skilled swordsman is known
to cut the opponent without giving
any time for them to feel any pain.
Those thrown by her will
learn that the hard way.
You can't defeat her, the skill
difference is too much.
No, no, no! No way! I will
beat her somehow!
There's never been anything
I couldn't get before!
I will definitely steal victory away from her!
And, and, and... get you, too!
No, nothing... really.
If there is a way, there is just
one way to win against her.
And that is?
To get the master, Inokuma Jigoro, the
7th degree black belt, as YOUR coach.
I'm 8TH degree, Jya!
Hang on tight!
Eh?
I said hang on tight!
Okay!
As I said before many times...
There's no way that Yawara
can throw a man!
One more question, do you know
where she is? Did she come here?
I don't know, okay?
You shouldn't hide things from us.
Isn't she in your house?
I said I don't know! Go home!
If you see her, call us.
How persistent! Go home!
Kaori's house is probably no good, either.
Ahh! That motorcycle!
It's Inokuma Yawara!
Oh shoot!
Wait, wait!
I'm sorry.
I was suspicious about you, Kazamatsuri-san.
I thought you were trying to figure
me out, like everyone else.
I even thought you were Sayaka-san's
spy. But.. since you did all this
for me Kazamatsuri-san...
I'm really sorry, Kazamatsuri-san... Ahh!
I'm sorry I'm not Kazamatsuri.
I don't know what's between you
and him, but it's not my style to
impose on your private life.
I'll ignore what you just said.
I'm going home!
Going home?
W... wait, where do you think you're going?
Let me go!
If you go home now, you can't do anything!
All this is your fault!
Is it all my fault?
Yeah, it's ALL your fault!
Oh yeah? Yeah! Okay! It's all my fault!
What are you trying to say
now? Just let me go!
No!
Let me go!
Just calm down now!
Geez!
Don't ever come before me again!
A... awesome!
It was way beyond my expectations!
She threw me without using any power.
If it's her, she can do it... the gold medal
and the National Achievement Award!
But...
Ah! Oww, oww!
Are you okay?
No, not really good. Oww!
Any injuries? Broken bones?
My whole's body's rattled, so I'm not sure.
Sorry.
Instead of me, we should be concerned
with your situation, since you have
no place to return to.
Oww, oww, oww!
Who is it?
Mm? Who is it? Wait, I've heard that cutsey voice somewhere before... hold on...
And, these adorably soft, maple
leaf handy-wandies...
I know... it must be Sayaka-chan!
No fun, no fun, no fun!
I tried really hard to fool you but you saw through it too quickly, daddy-waddy! I hate you!
I'm in trouble. What should
I do to make it up?
Try and guess!
Well.. let's see, something that'd
make my Sayaka happy...
I bought you 10 fur items recently,
and you've got a boatload of jewelry,
you have 5 cars, and 3 yachts...
oh, I know... airplanes!
You want an airplane, right, Sayaka?
No, no!
Actually,
I want one old person!
Old person?
Yes, a terrific old person! A judo master!
W... well, come on in!
I cleaned this place just last month.
This is a little bearable, right?
People need to bear through things, you know?
I... I'll make a spot for you
here, so hang on a sec.
Ahh, no, no, no! It's okay, don't worry!
Who is that?
Rikido-zan... the pro wrestler, Rikido-zan.
And this person?
Nagashima! You don't know him?
Ah, this is Yamashita athlete, right?
Yeah!
Ahh!
I'm not using this for weird
things... don't worry!
They're all weird posters.
What do you mean? They're
all superstars of the era!
Taking a small possible situation, tying it
to a sure chance, and grabbing the glory.
They all made my dreams come true!
And one day, you, too, will...
No, not me.
What is she doing out still?
Uhm, hello...
Pin pon pan pon! This number is no
longer in service, so... excuse me!
Ahh, you're Jigoro-san, correct?
I'm fine, thank you. Excuse me!
W... wait, Jigoro-sama!
Excuse me!
Jigoro-sensei!
Yes, what?
No way, this my room?
Okay, next is dinner prep.
Ah, it's okay, there's a good ramen
shop just around the corner.
You probably eat ramen all time, right?
Eh?
Are there any grocery shops nearby?
Yeah, there's a convenience store...
I'll make you beef stroganoff.
B... beef stroga.. what's that?
A thank you gift for today.
Hey, what's this car? Don't push, man!
Which newspaper company is it?
Stupid, it can't be a newspaper company!
News reporters, great job, great job.
I am here to escort you.
Inokuma-san, where are you going?
I've been invited to dinner. What
was it that's being served?
A bit of French cuisine, sire.
A bit, a bit! I'm eating that.
Delicious! This is really delicious! We should've called your grandfather over!
What's wrong, aren't you gonna eat? If
you don't eat, you won't become strong!
I don't care about getting strong.
When did you start doing judo?
I don't know...
But, I do remember stomach throwing
my father when I was 5 years old.
5 years old?!
I wanted to be praised by everyone.
Of course, grandpa was overjoyed, but at
that time, it seemed like my mother was
in the shadows of the dojo, crying.
At that time, I had no idea that
I was different than other kids.
But, my mother must have known.
When I got in junior high, I finally noticed it.
All my friends weren't doing
morning and night practices.
Everyone wore pretty clothes,
and dated boys, having fun...
While only I... only I...
I don't hate judo. But, I just want to
be a normal girl... just a normal girl.
I... I don't know how many times I cried...
for exactly the opposite reason.
I told you before, right, that my
dream was a sports star.
A sports star that gave everyone a chance
to dream... that's what I wanted to be.
Baseball, soccer, rugby... I did all
kinds, but none of them clicked.
In the end, I always cried... it was rough, you know, to give up each dream, one by one.
Ah, heck! All of that is history!
I'm pretty satisfied now, with being a newspaper reporter. People are strange, huh?
This is delicious!
Ahh, I'll clean it up!
Don't worry. I'm used to it.
Really, you can just leave it there...
Eeek!
What?
A c... cockroach just...
Eeek... ran.. it ran...
A cockroach ran! Gross!
She really is just a normal girl.
What are you doing? Please
hurry up and catch it!
What, me?
Ah, don't tell me that you're afraid of cockroaches, too, Matsuda-san!
Wha... no way, it's just a cockroach...
Dohhyah!
The cockroach flew!
Another plateful!
U... uhm... Inokuma-sensei.
Hm?
Isn't it time to discuss being
Sayaka's coach...
Don't sweat it.
Hah...
But...
But this food is really delicious.
Another plateful, jya!
The fifth helping... right?
What a grand person!
The boldness of requesting seconds
at a prestigious restaurant!
This is a challenge to the weight-classes
and rules and manners of the
Japanese Judo Federation!
He can do it! The master will definitely bring about a revolution in the Japanese judo world!
Another plateful, please!
971 days until Barcelona Olympics
Hey, Grandpa, are you really going
to be Sayaka-san's coach?
This is tasty, too. Yawara, I
want more kimpira goboh!
Geez... Grandpa, I'm going to be in a match.
W... what did you say?
Next time, on "Yawara"... Enough of
Judo! I'm going to be in a match!
If you don't watch it, I'll do a
yoko shihoh gatame on you!
yoko shihoh gatame--side four direction hold
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
I watched the video through the night.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stay right here next to me,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
I don't want you to grow up yet.