kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Wh... wh... wh... what's that?
What's up? What is it?
Oh yeah...
Last night, I let Yawara-san sleep
inside, while I stayed outside.
But what's going on so early in the morning?
Oh, morning practice!
She's been doing it every morning
for 10 years, no doubt.
Even though she claims to dislike judo,
she can't shake off that daily habit.
Wha... don't answer it, don't...!
Yes, this is the Matsuda residence.
Matsuda-san, are you up?
Yeah...
You have a phone call...
From the editor-in-chief.
Th... this is Matsuda.
You big fat idiot!
What are doing at a time like this! Why
are you fooling around with a girl?!
W... well... actually, uhm...
I've got a cold... and my little
sister came to take care of me...
I don't care about your excuses!
Last night, the Hon'ami family invited Inokuma Jigoro and held a private meeting!
Hah?
Inokuma Yawara is missing, too!
Despite you chasing her all this time,
why'd she slip through your fingers?!
Umm, what did you say
about Inokuma Jigoro?
Grandpa?
Look at the TV!
TV?
The switch, the switch!
As for the details of the private meeting,
the Hon'ami family has no comments.
But, according to inside sources,
the Hon'ami family was apparently
trying to hire 7th degree black belt...
But, according to inside sources,
the Hon'ami family was apparently
trying to hire 7th degree black belt...
G... Grandpa!
..Inokuma Jigoro, also the legal guardian of Inokuma Yawara, as their personal coach.
Knowing the fact that he raised
her rival, Inokuma Yawara...
Grandpa... Grandpa is..?
...it is a rather bold move for Hon'ami Sayaka.
How is Inokuma Yawara
going to handle this news?
Grandpa is Sayaka-san's coach?
How is Inokuma Yawara
going to handle this news?
Yawara Episode 8
Enough of Judo! I'm
Going To Be In a Match!
Inokuma-san, open up!
Just one comment, please!
What happened at last night's dinner meeting?
Are you really going to be
Hon'ami Sayaka's coach?
Eii! That delinquent girl!
How dare she stay out without my
permission! I'm going to give her the
lecture of her life when she gets back!
But, that meal at last night's
French restaurant...
Umm, Inokuma-sensei, what do you think?
This is truly delicious!
N... no, not the food. I was referring to
what we've been requesting of you..
to take over as Sayaka's coach.
Of course, if you agree, I can
arrange for an ample bonus.
And that's not all.
We'll even offer total support
to Yawara-san's debut.
The place of event is the
martial arts hall-size!
We'll bring over top level world-class
athletes and conduct a very
splashy debut as you wished.
I have one question.
Sure! Please ask!
Can I have this food in a doggy bag?
F... father... wh... what is a doggy bag?
This French food is truly delicious!
Wh... what a grand person!
Eii! That delinquent girl!
I brought that good food for her, too!
Where in the world did she go?
Grandpa is going to be Sayaka-san's coach?
I'm finally... alone, aren't I?
Come on, cheer up!
Oh hey, we should go out somewhere for fun!
Eh?
You just need to let loose
sometimes! Just have fun!
Now that that's settled, seconds, please!
Uryaahh!
This... Am I still weak even after THIS?
N... nobody's saying that!
Miss Sayaka, you're the strongest in Japan!
Yes, that's exactly right.
But that... that...
... please excuse this vulgar phrase...
that piece-of-shit old man!
I refuse.
R... refuse?
Even with all those benefits, you're
not willing to be Sayaka's coach?
Benefits have nothing to do with it.
Then, what more can we do for you?
Miss Sayaka, invite me when
you get a little stronger.
I don't teach wimps!
Wh... what did you say?
Oh, don't take back this doggy bag
just cuz I rejected you!
I've always gotten what I've wanted.
But, those two Inokumas!
Why can't I get it my way?
Sayaka-san's pretty ticked off.
I guess it can't be helped,
though. But, that time...
Well then, I bid you farewell. I look
forward to more dinner invitations!
Th... this isn't good!
I can't let him leave just like that!
I... Inokuma-sensei!
Eii! You persistent fool! I told you,
I'm not returning the doggy bag!
N... no... not that... umm...
C... could you sign this book?
Sign? Oh, very well!
Tha... thank you very much!
Inokuma Jigoro!
I got him to sign it!
Oh, what is that?
Oh, nothing at all!
U...umm, let's start the practice, shall we?
If you're weak on rides, you
shouldn't have ridden at all!
Hehe, I'm fine. But, you're unaffected...
Is it because your sense of balance
is more advanced from judo?
Don't talk about me like I'm a cat!
Grandpa! Let's ride that one next!
Come on, come on!
Whoa there, don't pull me so hard.
Oh hey, watch it, watch it.
Grandpa...
Sir...
Excuse me, sir?
Your order's ready.
How much?
980 yen, please.
Hey girl!
Hello!
Do you happen to be Inokuma Yawara?
The one on yesterday's paper?
N... no.
It's gotta be you! C'mon,
show me a judo move!
You've got the wrong person.
Aw, c'mon, show us!
P... please stop!
C'mon!
C'mon now!
Those jerks!
Geez, I've had...
Enough!
Let's go!
Even if you stay hidden, things
like that will continue.
What... should I do? I can't be outside anymore.
Well, then, you'll have to go public.
W... what?
Just do a match. It doesn't have
to be an official one, either.
You just need to show your skills to everyone.
How could I? If I do, it'll
only make things worse!
N... no it's not! L... let me finish...
Hey, hold it!
Let me go!
Let me finish...
Watch out!
Here!
Thanks!
What a waste!
With all that athletic ability and sharp skills...
But...
I just want to be a normal girl... a normal girl.
Yawara-san.
Do a match and...
LOSE in front of everybody!
Ma... Matsuda!
Where the hell were you all this time!
Were you on a date with that
"little sister" of yours?
Because you didn't follow through, we lost
the big news of Hon'ami Sayaka trying to
hire Inokuma Jigoro as her coach.
Our original scoop is down the
drain after losing that one!
Listen up! Go find Inokuma
Yawara, or you're fired!
No, that's not enough!
Go cut your stomach !
At about now, Inokuma Yawara
returned to her home.
Huh?
I was with Inokuma Yawara up until now.
And, she just agreed to do a match.
Wh... what did you say?
She is going to do a match!
And, under our sponsorship, too! The
place and opponent is our choice!
The place will be the Saikai College Judo Hall.
I plan to have the opponent be the 20kg heavier, 72kg-class defender, Tohdoh
Yuki. Any problems with that, sir?
N... no, I... I don't think so...
Tomorrow's front page alteration
will be in time, then?
Y... yes!
M... Matsuda-chan, you're the type of man...
Oh, how should I put it...
Banzai! Banzai!
Yawara-san, where have you
been all this time?
Who is that motorcycle guy
that kidnapped you?
P... please let me through.
Did you hear about your grandfather
becoming Sayaka-san's coach?
P... please quiet down!
I have nothing to tell you now.
For details, please see tomorrow's
Daily Every Sports.
That's all for now.
Oh great! Daily Every Sports beat us again!
I'm home!
G... Grandpa!
Argh! You delinquent girl!
Who with, where, and what have you
been doing all this time?
It's no big deal... I just stayed
over at a friend's house.
How could a yet-to-be married girl stay
out all night without permission...
Go join the nunnery! The nunnery!
Oh yeah. This is for you!
This is... good!
Right! I got it from a store
that hand-bakes it!
I don't care about that. Don't tell me you've spent the night with a random guy...
Oh yeah, that's right. I brought
you some taiyaki.
taiyaki--fish shaped sweet bean cake
This is also good! The beans are packed all the way into the tail portion. Delicious!
Oh well, I'm going to go change.
Oh, Grandpa. I saw the sports
news on TV today.
You're going to be Sayaka-san's coach, right? She's got a lot of potential, you know!
And unlike me, she's motivated, too!
Oh yeah. I have some news, too.
I'm... going to be in a match.
The Daily Every Sports is the sponsor.
I'm going to do the what-do-you-call-it...
an exhibition game at some judo hall.
Whatever happens to me won't
affect Grandpa anymore...
...because Grandpa will train Sayaka-san
and get the gold medal and the
National Achievement Award.
"Gold medal... and the National
Achievement Award."
I've heard that phrase a million
times over everyday, but...
I won't be a part of that anymore.
No more of Grandpa's rigorous training!
No more judo... no more...
Yawara!
Is what you just said true?
Say it one more...
Knock on the door before
you come in, okay!
Wh... what is that exhibi, exi, exhib...
The reporters will come
see me in my match.
Hey, that's just like a practice match!
Isn't my debut your long-awaited dream?
Even though it might not
matter to you anymore.
No! I won't allow that!
I didn't keep you under wraps all this
time just for that kind of cheap debut!
Just forget about me!
You're now Sayaka-san's coach, right?
Then you should get attention
with Sayaka-san....
...Grandpa.
I rejected that offer.
Rejected?
Really?
You're not going to be
Sayaka-san's coach?
How can I leave you before your debut?
And, I don't teach wimps!
What's with your face?
Grandpa!
And so, is what you said true?
Yeah. It'll probably be on
tomorrow's morning edition.
I guess it can't be helped.
You've refused to do a match until now,
but, you're finally willing to do a match.
We can set up glamorous
matches in the future so..
Yawara, you've finally decided!
I'm really happy!
But, Grandpa, I'm...
What? Inokuma Yawara is going to lose?
Losing... meaning, on purpose?
Yeah. That's right.
Master, seconds!
If she loses in front of everyone,
they'll see no talent in her.
Their hopes will fade into disappointment.
And she'll go back to being a normal girl, which will end the whole "Yawara" hype.
But why? You were so obsessed
with Yawara-san!
You said she was a once-in-
a-lifetime superstar!
There are those that love to bask
in all the fame and glory, and
there are those that just don't.
Matsuda-san, maybe you have
feelings for Yawara-san?
A guy with that kind of sleazy thought
won't ever understood my feelings!
Dammit!
Why do you think I left Yamagata to
work at such a measly paying job!
Is he a crying drunk?
Ever since I was a kid, I've idolized all kinds
of superstars for all my 25 years alive!
I wanted to use this job to share that excitement with everyone!
A noble reason, right?
Y... yes..
But, it's all over.
It's all a dream!
Oh, there'll be another one... a
second or third "Yawara-chan".
No there won't!
There won't be another!
Even if I wait 10 years.. or 20 years,
or even a 100 years!
S.sir...
A girl like that won't ever appear agai...
N... no!
Yawara. Where are you, Yawara?
Now that it's settled, it's time for some practice.
Yawara!
Oh, Grandpa. It's kinda late,
but I'll be making dinner.
I see. You can't fight on
an empty stomach.
This looks really delicious!
Eat some good food, so you can
whip the opponent in grand style
in that inky little practice match!
But... but, Grandpa.
I'm.. I'm going to LOSE.
964 days to Barcelona Olympics!
Ho,ho,hoh! Finally, Yawara's debut match! Win the match with a lightning fast ippon
and surprise the heck out of everyone!
Yeah. But, Grandpa, I...
What's wrong, Yawara? What's
taking you so long?
Next time, on "Yawara!"...
"Yawara's Debut Match! An Ippon Victory Before You Even Know It Happened! Jya!"
If you don't watch it, I'll explode
a yama-arashi attack on you!
yama-arashi--porcupine
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Kyonen wa anata to
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Eigakande miteta hazu
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Soba ni ite ne
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Ano koro no youni
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Kata o daitene
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Otana ni naranaide