From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
Translator's Notes:
The ice cream shop "Golgo 13 ice cream" is a spoof of Baskin Robins. Golgo 13 ran in the same anthology book as Yawara, so the artist spoofed his peer's comic. (Common practice among Japanese cartoonists.)
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
Translator's Notes:
The ice cream shop "Golgo 13 ice cream" is a spoof of Baskin Robins. Golgo 13 ran in the same anthology book as Yawara, so the artist spoofed his peer's comic. (Common practice among Japanese cartoonists.)
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
Translator's Notes:
The ice cream shop "Golgo 13 ice cream" is a spoof of Baskin Robins. Golgo 13 ran in the same anthology book as Yawara, so the artist spoofed his peer's comic. (Common practice among Japanese cartoonists.)
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Tanuki (a raccoon like animal) and Kitsune (a fox) are natural enemies. Please keep this in mind
as you watch this episode.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Tanuki (a raccoon like animal) and Kitsune (a fox) are natural enemies. Please keep this in mind
as you watch this episode.
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Even if you stay hidden,
things like that will continue.
What... should I do? I can't
be outside anymore.
Well, then, you'll have to go public.
Wh... what?
Do a match and...
LOSE in front of everybody!
Episode 9
Yawara's Debut Match! An Ippon Victory Before You Even Knew It Happened! Jya!
Next!
Hey, today's Miss Sayaka is...
Pretty ticked off, huh?
Did you say something?
Uh no! Such wonderful skills! Truly splendid!
I am, aren't I?
Since I became so powerful, all I need to do
is defeat Yawara Inokuma and live up to my reputation of being Japan's number one.
But, why... why, Yawara Inokuma?
Why do you avoid me and instead,
do such a meaningless match?
"Yawara" finally debuts!
At the Saikai College Judo Hall!
Opponent is over 20 kg heavier, Yuki Tohdoh!
As the person thrown by Yawara
Inokuma, Coach Kazamatsuri, what
are your feelings about this match?
Get Coach Kazamatsuri out!
Coach Kazamatsuri!
Just a moment, please. I shall read
Mr. Kazamatsuri's comments now.
"Yawara Inokuma's opponent, Yuki Tohdoh,
is a very strong defender in her weight
class for the national matches...
..and is over 20 kilograms heavier than her,
but in this case, that is pretty irrelevant.
I, Kazamatsuri, predict that
Yawara Inokuma will win."
End of comment.
Wait a sec! What does he mean by "...in
this case, that is pretty irrelevant"?
We need more than just that comment!
Yes, but...
We want him in person!
But, umm...
Get him out here!
Tokunaga-san, please forgive me.
Because of my nervous tendencies,
I've caused you all this trouble.
But, Yawara-san, your incredible skills
will finally be made public.
Yuki Tohdoh... she's not even close
to being your opponent!
Gimme a break!
So, Miss Yuki Tohdoh, you don't feel
you'll lose in the coming match?
You expect to win?
Of course! Matter of fact, I didn't need
to accept to do this match.
But I accepted for the sake of the
Japanese Judo World.
To "Yawara" or whatever her name was... I'll teach that girl the true terror of real judo!
Somebody, volunteer!
Me!
In that match, one minute...
No, 30 seconds, and I'll beat her!
But I doubt I'll even need
30 seconds, though!
And so, athlete Tohdoh is all fired up.
How is the mysterious Yawara Inokuma
going to fight against her?
The excitement is starting to build up!
What excitement is there to build up?
That stupid Daily Every reporter!
Yawara won't even need 10 seconds
to whip that opponent!
So, even as the Judo Club coach, Mr. Kaizuka, you knew nothing about Yawara Inokuma?
Y... yes, principal.
And as the PE teacher, Mr. Kawakami,
you didn't notice any hidden athletic
potential in her during class?
No potential. She's just a normal
high school female.
I didn't sense any sort of advanced
physical ability at all.
Then what is all the
commotion about?
If it is true, though, then it would be
highly honorable for our school.
Hey, Yawara, did you see
your opponent on TV?
She was scary-looking, like a
gorilla or something!
Why'd you agree to fight
a person like that?
If not, then no one would
believe that I'm weak.
Yeah, right... you seem to
look weak anyway!
The enemy's twice your size!
You're gonna get killed!
Listen, Yawara. If you're about
to get hurt, just cry!
If you cry, I'm sure she'll back off. Even she's got to have an ounce of sympathy in her!
Maybe I should fight for you!
Yeah, let Kaori do it!
Yeah! Let her, Yawara!
Inokuma.
Hanazono-kun.
Th... the time has finally come, hasn't it?
D... do your best.
What's up with that?
His head was steaming.
Wow!
Yes, this the Daily Every Sports editorial room.
Yawara Inokuma's profile?
Just read our paper... ours!
The place is Saikai College's Judo Hall.
So, Coach Kazamatsuri predicted
Yawara Inokuma's victory, eh?
Well, it's hard to determine the winner.
But, I can say this.
This match may reveal the genius girl
who might shoulder the Japan...
no, the world's Judo World.
This is surely the biggest scoop that this
Daily Every has had in its entire history!
Matsuda-san. Matsuda-san.
Oh, there you are.
What are you doing here?
The editor-in-chief's overjoyed.
And the editorial department is chaotic with
an overwhelming number of inquiries.
Yawara-chan's popularity is really enormous.
Oh, but she's gonna lose, right?
Ahh, shut up!
Oww...
What are you looking for?
Yawara Inokuma's...
Oh, Matsuda-san, you're still not
giving up on her, are you?
Well, I can see why, since you were
so obsessed with her.
You're trying to find a way to
not let her lose, right?
That's not it!
What I'm looking for is
Yawara Inokuma's father!
Yawara-chan's father?
The man having Jigoro Inokuma as the father and having Yawara Inokuma as the daughter...
He's got to have left his name in
the world of judo somewhere.
I see. It runs in the family...
just like a thoroughbred.
Quit jabbering and help me find him!
C'mon, c'mon, is that it?
That's it, Yawara!
This is the first time you've been
so fired up for practice!
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
But, that's not enough.
You'll need to improve more if you
want to astonish the world!
Let's go!
This will be the last practice with Grandpa.
And, it's the last judo for me.
Good, that's the spirit!
I'm going to lose, you know!
Okay, lower your hips now!
I'm sorry... really sorry, Grandpa!
Found him!
M... Matsuda-san.
1974 National Champion!
A rookie appeared like a comet!
This debut sounds just like the plan that Jigoro Inokuma set up for Yawara Inokuma!
Despite being nameless until the year
before, he appeared out of nowhere
and stole away the championship.
But, the following year, he was
nowhere to be found.
He ran away!
What?
One year after his debut, he succeeded in disappearing from the world of judo.
His name is?
His name is...
Kojiro Inokuma!
The match is finally tomorrow, huh?
Yes.
Do your best, okay? Oh yeah, no use,
since you're gonna lose, huh?
I'll do my best to lose.
I warn you, don't lose so easily.
You'll give away the setup if you do.
Just act like you're trying hard. Make sure
you attack every once in a while.
That way, people will think
that's all you are.
Yes.
You seem really refreshed.
I do?
You're totally different from last time.
You seemed like you were about
to cry the whole time.
I seemed to have troubled you, but
I'm bidding farewell to judo.
Thank you for everything.
Is your father... going to come?
Eh?
At tomorrow's match. Is Kojiro
Inokuma going to come?
Why? Why do you know about my father?
Maybe you can see your father again!
My dad won't come back yet.
My mom is out looking for him, but I haven't heard any news about finding him yet.
Your mother is out looking for him?
She comes back home a few times
out of the year, but otherwise,
she's out searching for him.
Why did your father run away? One year
after the national championships... why?
I don't know.
This is the last time I'll meet you like this.
To tell you the truth, I don't want you to lose.
I wanted you to win and win on,
like in my dreams.
You really saw that much in me...?
I'm sure there'll be another person
much more stronger than me!
Y... yeah, I guess so.
There'll be another, huh?
Well, I need to go now. We're going to
be busy for tomorrow's preparation.
Yes. Thank you very much.
You're a senior in high school. After quitting judo, what are you going to do?
I want to go to an all-female college.
Grandpa wants me to go to a
martial-arts related school, but I
want to major in housekeeping.
Housekeeping, huh? Then you
need to study hard.
Yes. Well then.
Later.
I've been hearing it. Ever since I saw you.
All that supportive cheering
from the large crowds!
Yawara! Yawara!
All right!
The cheers are getting smaller.
And tomorrow, everything will end.
Tomorrow...
Yuki Tohdoh, it's finally time!
How do you feel about today's match?
As I've said many times, today's
thing isn't even a match!
30 seconds! I'll win in 30 seconds!
You are...
Jigoro Inokuma!
30 seconds is such a waste. 5 seconds, 5 seconds! 5 seconds is all that's needed.
Another kitsune-udon!
5 seconds and who'll win?
Another tanuki-udon!
Of course Yawara!
Another kitsune-udon!
You bold chump!
Then I'll win in 3 seconds!
Another tanuki-udon!
Then I'll go for one second!
And then, with one finger,
she'll take you down!
Another kitsune-udon!
You old geezer!
Another tanuki-udon!
Not bad kitsune-udon for
a college mess hall!
Hey, hey, there's so many
people outside! I'm surprised!
Yawara really doesn't look
good in these, huh?
Yeah, really.
Right?
Besides, judo outfits have no
fashion quality whatsoever.
Yeah, no coloring.
It's too plain. Really plain.
You should put on a ribbon, at least.
Yeah, you need at least this one-point fashion.
Yup, that's a lot cuter, Yawara.
Dosuko--i! Dosuko--i! Dosuko--i!
(Dosuko--i! : An athletic grunt, more commonly used by huge sumo wrestlers)
Yawara.
If you're gonna run, now's the time.
It's too late to run.
Aren't you scared, Yawara?
Yeah, your opponent is the type that
bounces off 10 people at once.
O... of course I'm scared. Scared
enough to want to run away.
But, in order to calm down the
commotion, I need to do it.
But you might get killed!
In the least, you'll probably break
a couple of bones!
You should run away, Yawara.
Uhmm...
Hey, look guys!
Kazamatsuri-san!
It's almost time, huh?
Yes.
Who is it? Who is it?
Don't tell me he's the one
you've been dating!
Introduce him to us, Yawara!
U... uhmmm...
I am Kazamatsuri.
Wonderful!
W... we're Yawara's friends!
And I'm single, by the way!
Me too.
And me, too.
N... nice to meet you all.
Yawara-san, I might be a bit pretentious, but there's more than a 20 kilogram difference between you and your opponent.
You're at a disadvantage if
you're pinned down.
Please be more careful when the opponent
tries to pull a throw to a pindown combo.
Y... yes.
T... that's okay. If she's in a
pinch, she'll just cry.
Yeah, yeah.
If she cries, the match will end, right?
Well, it depends on the referee, but...
Yawara-san, anyways, you'll win for sure.
What a stud!
Wonderful!
I'm tingling!
I'll look forward to your
awesome display of skills.
Kazamatsuri-san.
U... uhh, we'll go on ahead.
Yawara, do your best with, whatever!
I know you still have your suspicions, but
this isn't the time to explain things, is it?
But it's not that I suspect you for...
That's okay. Just think about the match now.
But...
Kazamatsuri-san, but in this match...
Everybody in the hall. Thank you
for your patience.
We will now begin the match between
Yuki Tohdoh and Yawara Inokuma.
Well, shall we go?
Yes.
Well, well.
We see each other often, don't we?
Because you sniffed around like a hyena, Yawara-san is able to debut.
I appreciate that.
Yawara Inokuma!
You took my... my Kazamatsuri-san!
Inokuma!
Yawara Inokuma is here!
Go on, Yawara-san.
Yawara, why don't you give a good
face for the camera people?
Oh well, you could save your
best smile for when you get the
National Achievement Award, though!
Inokuma. Finally... it's finally time, huh?
No way she'll lose. She beated me,
the nation's third best, you know.
It's not too late!
Just cry, Yawara!
You're gonna die!
Bow!
Begin!
Hurry up and win it, Yawara.
You don't need to work
hard on this opponent.
Okay, do an ippon-zeoi there!
[ippon-zeoi : one-armed shoulder throw]
There you go!
Yuhkoh!
[Yuhkoh : partial 5 points]
Inokuma!
Yawara-san!
What the... ?
What's going on? Yawara!
957 days until Barcelona Olympics
N... no way! Mom? Mom's at the judo hall?
Eii, Yawara! What's taking you so long?
I didn't teach you that kind of judo!
Mom!
There, throw her!
Next time, on "Yawara!" ...
"An Ippon Zeoi With My Mom!"
"The 90's is Yawara's Era! Jya!"
If you don't watch it, I'll pin you
with an ude-hishigi jyuji gatame!
[ude-hishigi jyuji gatame : arm crushing cross-body lock]
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Subtitled by Neko Creations
Timed and edited by Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
I watched the video through the night.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
It should've been, that we were there,
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Watching it at the movies last year.
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Stay right here next to me,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Just like you did, in the past,
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
As you warmly embraced me.
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
I don't want you to grow up yet.