kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Is it really okay for us to ditch work?
If the Chief finds out, he'll raise hell.
Matsuda-san?
You haven't been too happy these days.
So, I guess you're still shocked about Yawara-san's feelings toward Kazamatsuri.
Shut up!
Quit mumbling.
I'm only interested in Inokuma
Yawara as a judo athlete.
Let's go, Kamoda.
Wait a minute!
Matsuda-san!
G.. geez.
W.. wait.
What are you doing?
I.. I'm sorry.
Yawara-san.
Episode 20
The Big Guest For Yawara
P.. please stop!
It's completely healed.
I.. i.. it is!
It doesn't hurt at all!
You should have come to me earlier
for such a simple fracture.
Thank you very much.
I never knew that you were
a bone-setting doctor.
My treatment results are quick, and even if the methods are rough, fractures are fixed in no time.
Now all you need to do is rub this balm on.
What is this balm?
My special blend.
It has boiled leech.
Le..?
It improves the circulation of the area wrapped in the cast that has had restricted blood flow.
I also have boiled black-widow spider
syrup, burnt gecko ointment, and
blue-green snake extract, too.
N.. no thank you!
Anyway, ever since Yawara-san won the national title, it must be really restless around here.
Yes, the college scouts have been
sending us lots of invitations.
Every college is bending over
backwards to get her.
All because once they get Yawara-san...
... it's more than guaranteed that
they'd win all the matches.
Just by showing a hint of what she can do,
it has caused this much commotion.
If she displays more of her strength,
the whole world will flip.
But Yawara-san will go to the nation's best, Saikai College, right?
Oh!
I'm going to try to get in there, too.
If things go well, I could go to the
same school with her again.
Their coach, Mr. Yuutenji, who I thought had just a big face, has a lot of passion, too.
Is that so?
Then Yawara-san will get into Saikai College, and conquer the nationals.
And go to the Olympics, and get the
gold medal, of course. Then..
..she'll receive the National
Achievement Award!
What's wrong, Hanazono-kun?
Inokuma, you keep getting
further away from me.
S.. Sensei! I.. I.. I..
What's wrong?
I.. think Yawara-san...
..to be able to see Yawara-san develop
into a superstar so closely..
..I am so happy!
Hanazono-kun, wait!
Don't tell me that you...
..were trying to go home without
paying for the treatment, huh?
What?
I see. Mitsuba Women's 2-year College, Housekeeping Major.
Yes, it's my first choice.
Mitsuba's entrance exams are pretty difficult.
And there aren't any athletic scholarship
admittances. And there aren't
any judo clubs, either.
Yes, I know. But, it's been my first choice before all of that, so, I'll do my best.
So, you're going to quit judo?
N.. no way.
Then what about your victory
at the Martial Arts Hall?
What were those tears of victory for..?
Well, I guess the reason for her doing that match was for Kazamatsuri anyway.
The guys in the judo club taught me something.
If you try your best, you can achieve anything.
That's why I'm going to do my
best to study for the exams.
You're serious..?
Yawara-san! It's true that Hon'ami Sayaka
was totally defeated by you.
But, she hasn't given up yet!
She went to train in Europe with Coach Kazamatsuri to become stronger.
To beat you next time!
With Kazamatsuri-san?
Whatever Sayaka-san does
won't affect me anymore.
Seems like Yawara-san seriously
made her decision.
Tres bon! Splendid!
Mademoiselle Sayaka, you are tres bien!
KABAmatsuri-san, your guidance
is excellent, too.
[KABA -- hippo]
I have nothing else to teach her.
I'm KAZAmatsuri.
But Pornalef-san, there is someone
who threw me very easily.
Yes, I saw it in the paper.
Yawara Inokuma, the ippon zeoi gal, yes?
[ippon zeoi -- one arm shoulder throw]
But, I cannot believe that she threw Sayaka-san in 2 seconds, jya.
I can't believe it either.
But it's a fact.
That's why we came to you, a man
who developed numerous world
class athletes, Pornalef-sensei.
Sayaka-san is already talented enough
to win a world competition, jya.
I'd like to meet Yawara Inokuma, jya.
Pornalef-sensei, your Japanese is very good...
..but would you please refrain from saying 'jya'?
It reminds me of someone I despise
and it gives me the chills.
Oh yes, I studied really hard to learn Japanese.
It's because I wanted to read this book, jya.
Th.. that's..!
Oh, I have it, too.
Oh, KABAmatsuri, you've read this book, too?
[KABA -- hippo]
No wonder your methods of coaching Sayaka-san are so excellent.
I'm KAZAmatsuri.
I learned the real meaning of judo from this book, and became even stronger.
This book is the bible for judo.
That's exactly right.
And, Inokuma Yawara is the granddaughter
of this book's author, Inokuma Jigoro.
Wh.. what?
Is that true, KABAmatsuri?
[KABA -- hippo]
Yes, and he personally trained her, too.
And, I'm KAZAmatsuri.
I see. Now it's understandable why Sayaka-san was thrown by her, jya.
Inokuma Yawara and Inokuma Jigoro are the worst sore spots for my eyes, jya-
It's not only you, Sayaka-san.
Yawara-san would be sore spots on the eyes
of 4 other athletes around the world, jya.
Four?
Yes.
I recognize four strong female judo athletes around the world, other than you, jya.
They'll surely compete viciously with the
goal of defeating Yawara Inokuma, jya.
Once more!
Kim seems very fired up for the Olympics.
Yes.
But she has another reason to be excited.
Another reason?
Yes, Japan's Inokuma Yawara.
Is this Inokuma strong?
She just made her debut in an official match...
...so it's hard to measure her strength,
but upon seeing a video of her in action,
Kim was sweating profusely, jya.
That level-headed Kim, sweating?
So, Teleshikova.
This is the Yawara Inokuma
that you asked to see.
Thank you very much. I shall
return to my training.
What's wrong, Teleshikova?
That little girl can't possibly
be a worthy opponent?
I've never been so excited in my life.
I really feel very happy to do judo,
from the bottom of my heart.
It's amazing that you do judo and
you're a top model, Ms. Belkens.
Modeling is my business. Judo is
just one of my hobbies.
I can win because I have the luxury to do so.
Oh, Ms. Belkens, did you hear about
the news of a rising star in Japan?
Yawara Inokuma.
Yes, she excites me, for a change.
An exciting life... that's the key to my beauty.
The women's judo world is brimming
with excitement, jya.
Korea's Kim.
Soviet's Teleshikova.
Belgium's queen, Belkens.
And, one more, Canada's giant..!
Are the rumors about the relationship true?
How is your every day life with him?
The viewers want to know about this!
He's just her friend, and she's not
in that kind of relationship...
But, sources in LA confirm that they've
been meeting in secrecy.
Well, that's...
Please give a straight answer. The truth.
Ouch..
Matsuda-san, I got a spot for you..
Matsuda-san?
Yawara-san, is this what you really want?
To quit judo, and become a
normal college student?
Is that going to satisfy you?
Ah, Matsuda-san, what are
you doing, ditching work?
Boring.
It might be boring, but it's still
a job. It can't be helped.
Who cares about who she sticks
with or what she does.
I'm a sports writer! Just because the celebrities department is short on
people... I don't have time for that.
I'm going home! You do the rest.
N.. no way!
That's..!
Jody Rockwell.
Matsuda-san.
Why in the world?
Matsuda-san!
I'm going to pass the exam!
Oh, it's me.
It's me! ME!
Yeah, about that affair.. I'm going to
visit you tomorrow, okay?
Hey, are you all right?
So, she canceled all her matches in Canada?
I see. No, thank you.
Jody Rockwell.
Why did she come to Japan?
Matsuda!
What is this wimpy article?
How many years have you been writing?
You've been daydreaming too much these days!
We don't have the luxury to
feed lazy employees!
Got that?
If you do, then you better fix your
attitude and rewrite this piece!
N.. no, it can't be!
Let's go, Kamoda!
Hey, Matsuda!
S.. sorry, we're leaving.
W.. wait up!
You guys snuck out of school again?
Well, morning practices make us so hungry.
You guys have become more macho.
Here you go.
You're giving us extra helpings again?
Oh yeah. Since you guys raised your first victory, you need to become even stronger.
I'm rooting for you all.
O.. oba-chan!
Whatever. You guys lost by default
in the second round anyway.
Sudoh!
Oba-chan, I want a ramen, too.
Sudoh, it's your fault we lost by default.
How dare you get injured
from a senseless fight!
Yeah.
Hanazono-san fought with his fracture
and got us to win the first round.
If you weren't injured, we might've
won the second round, too.
Second round?
Why are you guys so small-minded?
If I fought, we'd be champs! Champs!
Listen up, upperclassmen dudes.
Yawara-chan endorses my strength. I'm not satisfied with winning just the first round.
We were told that we were great
by Yawara-san, too.
Her motherly instincts were just tickled.
If you're a man, impress Yawara-san
with your accomplishments!
Hey, watch it --
Whoa!
Wh.. what would you like?
Go-nin mae!
[Go-nin mae -- Five helpings]
Go-nin mae?!
Yes! Go-nin mae!
[Go-nin mae -- Five helpings]
W.. w.. what is this woman?
How is our judo club?
Well, it's okay.
Thank you very much.
That guy in the front is pretty good,
but has weak hips.
That short one in the far right corner has
sharp skills but is weak in competitions.
Astonishing! With just a short observation,
not only did he pick out my start players...
...but he also pinpointed their weaknesses!
Very terrifying, Inokuma Jigoro-sensei!
And, Inokuma Yawara, who was personally trained by him... I want her no matter what!
Sensei, your strength at such
an age is amazing.
What do you make of our judo club facilities?
No matter what toys you get, it won't
make you stronger in judo.
But, you seem to be enjoying them.
Any place would be good training for Yawara.
I think I should let you have Yawara for a while.
Th.. thank you very much!
I will make her the nation's best,
even if it costs me my life!
No, I will make Yawara-san the world's best!
Yuutenji-san.
Do you have any tea snacks?
Y.. yes. I have a mountain of ichigo daifuku.
[ichigo daifuku -- strawberry ricecakes]
I'm not going to Saikai College.
But you can go there without
taking any exams, right?
I'm jealous. I'd want to go in your place.
I want to go to Mitsuba Women's 2-year College.
It's difficult to get in there.
Why there?
I'm going to study really hard.
And mark the start of my lovely college life!
I'm going to give it my all!
Yawara-san!
Yawara-san! Something's up!
What's wrong, Kohno-kun?
As I said, something's up!
A l.. large woman is.. this f.. foreigner..!
Well, she eats five, big helpings of ramen and..!
What are you guys talking about?
Calm down and start from the top.
W.. well, this foreigner woman that eats
five helpings of ramen is waiting
in the dojo in her judo uniform.
She's saying your name, Yawara-san,
but since it's in English, we have
no idea what she's saying.
U.. umm..
"Wh.. where do you come from?"
Eh, what did she say?
Seems like she said she's from Canada.
Oh!
She understood!
Way to go!
She's still here.
There, Yawara-san. Her.
Who is she?
Don't know.
What should we say next?
I don't know. Something
about Canada, maybe?
Yawara.
Y.. yes?
U.. umm. Hello?
Wh.. what did she say?
Uh... Tatakaimashou... 'Let's fight.'
Let's fight?!
Eh? No way!
Matsuda-san.
I don't know what, but I have this feeling
that something's going to happen.
My hunch was right!
As one of the key, world-class athletes,
she must've gotten restless...
...from reading my articles and the mass
media's coverage of Yawara-san.
Who is she?
Her name is Jody Rockwell.
She's the world's over-72 kg defender.
And she recently won the World Women's
Judo Competition in Sydney, Australia.
The biggest of the big competitors!
Yawara Inokuma. I came all this way
from Canada to see you.
Come on, let's fight.
U.. umm..
So, Matsuda-san, this means..
Yeah. She came all the way to
Japan to fight Yawara-san.
Splendid! Splendid! Tres bien!
Sayaka-san is fired up.
Fired up more than ever!
No matter how many there are in the world...
... I shall be the one to defeat Inokuma Yawara!
Tanomou, Inokuma Yawara!
[Tanomou -- I challenge you!]
U.. umm..
What should I do?
866 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Oh my gosh, Grandpa!
This weird foreigner came and..
D.. delicious!
This horse mackerel is pretty tasty.
Where did you get this, Yawara?
Forget that!
Look, she even came to our house!
Oh, hey Jodei or whatever, why don't you
eat some of what Yawara cooked?
Please, Grandpa!
Next time, on "Yawara!" --
Yawara and the Blue-eyed House Guest
Another helping of the gobou no nitsuke.
[gobou no nitsuke -- boiled burdock]
This episode was sponsored by:
Julie Divola
Christopher Dewane
Scott Holliday
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Soba ni ite ne
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Otana ni naranaide