From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
Yawara Inokuma, I came all the way
from Canada to see you.
Eh? No way!
Tanomou, Inokuma Yawara!
[Tanomou -- I challenge you!]
Yawara and the Blue-eyed House Guest
Well, you know, umm...
Yawara-san versus Rockwell.
The match of the century!
You'd better get some good shots, Kamoda!
M.. Matsuda-san, you're shaking my camera.
To tell you the truth, I can't
speak English that well.
I'm studying a lot of it for my college entrance exam, so when I'm better at it, then we could -
TANOMOU!
[TANOMOU! -- I challenge you!]
She's saying "tanomou", just like a dojo raider.
All she knows are these weird
Japanese phrases.
Wh.. what's going on?
Ha.. Hanazono-san.
W.. we're in trouble!
Wha.. who is that?
She came out of nowhere to challenge Yawara-san to a match.
What?
Tanomou, Yawara.
[Tanomou -- I challenge you.]
Wh.. what's wrong, Hanazono-san?
Don't tell me that she's... Jody Rockwell!
Oh, so she's your friend?
No!
I saw her on TV.
In last year's women's judo world championship, she won the 72kg
and over class.. a champ!
She won the judo world championship?
It's dangerous, even for Yawara-san!
Tanomou, Yawara Inokuma!
[Tanomou -- I'm asking you]
Please don't ask me anything.
I don't want to fight you.
S.. stop it, you!
Okay, Inokuma, run away now.
B.. but...
Just leave it to Hanazono-san, and take off.
But..
I.. Inokuma. I, Hanazono, vow to sacrifice myself to keep her from laying a finger on you --
She's coming!
Yawara-san, hurry!
Yawara-san!
I, Hanazono, won't give up so easily --
With the three of us, we ought
to be able to stop her.
How could those guys get in the way!
I guess this dream match went down the drain.
Isn't she asking for her address?
No, we can't give her Yawara-san's address!
Screw you! We aren't gonna tell you --
Sure.
It's Tokyo, in the Setagaya-ku section...
Gosh, that scared me.
Who is she, anyway?
I wonder if the judo team is okay.
She seemed really strong..
Yawara!
I've got some good news!
Eh! You decided what?
I decided to officially enroll you
into the Saikai College.
Without even asking me first?
I wanted to see you happy face
by surprising you.
That college holds up to its reputation.
You can definitely sharpen you skills there.
Why do you...
..always, always, always...
..decide things for me on your own!
Oh, are you that happy, Yawara?
I'm angry!
Yeah, there was a thing called 'jungle gym'
that you'll probably like.
It's an athletic gym!
I suppose.
Forget it. I'm never going
to go to Saikai College.
Where do you think you're going,
you selfish child?
I'm going to take the exam for
Mitsuba 2-year Women's College.
Mitsuba? Haven't heard of it.
Does it have a judo club?
No.
It doesn't have a judo club, nor even a dojo.
And, no sweaty guys, either.
What are you going to do at a place like that?
I'm going to enjoy my college life to the fullest.
Studying, wearing pretty clothes,
and falling in love.
Stop blathering such silliness again!
It may be silly to you, but...
.. it's really important to me. I'm never
going to go to Saikai College!
I ate a mountain-full of strawberry rice
cakes that Coach Yuutenji gave me.
I can't refuse the offer after that.
Oh please. Big deal.
Don't trade me for some strawberry rice cakes.
Tanomou.
[Tanomou -- Please.]
Who's this?
She chased me all the way from school.
She wants to fight me.
Tanomou.
[Tanomou -- Please.]
Huh, she is a cut or two above anyone
that Yawara's had to fight so far.
This sounds fun. I'd like to see her strength.
Yawara, do her a favor.
No way.
You're so spineless.
Tanomou!
[Tanomou! -- Please!]
Very well. Go change into your dogi.
[dogi -- judo uniform]
Grandpa.
Hurry, Kamoda!
Gotcha!
We made it on time!
But, isn't something strange?
Oh yeah.
Why is the Gramps wearing a dogi?
Okay, give me your best shot.
Before you fight Yawara, I want to
see just how strong you are.
Wh.. what the...?
Stop it, Grandpa.
Come on!
Th.. this is..!
Grandpa!
Ma.. mairimashita!
[Mairimashita! -- I give up!]
What a gramps! He made that Rockwell cry, without even fighting her.
Oh gosh, he made her cry.
Okawari!
[Okawari -- Seconds]
Grandpa, are you really going
to take her in as a student?
This is her sixth bowl. Our food
budget will bust at this rate.
She's got something if she was able to
feel my strength in that confrontation.
She'll be a great workout partner for you.
B.. but...
Okawari!
[Okawari! -- Seconds!]
J.. Jody!
Hurry up, Yawara!
J.. Jody, I was studying for the
exam until 4am this morning.
I haven't slept much.
Oh, lack of sleep isn't good.
"Kids who sleep, grow."
56. 57. 58. 59. 60. 61. 62. 63. 64. 65. 66. 67.
Oh no. If I keep this up, I'll fail the exam.
If I fail to pass Mitsuba College's exam...
56. 57. 58. 59. 60. 61. 62. 63. 64. 65. 66. 67.
..I might be forced into Saikai College!
Jody, how long are you staying here?
Yes, for a while.
I became Jigoro-sensei's student.
Sensei is very strong.
But, you're strong too, Yawara.
Until I fight you, I'm not going back to Canada.
Belgium
Absolutely beautiful.
You've become even more glamorous
since I last saw you.
You shine as brilliantly as a diamond.
And you stand proud and
elegant like a crimson rose.
None of the women here can stand a chance against your gleaming beauty.
I suppose it's true.
Your father has helped me out a lot.
Please enjoy your stay in Belgium
as much as possible.
Ambassador, I didn't come
to this country for fun.
I came here to fight Belgium's
queen of judo, Belkens.
But I hear that she's out of town.
She probably knew that I was coming,
and ran away.
Belkens is a judo athlete and
also a famous fashion model...
...so she travels around the world quite often.
No, she must have ran away.
Right, Kazamatsuri-san?
But, Sayaka-san, even if Belkens
isn't here, there's still Stelkes.
Stelkes?
Look, that woman dancing over there.
She follows Belkens in strength and skill.
She might be a rather difficult
opponent for you, Sayaka-san.
S.. Sayaka-san.
Excuse me.
S.. Sayaka-san!
You're not much of a match for me!
Well, let's dance, Kazamatsuri-san.
Y.. yes.
My reputation...
I'm going to fail.
If I keep this up, I'm going
to fail my entrance exam.
Just as I thought.
She sure is a world class defender.
The two weeks since Jodei came, Yawara has been working very hard during practice.
I'm definitely going to fail.
Okay, how about "Oonin no Ran"?
Umm, 1467.
Post-meal workout, Yawara.
I'm going to fail.
Frequently.
"Shiba shiba"?
How about "hounding"?
Tanomou, Yawara!
Following, stalking.
Bus is no good.
Walking exercise to the house.
Survive, Yawara.
Yawara-san seems to have a handful.
Yeah.
"Desperate." Beyond hope.
Sorry, but I won't workout with her anymore.
I'm not going to open this no matter
how much she calls for me!
Tanomou!
Yawara, tanomou!
Yawara, let's train some more.
Fail. I'm going to fail.
Fail...
Inokuma-san.
Yawara. Yawara.
In deep sleep, Inokuma-san?
Yes. No, what page do I read from?
Don't bother. You're probably already
set to enroll in Saikai College with
a judo scholarship, right?
Which means, that my class is
meaningless to you, right?
No. That's not true.
Whatever. Read page 86 of
the textbook, Nakagawa-kun.
Yes.
Let's fight. Tanomou, Yawara.
Jodei.
You want to fight Yawara that badly?
Wh.. what?
Cigarettes are a no-no.
You won't grow if you do.
What the hell?
None of your business, stupid.
Why you!
Women's
change room
Inokuma-kun!
There's trouble. A weird foreigner is out behind the gym, calling your name.
Y.. you did all this?
Yes. When I told them that cigarettes
are bad, they wanted to fight me.
S.. someone, bring the stretchers.
I can't believe this.
Don't worry, I didn't use all my force.
Go home.
Go back to Canada.
I don't want to fight you. I don't want to do judo.
I'm studying for the entrance exams right now, so don't cause any trouble!
Don't wake me up so early!
Why'd you chase her away?
I'm asking you why you chased a girl that
came all the way from Canada away?
She was a nice person, huh, even though
she ate 5 helpings worth of rice.
Okawari.
[Okawari -- Seconds]
The dining room seems so
empty all of a sudden.
That's not the point.
She studied Japanese really hard,
so that she could fight you.
She must've thought that you'd fight her
if she was able to say it right.
Ohayou.
[Ohayou -- Good morning]
Konnichiwa.
[Konnichiwa -- Good afternoon]
She was studying Japanese
every night until daybreak.
Konnichiwa.
She was studying Japanese
every night until daybreak.
S.. so she didn't sleep, studied all night, and went to early morning practices like me?
And yet, she was able to speak Japanese
so well in such a short time?
I studied English really hard, too,
but I can't speak it that well.
Her strong desire to have a match with
you gave her the edge over you.
Your petty desire to study for the entrance
exam is nothing compared to her desire.
Jody!
I forgot something.
What's wrong, Yawara?
I'm so sorry, Jody.
I said such mean things to you.
I'm so sorry.
Let's do a match, Jody!
Jody!
She took the bait.
Bow!
859 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Finally the match, Yawara!
Against a world class athlete!
It seems like things out turning out
just like you planned, Grandpa.
If you beat Jodei, there's no doubt
that you're the world's best.
Actually, I don't have the time to do this.
I'm falling behind in my studies, too.
Don't just stand there, Yawara. We're about
to start. Hurry up and go change.
Next time on "Yawara!" --
"Let's Fight, Yawara"
I'll do an okuri eri jime on you if you don't.
[okuri eri jime -- sliding collar lock]
This episode was sponsored by:
Mark A. Geller
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental