kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Yawara Inokuma, I came all the way
from Canada to see you.
56, 57...
I'll fail. If I keep this up,
I'll fail the entrance exam.
Why'd you chase her away?
She studied Japanese really hard,
so that she could fight you.
She must've thought that you'd fight her
if she was able to say it right.
S.. so she didn't sleep, studied all night, and went to early morning practices like me?
Jody!
What's wrong, Yawara?
I'm so sorry, Jody.
I said such mean things to you.
I'm so sorry.
Let's do a match, Jody!
She took the bait.
Let's Fight, Yawara!
This is bad, Matsuda-san.
We're like burglars.
If we keep doing this, we'll get
arrested for trespassing.
Stop bickering and get your butt up there.
You idiot! Using my face as a stepladder..!
Gimme a hand here. Now, pull hard.
That Jody Rockwell is at
the Inokuma household.
The 72kg heavyweight world-class defender, Jody Rockwell, and Inokuma Yawara...
... are under one roof, so there
has to be something going on.
You're such a pervert.
What's going on in there then?
You're such a... such a...
If my hunch is right, something's
going on for sure.
We don't even get paid overtime for this...
Oh.. oh gosh!
Matsuda-san, Yawara-san and
Rockwell are f.. finally --
You're too loud. Come on,
get the camera ready.
Sneaking around again?
You hyenas!
M.. Matsuda-san.
H.. hey there.
Stop standing there and come here!
S.. sorry! We won't sneak
around anymore! Forgive us!
Sit there.
G.. Grandpa?
That line of the tatami will be
the boundary. Understand?
I see. The line referee.
You're there.
Sit up straight now.
Yes.
Oh?
That's a nice watch for a measly salary.
Th.. thank you.
The time limit is four minutes.
Keep your eyes peeled for that.
I.. I will.
Okay, we can start the match now.
Bow!
Umm, Matsuda-san.
Please don't put it in the paper.
O.. of course I'll splash it on the
front page as an exclusive scoop!
Not! I won't ever do that.
Promise? I don't want to be
troubled or bothered by it.
Wait up! What's that supposed to mean?
When did I ever give you trouble?
All the time.
How could you think like that? I always try my hardest to think and do what's best for you -
W.. well, you know...
Anyway, please don't cover this story.
You don't need to tell me twice.
You aren't getting away with this.
It's all settled. You can fight
all you want, Yawara.
And so... Bow!
Begin!
Darn!
I can't even cover this story, but if Yawara-san happens to win this match...
...it will be quite a feat!
Yawara, I'm very happy to come to Japan.
I can finally test your true strength.
It's the same as Jigoro-sensei.
There are no gaps to step into.
If I step in randomly, I'll be in trouble.
But, I came here just for this fight.
Not for a staring match.
I don't know what will happen, but I'm coming!
J.. jyogai.
[yogai -- Out of bounds]
That was close.
She was about to score an
ippon victory from me.
Yawara. This girl is.. very, very strong.
Jody. She's... strong.
Her look's changed.
I've never seen Yawara-san
with that look in her eyes.
Flipping out, huh, Yawara.
The world has strong people like her.
You're still just a small fish in a small pond.
Begin!
Tokunaga.
Y.. yes?
Are we not at the final destination of my around-the-world training tour, Seoul, yet?
We're almost there, Miss.
You keep saying that.
Go tell the pilot to fly faster.
B.. but...
"The Sayaka" plane is already
going as fast as it can, Miss.
I'm so bored.
Kazamatsuri-san.
What were you thinking about for so long?
The same thing as you, Sayaka-san.
Even as we speak, Inokuma Yawara
is getting stronger by the minute.
At least, that's what I feel.
We'll start training now.
Make preparations, Tokunaga.
Preparations? But how?
Clear away the junk here and
make this space into a dojo.
B.. but..
Right now.
Yes.
Get moving, Tokunaga.
Miss...
Yuko!
[Yuko -- partial 5 points]
Pay attention, timekeeper. It's out of bounds.
Right.
Yawara-san is forcefully attacked.
Is it that hard to go against
a world level athlete?
Begin!
Oh no!
Oh man!
If that giant completes the tate shihoh gatame, it'll be impossible to break free!
[tate shihoh gatame -- vertical 4-corner hold]
She's pinned! There's no way out!
Quit whining, timekeeper.
It's an osae komi. Time it for 30 seconds.
[osae komi -- pindown]
Y.. yeah.
But at this rate, Yawara-san will lose.
If she does lose this bad, then she deserves it.
She should lose big at least once and
realize the harsh reality of fights.
B.. but, wait..
Keep your distance, assistant referee.
What's the time?
10 seconds past.
Why aren't you concerned?
Yawara-san's about to lose for the first time.
Fine.
That's why I let her fight Jodei in the first place.
Time?
15 seconds past.
How about it, Kim Yonsku athlete.
Will you accept the fight?
Hon'ami Sayaka.
Now I remember.
Inokuma Yawara defeated your
sorry little rich girl butt, right?
Translator, what did she say?
Gee, I shouldn't translate that for you.
You came all the way to Seoul to get
your butt kicked by me, right?
I shouldn't translate that for you, either.
I'd be more than happy to take you on!
This girl barks way too much and irritates me.
She must be really scared of losing to me.
Not really, but it shouldn't
be translated anyway.
Begin!
Yawara doesn't have enough
guts to break the hold.
It's punishment for not practicing
seriously enough these days.
She's been taking it too easily after winning that petty Martial Arts Hall Championship.
What's the time?
20 seconds past.
What! It's already 20 seconds!
She b.. broke free.
Whoa! She did it!
And you thought she'd lose!
This is interesting.
Now she's finally serious.
Serious?
So she wasn't serious until now?
Of course not.
The match against Tohdoh Yuki and at the Martial Arts Hall was all play for her.
Play?
Yuko!
[Yuko -- partial 5 points]
I'm thrilled!
This is the first time I fought
a strong person like you!
Let's have more fun!
She was able to try an ude-garami
from that off- balance position!
[ude-garami -- entangled armlock]
She's really amazing!
I was about to get joint-locked by her.
She's finally met her match.
Yawara's encountered a strong opponent for the first time, so she's actually enjoying it.
Waza-ari!
[Waza-ari -- semi 7 points]
How strong!
Yawara-san was that strong?
Kinda late to notice that.
Well, in all her matches so far, she threw her opponents as soon as they touched her, so..
..it's the first time I've seen such a
fired-up Yawara-san in a match.
That's..!
Of all the grappling style martial arts, Korean wrestling has the closest in-fighting style.
Unlike Japanese wrestling (sumo), in which the opponent is just pushed out of bounds...
...Korean wrestling is a power throw game.
Kim's judo style incorporates Korean wrestling.
She's hard to beat, even for Sayaka-san.
Yuko!
[Yuko -- partial 5 points]
She's struggling.
Of all her matches in her around-the-world fighting tour, this is her biggest struggle.
She's so exponentially strong!
Eii! You're so loud.
This is still nothing.
Still nothing?
Look, she still can't get an ippon victory even after whipping out all those moves.
That big idiot.
B.. but, her opponent is a world champ.
Why can't you be nice for once and
praise her for doing so well?
Too soft. You're so soft.
That's why you can't get better than being a third-rate reporter at a third-rate newspaper.
That's none of your business.
How can I praise her if she hasn't accomplished her objectives?
When she becomes a world champ, with an Olympic gold medal and the National Achievement Award, then -
Then what?
I'll finally praise her.
Inokuma Yawara wasn't strong.
You're too weak.
Translator, what did she say?
I shouldn't translate that for you, either.
Sayaka-san, that's not what you
should be thinking about.
She's had it!
Yuko!
[Yuko -- partial 5 points]
Excellent!
She retaliated against Kim's
speedy combo moves.
Sayaka-san's become so much stronger.
I've got you now!
Are you okay, Jody?
I'm okay.
It's not good to worry about the
opponent during a match, Yawara.
Here I come!
Let's stop, Jody.
Your arm is seriously injured.
Take care of your arm.
Don't ruin your arm over a practice match.
Look, i.. it's okay! Yawara, let's fight!
No.
You can't fight at full-strength anymore, Jody.
End of match!
A draw!
I came all the way... from Canada!
To fight you, Yawara!
Because of Jodei's injury, this match is nulled.
A draw!
I've never had so much fun
doing judo until now!
Please, fight me, Yawara!
Yawara, please!
Jody..
This is the first time I've ever had fun, too.
So, next time..
Next time?
When your arm is healed,
let's fight again, okay?
At a competition somewhere.
R.. really? Yawara?
Yes. I promise.
Again, at a competition, somewhere!
She promised!
You hear that?
Oh yeah!
For real?
Yes.
I really hate you.
I'll kick your butt in an official
competition next time.
Translator, what did she say?
I shouldn't translate that for you, either.
I really hate this person.
I'll beat her the next time around.
I really shouldn't translate that for you, either.
Miss!
Sayaka-san!
Is it really okay for us to be treated for dinner?
Yawara, you're a strong judo athlete
and a very good cook.
Would you like seconds, Matsuda-san?
They're probably gonna ask us not to do a story on tonight's match by treating us to dinner.
So basically, we're being bribed.
Stop being so immature, Matsuda-san.
So, Matsuda-san, you're finished?
H.. hey, wait up!
I never said I was done.
Then, stop complaining and enjoy the meal.
You shouldn't fight with your boyfriend like that.
B.. boyfriend?!
This kind of guy isn't my boyfriend!
Don't talk about me like that!
Come on, shake hands and make up.
Matsuda-san, you're blushing. How cute!
Oww!
A third-rate sports reporter like you won't
be allowed to hold hands with Yawara.
Not even in ten.. no a hundred
thousand years from now either.
Get up, Matsuda-san.
Grandpa.
Jigoro-sensei. You're great!
Wonderful! Fantastic!
I'm fundara-stick, jya!
What the heck is that?
831 Days Until Barcelona Olympics
As soon as I thought I made a new friend,
Jody, she went back to Canada.
Jodei has a lot world level matches coming up.
You need to practice to prepare
yourself for the world.
But Jody has a wonderful boyfriend.
I'm envious.
What the heck are you thinking about?
Come on, do some matches.
You need to build up your record
for Jodei's sake, too.
When will I ever make a boyfriend?
Next time, on "Yawara" --
"See You Again, Yawara"
I'll do a kata-guruma throw on
those who don't watch.
[kata-guruma -- shoulder wheel]
This episode was sponsored by:
Josan
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Hiza wo daite miteta
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Soba ni ite ne
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Otana ni naranaide
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental