From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
This is the first time I've ever had fun, too.
So, next time..
Next time?
When your arm is healed,
let's fight again, okay?
At a competition somewhere.
R.. really? Yawara?
Yes. I promise.
See You Again, Yawara
I should go.
What's wrong, Yawara?
You don't seem too happy.
It'll be lonely without you, Jody.
No, Yawara, we'll be able to meet
again at a tournament next time.
Yeah, the whole world will be able
to see the two of you fight.
Yes.
And, we'll do our best then, too.
Promise, Yawara?
Jody, you'll do a match against the
Soviet team when you get back.
Is your injured arm all right?
No problem.
Jigoro-sensei's treatment is very good.
It'll heal completely in time.
Grandpa should've come to see you off, too.
He said he'd come by later, but...
I'm sorry, Jody.
Don't apologize.
I learned so much from Jigoro-sensei already.
He's the world's best sensei.
Yawara, I'm very envious of you.
Oh really?
We will now begin boarding for
flight 732 to Toronto at gate...
Hey, it's time.
We will now begin boarding for
flight 732 to Toronto at gate...
Well, Yawara and Matsuda, take care.
You too, Jody.
Good luck on your upcoming match.
Yawara, you need to keep your boyfriend
under your thumb, okay?
Boyfriend?
Oh please!
A guy like him is not my boyfriend!
What kind of guy am I, huh?
Don't blush too much now.
There's a big difference in the outcomes of matches if you have or don't have a boyfriend.
Y.. you don't understand...
Matsuda, take care of Yawara.
Well, until we fight again, Yawara.
Jody..
Bye!
Jody.
Jodei!
You will win, Jya
You better win the Match
against the Soviet team.
Jigoro-sensei!
Let me go!
I'm just seeing someone off!
Non-passengers aren't supposed to get this far.
How'd you get in?
So you did come for me, sensei.
Jodei, Keep winning and winning
the world level matches.
You do that, and you'll one day fight Yawara --
Enough, Gramps!
Jodei!
Jigoro-sensei.
I will.. keep winning!
She left.
Yeah.
I hope she wins the match.
I'm sure she will.
Wow, it's so pretty.
Oh yeah, an airport at night
is an ideal dating spot.
Then, it would be nice to eat somewhere
in the bay area and then..
Well, I need to go home and study.
Let's go eat something, at least.
Don't assume anything,
just because Jody said so.
I.. it's just eating. What's there to assume?
What a brat. Gosh --
Gosh, the customs inspection always
wastes our time. I hate it.
Kazamatsuri-san!
Yawara-san!
Hon'ami Sayaka!
Well, well, what a coincidence.
This restaurant is owned by my company.
Please have all you want.
But, I had no idea that you two were a couple. Isn't it a perfect match, Kazamatsuri-san?
We are not going out.
We were just sending off Jody Rockwell.
I know.
Yawara-san won't possibly date a fishy newspaper reporter like him.
I am not fishy! You're the fishy one!
Here is the caviar and ikra dish.
It must be great to have an energetic
boyfriend, Yawara-san.
I told you he's not.
But, to think that Jigoro-sensei took in
that Jody Rockwell as his student...
Jigoro-san teaches only really strong students.
Unlike a certain someone
who got rejected by him.
Oh, I'm very relieved to think that I didn't
get that weirdo as my sensei.
Uhh, have you decided what to order, sir?
How am I supposed to read this bad, worm-scribbled writing?
Uhh, it isn't worm scribbling. It's in French.
Just give me the best tasting food then.
Hah?
You guys serve good food, right?
When I asked the taxi driver where to
get good food, he brought me here.
So, would you like the chef's choice, then?
Sure, give me the extra large helping
of the shufu's choice.
[shufu -- house wife]
Yes.
Yeah, even I was taken aback by that.
Now that's quite a gathering.
And, what was the outcome of the
fight against Jody Rockwell?
It was incredible!
Yawara-san was leading the whole way.
She handled Jody's giant body with ease and attacked continuously like a storm, then...
But, she was really strong.
The match ended in a draw.
Oh, that's it?
So it turns out that you couldn't
get an ippon victory from her?
Pathetic.
No she's not! Because of Jody's injury,
she canceled the match.
That's just an excuse.
But, during the same time period, I've become stronger than Yawara-san, right?
W.. well, yes.
Oh, you're so sure of yourself.
Absolutely.
For the past two months, we went on an
almost bloody, around-the-world training
tour to fight world class athletes.
That Sayaka on a training tour? How brave.
But, this sure is a weird miso soup.
You officially trained at the Pornalef dojo?
I took on his comprehensive training curriculum with ease.
He seldom praised people, but when
he saw how wonderful I was, he said..
Tres Bien, Jya! Tres Bien, Jya!
According to him, Sayaka-san is the most talented athlete he's developed so far.
Why does he say 'Jya' a lot?
Eh...
Oh, Pornalef-sensei is an avid follower
of Jigoro-sensei's judo style.
Eh?
My Grandpa is that famous?
It's just a horrible mistake.
Eii, what the heck are they talking about?
Seems like they're talking about me, but..
Here is the caviar and ikra dish. Huh?
U.. umm, sir?
You went against Belgium's Stelkes
and Korea's Kim Yonsku?
Yes. She flipped Stelkes in a flash.
But, against Korea's secret weapon, Kim Yonsku, the fierce match ended in a draw, leaving bitter frustration for both of them.
Let me point out that if I hadn't been tired
from the plane rides, I would have taken
her down in less than 10 seconds.
She was rather lucky.
I have become really strong.
Many times more than the previous
match in the Martial Arts Hall.
Yawara-san, you no longer come
close to being my rival.
G.. good for you.
Whatever. You may have become stronger, but Yawara-san's strength is way more than that.
Oh, shall we find out now?
Right, Yawara-san?
Not on your life.
Oh, so you're scared of me?
Don't sweat it.
Grandpa!
Jigoro-sensei!
Jigoro-san!
I heard it all. Don't get ahead of yourselves.
Settle the match in an official tournament.
What's this?
Yawara's tournament schedule.
I've entered her in all of them.
What!?
From small ones to large ones.
10 tournaments in 3 months!
I can't believe it!
I'm not doing any tournaments.
Didn't you promise?
Eh?
You promised to do a match with Jodei, right?
You've only been in Just one
official tournament so far.
The tournaments that Jodei does
are world class leveled ones.
You think a rookie with no substantial
record like you can participate in
those world class tournaments?
If you want to keep the promise
with Jodei, do the tournaments!
Do them and do some more, compile
a winning record, then get in a world
class tournament to fight Jodei!
B.. but, I have to study for the entrance exams..
Oh, okay.
So you're the type of kid that
breaks promises just like that.
Okay, okay.
I'm fine with it, but if Jodei hears about it, there's no saying how sad she'll be.
Probably sad, and dejected...
..oh, I can just feel her pain!
Yawara-san!
If you want to fight Yawara, just do one
of the tournaments on her schedule.
There's a lot to choose from.
Yawara-san!
Wait, Yawara-san!
What are you going to do?
As Jigoro-san said, you don't have
enough official records to be able
to fight Jody in a tournament.
If you don't do anything, then it'll take a long time before you can fulfill your promise.
You're going to try to enter the Mitsuba 2-year Women's College, housekeeping major, right?
If you follow that tournament schedule,
you'll surely fail the exam.
Maybe you should take back your promise?
Maybe I should.. try it.
I can't possibly break a promise with Jody, who came all the way from Canada just to fight me.
You sure?
So, you're not going to study for the
entrance exams and enter Saikai
College as a scholarship athlete?
I'll study for the exams, too.
I'll study and do the tournaments for Jody.
I think I should try to do everything I want to do.
Everything you want to do?
You've always been avoiding judo,
but you want to fight Jody?
I'm not sure, but when I fought Jody,
it was the first time..
..I felt a sort of excitement from judo, and, well..
..so, I want to fight Jody one more time.
Just Jody.
She's fired up.
It's still a small flame, but Jody Rockwell definitely started a fire within Yawara-san.
Ippon!
[Ippon -- victory]
Champion! Inokuma Yawara, first degree black belt, is the Ruby Women's Judo Cup Champion.
As with the Oshiuri Cup tournament,
she won with all ippon victories.
The invincible Inokuma!
Jigoro's secret notebook
This wasn't much of a tournament,
but one win so far.
Next is the Magatama Cup, five days from now.
If Yawara wins all 10 tournaments within 3 months, her reputation will skyrocket.
This plan is infallibly successful.
But, why did Yawara agree
to this setup so easily?
If she doesn't do these 10 tournaments,
she can't be in a world tournament.
And her promise with Jodei would be broken...
..what a great setup!
How can she participate in
such a minor tournament?
Even if I wanted to fight her, I can't possibly lower myself to be in this kind of tournament.
My reputation would be ruined.
Let's go home, Kazamatsuri-san.
Champion, Inokuma Yawara athlete.
Yawara-san.
Isn't it amazing?
Compared to the match against Rockwell,
she won this cup without even trying.
Just as I thought.
About what?
Yawara-san is doing too much.
She probably pulled an all-nighter yesterday, studying for exams.
Eh?
She got first place after doing an all-nighter?
Her execution wasn't as sharp as usual.
She doesn't understand how
important sleep is for athletes.
You're going to break down if you
keep this up, Yawara-san.
33 times.
You yawned 33 times while you're with us.
No boys will approach you.
I know you have to study, but staying up
all night will make you ugly.
Hey, tomorrow's Sunday. Maybe we
should go out to do something.
Like eat lunch at a French restaurant.
You've got to come for a change, Yawara.
Tomorrow is the Magatama Cup.
I'm sorry, tomorrow I have..
A date, right?
You going on a date with
Kazamatsuri-san, right?
N.. no.
Inokuma.
Hanazono-kun.
Inokuma, I heard that you won the
Ruby Cup with all ippon victories.
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Yawara, you still doing judo?
Well, sort of.
Tomorrow is the Magatama Cup, right?
Good luck.
Oh, so it's not a date. I see.
You're finally devoting yourself to judo, huh?
Inokuma, my heart is very full. You taught me that dreams come true through effort.
Umm, Hanazono-kun..
I will also pursue judo like you.
And.. and..
..if I get into Saikai College with you,
I want to ask you...
Oh, forget it. Don't worry about it.
Well, good luck.
Musashiyama. Fight-oh, fight-oh.
There, Yawara-chan, throw her now!
Honey, rewind it back so we can watch it again.
Okay, okay.
It gets better the more we watch it.
I still can't believe it.
Oh yeah.
Oh, Yawara-chan. It's so great to see the girl that we saw growing up fight so bravely on TV.
You're so bad, Jigoro-san. Hiding her
from the public for such a long time.
But, this match is nothing.
The true objective is the Olympic Gold Medal.
Gold Medal?!
A gold Medal, huh? That's big.
But if it's Yawara-chan, maybe.. just maybe..
Yes.
If it's Yawara-chan, maybe.. just maybe..
Okay, then to celebrate Yawara-chan's chance to win the gold medal, let's have a party.
Yeah, I'll make all the sushi we need.
Let's go all-out.
We should drink the famous Meisei Hell sake, and get the super deluxe sushi platter.
I'm working hard, Jody.
Are you training hard, too?
Kazamatsuri-san.
As you said, am I shining most
brilliantly when I do judo?
Am I, Kazamatsuri-san?
Geez, how late is she going stay up?
Hurry up and go to sleep already. Don't you have a tournament tomorrow?
That was a big cat.
..Yawara..
..the National Achievement Award...
We will now begin the final round
of the under 48kg class match.
I drank a bit too much last night.
Bow!
Begin!
Yawara!
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory]
That was close.
Wow!
Yawara-chan's amazing!
Well, that's two tournaments down.
But, that was sad, Yawara!
Magatama Women's Judo Cup Champion, Inokuma Yawara, first degree black belt.
As usual, she won with all ippon victories.
How long will her winning streak be?
Invincible Inokuma!
Yawara-san.
Gosh, Shin-chan.
You're glued to the TV and you're
ignoring me. I hate you!
That's not true.
I'm only interested in you.
Really?
Yeah, of course.
I'm so happy!
What's wrong, Yawara-san?
That wasn't your usual judo style.
Is something going on, Yawara-san?
Yawara-san.
What was that match all about?
What do you mean?
You spaced out a bit, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You can't go full strength on lack of sleep.
What's scarier is an injury. At that rate,
you might get seriously injured.
Don't worry about me.
You should worry about yourself staying
out all night, Matsuda-san.
You have bags under your eyes.
Well, a lot of girls do ask me out, you know.
Get some sleep already!
Say hi to your girlfriend!
Geez.
Well, back to studying.
824 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Yawara! What's with that last match?
A half-assed effort like that won't get
you any closer to fighting Jodei.
But, Grandpa..
But, schmut! How dare you
sleep during a match!
You were probably studying
for exams, weren't you?
Well..
Well, schmell! I forbid you to study!
Hey..
Hey, schmey!
Wait..
Wait, schwait, Kuwait!
Next, on "Yawara!" --
Yawara's Personal Tutor is a Love Expert.
I will drop those who don't
watch it with a tai-otoshi.
[tai-otoshi -- body drop]
This episode was sponsored by:
Julie Divola
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental