kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory]
Magatama Women's Judo Cup Champion, Inokuma Yawara, first degree black belt.
As usual, she won with all ippon victories.
How long will her winning streak be?
Maybe I should.. try it.
I can't possibly break a promise with Jody, who came all the way from Canada just to fight me.
You sure?
So, you're not going to study for the
entrance exams and enter Saikai
College as a scholarship athlete?
I'll study for the exams, too.
I'll study and do the tournaments for Jody.
I think I should try to do everything I want to do.
Don't overdo it, Yawara-san.
Yawara's Personal Tutor is a Love Expert
Eii, Yawara!
Why are you so wimpy these days?
But, Grandpa..
No buts or schmuts!
Explain to me why your performance in
the past few tournaments sucked!
I won four straight tournaments.
Is there a problem with that?
You can't fool me.
Jigoro
Memo
Your first tournament was so-so,
but in the second tournament, you
actually fell asleep during a match.
Your first tournament was so-so,
but in the second tournament, you
actually fell asleep during a match.
And in the third and fourth tournaments, the match times grew longer and longer.
In the last tournament's final round, it almost dragged on to a post-round decision...
...but you did a wimpy ippon zeoi and
barely won with an ippon victory.
But, at least I won them, right?
At least?
At least you won?
That's the problem!
When I won 5 straight National Championships in a row, my match times were less than a blink.
And people in the audience were so paralyzed with fear that they're still like that to this day.
I know.
You're great, Grandpa.
But I'm not as great as you!
Shut up!
My textbooks!
You went through my room again, didn't you?
Geez!
Give them back!
No.
It's useless to waste your time studying without sleeping all night long.
Useless?
What's useless about my exam studies?
Your already set to enroll into Saikai College.
I'm not going there!
Look, don't you ever do so poorly
in any more tournaments.
I'll keep these textbooks.
Give them back to me!
Not fair!
Geez, I have to use up my month's
allowance for these.
And, I'm the one trying to budget
the family expenses, too.
Geez!
Welcome.
Me?
Yes, I've been worried about you.
But, you weren't home when I dropped by.
I'm so glad I bumped into you at that bookstore.
Why were you worried about me?
Yawara-san, in the past few matches,
you've been lacking the usual finesse.
In fact, it's getting worse.
What's going on?
Yes?
Please bring a cake.
Give me a Charlotte Boire.
Oh, that's all?
Just studying for exams?
It's no laughing matter.
I'm sorry.
Well, please eat.
I will, thank you.
I'm staring, aren't I?
You're probably uncomfortable
with me watching you.
Not really..
I thought that perhaps you didn't feel well, but..
..I see, you're trying to get into Mitsuba
2-Year Women's College?
That's a great school.
I know a few girls --
No, I know a few good professors there.
They're all great people.
But, I don't think I can study at home anymore.
Grandpa never changes his
stubborn mind on decisions.
How about this?
I'll be your tutor.
I'll tutor you at my condo.
B.. but, I can't..
I want help you, Yawara-san.
Me?
Saikai
College
Jouyuu
Cup
Women's Judo Tournament
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory]
Incredible!
She made it to finals, just like that!
Coach Yuutenji, I didn't know
she was this great!
President, then we have no problems
with her scholarship appointment?
Not even a problem!
We'll surely win a Barcelona Olympic
gold medal for our school!
Thank you very much.
Inokuma-sensei!
Isn't Yawara-san on a roll today?
Yeah.
I've heard that she hasn't been
doing too well these days...
...but she is absolutely fabulous today!
Apparently, she seems to have gotten out
of the slump and doing rather well.
This is great! Even the president is over-joyed!
Of course he is.
Another plateful of ichigo daifuku.
[ichigo daifuku -- strawberry rice cakes]
Yes!
Inokuma-sensei, nice to meet you.
Please enroll Yawara-san into our college.
Leave it to me, President.
What are you doing?
Get him the ichigo daifuku, pronto.
[ichigo daifuku -- strawberry rice cakes]
Make it a big pile.
Certainly.
Look at that. My 'exam studies
prevention' plan succeeded!
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory]
She's back at full-strength!
She must have recovered
from that temporary slump.
But, I'm sure she hasn't given up her studies.
Why is she doing so well then?
Thanks for waiting, Yawara-san.
Yes.
That guy!
I thought something was up!
Let's go, Kamoda!
S.. sure.
Oh man!
He's taking her to his condo!
You're going right into a
dangerous trap, Yawara-san!
Yes. It isn't "have been."
Since it's a past subjunctive verb,
it's "had been".
Okay.
Then, what is this one?
Umm, would I use "have been"?
Yes.
You're doing great, Yawara-san.
Something wrong?
No, nothing.
Are you tired? Maybe we should take a break?
No, I'm okay.
But, Kazamatsuri-san, you're so gifted.
You're good at judo and you're so smart.
Well, I am gifted.. no, not that gifted.
Rather, I'm amazed at you, Yawara-san, trying to do judo and exam studying at the same time.
I'm not that great..
Have more confidence in yourself.
You can accomplish anything you set
your mind to. Really. I assure you.
Geez!
What are they doing?
It's been over 3 hours now! 3 hours!
M.. Matsuda-san, I can't breathe!
Damn, that Kazamatsuri!
Don't tell me...
Studs are so lucky.
You idiot!
Don't think so nasty!
You were thinking like that, too, Matsuda-san.
Th.. there she is!
Wait up, Matsuda-san!
Thank you very much for tutoring me
and giving me a ride home.
No problem.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Yes.
Goodnight.
Eii, that Yawara.
What is she doing all this time.. huh?
I'm home.
You stupid fool! What time do you think --
I'm sorry I'm back this late.
You're eating instant noodles again?
I'll make you a really delicious meal now, okay?
Maybe I should make pork soup?
And maybe some age-dashi tofu,
sawara teriyaki and...
Kimpira gobo, jya!
That was close.
Were you trying to crash into me?
You wouldn't be able to pay for the
damages with your measly salary.
What did you do with Yawara-san?
Why was Yawara-san at your condo?
How pathetic. Are you jealous?
N.. no way!
As a newspaper reporter, I'm just
concerned about her future!
That's what you say, but you have
feelings for her, don't you?
Why don't you just admit it?
Just shut up!
You don't have a right to say that,
since you and Hon'ami Sayaka are...
You're mistaken.
There's nothing going on between
me and Sayaka-san.
Even if there was, it's none
of your business anyway.
Excuse me.
Oh, really?
So I can tell Miss Sayaka about
what happened tonight?
Wha -- w.. w.. wait..
Kazamatsuri-san.
Sayaka-san.
Do you have some time tomorrow night?
I found a wonderful Greek restaurant, so...
I'm sorry, but..
Aww...
An old high school friend is dropping
by my place tomorrow.
I.. it's a guy!
A guy friend, of course.
He's a pretty hideous guy, too.
Please, don't trouble me.
Sayaka-san is really possessive
in the first place.
Hmph.
I didn't do anything to Yawara-san.
I was just tutoring her.
Tutoring?
Yeah.
I was just trying to help her
with her exam studies.
Oh, is that it? No wonder.
Of course. That's the only reason
she'd go to your place anyway --
Wait! Either way, she's in danger!
Why do have such a happy face, Yawara?
No reason.
I know.
You were thinking about
Kazamatsuri-san, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
You're so lucky, especially at this
depressing time of exam studying....
No, no.
Don't hide it from us.
I'm not.
Look at that relaxed smile.
I'm so jealous!
Tell us the truth.
Oww, oww.
Kyoko, you look serious.
Hey!
Matsuda-san?
No, Matsuda-san.
It's a past conjunctive verb, so it's "had been."
R.. really? So it is!
You spelled it wrong, too.
I'm sorry.
And you call yourself a tutor? Liar.
Well, I guess high schools are
much tougher these days.
H.. hey, we should study geography.
That was one of my stronger subjects.
There aren't any geography questions
on college entrance exams.
O.. oh, that's right.
Read this part then.
As mat per fure in...
Your pronunciation is bad, too.
Oh, look at the time.
I'm going home.
Going home? But we just started.
Just started? You call this tutoring?
I'm trying for Mitsuba College, and
keeping a promise with Jody.
Don't drag me down like this.
H.. hey. I'll take you home.
No thank you.
Don't hold back.
I can bike you home really quickly.
I refuse to ride with a biker that
dumps his bike into a river.
I'm never going to have you
tutor me, ever! Goodbye!
H.. hey!
You suck, Matsuda Kousaku. Straighten up!
I will not get depressed over this!
[imitating the gesture of when
the Masked Rider morphs]
Darn!
I apologize for being mean
just now. Excuse me.
Hey, what's "regret"?
How should I know?
Why don't you ask Kazamatsuri-san?
Why you --
You!
Ch.. Chief.
Matsuda, I thought you were unusually
diligent, but what were you doing?
Oh, I am sorry.
You're gonna help out with the
proofreading. All night!
Oh my God.
Don't "oh my god" me, you idiot!
Now get to work!
"But, it is often difficult to distinguish a person's true feeling," Tom Buchanan said to me.
That's perfect. You're excellent, Yawara-san.
No, you teach very well, Kazamatsuri-san.
No, you're very smart.
You won't have any problems
getting into Mitsuba College.
I don't know.
But, Kazamatsuri-san, why are
you so good with English?
Once, I was very fascinated by the works
of a certain American poet.
I wanted to read the poems in the original language, so I really studied English.
Poems?
"We loved with a love that was more than love."
She was just a child. And so was I.
In this coastal kingdom, we loved
each other regardless.
We loved each other more than love could.
Just a few lines from Edgar
Allen Poe's "Anabel Lee".
Like this poem, I'm probably looking...
for that single, eternal woman to love.
Or something like that. Was that
a little pretentious?
Not really..
Yes?
Shin-chan. It's me!
Holy! M.. Mariko!
Last time was so good!
I've been thinking about you ever since then.
I.. I'm grateful for all your help!
Can I?
Oh sure.
Can I come over now?
Oh really?
NO!
I.. I'm bedridden with a really
bad headache right now.
Maybe next time?
Umm, I'll..
Yes?
Make some tea.
Tea, huh?
Oh no!
The cup with the lipstick stain of White Lily College girl, Megumi, is still in the kitchen.
Hello? Shin-chan? Shin-chan?
Umm, Kazamatsuri-san's cup is...
..oh, is that it?
Hey, that's okay.
You must be tired from doing
judo and exam studying.
I'm actually very energized. I'm not tired at all.
No, no. Just sit there.
You're very nice, Kazamatsuri-san.
Well, you can't waste any time.
Just do these problems for now.
Yes?
Yukari!
You're there, right, Shinnosuke-san?
Let me in.
N.. no, not today. I have a cold.
Oh my.
Then I'll make you all nice and warm!
N.. no, I don't want to pass this on to you.
I'll give you a call, okay?
Aww, I suppose.
Well, here you go.
I just took it off.
Think about me when you see that, okay?
Well, take care.
Are you all right?
I'm okay. Don't worry.
Just go back and study, okay? Okay?
Yes.
Hello?
Shin-chan, this is Mariko.
I thought I heard a girl's voice
in the background.
It's my little sister. My little sister.
Weren't you an only child, Shin-chan?
My dad had an illegitimate child. He's so bad!
Kazamatsuri-san, I'll go make some tea.
It's all right. Really.
You should do those problems..
I already did them.
And, I want to help you out, too, Kazamatsuri-san.
I appreciate the thought.
Come on, let's get back to studying.
You're an excellent student, Yawara-san.
Kazamatsuri-san!
Let's take your friend to eat out with us..
Hello? Shin-chan?
What's going on?
Shin-chan?
817 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Why? Why is Sayaka-san..?
Are Sayaka-san and Kazamatsuri-san actually..?
That Yawara.
Thinking about that Kaza-MIDORI again, huh?
Come on, Yawara!
Hurry up, sit down and watch the TV!
Jodei's match is about to start!
What? Jody!
Cheer her on!
Look at Jodei fight and settle down for once.
Next time, on "Yawara!" --
Love, Exam Studies, and Yawara's Feelings.
I'll do a sankaku jime on
those who don't watch.
[sankaku jime -- triangle choke]
This episode was sponsored by:
Tom Smith
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Hiza wo daite miteta
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Stand by me
Soba ni ite ne
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental
Otana ni naranaide