From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
I appreciate the thought, okay?
Kazamatsuri-san!
Let's take your friend to eat out with us..
Love, Exam Studies, and Yawara's Feelings
What's happening?
O.. Oh!
Well, Yawara-san is at Kazamatsuri-san's
place again.
Darnit, that Kazamatsuri!
Just because he's a little good at English..!
Matsuda-san, is this really sports coverage?
Seems more to me like the thing
you hate -- a celebrity stakeout.
Kamoda.
Good job. It's my turn now.
Geez, when it's about Yawara-san, your job and personal feelings get so mixed up.
The safety of the superstar of
the century is in question!
This is an outright news coverage!
What the heck are you thinking, anyway?
Good evening, Sayaka-san.
Well, what a coincidence!
It's going to be an interesting night!
Oh yes! We should all go out to dinner!
I recently found a great restaurant.
How about it, Sayaka-san?
You're such a DOROBO-NEKO.
[Dorobo-neko -- cat thief]
You want someone else's thing that badly?
How immoral!
I was just...
Yes, she couldn't study at her house, so I offered to tutor her in my room, that's all.
What an obvious lie.
So you want Kazamatsuri-san,
no matter what?
That's not what I wanted to do.
Now listen carefully.
Kazamatsuri-san will graduate soon and become part of the Hon'ami Group.
In an executive position, too.
Do you know why?
It's because he'll take over the
Hon'ami Group someday.
Taking over Hon'ami Group...
you know why that is, right?
It's because Kazamatsuri-san is my fiance!
Fiance?
Well, actually...
So, no matter what you do with Kazamatsuri-san, it's of no use.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Thank you for tutoring me.
U.. umm..
Yawara-san.
Goodnight.
Brrr, it's so cold!
Y.. Yawara-san?
Yawara-san, what's wrong?
Wh.. what's wrong, Yawara-san?
Yawara-san?
Yawara-san!
Kazamatsuri, why you...!
What did you do to Yawara-san!?
Oh, the third-rate newspaper reporter.
Hon'ami Sayaka! You were here, too?
Your girlfriend is quite a girl.
Quite a girl?
Wh.. what the heck is that?
Kazamatsuri-san, I won't tell
Daddy about today.
But, don't ever get lured by her again.
Please keep your guard up.
Well then, goodbye.
Kazamatsuri!
What did you do to Yawara-san?
She was crying!
I don't need to discuss private matters
with newspaper reporters.
Y.. You better not have done anything heinous!
How rude! I'm not that kind of guy!
Besides, with Sayaka-san here,
I couldn't have possibly done that!
You sure?
I'm sure!
You really sure?
Really sure!
You really really sure?
Enough!
Anyway, this has nothing to do with you.
Go home! Goodbye!
W.. wait up!
Darnit...!
Kazamatsuri-san..
Kazamatsuri-san, you were
Sayaka-san's fiance?
Seishin-kan Women's Judo Cup
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory!]
Champion! Inokuma Yawara, 1st Degree, won this tournament with all ippon victories!
Well, at least she won, but..
..I don't recall teaching her such reckless judo!
Inokuma-san, you're incredible!
Since your debut, you've won
7 tournaments so far!
You're on a roll!
Are you going to run straight
to the Barcelona Olympics?
I don't really care about the Olympics..
You're now invincible in Japan.
Is the world the next level --
I won't let you do that.
Ho.. Hon'ami Sayaka!
Sayaka-san.
I've let Inokuma-san run loose a bit too long.
So I entered the next tournament.
Enjoy this moment, it won't last much longer.
Will it be her revenge for the
Martial Arts Hall Defeat!?
Hon'ami Sayaka's
Bold Challenge
to the
Undefeated
Inokuma Yawara
That Miss sure is something!
"After the around-the-world training
tour, Inokuma Yawara isn't
intimidating enough," it says.
Talk about confidence! But,
that upfront confidence!
I really like that about that Miss.
Yawara! You can learn a lot from her attitude!
Grandpa, hurry up and eat.
I need to go take a practice exam.
Oh, what is this?
She said that she'd take revenge
and defeat you in under a minute!
If you're not going to eat,
then I'm clearing the table.
Hold it!
Yawara! You aren't thinking clearly these days.
You're so into the newspaper that you
haven't touched your breakfast yet!
Nope. I'm not just talking about now.
Even in yesterday's matches, you were
doing some reckless throws.
No, I was doing okay in those matches.
You're having boy problems, aren't you?
Gulp!
Gotcha, didn't I? It shows clearly on your face.
No, it doesn't, Grandpa.
What are you talking about?
Are you troubled by that KazaMIDORI?
KazaMI--? It's Kazamatsuri-san!
Kazamatsuri, KazaMIDORI, same difference!
Stop! Quit worrying about that kind of guy!
He turns to you, then turns to Miss Sayaka, and maybe many other girls, too.
That's a perfect KazaMIDORI for you!
[KazaMIDORI -- weather vane]
Kazamatsuri-san has nothing to do with this!
Forget him.
Just think about your upcoming
match against Hon'ami Sayaka.
Don't underestimate that Miss' tenacity.
Geez!
Decide if you're gonna eat or read!
I'm leaving soon.
You talk just like your dead grandma,
my beloved Kaneko.
Geez..
Jody!
Wh.. why are you so loud?
Grandpa, look!
Jody's match against the Soviet team
is going to be televised today!
Canada vs. Soviet, Montreal Invitational (live)
Jody's match against the Soviet team
is going to be televised today!
So it is!
I can't wait to see this!
No!
This is the first time I've had
so much fun doing judo!
Please, fight me, Yawara!
Yawara, please!
Jody..
Yawara!
This is the first time I've ever had fun, too.
When your arm is healed,
let's fight again, okay?
At a competition somewhere.
Really?
Yes.
Jody..
My head is pounding.
Every time I take a practice exam,
I lose even more confidence.
How'd you do, Yawara?
Horrible.
Well, let's go play around for a change!
Let's go eat a huge cake!
I need to go straight home.
A date, right?
You're having a date with Kazamatsuri-san, right Yawara?
Kazamatsuri-san?
Kazamatsuri-san is my fiance.
No, that's not it.
Oh, it's alright.
During the desolate exam-study season,
you need to have that kind of oasis.
I want a heart-fluttering oasis like that, too.
That's not what I'm doing! I need
to watch something on TV --
Hey!
Matsuda-san.
I was waiting for you.
You know about today's TV coverage of
the Canada vs. Soviet match, right?
I wanted to get a comment from you.
Me?
Yeah. I didn't feature this yet,
but in tomorrow's headline...
It's gonna read, "Jody Rockwell And
Inokuma Yawara Are Destined Rivals!"
What?
Yawara, you're going to date HIM today?
You gave up on Kazamatsuri-san
and went for THAT guy?
THAT guy?
What do you mean by "THAT guy"? Huh?
I am not going out with THIS kind of guy.
THIS kind of guy?
I see, Yawara.
You got dumped by Kazamatsuri-san and recklessly went out with him, right?
You need to take better care of yourself.
They're not pulling any punches, are they?
Yawara-san!
Kazamatsuri-san.
Yawara-san, I apologize for the other day.
I wanted to make it up to you today.
Make it up?
Don't tell me you really did
something to her the other day!
You again?
I told you that this was a private matter.
Let's go, Yawara-san.
W.. wait now!
Excuse us.
Wait!
Darnit!
Y.. Yawara-san!
Yawara-san, where do you think
you're going with Kazamatsuri?
Aren't you going to watch today's match?
It's Jody's match. You gotta watch it!
Jody's match! The girl that got you
fired up for the first time!
Don't you understand?
You better watch it!
Darnit!
Y.. Yawara-san, watch Jody's match!
You better watch it!
I'd love to meet her in private, too.
Are you mad about the other day?
Not really..
The executive position in the Hon'ami Group, as Sayaka-san said, is true.
But, it has nothing to do with
my relationship with her.
Yawara-san, your presence in my
heart gets bigger all the time..
..ever since I first met you.
So, I didn't want you to misunderstand anything, like that incident the other day.
Kazamatsuri-san.
I don't want to mislead you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Thank you.
Well then, I should take you
to a nice restaurant.
It hasn't been covered in a magazine yet,
but the chocolate cake is delicious.
It's Jody's match! You gotta watch it!
After that, how about a movie?
You need to have a little fun now and then.
I.. need to watch Jody's match.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Oh. It's okay.
Then, I'll give you a ride home.
But, I won't make it home in time like this...
Then, I'll see you later.
I'm sorry for having to turn you down.
Please don't worry about it.
But promise to meet with me next time, okay?
Yes.
Goodbye.
Take care.
I'm home!
Grandpa, Jody's match. The match!
It's about to start.
Anyway, Yawara. Where have you been?
You're smiling from ear to ear.
N.. no, I'm not.
You were probably fooling around
with a guy, weren't you?
All during Jody's important world championship too, you fool!
I did not --
This is the Canada vs. Soviet Invitational Match, held in Montreal, Canada.
Last year's 72kg and over class,
world champion defender,
Jody Rockwell, from Canada.
Jody!
And, appearing out of nowhere,
the Soviet Women's Judo's secret
weapon, Anna Teleshikova.
Begin!
Go for it, Jody!
Rockwell went for a tai-otoshi!
[tai-otoshi -- body drop]
She got it!
Th.. this..!
What happened?
After losing her balance from an attempted tai-otoshi, Rockwell hasn't gotten up yet. [tai-otoshi -- body drop]
The referees have stopped the
time to examine the situation.
Did an accident occur?
It's no accident!
Didn't anyone see that Tele-whatever do that?
What?
Let's see the replay.
Rockwell goes for the tai-otoshi.
[tai-otoshi -- body drop]
Right here, she loses her balance and..
Oh!
Rockwell's left knee is bent the opposite way!
Jody!
What is that announcer looking at?
She didn't lose her balance!
That Tele-whatever kicked
Jodei's supporting foot!
Oh wow, Rockwell is standing up. Is she okay?
What? Jodei's left knee tendon should
have been completely snapped off.
A normal person would be
convulsing right now.
Oh no, they should stop the match!
No, Jody! Don't fight with that leg!
The match continues.
Begin!
Whoa!
Teleshikova went straight for the
injured knee for an oo-soto gari!
[oo-soto gari -- large outer reap]
Stop it! Stop it already!
You're too soft, Yawara!
This is what a real fight involves!
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory!]
Jody!
How disturbing!
Jody Rockwell has been defeated!
Soviet's Anna Teleshikova beat the world-champ defender, Rockwell,
with an oo-soto gari ippon victory!
[oo-soto gari -- large outer reap]
Don't tell me she calculated
every move for this win!
What a sight.
Rockwell is totally immobile.
She's being taken away in a stretcher.
Jody! Jody!
Jody!
810 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Yawara, hurry it up!
You're going to be late to Miss Sayaka's party.
Grandpa!
You weren't invited, Grandpa!
Wow, look at all that food!
Geez, and Jody was seriously injured, too...
Jodei will definitely recover!
And this whole, roasted chicken is delicious!
Next time, on Yawara! --
"A Shocking Invitation For Yawara!"
Another plateful of that meat
with miso sauce on it, jya!
Young chicken, dipped in sauce!
This episode was sponsored by:
Christopher Dewane
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental