kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
Ippon!
[Ippon -- Victory!]
How disturbing!
Jody Rockwell has been defeated!
Soviet's Anna Teleshikova beat the world-champ defender, Jody Rockwell, with
a splendid oo-soto gari ippon victory!
[oo-soto gari -- large outer reap]
Don't tell me she calculated
every move for this win!
What a sight.
Rockwell is totally immobile.
She's being taken away in a stretcher.
A Shocking Invitation For Yawara!
It'll take her 6 months to recover.
But even if she's healed, how long will it
take until she can do judo again...?
After all, her ligament behind
her left knee was torn off.
I guess your plan of fighting
Jody in a tournament will be
on the back burner for a while.
So what are you going to do, Yawara-san?
You still have 3 tournaments left.
I see.
But don't tell me you've given up judo.
But Jody won't be...
Don't worry. She'll come back for sure!
Did you forget, Yawara-san? How excited
you were when you fought her?
And that you wanted to fight Jody again?
That's why you need to keep doing judo.
Right?
I need to go back to my exam studies.
Excuse me.
Teleshikova's post-match interview,
describing the details of the match.
Teleshikova..
It has nothing to do with me.
Yawara-san!
W.. wait!
Please read it.
Thank you very much.
Teleshikova-san, your feelings on
defeating the tough Rockwell?
I had enough data on Rockwell.
With a strategy utilizing this data,
there was no doubt that I would win.
You're quite confident.
Now that you've defeated Rockwell, is there anyone that would be a threat to you?
Well..
There is one person that
I have been thinking about.
It's hard to tell her strength, without
having enough data on her.
Yawara Inokuma.
I want to fight Japan's Yawara Inokuma.
Unless I defeat her, I don't feel
that I'm the world's best.
Come on, Yawara!
Ippon!
Hon'ami Sayaka has made it to the finals!
She's become stronger!
Hon'ami Sayaka has become two
to three times more powerful!
She's made a great comeback since
her defeat to Inokuma Yawara!
Ippon!
Hon'ami-san, a comment please!
What do you think about Inokuma's
withdrawal from this tournament?
Err, that's..!
Yawara-san, are you watching?
You are no longer my rival or anything!
Are you so scared of losing to me? Chicken!
Yawara!
What is she doing, that stupid child!
Yawara-san didn't come, after all.
Yawara-san.
Yawara!
Where are you, Yawara!?
Come out, Yawara!
How dare you ditch the tournament!
Did you forget about your promise to Jodei?
You can't fool me when you said that your
back hurts or you have a headache!
You were all fine and dandy this morning!
Open.. up! Yawara!
Father, you're so lively, as usual.
I brought your favorites, Mutsuwan scallops and the famous Osore-zan sake.
Ta.. Tamao-san.
Oh! Mom!
I'm back.
Oh.. my.
Ya.. Yawara, you..!
Sayaka-san, what's wrong?
Including today's match,
you've been irritated lately.
I am not.. irritated!
It's Yawara-san's fault, isn't it?
Kazamatsuri-san, do you know
what next next Monday is?
Eh?
It's Miss Sayaka's birthday.
O.. oh yes, it's your birthday, right?
Umm, you'll be 19 years --
I will be 18!
How can I face my birthday..
..while I'm still lost to Inokuma Yawara..
for my 18th birthday!
While I'm still lost to her!
I can't have a "Happy" Birthday like that!
Sa.. Sayaka-san..!
Yawara..
So, this Jody-san came
all the way from Canada?
But how is she doing with that injury?
Even if she recovers, it's hard to tell
if she can ever do judo again or not.
I feel so sorry for Jody.
But that's too bad, since Jody-san
made you so excited about judo.
Not anymore.
I hate judo, since it causes
people to have serious injuries.
But because you were in that tournament,
Dad supposedly came back.
What?
I heard that a person who looked like Dad was in Aomori's Osore-zan area, so I went there.
According to Itako-san, that man said...
"I need to go to Tokyo's Martial Arts Hall. Thank you for everything."
After saying that, he disappeared.
When did that happen?
It was 2 days before your tournament
in the Martial Arts Hall.
Dad came to watch my tournament?
Yes.
That runaway son, Kojiro...
Tamao-san, can I have another drink?
Oh sure. Coming.
This is Sayaka. Good morning!
Kazamatsuri-san, do you
remember today's schedule?
Breakfast at Sayaka's at 7am,
judo practice with Sayaka at 8am.
Shopping for clothes with Sayaka at 10am.
Dance lessons with Sayaka at 11am.
Lunch at a French restaurant
with Sayaka at 12pm.
A drive with Sayaka at 1pm.
Well then, I'll see you.
No, no... NO!
If I keep this up, I won't have
time to date other girls!
Especially with Yawara-san,
since that last meeting.
I wonder if I removed all doubts from her then.
And, she did withdraw from the
tournament the other day, maybe...
Umm..
This is the Inokuma residence.
This is Inokuma. Who is this?
Umm, err...
U.. umm, I'm a fan of Inokuma
Jigoro-sensei, but..
Oh really!?
Y.. yes!
Is that so?
So what do you want? An autograph?
Y.. yes, please.
Oh.. no, I can't possibly visit you at your house!
Well, thank you, nonetheless.
Th.. that was nerve wrecking.
Oh.. yeah!
Yawara, time for practice!
Come to the dojo, now!
Grandpa.
I have to study for exams.
Don't give me that!
You don't need to study for anything!
You know what college you're going to!
I'm not going to Saikai College.
Oh, weren't you saying that there was a senior's meeting at Zen-san's?
Senior's meeting?
Oh gosh, I completely forgot! This is bad!
No!
Yawara, you better do 1000 uchi-komis
before I get back!
[uchi-komi -- repeated throw practice]
Geez, Grandpa.
For me?
The sender has paid for everything.
Thank you very much.
From Kazamatsuri
Kazamatsuri-san.
It's very sudden, but I just
had to send you flowers.
I was very worried about removing
any doubts the other day...
...since we had so little time to discuss matters.
But, I'm hoping that you
understand my feelings.
Good luck on your exam studies.
Sincerely, Kazamatsuri.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Closed for the day
Maru-zen Electronics Shop
You're late, Jigoro-san.
That's.. so.. very..
I'm home.
Oh. Yawara, there's a letter for you!
P.S. It's a casual party, so please come wearing comfortable clothing. Sayaka
And, I received this, so... yes.
What? An invitation for you?
Oh, really?
I'm going to be at that party,
so you should come also.
But, is it really alright for me to
attend Sayaka-san's party?
What are you saying?
Outside of matches, you and Sayaka-san
are good friends, right?
I see. Yes.
Then I'll see you at the party.
A.. and, thank you for the flowers.
I believe in you, Kazamatsuri-san.
Goodbye.
Kazamatsuri-san.
She's so cute.
But, Yawara-san was invited?
What is Sayaka-san thinking?
Is this okay?
Oh yes. It's fabulous!
But it's Sayaka-san's party, so maybe everyone's all dressed up...
Don't worry.
She said that it's fine to come
in comfortable clothes, right?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going.
Don't get careless.
I won't.
Well then.
Oh.
Father, where are you going?
To a party, jya!
Welcome to the party.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Thank you very much for inviting me.
Please enter.
Oh gosh! Everyone's so dressed up!
Umm, I'm going...
Yawara-san!
I've been waiting for you.
Kazamatsuri-san!
What is that Miss Sayaka thinking, inviting
the media for her dumb birthday party?
Kamoda, get some manners!
Hey, over there.
Ya.. Yawara-san!
Welcome, Yawara-san.
Sayaka-san.
Please enjoy your stay at this party.
P.S. It's a casual party, so please come wearing comfortable clothing. Sayaka
I've been had!
Gotcha.
Escorting her? How nice of you.
Well, since Yawara-san looked
so wonderful, I just had to...
Very true. She's in such comfortable clothing.
Isn't she?
Oh yes! Inokuma-sensei came here before you.
What?
Oh, Yawara, you're late.
You'd better hurry, or all the
good food will be gone.
This is the worst.
Yawara-san. Hi!
Matsuda-san.
Sayaka-san, wasn't the newspaper coverage supposed to be done by the Big 3 papers?
Sorry for being a third-rate newspaper!
Oh, Matsuda-san, that necktie
looks great on you.
"Even the packhorse driver looks
fine in proper dress," right?
No, I thought you were celebrating shichi-go-san.
[Shichi-go-san -- Children's holiday celebrating 3rd, 5th, and 7th birthdays.]
I invited them. Since today is such a special day.
What are you up to, Hon'ami Sayaka?
Thank you for attending my birthday party.
Without every one of you, I could not
have celebrated my birthday.
Please enjoy your stay.
To start off, we'll have Sayaka-sama blow
out the candles on her birthday cake.
That's Miss Sayaka for you.
Everything's so flashy.
Now we'll have Sayaka-sama's father
and also Hon'ami Group's CEO...
...Hon'ami Kinnosuke give a few comments.
Thank you very much for attending the birthday party of my only daughter, Sayaka, today.
Yawara, this snail is delicious!
We have great news, also.
Kazamatsuri-kun, please come here.
Kazamatsuri-san?
As everyone knows, Kazamatsuri-kun
is Sayaka's judo coach.
When he graduates from college next spring, he will work for the Hon'ami group.
And, he is the only son of the well-established Kazamatsuri Brewery...
...which has decided to merge
with the Hon'ami Group.
Kazamatsuri-kun's father
and mother are very elated.
These black fish eggs are also delicious.
Kazamatsuri-kun's father
and mother are very elated.
And, we have a much bigger and happier news!
Our only daughter, Sayaka,
and Kazamaturi-kun...
..are now engaged!
What?
W.. wait.
This is a very happy outcome!
F.. Father.. what's this about?
Shinnosuke, now our Kazamatsuri
Brewery is in safe hands.
N.. no way.
So that means...
Wait, everyone --
This is Sayaka.
To be engaged to Kazamatsuri-san
is the happiest event for me.
But, in order to have a blissful marriage,
I must do one thing.
That is, to defeat Inokuma Yawara,
and become Number One in Japan!
What a persistent Miss!
Right, Yawara?
Kazamatsuri-san is engaged to Sayaka-san..
..engaged!
Wh.. what's wrong, Yawara?
Here, have a lobster. Lobster!
She's totally out of it.
Well then, I'll take on the challenge for her!
Sorry to crash your party, but you'll never beat Yawara in a hundred or two hundred years!
I'll give that right back to you.
And to Yawara-san, who is running
away with her tail between her legs.
What? Yawara?
Yawara!
Yawara-san!
I.. I was the only one thinking
we had something.
Kazamatsuri-san...
I'm.. such a fool!
After all this, even Inokuma Yawara
would come back to fight me.
Let's settle this once and for all..
Inokuma Yawara-san!
803 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
The food was good, and it
was an enticing party!
You don't even know how I feel, Grandpa!
What about your feelings?
Now you can forget about that KazaMIDORI and devote yourself to judo, Yawara!
Kazamatsuri-san isn't that kind of person!
Next time, on Yawara! --
"Yawara and the Love Square"
I'll do an utsuri-goshi on
those who don't watch!
[utsuri-goshi -- hip shift]
This episode was sponsored by:
Mark A. Geller
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Hiza wo daite miteta
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Soba ni ite ne
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Otana ni naranaide
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental