From my lips a melody pierces
through the sunset one day.
And as I scanned the town below,
it was you that I clearly saw.
That piece of really burning dream.
Please don't just throw it away!
So just one more time, won't you please
rekindle your heart's desire.
Mixed with the wave of people at the crossroads, with who, where and what are you doing now?
Just like the fun of finding a diamond
buried within a pile of sand!
Wonders are always reserved inside your heart.
The wish in your eyes will
become true some day.
"He told me to hurry up."
Okay, this will be on the exam.
The structure of this sentence is S+V+O+O.
The second O is to. Okay then,
Katto, please read.
Thank you for attending my birthday party.
This snail is delicious!
Grandpa!
We have great news, also.
Kazamatsuri-kun, please come here.
Kazamatsuri-san?
Our only daughter, Sayaka, and Kazamatsuri-kun...
..are now engaged!
I need to work hard.
Entrance exam studying is the
only thing going for me.
Only the exam studies.
Yawara and the Love Square
What? Special admittance to that college?
I'm sorry for hiding it from you guys!
But I didn't think I'd get it.
Th.. that's so unfair for only you to
escape from this exam study hell.
Hey, say something to her, Yawara and Kazumi.
A.. actually, me too.
What?
For the longest time, I've been trying to decide between college and hair-dressing school.
But, I made my decision.
No way.
Kazumi, you've never mentioned this before!
It was kinda hard to bring it up.
I.. I can't believe it!
Is that all our female friendship amounted to?
I thought we were supposed to go through
this entrance exam hell together.
I'm really sorry.
I'll buy you a chocolate parfait.
And once I become a pro hair dresser,
I'll set your hair for you!
Why should I? Not even.
Sorry.
But, I'm happy for both of you,
Kyoko and Kazumi.
Congratulations.
Kyoko and Kazumi seemed so happy.
Feels like I'm the only one left behind.
It's so frustrating.
Hi!
Hon'ami Sayaka's Shocking Engagement Announcement!!
Her Judo Coach is her Fiance!
He's basically marrying into fortune.
Hon'ami Sayaka's Shocking Engagement Announcement!!
Her Judo Coach is her Fiance!
Kazamatsuri's main objective for being
her coach was to do that.
What a low-life..
He's not that kind of person!
Then what kind is he?
He's been approaching you while
this has been going on.
I was the only one thinking that there
was something going on between
me and Kazamatsuri-san.
Regardless, Kazamatsuri-san
isn't a bad person.
He was really nice to me.
Why are you SOOO nice about it?
Making girls think like that is his technique!
He's a playboy!
No he's not!
Besides, why are you concerned
about this anyway?
I'm just trying to rescue you
from that evil creature..
What evil creature?
A.. anyway, forget him pronto.
That's the best thing for you to do.
I...
..want to forget him, too.
O.. okay!
Let's go have some fun!
Tomorrow will be a new starting point.
You can work on finding a new love.
Right? Right? Right?
You've been sighing so much.
Unusual for a recently engaged man.
As I said, I was trapped into that!
Yeah, sure.
Her parents decided to make me
marry her when she graduated
from college without my consent.
I can't stand that I have to be tied
down as her fiance until then.
I can't stand being the other woman.
As I said, I was trapped into that!
You really sure?
I'm really really sure.
You're the woman of my dreams.
So "Yawara-san" is the REAL woman you want?
Did I say that?
While you were sleeping.
Then there's Hiromi-san,
Mayumi-san, and Mieko-san...
Ah! No! I'll get that!
Yes, this is Kazamatsuri.
This is Sayaka.
I'm going to go shopping.
Will you be able to go?
Err, well, actually, today, uhh...
Then we're on our way to pick you up.
Well then.
Sorry, but can you leave now?
What? I thought I could spend the night here!
That's okay. Hurry up and leave. Okay? Okay?
Gee, skating is so hard.
Hey, what's wrong, Yawara-san?
Hurry up and come over here!
Hey, wait for me!
Come here!
Watch out!
Yawara-san.
Look!
These melon rice cakes are superb!
N.. no, no! I've had plenty already!
Such a small appetite for a huge man like you.
Well, when I was younger, I used to eat 8 helpings, but these days, I'm down to 5 helpings.
But, Coach Yuutenji, you're very consistent.
You've been visiting us every month now.
Well, I've heard that other colleges have
been trying to recruit Yawara-san...
...so that thought has prevented
me from sleeping at night.
Such a small heart for a huge man like you.
I, Inokuma Jigoro, stands by his promise!
I'm going to put Yawara in Saikai College.
Yawara has been dancing for joy, too.
Thank you very much --
I haven't been dancing for joy!
Yawara-san.
You're late! Late, Yawara!
Where and what have you been doing?
Studying for exams with friends, of course.
S.. studying for exams?
But I thought Yawara-san was
going to Saikai College?
I'm not going to Saikai Coll --
Whoa!
Excuse us!
What type of ridiculous
nonsense are you saying?
You're the one saying ridiculous
nonsense, Grandpa!
I said it a million times that I am
NOT going to Saikai College!
Eii, don't give me that!
I said I'm not going!
Not in this life time!
Hey wait, you be-bopping delinquent child!
Here you are. Thank you for waiting.
Oh, are you feeling ill, Yuutenji-san?
Your face is rather pale.
Another day wasted, being
stuck with Sayaka-san.
If Sayaka-san keeps controlling
me like this.. oh no!
Master, seconds!
Here you go.
Come on, what is it?
You wanted to talk, so do so.
Seconds!
Oh please.
I don't have time to waste
over drunks, so excuse me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, I'm sorry, I don't want
to drink with you either. But..
..I have to be drunk to say
what I'm about to say.
Say what? What are you talking about?
It's about Yawara-san.
Yawara-san?
Yawara-san has been depressed ever since the news about your engagement.
She can't study or even do judo like that.
I see. So Yawara-san is that down...
But, I suppose it's hard to see the guy she loves get engaged to someone else.
Don't say it yourself, you transparent, lady-killer, perverted flirt!
I.. I'm the victim, too!
I never expected to be trapped into Sayaka-san's engagement!
Oh, is that so?
If that's so, then go see Yawara-san!
What?
Go see Yawara-san and bring her spirit up a bit.
I.. I'd like to do that, too, but Sayaka-san has been keeping me under her thumb these days.
I'm stuck with her all day tomorrow, too.
I'll take care of that end.
What?
I'll keep Miss Sayaka occupied.
Ma.. Matsuda-kun, you're
such a nice guy, after all!
L.. let's drink up then! Have fun!
Okay? Okay?
They're wilting... the flowers I received
from Kazamatsuri-san.
Thanks for waiting, Yawara-san.
Yes.
I'm probably looking for that single,
eternal woman to love.
Or something like that. Was that
a little pretentious?
Not really..
Our only daughter, Sayaka,
and Kazamaturi-kun...
..are now engaged!
Yawara, phone call. From somone
called Kazamatsuri-san.
Kazamatsuri-san?
It's been a while, huh, Yawara-san?
I was actually nervous when I called
you last night, since I didn't know
if you'd see me ever again.
Umm, congratulations.
Sayaka-san is so pretty,
and more mature than I am.
She's your perfect match, Kazamatsuri-san.
Oh gosh, that was harsh, Yawara-san.
Actually, that's what I wanted to talk about.
My engagement to Sayaka-san is a trap.
Trap?
Yes.
Just like a bird in cage, I was trapped.
I'm so excited to have you
introduce us to your fiance!
I saw him in the newspaper once,
but he looks so handsome!
Well, he is quite a catch!
My, so he's quite a catch!
I'm so envious of you, Sayaka-san!
Speaking of.. you're late, Kazamatsuri-san...
It's true that I'm going to work in
the Hon'ami Group upon graduation.
And as I said, it has nothing to do
with my dealing with Sayaka-san.
But, other people perceived it differently, and fabricated this situation, layer upon layer..
..and entrapped me live, like a helpless bunny.
Everything was a lie!
A totally made-up scheme!
What is Kazamatsuri-san doing?
Yawara-san, you're the only
person I don't want to fool.
Do you understand my dilemma, Yawara-san?
Kazamatsuri-san.
Oh gosh, I forgot! Sayaka-san's beeper!
Oh.. well, shall we go now?
What is this peculiar premonition that I feel?
Kazamatsuri isn't going to come.
You're that third-rate newspaper reporter.
Why are you here?
I bumped into Kazamatsuri, and he
asked me to tell you that he had
an emergency and can't come.
Emergency?
What is this emergency?
A professor called him over,
about his graduation thesis.
Thesis?
I see. I suppose it can't be helped.
The professor could be a woman.
You know how he is, so...
Wha--?
Kazamatsuri-san can't do such a thing!
Oh, is that Sayaka-san's boyfriend?
He looks so different from the pictures.
N.. no, not this junky garbage.
J.. junky garbage?
Of course not!
A guy looking like some raw garbage...
..can't possibly be Sayaka-san's boyfriend!
R.. raw garbage?
Wh.. what?
He's coming this way!
Oh no.
What should we do?
M.. Mother! Father!
I'm Kazamatsuri Shinnosuke!
My specialty is food-shoveling!
Oh gosh, what is he?
He's a psycho! A psycho!
Mother!
My gosh, how vulgar.
But, Kazamatsuri-san is so mean.
He should've told me that he'd be at school.
Today is Sunday.
Thanks for the meal.
Well, see you later.
Huh, I ate too much.
Yawara-san must be with
that Kazamatsuri now...
Dammit, what am I doing?
Wait just a second.
I'm human, so I can't say that I don't lie.
But, I want to be honest and truthful with you.
Yawara-san, ever since I met you, your presence in my heart has gotten even larger.
Even larger as the days add on...
Kazamatsuri-san, how can
you say that out in public?
I don't care who hears me.
Even if the whole world hears me.
Umm, excuse me.
You two have been selected as the Oshiuri TV Afternoon Wide Show's "Couple of the Day"!
Congratulations!
Look, you're on TV as we speak!
If Sayaka-san sees us like this..!
Come on, tell me what you're hiding from me.
You're mistaken. I'm not hiding anything.
Huh?
Oh, wait!
Well, wasn't that a cute couple?
Today's couple, at Harajuku's
Pedestrian Haven.
To..
Tokunaga!
Yes!
Tokunaga! Tokunaga! Tokunaga!
It hurts, Kazamatsuri-san!
Oh, I'm sorry.
They caught me off guard.
Shall we have a seat somewhere?
What are you doing, Tokunaga?
Go faster!
B.. but, Miss, we're in Pedestrian Haven!
Anyway, do you believe me, Yawara-san?
Find Kazamatsuri-san and Inokuma DOROBO-NEKO Yawara, no matter what!
[dorobo neko -- cat thief]
I won't let you!
I'm hurting, Yawara-san. My heart bleeds
when I think that you're still doubting me.
Kazamatsuri-san.
Please. Forgive me.
Forgive you... for?
I believe in you, Kazamatsuri-san.
Ya.. Yawara-san!
T.. To.. Tokunaga!
Yawara-san!
I cannot forgive you!
Miss..!
Please..! Please!
I cannot forgive you, DOROBO-NEKO Yawara!
[dorobo-neko -- cat thief]
No violence..!
Well, Kazamatsuri-san..
It's tough, but good luck
with your exam studies.
If you try hard enough,
anything will be possible.
Yes.
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight.
Kazamatsuri-san.
All right, study, study! Fight, Yawara!
What a big cat!
There you go.
Your smile fits you the best.
796 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
Yawara! How dare you come back
so late again, you delinquent girl!
Thank you very much, Kazamatsuri-san.
Hurry up and make dinner, Yawara.
I'm so glad. Kazamatsuri-san was the
kind of person I thought he was.
Hey, Yawara, you're a
yet-to-be married girl, so...
Oh, the phone's ringing?
Yawara! Come here and sit down!
Next time, on Yawara! --
"The Madonna of my Youth, Yawara"
I'll do a morote-gari on those who don't watch!
[morote-gari -- two-hand reap]
This episode was sponsored by:
Sailor Cypher
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
As I hugged my knees during the falling rain,
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
I watched the video through the night.
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
The big, blue lake and deep, green prairies.
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Nostalgic scenery that I saw again.
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
It should've been, that we were there,
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Watching it at the movies last year.
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stay right here next to me,
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Just like you did, in the past,
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
As you warmly embraced me.
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
The time just passes on as usual, but no,
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
I don't want you to grow up yet.
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental