kuchibiruni melody itsushika kizamu yuugure.
Machi o mioroseba kimi no sugata mieru.
Akirame kirenai. Yume no kakera sutenaide!
Mooichido sono mune atatame naoshiteyo.
Koosaten no hito no nagare.
Ima, dare, doko, nani shiteru?
Suna no naka no daiyamondo
Sagasu mitaina tokimeki!
kiseki wa itsudemo kimi no heart shidai.
Hitomi no negai wa itsuka kanawu hazuyoo.
My rather tasteless and gloomy high school life.
But from within that darkness,
you seem to shine so brilliantly.
You keep getting farther away from me.
If I could only watch from afar..
..forever and ever.
The Madonna of my Youth, Yawara
Yawara goofed again.
I'm sorry.
It's so strange that she's supposed
to be a genius judo girl.
But, it's farewell to judo.
Yawara's going to be a glamorous
college girl soon.
Farewell to bad-looking uniforms!
We're going to find a great guy, too!
I.. Inokuma..
Hanazono-kun.
Yes?
I.. Inokuma!
H.. hi! Fancy meeting you here!
Umm, the ball.
Oh.
Yawara-chan, you got some time?
Sudoh-kun.
If you don't go out with me today,
I won't give the ball back.
Sudoh!
I can't.
I'm busy studying for exams.
Sudoh-kun, you should be busy, too, training for the upcoming fall rookie tournament.
Kohno-kun and the others are working
hard to get past the second round, right?
If only you'd coach us, Yawara-chan,
I'd train seriously.
Especially with heavy ne-waza training. [ne-waza -- groundwork]
Sudoh!
How can you say such an absolutely disgusting and extremely shameless thing to her!
I can't forgive you!
I give up!
You need to take care of yourself, Hanazono-kun.
It's an important time for you, too.
Huh?
Th.. thank you, Inokuma!
I'm deeply touched by your kind words!
Be deeply touched by yourself.
I need to go see Yawara-chan.
Hey, be deeply touched, too!
I.. am!
Hanazono
Certain victory
Math
Aim for Saikai College!
No, no! I have to concentrate!
Inokuma Yawara-sama
Inokuma, I vowed to only see you from afar...
...but just like this small drawer, my heart is overflowing with so much feelings for you.
Yes, Inokuma residence.
Sudoh-kun?
I figured you were disappointed by someone interfering in our affairs, Yawara-chan.
So, how about a date on Sunday tomorrow,
at 10AM? Just the two of us?
I said I can't.
Yawara!
Grandpa.
It's from that flirt, KazaMIDORI, isn't it?
I won't allow it!
You have plans for tomorrow already.
I'll reject him for you!
This has nothing to do with you, Grandpa.
You're going to Saikai College
with me tomorrow!
I am not!
Yes, you are!
Geez!
Okay, I'll go on a date with you tomorrow.
Yawara!
R.. really?
I'll see you in front of the Hachiko
dog statue at 10AM.
Yawara-chan actually likes me!
I'm so happy!
Oh shoot...
Huh? Wasn't that Sudoh?
Sudoh?
Yawara! I won't allow this!
You're ten years too young to date!
It's none of your business, Grandpa.
Oh, another phone call.
Hanazono-kun, what's going on?
Hanazono
W.. well, err, how are you?
Huh? We just saw each other
at school today. Why?
W.. well, you know...
Inokuma Yawara-sama
..Inokuma, are you available tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow is..
If you have to do something, then that's fine.
Well then...
Oh, Hanazono-kun, did you want to
go out somewhere for a change?
What?
Let's go on a date tomorrow.
D.. d.. da.. date!
Yawara!
Don't tell me that you're going
to date that gorilla man!
Grandpa, your blood pressure will rise.
What a screwed up sense of taste in men!
Well, Hanazono-kun, meet you at the
Hachiko dog statue at 10AM, okay?
Y.. yes..
I'm.. I'm such a fortunate man!
That Yawara. She's getting
brattier by the minute.
I'll make sure she doesn't go on a date today.
Father, breakfast is ready.
I can't eat now!
Oh really?
The yellowtail teriyaki and dried
daikon radish came out great...
Y.. yellowtail teriyaki and dried daikon radish?
Yawara hasn't woken up yet, either.
W.. well, I suppose I should eat.
After all, you can't fight on an empty stomach.
Hanazono-kun.
I.. Inokuma.
Did you have to wait long?
N.. no, I just came, too.
Shall we go, then?
Oh wait.
We have to wait for one more person.
Yawara-chan!
S.. Sudoh!
Huh? Hanazono-san?
Wh.. what are you doing here?
I should ask you the same!
Come on, you guys, let's all have a fun date.
Gosh darnit, I thought I was going
to be with Yawara-chan all night...
...and have morning coffee with her, alone.
An absolutely disgusting and
extremely shameless guy like you
shouldn't be near Inokuma!
All you're trying to do is get between
me and Yawara-chan!
How dare you speak to an
upperclassman like that!
Hey, are you guys coming or what?
Yes, coming! Coming!
Wh.. why do I have to sit with you?
Shut up! It's better that way.
Yawara-chan!
And you call yourself a Musashiyama
Judo Athlete, huh?
That set and..
Yes, it'll take a moment..
I.. it's my chance.
Now's my chance to express my feelings.
Inokuma --
Hanazono-kun..
Are you doing okay with your exam studies?
Y.. yes.
Well, I can't be recruited into a college
like you that easily, so I have
to work really hard to get in.
I need to work hard, too.
What am I doing? I.. it's now or never!
I'm going to learn a lot in the 2-year college, Housekeeping major.
2-year college, Housekeeping major?
I've been trained to do judo
ever since I could remember.
But, there's a lot of things I want to do as a girl.
And, I don't like judo anymore, because it
gets people hurt and splits up families.
I want to be a normal girl. Just a normal girl.
Th.. then what about judo?
What?!
No, you can't quit judo!
Hanazono-kun.
Who cares? If that's what Yawara-chan wants.
Right, Yawara-chan?
Sudoh! Are you satisfied with that?
You're supposed to be some
sort of judo athlete, too!
Heh!
It's not cool to be such an
intense athlete anymore.
Whatever Yawara-chan does, I'm on her side.
Inokuma has an innate genius ability!
An ability that can't be attained
through hard work alone!
Inokuma can't quit judo!
Let Yawara-chan do what she wants to.
It's none of your business anyway.
Maybe so, but when..
..when Inokuma shines brilliantly in judo, I.. I..
Hanazono-kun!
I.. love you like that!
What's he so excited over?
Oh well, that leaves me alone
with Yawara-chan!
Hanazono-kun..
Inokuma..
I'm.. I'm extremely saddened!
Thank you, Sudoh-kun. I had a nice time today.
Going home already? The night's still young.
Why can't we hang out until morning?
I need to study for exams.
You need to go train for
the rookie tournament, too.
Oh, and don't get into any fights and cause trouble for the team like the last time, okay?
Well, I guess you put me in my place.
Promise me.
See you later.
Bye-bye, Yawara-chan!
Sudoh-chan, we found you!
You seem to be in a good mood, Sudoh.
A.. am I?
I knew there was a reason why a flirt
like you would join a judo team, but..
..so you were after Yawara, huh?
So you stopped hanging out with us
delinquents and started doing judo
for a youthful glory, huh?
I'm jealous.
W.. well, I guess.
Enough of your crap!
We aren't gonna let you be a goody
two-shoes and have fun that easily!
Have fun? I'm getting real close to that...
Bull shit!
If you want to get out of the group, then you'll have to deal with the consequences!
We'll see you at that park at 4PM tomorrow.
Don't even try to run away, otherwise we'll go visit your pathetic little judo club in person.
Okay then. I'll be there.
See you, Sudoh. Don't forget it.
Sudoh.
Come on now!
Hanazono-sempai is rather excited,
even though he's not going to be
in the rookie tournament.
I wonder why?
Inokuma, I can't believe that
you're giving up judo.
You need to keep doing judo.
Hey, having fun yet, everyone?
Sudoh!
How dare you come so late, you slacker!
Here you go, Hanazono-san.
Club Retirement Letter
Th.. this is..!
It's a retirement letter!
Are you serious, Sudoh?
Of course I am.
I can't be in such a sad club for long,
since I might rot here.
Feels so good to quit!
What's going on?
He just joined to get close to Yawara-san!
U.. umm...
And so.. goodbye.
Wait up!
I'm disappointed because you
had an absolutely disgusting,
and extremely shameless reason
to join and for quitting the club.
Was all the blood, guts, and tears that we shed together in the last eight months just an act?
Was judo just a side hobby for you?
Hanazono-san.. and everyone. Farewell.
Darnit! Sudoh...!
Judo Club
Oh, Sudoh-kun?
Sudoh-kun?
Sudoh bowed to the judo club room?
Are you sure, Yawara-san?
That's weird, because he just slapped a retirement letter and left us in the cold.
Sudoh-kun quit the club?
Yes. And with just four of us now,
we can't enter the rookie tournament.
Umm..
Enough of Sudoh! Forget about him already.
That's not it! I was forced
into silence by Sudoh-kun!
What?
Well...
He's going to take care of his
old friends, once and for all?
Is he serious?
Of course he is!
He said not to tell anyone, but...
I've never seen him look so serious!
He gave the retirement letter so that his fight won't cause any trouble for the judo club...
...especially before the tournament!
He's really serious about it!
Sudoh-kun is keeping my promise...
We need to go stop him!
Yeah, we do!
Hanazono-sempai!
Sudoh.. you're so..!
Sudoh!
Come on, fight us, Sudoh.
Don't tell me you became
spineless for Yawara-chan.
Oh yeah, I saw Yawara-chan on TV.
She's pretty hot!
Especially when her chest gets
exposed from the ruffled judo outfit!
How dare you say such absolutely disgusting and extremely shameless things...
...just because I haven't stopped you!
Whoa. He's so madly in love with her.
This has nothing to do with Yawara-chan!
I'll pay you guys back with interest!
Heh, just because you can do a little judo, doesn't give you the right to act like a big shot!
It would be a waste to use
judo on cruds like you!
I can beat you guys without it!
Sudoh! Sudoh!
Ha.. Hanazono-sempai.
Wait.. wait up!
It's my responsibility to take
care of my kouhai's matters!
I am Hanazono Kaoru, the Musashiyama
judo team captain!
Please, let him go! I beg you!
Are you stupid? I thought I gave
you my retirement letter!
We're no longer sempai or kouhai!
I don't remember receiving
any retirement letters!
Wh.. why'd you do that?
Now you're still an official
Musashiyama judo team member.
You'll have to be in the upcoming
rookie tournament.
Why'd you have to do that...
What are you doing? You need
to beg for forgiveness, too!
We wouldn't need cops or the military if
things were settled with begging, right?
Please, understand our plight.
Hanazono-kun! Sudoh-kun!
Sudoh!
Inokuma!
Yawara-chan!
Don't come, Inokuma. You shouldn't!
Hanazono-kun?
You need to take care of yourself, since
you're going to get the gold medal...
...at the Barcelona Olympics and
the National Achievement Award.
You shouldn't get mixed up
with these delinquents!
Sorry for being a delinquent!
We're trying to bear through this thing so Sudoh can continue doing judo!
You're just forcing my head down..!
So, Inokuma, please bear with us, too!
But, I don't really want to do judo anymore...
It's so boring to mess with these mushy fellas.
We should go have some fun
with Yawara-chan instead.
Don't you guys dare lay a
finger on Yawara-chan --
Run away, Inokuma!
Ya.. Yawara-san!
I'm sorry, but I'm not going anywhere.
Whoa, take it easy on us, Yawara-chan.
You're so hot when you get mad, too!
Inokuma!
Yawara!
Grandpa!
Stop wasting your time here!
Since you ditched me yesterday,
you're doing pre-supper training!
Hey gramps, you're in the way! Shove off!
What!! How dare you do that,
you insensitive fools!
Young folks these days don't
value food like we used to.
It was the post-war period...
In the rubble of the obliterated Tokyo,
Kaneko and I shared a meager
bowl of suiton to stave off hunger.
But, what about the present Japan?
What's so great about GOURMET? And FRENCH food? And BEEF-STRONG CONGO! [trying to say beef stroganoff]
We.. we're very sorry!
I'll never forget the taste of that bowl of suiton.
Oh my gosh, Grandpa, why do you have those?
Well, I strongly refused the offer, but Tome-san from the fruit shop told me to take it home!
Th.. this is some hot stuff!
Very stimulating!
Hey, these are mine!
Are you guys okay, Hanazono-kun? Sudoh-kun?
Inokuma, thank you for holding
yourself back like that.
So you haven't given up judo yet!
I'm really happy, Inokuma!
Aren't you grateful, Sudoh?
I'm not really --
Shut up! Don't say anything!
I know exactly how you feel!
Sudoh, you're so..!
He.. hey, stop it! Please stop it!
Sudoh. Sudoh. Sudoh. Sudoh.
Everyone, Sudoh has returned to our team.
Let's get back to our training
for the rookie tournament!
Yes!
Let's run towards the sunset!
Yeah, as if I'm going to hang around and
do the mushy youthful glory thing.
You come, too!
H.. hey, I don't like doing this kind of thing!
Fight-oh! Fight-oh!
Since you guys are under-age,
I can't lend them to you.
But, I can share the plot with you.
P.. please do so!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Geez, Grandpa.
789 Days to the Barcelona Olympics
With my guidance, I was able to lead
the lost sheep onto the right path.
What guidance? You borrowed
such sleazy video tapes.
They forced it onto me!
It was Zen-san.. no Gen-san...
You're lying.
I'm not lying! Zen-san... no, Tome-san...
Next time, on Yawara! --
"The Other One-Sided Love"
I'll do a tani-otoshi on those who don't watch! [tani-otoshi -- valley drop]
This episode was sponsored by:
Josan
Thank You Very Much!
Translated by:
Anastasia Shimabuku Moreno
Timed by: Studio Wannabe
Edited by: Neko-chan
Ame no hi no yoru video o
Subtitled by: Neko Creations
Hiza wo daite miteta
Yawara is based on the book by:
Naoki Urasawa
Midori no oka to mizu umi
Execute Producer: Hidenori Taga
Producer: Michihiko Suwa
Director: Hiroko Tokita
Character Design: Yoshinori Kanemori
Natsukashii keshiki ni aeta
Production: Yomiuri TV, Kitty Film
Co-Production: Mad House
Kyonen wa anata to
Art Director: Yuji Ikeda
Sound Director: Yasuo Uragami
Eigakande miteta hazu
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Stand by me
Planner: Shigekazu Ochiai
Series Supervisor: Toshiki Inoue
Soba ni ite ne
Yawara Inokuma: Yuko Minaguchi
Ano koro no youni
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Kata o daitene
Jigoro Inokuma: Ichiro Nagai
Kousaku Matsuda: Toshihiko Seki
Stand by me
Sayaka Honami: Yoshino Takamori
Shinnosuke Kazamatsuri: Akira Kamiya
Tokiwa sugite shimau kedo. Iya yo.
Miracle Girl sung by: Mariko Nagai
Stand By Me sung by: Rika Himenogi
Otana ni naranaide
Please distribute freely
Not for sale or rental