Original file: DH2:H2Ep22.txt.js
H2, Episode #22, "Pinch-Hitting for a Date: the Two Unable to Return  Home"
0:00:14.00 0:00:15.00
0:00:16.00 0:00:17.00
0:00:24.00 0:00:25.00
0:00:26.00 0:00:27.00
0:00:28.00 0:00:29.00
0:00:30.00 0:00:31.00
0:00:42.00 0:00:43.00
0:02:10.00 0:02:11.00
0:02:16.00 0:02:17.00
Shin-Tokoroguchiko Station
0:04:16.00 0:04:17.00
Examination Room"}
"Pharmacy"}
Note: "up-bound" means "bound for Tokyo area"
0:06:10.00 0:06:11.00
0:06:38.00 0:06:39.00
Processed by Central Anime's NUMIT On 06/17/2013
Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
I'm Kunimi Hiro, a first year pitcher with Senkawa High School's baseball club.
I'm a close friend of Tachibana Hideo, the cleanup hitter for Meiwa.
He asked me to pinch-hit on
his date, and I couldn't say no.
The date is with Hikari,
my childhood friend.
I've known her
since we were little...
...so there shouldn't be any reason for me to feel nervous, but...
Episode 22
Pinch-Hitting for a Date:
The Couple is Unable to Return Home
Mr. Madison's Bridge
Nontenora
Red Broncross
Hey...
Oh, no...
Dummy.
Oh, you weren't on the train ?
Nope.
I figured this would happen.
You've always done things
like this since you were little.
Here.
Thanks.
This flavor brings back memories.
I thought so.
We haven't gone out together in a while.
Really ?
Well.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
What is it ?
Nothing.
What is it ? It bugs me.
It bothers you ?
Yeah.
I just thought, "Until recently, you
couldn't even reach the strap handle."
Oh, that ?
Didn't I tell you ?
I have big hands and feet,
so I'll definitely grow bigger.
You've certainly grown.
Here, please have one.
Thank you.
When I'm needed by someone...
...I learn for the first time where I am right now.
Just as the metronome gets interrupted...
...so few people can hear the monotonous sound.
With a clunk, I place my forehead on the display window.
For what can I cry ? I look up beyond the sky.
When you're not with me, you overflow.
On the streets and by the windows, the clues overflow.
Loneliness doesn't corner us.
Rather, it teaches us whom we cannot lose.
Even those long, difficult nights that make us retreat...
...we'll be able to laugh about someday, like a childhood scar.
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Hey.
Huh ?
Was the can of juice tasty ?
Thanks for that.
You know him ?
Kind of.
I got to know him
about three hours ago.
Shin-Tokoroguchiko Station
Service suspended between
Shirai and Mikami,
due to flooding on the tracks.
Thank you for your patience.
Man, it was amazing.
Because of the sudden rainstorm, the concert was cut short.
Girls' underwear was showing through, and train service is stopped.
Really, we've got to have more
outdoor concerts during summer.
I told you so.
Yeah.
It's 8:30.
Do you think this is that
well-known course of events...
...where the couple who can't go
home and spend the night together ?
I'm very sorry.
In half an hour or so, they say that train service will resume.
Okay.
Let's go spend some time
at the café near the station.
Run !
EYECATCH
What kind of things do you
usually talk about with Hideo ?
You want to know ?
I'm curious.
I see.
About social service, environmental issues...
...taxes...
And about our dreams
for the future, I guess.
Dreams ?
What's Hideo's dream for the future ?
First, the Koushien.
Then professional ball.
Rookie of the Year.
All-Star appearance.
Individual titles.
The team winning the championship.
Breaking several records, and retiring afterward.
Become a commentator
and then a field manager.
And three children in
a heartwarming home.
And you're the wife.
He didn't say that part.
There's no need to even hear it.
You want to become a pro, too ?
I wonder.
Playing baseball for
a living sounds tough.
Well, I'm sure I'll play baseball until I can't move anymore.
But it can be bush-league or anything, in my case.
I suppose.
I always want you to
play baseball for fun.
So ?
Hm ?
What's your dream ?
The perfect crime and political reform.
Oh, the rain seems to have stopped.
I do want to get married.
But before that, I want to find a
job where I can feel confident.
And become an independent adult who has her own perspective.
So you want to become a
"career-focused woman" ?
I don't mean something grand like that.
But at least, I don't want to live
my life just following my partner.
So I don't really mind if my husband is a professional baseball player...
...or an ace pitcher for the
neighborhood baseball league...
Oops.
What do you mean, "oops" ?
Well, the trains seem
to be running. Let's go.
Thank you.
What are you doing ? We'll be late.
Yeah.
Well, I guess we avoided trouble.
What do you mean ?
If we couldn't go home and had to spend
the night together, Hideo would beat me up.
Why ?
Why ? It's a given !
A man and a woman
spending the night together...
What could possibly happen between you and me ?
Oh, you sound confident.
It's a given.
It's strange.
I wonder where it went.
Um...
There's no ring here.
You shouldn't make
such a hasty conclusion.
I can't find it.
Really, I wonder where it went.
Shall we give up ? Okay ?
No ! Look for it !
Okay ?
That's right.
It's an engagement ring.
Yes, that's right, Miss !
Oh, it's Hikari, right ?
You're definitely right !
You must be happy to
have such a great girlfriend.
I'm sorry I'm such a bad girlfriend !
I didn't mean it like that.
I mean, it's your fault, Lacchie !
It's your fault for proposing to me in a place like this !
I wanted to put it on your finger after the concert !
Well, you shouldn't fight, Lacchie.
That's right. You'll find it.
Really...?
Can it be found...?
We will find it.
It's here !
Really ?
Thank goodness !
This is...
Yeah.
Right now, it's still a glass ring, but someday, I'll give you the real ring.
A shiny one. So have faith in me, and stay with me.
I guess they're shining.
Yeah, it's shiny.
Right ?
Hikari.
Huh ?
Hurry up, or we'll
be late for the train.
Yeah, let's go.
By the time we get home, it'll be midnight.
Thanks for that.
Leave them alone !
We don't have time !
Yeah...
Hikari.
Hikari !
Darling, I can't hold it anymore !
The baby's coming out !
He's coming out !
Are you okay ? Hang in there !
We're definitely not helping them.
Darling, I can't hold it anymore !
Hang in there ! I'll take you to the hospital right way !
Dammit !
The baby's coming out...!
Yamada Clinic
Clinic Departments:
Surgery - Gynecology - Internal Medicine
"Up-bound" train service
has ended for today.
Well then...
I'm glad that couple made it in time.
Yeah.
Concert Site
Well then, what are we
going to do, "Big Sister" ?
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Man:
Woman:
Husband's Voice:
Wife's Voice:
Chiba Isshin
Neya Michiko
Tobita Nobuo
Hagimori Junko
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Movie Titles: Nontenora - is probably Cinderella.  Red Broncross - is probably Rumble in the Bronx. Or "Red Bronx" as it was also called.
Train service sign meaning: "Up-bound" means
"bound for Tokyo area."
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
Oh well, in the end,
we couldn't go home.
But I feel safe with Hiro.
What do you mean by that ?
I mean, we're like siblings.
You don't understand. You're an attractive woman who makes men's hearts throb.
Is that what you say ?
Well, I might, or might not.
Oh, Hiro is going to turn into a wolf !
Next episode of H2 is, "I Can't Sleep... A Night With Just the Two of Us."
Next episode of H2 is
I Can't Sleep...
A Night With Just the Two of Us
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?