Presented by Central Anime
I don't know what it is...
...but I have to say something to you.
Ah, hidden deep inside my heart...
...a strange box is making a noise now.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
The game starts now.
One down, two down, but I can still go on.
It makes my heart bound.
When going against the wind, throw your chest out more.
At last, with a bang, it's a rainbow grand slam.
A rock concert I went to with Hikari.
Service suspended between
Shirai and Mikami,
due to flooding on the tracks.
Thank you for your patience.
Because of a rainstorm,
train service stopped...
...and many accidents followed.
"Up-bound" train service
has ended for today.
We couldn't go home...
...and we, Hikari and I, ended up in a scenario where we had to spend the night together.
Episode 23
I Can't Sleep...
A Night With Just the Two of Us
Concert Site
Welcome to our inn.
Well, I'm glad we were able to find a nice inn, Big Sister.
Yeah.
Well, there was the rainstorm, and then a childbirth.
In the end, we missed the last train.
It really was awful today, Big Sister.
You're right.
But the concert was great,
so I guess it balances out.
Right, Big Sister ?
Yeah.
The bath is open 24 hours.
Oh, it is ?
That's great.
I'll take a relaxing bath and
recover from the long day.
Right, Big Sister ?
Yeah.
Well, please enjoy your stay.
She looked like she was a little
suspicious, didn't she, Big Sister ?
I suppose.
It might have worked three years ago...
...but now, it's a bit of a stretch to present ourselves as siblings.
I wonder what we seemed like to her.
Who knows ?
Keep it clean.
I thought we bought two.
One of them is for Hide-chan.
Oh.
You bought two T-shirts, too, right ?
Yep.
For a thing like this.
What do you mean,
"For a thing like this" ?
Oh, nothing.
It's just that if we
hadn't bought that stuff...
...we might have been able to get a taxi to go home.
Are you trying to
say this is my fault ?
Not really. I just thought we might have gotten a taxi to go home.
You don't give up, do you ?
You should be glad that
we're not sleeping outdoors.
Yeah.
I'm going to call home.
Okay.
What does she plan to tell them ?
You missed the last train ?
The concert was that long ?
Yeah. So I'll stay overnight tonight.
Honestly, you're so troublesome.
I'm sorry.
But Hiro is with you, right ?
Yeah.
Okay then. Don't worry your parents too much, okay ?
Sure. Bye.
Oh, yes. You had a phone call, from Tachibana.
Yasui Inn
Oh.
What did your mother say ?
About what ?
You explained to her why this happened, right ?
The ring search, the
childbirth incident, and such.
Not really.
What ?
I just said that we missed the train, so we'd stay overnight. That's all.
Hey...
I mean, the more I explain things,
the more it sounds like an excuse.
And your mother didn't say anything ?
She's not worried because you're with me, I guess.
Wasn't the last time we looked like siblings three years ago ?
To my mother, you're
like a part of the family.
Oh, well.
I guess she doesn't understand how her daughter looks to boys our age.
How do I look to them ?
Huh ?
Hmm...
I mean, you know, well it's like...
...you're an attractive woman
who makes men's hearts throb.
This is the first time
I've been told that.
What are you talking about ?
Since junior high, you've received piles of love letters with corny phrases like that.
By you, I mean.
Yasui Inn
Well, we were so close
that I didn't see you clearly.
It's only recently...
...that I started to vaguely understand why
the guys around me were fussing over you.
I wasn't seeing you clearly, either.
Because you were too small.
No !
Oh, man.
It was healing well, but because of this stupid concert, it's swelling up again.
See ?
Oh, it's true.
What do you mean, "it's true" ?
Aren't you supposed to
worry or something ?
The bath here seems
to be good for bruises.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll go take a bath, Big Sister.
Large Public Bath
Hot water
Women
It's hot !
Hm ?
Uh, oh !
It's a mixed bath ?
Is it the common setup...
...where there are separate entrances but they go to the same place ?
That means...
What ?
Crap !
EYECATCH
So I missed the last train.
I didn't have enough money for a taxi, but I
had enough to stay the night at a cheap inn.
What a coincidence.
We came for the same concert, and ended up at the same inn for similar reasons.
Right.
So who did you come with ?
You didn't come here alone, did you ?
Ah.
It's Noda.
I see.
What about you ?
Don't ask such a thoughtless question.
Do you think I would come this far for a concert with a guy ?
Huh ?
Don't tell anyone you saw me here.
Lots of girls will be
sad if they find out.
Sure.
I'll get going, then.
Well, it probably goes without saying, but don't intrude on us, okay ?
No way I would.
You came here with a guy, huh ?
I'm envious that you
can be so carefree.
Don't come peeping on us, okay ?
No way I would.
Hey, Kine.
Lend me a 100 yen coin.
I can't watch the porn channel.
100 yen.
It's hot.
That was such a long bath.
I guess.
Can you get out of the way ?
I want to get my bag.
Well, I guess I'll watch some TV.
Silly !
You don't have to stop.
Well, if I start to watch, I can't stop.
Oh, is that how it is ?
Wow...
Do you want something to drink ?
No thanks.
What's so good about this stuff ?
People who don't understand won't understand.
I guess that's true.
Do you want to use the brush ?
With each palm touching the other's, we walked in the sun.
It's full of warmth, and we talked about lots of things.
Being together shouldn't feel painful.
Just keep carrying this brimming feeling.
There are many things where just
being kind doesn't move us forward.
But I don't hesitate to do things
for you, and for the two of us.
There will be a day when you can
see love like a gentle rainbow.
If you don't try to notice...
...you'll overlook it, and you'll make a mistake.
As we repeat the laughing and smiling...
...everyday that we can't relive is formed.
You want the futons further apart ?
It doesn't matter.
Either way, I can't escape if you come after me.
What do you mean by that ?
Back in the day, I could
beat you in a sumo match.
But now, I don't stand
a chance even if I resist.
Hey...
Now, let's go to bed.
Noda
Yasui Inn
She feels safe falling asleep even though I'm right by her.
Nothing has changed
since three years ago.
Do you regret introducing Hikari to Tachibana ?
Let's go to the Koushien, Manager.
This is troubling.
I can't sleep...
...Hide-chan.
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Next Episode
If you have a hand...
Hikari's Mom:
Innkeeper:
Friend:
Ikemoto Sayuri
Takeguchi Akiko
Aizawa Masaki
...that I can hold forever as I walk.
Notes:
Noda was reading "Saturday" and if you looked closely
at the front you'll see H2.
Yasui Inn Unspoken Joke: The name of the inn is a joke.
"Yasui" is an actual surname, but it is also a homophone for the word, "cheap."  So it sounds the same as "Cheap Inn."
I want you to let me hear you
come closer and open the door...
Notes:
...rather than the footsteps that
sound further and further away.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
The star I'm watching today...
...glistened yesterday.
In the town full of things that disappear...
...I thought to myself, wishfully:
Let's return to "two of us," let's return together...
...rather than losing our time to regret.
Happiness is not something...
...that someone does for me.
It means that I have someone I can embrace.
The Koushien tournament has ended, and summer is nearing its end.
Yeah, but there's still one more event remaining.
Oh, the fireworks display.
That's right. So let's not be
awkward with each other.
What are you talking about ?
I mean, about us
spending the night together.
I don't worry about that at all.
Really ?
Next episode of H2 is, "The Summer for Each of Us, Like Fireworks."
I Can't Sleep...
Next episode of H2 is
The Summer for Each of Us, Like Fireworks
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?