Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Yasui Inn
Hikari and I had a sleepless night.
Well, I was actually snoring and sleeping.
The next day, the sky was bright, as though nothing had happened.
Nothing really happened, but
I couldn't tell Hideo about this.
That's right. I couldn't tell Hideo.
I Can't Sleep...
Episode 24
The Summer for Each of Us, Like Fireworks
Thank you.
Fight
Youkou
We're blessed with great weather here at Koushien Stadium.
As you can see,
the stadium is packed.
This is the final game
of the summer tournament.
The commentator, as you know, is Mr. Nehori Ichitarou.
Wow.
Pleased to meet you.
Top of the first,
Saeki Chuuou is up to bat.
Well, this sure is
a Japanese summer.
Now, the pitcher, Yamashita,
prepares to throw his first pitch !
He throws !
Strike !
The second pitch.
It's hit !
The third baseman deftly handles a hard-hit ball.
As expected, the teams in the finals sure are good.
Yasui Inn
I can't sleep, Hide-chan.
Bottom of the first, Youkou High School has an early scoring opportunity.
Runners on second and third with one out, the batter is the cleanup hitter, Yoshida.
All right, Tachibana ! One more !
Please !
Okay, one more !
Bottom of the sixth,
Youkou's inning continues.
It's a hit ! They scored their ninth run !
Moron ! That's not right !
Saeki Chuuou
Youkou
Well, it's the sixth inning, and the game has turned into an unexpectedly lopsided one.
This is this year's final game of the
National High School Baseball Tournament.
Saeki Chuuou is making its first appearance at the Koushien...
...and it has miraculously advanced this far with one come-from-behind win after another.
But they've been forced onto the
defensive against Youkou High School...
...widely thought of as the favorite to win the championship.
It's gone over the outfielders !
It's their tenth run !
Oh, an error ! The third base runner charges home plate !
Safe !
What the heck are they doing ?
Why do they throw when
it wouldn't make it in time ?
What is their manager thinking ?
Pull yourselves together !
Um, it's troubling other customers.
Could you please keep it down ?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got a little carried away.
Sorry about that.
Oh...
Can I have another cup of coffee ?
This is your seventh...
It's 11-0, a commanding lead.
I hope they'll hang in there and finish out the game.
That's right.
In terms of lopsided
games at the Koushien...
...the game that comes to
mind is from ten years ago.
Yes, there was one.
That game by Sousei High School.
The 0-30, no-hitter loss.
Man, again ?
If you mention that, Yanagi's
father, meaning our principal...
...will get irritated.
After all, the Koushien doesn't
do called games. It was rough.
Yes, exactly.
When there's that much
of a gap between teams...
...I wish we could have
called off that game.
You shouldn't say stuff like that, idiot !
You should have seen how they'd compete in terms of their achievement test scores !
The school that gets "no-hit shutout" would be their opponent !
That year, Sousei Baseball Club was the best team in the nation, in terms of academics !
For three years, those guys
never lowered their grades...
...and worked hard on both academics and baseball !
If it's a school baseball competition...
...you should judge them based on both academics and sports !
Oh...
Sir...
Can I have another cup of coffee ?
Sure...
Oh, the runner is taking a big lead.
A throw from the
catcher to second base.
It's an out !
How stupid !
What are they doing ?
That's not how you do it !
Let me manage the team !
Aim for the Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
Saeki Chuuou
Youkou
The game is over. 16-0.
Youkou High School wins the
summer Koushien tournament !
Well...
Well, well...
"Liquor, Food Tachi..."}
Ah.
Hi.
What are you doing ?
I came here to clean the room. What about you, Hiro ?
Um, well, I just came by to get the undershirts that I forgot.
Um...
Oh, crap.
Here.
Oh, you have those kinds of books ?
It's your study guide, right ?
Moron !
Oh, Hiro.
Hide-chan is coming back from his training camp tomorrow.
I see.
It's tomorrow for us, too.
What ?
Senkawa High School
Baseball Field
Construction Site
The construction work for the baseball field starts.
Oh.
Bye.
If I find any more of your "study guides"
as I clean the room, I'll save those for you.
What ?!
Aim for Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
Well.
Well, well, well...
"Back up," "hot blood."
"Come out, Heroes."
Hm.
Come Out
Heroes
Aim for Koushien
Kunimi Hiro
It's not over yet.
One hundred more pitches...
Here I go, Noda !
Okay.
Good job, Hiro. One more out.
Let's pull ourselves together...
Okay. Let's finish with
the 140 km forkball...
We did it, Noda !
What...
EYECATCH
Did anything happen while
I was away at training camp ?
Um, not really.
How's Hiro doing ?
He's being his usual lazy self.
That sounds just like him.
He should follow your
example a little more.
I mean, Hiro is...
Oh, yeah.
The fireworks display is today.
It's that time of the year already.
Cool-Down Fireworks Display Festival
Welcome.
Ring Toss
1 Try - 200 yen
Here you go.
It's such a big crowd.
But anyway, where has Hiro gone ?
He should know about
the fireworks display.
Ever since he was a child, he was
always excited about these festivals.
He's probably chasing
some lady's tail right now.
Where in the world did he go ?
Huh ?
Where did Atsushi go ?
He's not here ?
No.
For goodness sakes,
everyone's so self-centered.
Really.
Hey, Meiwa's cleanup batter.
Who are you ?
Moron ! It's me !
Oh, Fune.
It's Kine !
Ah, yeah, it's Kine.
Have you seen Koga ?
Huh ?
I haven't seen her today.
I see. I was supposed
to meet her here.
More importantly, have you seen your team's battery ?
Why should I care about those guys ?!
Get out of my way !
Koga !
Koga is also missing...?
Where did that beauty go ?
Welcome !
Would you like some tasty yakisoba ?
Next customer, please !
A big serving, please.
Give me some extra, okay ?
Sure.
What are you doing here ?
Well, I was just passing by.
Kunimi, thanks for the wait...
Oh.
Good evening, Noda.
Hi.
It looked dangerous, so...
For me.
My mother was supposed to do this,
but she had a sudden schedule conflict.
I was told to pinch-hit for her.
I see.
So Hiro is pinch-hitting
for the pinch-hitter ?
That's right.
I'm the dependable
savior in times of need.
One plate of yakisoba, please.
Sure.
Two here, please.
Sure, right away !
I guess I'll be the ball boy.
Oh.
Oh well.
Geez.
You should stay calm while you do it.
Eh ?
Yeah.
Mister, one more time !
Sure.
Okay, next customer !
Howdy, Miss.
I'm Kunimi Tarou, of the third section of the sales department of Koga Trading Company.
And his wife.
You two look like newlyweds. Are you on a date ?
Well, I saw you from over there.
I didn't know that our stupid son was here with you.
And he looks like
a good match.
Shut up !
If you're not going to buy anything, just go away !
Hey.
You're fine, Miss.
Umm...
Kunimi Tarou of the third
section of the sales department...
...will protect you, even
if it costs him his life.
Honey, hang in there !
Your promotion depends on it !
You want some of this ?
Huh ?
Here's the pack you're waiting for.
Thanks.
I never thought you'd create a baseball club, Father.
Everyone's grateful to you.
Including me, of course.
Hello.
Well, this is where you can see the fireworks the best.
Everyone came over
here by coincidence.
Construction Site
Senkawa High School
Baseball Field
The backstop net is on that side ?
Yes.
You always stand under this tree.
What ?
When you watch fireworks, that is.
That's right.
I see. That's how you all
ended up cooking yakisoba.
Yeah.
And in exchange for my
valuable work, we got this.
Wow.
Now, let's go to Hideo's place and
have a yakisoba party with free drinks.
One drink per person, okay ?
That means...
A can of juice, a can of coke,
a can of oolong tea, a can of coffee.
A total of four cans for me.
You only get one of those !
Then I'll take one big bottle.
What ?
Hideo, you've lost.
What a mess !
We'll take it like
a free-and-easy party.
Phew.
Now, all the leftovers are taken care of.
You sure ate a lot.
It was better than I thought, Hiro.
Yeah.
See ?
You can become the prince
of the yakisoba world anytime.
Why, you...!
Hey !
If I become one, I'm never going to hire you, even for part-time work.
I'm not going to do anything other than professional baseball, so I don't care !
You jerk ! I'm going to
break your arm now !
You jerk !
Are you giving up ?
No way !
Don't back down, Hide-chan !
Go get him !
Somebody, cheer for me, too !
Go for it !
Damn...
Ouch ! It hurts !
Lousy baseball player !
Shut up, Yakisoba Brat !
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
"Brat" ? Who are you
to talk to me like that ?
Ouch ! Ouch !
There !
Oh, I'll clean this up.
I'll help, too.
Moron.
There.
Safe.
Nice backup.
Thanks.
She's always like this. So she has all kinds of wounds all over her.
But I'm fine. I have a
band-aid with me today, too.
Oh.
What ?
It's not good enough ?
Koga !
Hey, Koga !
Oh, it's the grand finale.
Oh, really ?
Let's see.
Wow.
Participants Wanted !
Back Up the
Hot Blood !
Come Out, Heroes
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
Good luck,
Kumini Hiro !
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Kunimi Tarou:
Principal Yanagi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Mitsuya Yuji
Komura Tetsuo
Koga Fujio:
Mrs. Kunimi:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Commentator:
Hironaga:
Yamaguchi:
Waitress:
Matsumoto Yasunori
Takizawa Kumiko
Izaki Hisayoshi
Kakegawa Hirohiko
Takagi Wataru
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Notes:
Hawaiin Shirt Guy in Restaurant: If you recall, Sousei High School is known to be an academically superior school. This guy is talking about how Sousei was so much more superior to the other school in terms of academics.
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
So they're constructing the field for
Senkawa High School's baseball club.
Yeah, it's different when
it becomes an actual club.
You seem motivated.
We have a club room, and we're getting some newcomers, too.
So you're seriously starting
to prepare for the Koushien now ?
Of course !
But...
Is something bothering you ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"The Coach Has Arrived ! I'm Koga Fujio."
Next episode of H2 is
The Coach Has Arrived ! I'm Koga Fujio
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?