H2, Episode #25, "The Coach Has Arrived ! I'm Koga Fujio."
Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
This summer, we fought against Meiwa with all our passion.
And our baseball club was established.
As all of us store our feelings within
our hearts, the summer has passed.
The construction of Senkawa High School's baseball club field began.
And yes, a new season has come for us.
I Can't Sleep...
Episode 25
The Coach Has Arrived ! I'm Koga Fujio
Senkawa High School Baseball Field Construction Site
You're early.
Who are you ?
I'm Hikari, the only daughter of Amamiya Bookstore.
You don't remember ?
The new semester is starting, and you're going to be late.
Your baseball club is starting.
You came by just to say that ?
It's because you didn't come by.
"Hikari, we have a game today."
"Hikari, I'm pitching for
the first time today."
...
The one who always reported
everything to me was you, Mister.
We go to different schools. There will be times I won't take the trouble to keep you posted.
Is that how it is ?
That's how it is.
I guess it is.
Hikari, you probably know this already, but our baseball club starts today.
You should get fired up !
I am !
Run, Kunimi Hiro !
Yeah !
Hey.
Oh, hello.
Private School - Senkawa High School
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
Participants Wanted !
Back Up the
Hot Blood!
Heroes,
Come Out
Oh, we have a baseball club now ?
I hear that they put up a good fight against Meiwa Daiichi.
Who was it ? There was someone who put in a great performance.
Who was it ?
You know, the guy who
was in the soccer club.
Oh, you mean Kunimi !
There was someone else, too.
There were others, not just Kunimi.
Yeah, that's right.
Right, there was Noda.
No !
Yanagi did well, too.
Hey, ace striker.
That's right.
I'm the ace striker...
I hear that you played
in that game, too.
Well, for me, their style of
baseball is just child's play.
But really, it's impressive.
Well, I gave it a
little bit of my best.
Kine, you're in the soccer club, right ?
O...of course, Captain !
Oh gosh, why do you ask ?
That's fine then.
Club
Okay, it's done.
Baseball Club
Baseball Club.
Yeah, it sounds great.
Yeah.
With this, we third years
have no more regrets.
We're going to retire, but
good luck to the rest of you.
Thank you, Seniors !
I got it !
Baseball Club
Is everyone here ?
I don't know how long
we've all waited for this !
Don't cry.
Huh ? Where are Kunimi and Noda ?
Girls' Track Team
It's heavy today. It's not good.
Yeah, let's hang in there.
I have to do the hurdles today.
It's a great environment.
Yeah, we have a great view.
Um...
I mean, the track team's practice is great for building lean muscle.
That's right. It's worth
researching for training methods.
I feel like I got faster
during summer break.
This is nice.
I'm opening it.
This is the club room for the
Senkawa High School Baseball Club.
We did it !
This feels like a dream !
This is the Baseball Club's floor !
It's kind of big.
This has been our dream !
Hey.
Hello.
Who is he ?
He's our manager's big brother.
What are you doing here ?
This and that.
Can we remove the rope ?
Sure.
Your brother works
for a transport company ?
I heard he got a job, but...
Do it from that side.
You're siblings and you
don't talk to one another ?
There's a big age difference.
Wow ! We've got
so many new balls !
We have bats and gloves, too.
The construction of our baseball field has begun, too. We're getting everything we need !
My father is thorough when
he decides to do something.
Hiro, take that side.
Hey.
Akagi...
What are you doing ?
Let's lend them a hand.
Okay...
Thank you.
We appreciate it.
Akagi.
Kunimi, since you're a
former soccer club member...
...I wanted to congratulate you on your new start.
So we came here to help.
Right, Kine ?
Um, that's right.
Thanks.
You're all legitimate baseball club members. You should hold your heads high.
The people I dislike the most are ones who don't stand tall.
...
He was peeking in all along.
Well, it was just a matter of how long he could continue to peek in and refrain from joining us.
Kunimi.
You want me to, Captain ?
Um, I'm still not used
to being called "Captain."
Anyway, take a look.
Yamaguchi and the other
seniors have just retired...
...and I want to stand firm as the new captain, but...
"50 practice swings" "Catch 30 minutes" "Tee batting 1 hour"}
Practice Menu
Running 15 minutes
Stretching 10 minutes
30 sit-ups
30 push-ups
50 practice swings
Catch 30 minutes
Tee batting 1 hour
You can change it as you see fit.
But is it okay for a first year like
me to set the practice menu ?
If you do it, everyone
will go along with it.
Hmm...
Let's establish this baseball club's tradition together !
Let's do it.
Um.
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Body, Mind, Heart
Oh, no...
What is it ? It's creepy.
I can just picture Hiro.
Hiro ?
He's probably making a
difficult face and working hard.
Ah.
And he's acting
like he's not fired up.
He wears a poker
face at critical times.
Especially when he's
entrusted with important tasks.
His personality is suited
to being a pitcher.
He's suited to be a pitcher, huh ?
Man, you're so easily moved
by words like "starting a tradition."
Are you one to talk ?
Well...
So...
No.
Two hundred practice swings.
Won't that be too
hard for everyone ?
They'll try hard.
Then push-ups.
Sit-ups ?
We won't be able to use the field for a while, after all.
We'll work on playing catch and
building fundamental body strength.
That's right.
Speaking of which, why is he here ?
Maybe he's a sociable person.
EYECATCH
So how's the baseball club going ?
It's amazingly fun.
After all, the girls' track team club room is next to ours.
Huh ?
We get a parade of beautiful legs.
Oh, you must feel lucky.
It's so irresistible, right ?
Yeah.
You guys are talking about
that kind of stuff again ?
I'm not going to show it to you.
I thought you were
focused on baseball.
It just started. We're still
in a preparatory stage.
Practice Menu:
Running 30 minutes
Stretching 20 minutes
50 sit-ups
50 push-ups
200 practice swings
Play Catch 1 hour
Tee batting 2 hours
Hmm.
We do twice as much as this.
Noda, multiply that by two.
Don't get worked up.
So who's your coach ?
Huh ?
Coach ?
What ?
I don't know...
Senkawa
Kunimi, is this "road work for 1 hour"...
...which is written after 50 push-ups and 50 sit-ups, for tomorrow ?
No, it's all for one day.
Oh, I see...
It's the first step toward the Koushien.
Oh...
What ?
The Koushien ?
No way...
By the way, what happened to the coach issue ?
I was told to come to the Principal's Office later.
I think it's about that matter.
I see. I'm looking forward to that.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight...
...fight, fight, fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight, fight.
He's here again.
Hey.
Hello.
He must have a lot
of time on his hands.
I guess.
Fight, fight...
Let's slow down.
I guess.
Things are just starting out, after all.
Abrupt and excessive workouts will fatigue them, rather than building physical strength.
We should take it one step at a time.
Senkawa Baseball Club, hang in there !
You seem happy.
I can call them
"baseball club," after all.
But I wonder if things
have really changed.
Things are definitely changing.
I can't actually
feel the difference yet.
The wind feels different, doesn't it ?
The wind ?
Okay, let's go.
What ? Still...?
Yes, it's the autumn wind.
Dammit !
Goal !
What ? They're worn
out after the roadwork ?
I can't bear to watch this.
Man, they're beyond help.
Honestly, he's beyond help.
I can't do this anymore...
This is hard...
This really is...hard.
No...
Maybe this practice
menu is a bit much.
They just haven't
found their pace yet.
Captain.
Arikawa.
Oh, me.
The principal wants you.
Is it the coach thing ?
Probably.
Phew, it's cold !
But really, are we going to do
this much in practice every day ?
We're going for the Koushien, after all.
The Koushien, huh ?
Yes, the Koushien.
Didn't we just want to
play baseball for fun ?
Yeah, I suppose so.
The Koushien is just a pipe-dream.
Rather, it's more of
a joke than a dream.
What ? Are you
giving up on the Koushien ?
How many high schools do you think there are ?
It's impossible.
It's definitely impossible.
This is pathetic. They've finally
become a baseball club, and this is it ?
Akagi.
What brings you here ?
I said come here !
I'll tell you why I've always
thought you were pathetic !
As a player and as a teammate !
Teammates ?
Kunimi, where are you headed ?
To the Koushien, Akagi.
I'm going to the National Stadium.
Knowing where we're headed
makes things clear and easy, right ?
That's right.
Even if it's tough, we work hard.
And that makes it even more worthwhile when we actually get there, right ?
I feel sorry for people
who don't have a goal.
Is he a protagonist
in a young-adult drama ?
The baseball fan club was just a trifle.
But you guys worked hard to create a baseball club so that you could go to the Koushien.
And that impressed me.
Wow, he's starting to get
carried away all on his own.
I started to have a dream. Don't give up halfway !
Keep running until the end !
Got that ?
Y...yes.
Now, 200 practice swings, right ?
Oh no, he's here again ?
I'm going to do it.
We'll make our dream come true !
And then there's
someone who gets excited.
The wind is cool, and it feels good.
Let's take it one step at a time, at your own pace.
Yeah.
As long as you do it until the end.
Until our dream...
...comes true ?
Yes.
After the practice swings,
you'll hit 100 tosses.
Yeah !
Now, let's get back to training !
Yeah ! Aim for the Koushien !
Aim for Koushien !
Let's do it !
They're such strange people.
Kine.
Which one do you want to pursue ?
The National or the Koushien ?
Both.
He who runs after two hares will catch neither, they say.
But you won't know until
you run after them, right ?
What's with that swing ?
You're still swinging like a mosquito can land on it  !
It's the hip rotation ! It's the hips !
The noisy one is back.
Yeah.
Hey ! You should properly file the enrollment form !
Don't be such a square.
We know each other so well.
How much do we
really know each other ?
Captain, what happened
to the coach issue ?
Him...
Oh, he's my brother.
Oh, he's my brother. I'm sorry. He just has too much time on his hands.
I'm sorry. He just has too much time on his hands.
That's not it. Um...
Hey, guys, come over here.
This is...
This is our manager's big brother.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I mean...
So what happened to the coach ?
I'm Koga Fujio.
Huh...?
So what happened to the coach ?
Nice to meet you.
Huh...?
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Koga Fujio:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Matsumoto Yasunori
Izaki Hisayoshi
Hironaga:
Akagi:
Yamaguchi:
Arikawa:
Tanaka:
Track Club Girl:
Takagi Wataru
Ugaki Shuusei
Yamazaki Takumi
Chiba Isshin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Konishi Hiroko
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Notes:
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hiro, you guys are going to play a game,
even though your field's not finished ?
The third years are retiring
after summer, you know.
They become busy studying for the entrance exam, after all.
If the seniors hadn't formed the fan club, we wouldn't have been here.
So you're going to play a send-off game, to express your gratitude.
But the opponent team is...
What ? It's your father's team ?
Next episode of H2 is, "Farewell, Seniors !
A Tearful Send-Off Game."
Next episode of H2 is
Farewell, Seniors ! A Tearful Send-Off Game
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?