Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
After this and that, we have a coach.
Baseball Club
And Senkawa High School
Baseball Club has been launched.
But we only made it this far because our seniors started the baseball fan club.
I Can't Sleep...
Episode 26
Farewell, Seniors ! A Tearful Send-Off Game
Baseball Club
This really is a club room.
Yeah. It's definitely a club room.
It's definitely a club room.
I can't forget the time we marched into the principal's office, just the two of us.
Yeah. We were really surprised.
You really want to play baseball ?
Um, yes. Please let us.
Okay, then.
I will gladly fill out
your transfer request.
Which school would
you like to transfer to ?
What ? No !
Please wait.
We just wanted to...
If you want to play baseball,
you should attend another school.
I hate baseball.
So it ended up being
The Baseball Fan Club.
And now it's been upgraded to an actual baseball club.
Moreover, with a club room.
Yeah.
If this had happened a year earlier, we could have used this room, too.
The exclusive practice field, too.
Senior Yamaguchi, Senior Nemoto.
Hi, Manager.
Come on in.
If you have time, can
you watch us practice ?
Hey, are you trying to tempt students
prepping for college entrance exams ?
Our grades are a little
below average, you know ?
I don't want to spend a year
prepping for the exam again.
That's right.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight...
A send-off game ?
We have this baseball club only
because our seniors started the fan club.
See ? We should share
our enjoyment with them.
So, a send-off game ?
Yeah, that's a great idea.
It would've been nice to use
this field to play that game, but...
Okay, let's do it.
As the new captain, I was thinking we'd want to do something for them, too.
Even if we use another ballpark, the seniors will surely be happy.
Look. Your ballpark will soon
be born with a baby's first cry.
Hey.
So how did it go ?
I was able to reserve a ballpark...
...but I'm having a hard time
finding a team to play us.
Good luck,
Kunimi Hiro !
You know, lots of teams are
preparing for the fall tournament.
That's true.
So I want to ask the
Greengrocer Kuma's team.
I see.
The shopping-street team, huh ?
Come to think of it, the seniors used to play games with them.
A send-off game.
Private School - Senkawa High School
Wow, that's great !
About the date, will next Sunday work for you ?
If we wait too long, you
might be busy studying.
Is that okay with you ?
Yeah, it works for me.
Me, too.
I'm relieved. We started to set the date before asking you.
So I was worried that things
might not work out.
Don't worry about such a thing.
You're the captain of the baseball club,
not the fan club. You should feel confident.
O...okay !
Then, please excuse us.
The mock exam is
on Sunday, too, isn't it ?
Well, that's just one of them.
If we pass, we pass.
If we fail, we fail.
I guess you're right.
For exams, all you need is
to hit a homerun in the end.
Wow, you talk big !
Central Park Baseball Field
Greengrocer Kuma
Fish Tome
Suehiro Meat Shop
Send-Off Game for the Seniors
Shopping Street Team x Senkawa High School Baseball Club
It makes me blush a bit.
Me, too.
It shouldn't be that way.
You will be the first alums of our
glorious Senkawa Baseball Club.
You definitely deserve this.
The first alums...
We'll probably be treated as fossils or antiques one day.
Oh, here.
That's a ball you used to
use until just recently, right ?
Yeah.
They're kind of like our lucky charms.
This is our last game, so I was hoping to get at least one hit.
Hey !
Hello.
We hear this is the send-off game for Yamaguchi and Nemoto.
Yes, it is.
Regardless, we're not going to go easy on you. So you should be prepared.
After all, our match record is 4 wins and 4 losses so far.
If we lose the series as you graduate...
...it'll be an embarrassment
to us, the Shopping Street Team.
Right, Ken ?
Yeah.
Then, can you do the usual ?
Okay, got it.
Well, this is the send-off game, so I'll give you a special deal.
If you win, I'll give you a big serving
of the usual ramen, plus pot-stickers.
Wow !
Hey, you first year over there.
You're going to lose anyway. You
shouldn't be celebrating ahead of time.
Oh, you sure talk big.
But we're not the
same as we used to be.
After all, we're the newborn
Senkawa High School Baseball Club.
It's just a name
change from the fan club.
You don't even have a coach.
We actually have a coach now.
He can't be here today.
Moron !
A coach who doesn't attend games should be fired !
That's right !
Hm ?
Hey.
D...Dad ?
Mr. Kunimi...
Team
Shopping Street Team
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
Oh no...
Sorry about that.
It's been a while,
so it can't be helped.
I don't even know if
I can throw strikes, either.
All right, let's relax.
Send-Off Game for the Seniors
Shopping Street Team x Senkawa High School Baseball Club
Let's do it !
Yeah !
Play ball !
A great pitch to hit !
Out.
Senior Yamaguchi, nice pitch !
Oh !
Safe !
Don't worry.
Sure...
Yeah !
A bomb right out of the gate.
It's not unusual in the first inning.
But really, he hit a
rubber ball that far ?
He may not look the part, but
Mr. Kuma actually went to the Koushien.
The Koushien...?
Oh boy.
Team
Shopping Street Team
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
What ? My father is the starting pitcher ?
Oh, come on...
Are you serious ?
You know, I'm the first one to teach Hiro baseball.
Wow...
Is that true, Kunimi ?
Usually, a kid's first catch
partner is their father, right ?
I see.
Just leave it to me !
EYECATCH
I predict a homerun !
That won't happen. I'm going to strike you out in three pitches.
Here I come.
Take this Kunimi Ball Tarou Number 1 !
Hit by pitch.
Man. That was a miracle pitch ?
Oh, sorry about that.
Ouch...
Oh no...
Ball four.
I'm not great at the
start of the game.
Senior Yamaguchi, you've got a scoring opportunity !
This is your last game.
Try to square up and hit.
Here you go with your
"whisper talk tactics."
This time, I'll get it done.
Kunimi Ball Tarou Number 2 !
Got it !
Out.
Yes !
Tough luck.
I timed it just right...
Good luck, Senior Nemoto.
We've been waiting
for you, cleanup batter.
Now, will Mr. Nemoto be able to live up
to expectations as the cleanup hitter ?
I'm not going to fall for your tactics.
Here comes Kunimi Ball Tarou Number 3.
Got it !
Darn...
Three outs. Change.
This is more like it !
Nice batting, Senior Nemoto.
Here you go.
Welcome !
Hello.
Can I have a daikon ?
Sure.
A daikon, right ? Thanks.
Ma'am, where's the store master ?
As always, he's out
for a bush-league game.
They have the send-off game
for the third years of Senkawa...
...the team they've been
playing against all this time.
I see.
Oh well. Business is less
important for that baseball fanatic.
Team
Shopping Street Team
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
Good luck, Kunimi !
Thanks !
Oh, I see.
His father's named Kunimi, too.
Hiro !
What is it ?
You've grown.
I guess.
Your father is proud of you. But you're still not there yet.
You must surpass your
father and fly further.
Geez. I'm not a butterfly.
Let's face off !
All right.
Oh ?
...?
See that, Hiro ?
Such magical glove-work !
Yeah, right.
It was just a fluke.
Huh ?
Uh, oh...
Timeout.
Kunimi, things aren't
going too well, huh ?
I'm just starting to get hot.
Okay, then.
If we lose...
...you can pick up the tab for the big serving of ramen and pot-stickers at Ken's, right ?
Right ?
I'm out of gas.
Pitching change.
All right, I'm going to follow up !
Strike ! Batter out !
Damn !
Strike ! Batter out ! Change !
Yamaguchi, Nemoto,
don't worry about it !
Things are just getting started !
Let's pull ourselves together !
Out !
It feels like we're playing against a different team.
You're right.
Can they change so much, just by going from fan club to actual baseball club ?
They're working hard, too.
That's right. If we stay complacent, they won't play with us anymore.
Team
Shopping Street Team
Senkawa High School Baseball Club
This is the last inning !
Let's make a comeback win !
Hey, Tome.
Kuma, this isn't good.
Okay, pitching change.
The star pitcher is
now on the mound.
A Koushien player is pitching ?
That's not fair !
Be quiet. You guys are aiming
for the Koushien, too, aren't you ?
He's right.
Strike !
Strike two !
Strike ! Batter out !
The final inning. Runners on first and second, and our at-bats are coming up.
This really is our last.
Yeah.
Timeout !
If you want to play baseball,
you should attend another school.
I hate baseball.
Excuse me, Mr. Kuma.
What is it ?
Could you use this
ball for me and Nemoto ?
Oh.
This is a hardball.
This is the first ball we purchased when we started the fan club.
All right, then.
You want to get struck out
with a memorable ball, huh ?
No, I'm going to hit it.
No matter what !
Of course, I won't
take it easy on you !
Foul !
He might just pull it off.
He's getting his timing right.
You did it, Senior Yamaguchi !
Safe.
Nice batting !
Okay, my turn !
This must be the first
time you've given up a hit.
Yeah.
Now, we're down by just one run !
We're putting some pressure on them !
Senior Nemoto, follow it up !
Leave it to me !
Strike !
Strike two !
I guess I can't hit it after all.
Timeout !
Nemoto, relax.
Oh, do I look tense ?
You were totally tense.
More importantly, look how he pitches.
He has some velocity, and he can locate his pitches.
Hm ?
No wonder he's been to the Koushien.
Yeah.
When Mr. Kuma comes up in to
close out the game, we always lose.
But he has his weakness, too.
Weakness ?
He pitches with the exact same pace.
One, two, and three.
I see.
The important thing
is to get the timing right.
Okay.
Play !
Time it by one, two, and three.
One...
...two, and...
...three !
You did it !
It's a walkoff homerun !
We did it.
It was a great game.
Heave-ho ! Heave-ho !
Everyone loves baseball.
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Principal Yanagi:
Kunimi Tarou:
Koga Fujio:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Komura Tetsuo
Mitsuya Yuji
Matsumoto Yasunori
Ken:
Arikawa:
Yamaguchi:
Storekeeper:
Nemoto:
Mr. Tome:
Yassan:
Mr. Kuma:
Ono Kenichi
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Mizuhara Rin
Yanagisawa Eiji
Nagashima Yuuichi (Cho)
Yoshikawa Toranori
Nagasako Takashi
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Notes:
Transfer Form:  Too quick to throw it all up.
Here's what was on it.
Transfer Request - Name:
"This testifies that the student named on the right has attended the present school."
Year Month Day
Senkawa High School, Principal Yanagi Senichirou
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
The "whisper talk tactic" is a tactic that became widely known after a famous catcher of NPB named Nomura started using it. Basically, you whisper into the ears of the hitter, and try to get into his head, so that the hitter will be out of sync and gets himself out.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
The fall tournament has begun.
If you win it, you can go to the Koushien next spring.
They came really close
before losing this summer.
Yeah, we definitely want Hideo
to go to the Koushien this spring.
It'll be fine. See ? He hit a homerun in the first game.
He definitely doesn't restrain himself.
He sure is a big-shot slugger, right ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"Hide-chan's Phantom Homerun."
Are you having a refreshing workout ?
Next episode of H2 is
Hide-chan's Phantom Homerun
Look forward to it !