Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
One day, during summer break...
...I pinch-hit for Hideo, and
went out on a date with Hikari.
"Up-bound" train service
has ended for today.
Did Hikari tell Hideo that we couldn't
go home and spent the night together ?
I Can't Sleep...
Episode 26
Hide-chan's Phantom Homerun
Meiwa Daiichi High School
Hikari !
It looks like it's going to rain.
You should go home early.
Working overtime ?
Yeah, the fall tournament starts tomorrow.
See you.
Private School - Senkawa High School
It looks like it's going to rain.
I hear that a typhoon is coming.
I thought it was your stomach.
You heard it ? Let's eat
some ramen and go home.
Let's do that.
Autumn is the season of appetite.
If you work out hard, you get hungry.
That's right !
Let's go ! Let's go !
But we have to go Dutch.
Amamiya
Rain...
She feels safe falling asleep, even though I'm right by her.
Nothing has changed
since three years ago.
I guess Meiwa's first game tomorrow will be called off.
Autumn is definitely
the season for sports !
Yeah.
Hey.
You know him ?
Yeah.
Who is he ?
He was a neighbor when we were in elementary school.
He'd moved away 5 years ago,
but he came back here, apparently.
Were you a good friend of his ?
Yeah, we used to hang out a lot.
Hey, Rival.
You seem to be on
top of your game.
Well, you should enjoy it while it lasts,
until our baseball club joins the competition.
Our baseball club ?
You don't even come to our practice. You shouldn't act tough.
Don't worry about that. Once the ballpark is built, I'll come to your practice, too.
After all, I'm busy playing
both soccer and baseball.
Between those,
I have to go on dates, too.
Why are you acting so vain ?
You didn't tell anyone what
happened the other day, did you ?
What happened the other day ?
You know, at the inn where we spent the night, after the outdoor concert.
Hmm ?
Oh well. She tells me, "I don't want to go home tonight."
By coincidence, we ended up in the same inn as you two.
You two ?
You and Kunimi.
And my partner was...
Don't imagine something naughty, okay ?
We spent the night purely as
wholesome high school students.
I didn't go to any outdoor concert.
Huh ?
What ?
Hiro was also with a girl that night.
And she was an absolute beauty.
What ? Did you lie to me ?
That's unfair !
You spent the night
with a girl at that inn ?
Damn you...
As for us...
Us...
"As for us" ?
Well, we popular guys have
our own hardships, I suppose.
Go, go [team name indistinguishable]
Oh, it's time for the game.
Now, make sure to cheer for me.
Well, you should enjoy it while it lasts,
until our baseball club joins the competition.
Our baseball club ?
You don't even come to practice. You shouldn't act tough.
Don't worry about that. Once the ballpark is built, I'll come to your practice, too.
Hey, Kunimi !
The girl you spent the night with wasn't Koga, was it ?
Of course not, moron.
It was my big sister.
That's what I thought !
Tachiouji
Meiwa
Hiro.
Your sister's here.
Tachiouji
Hino
Toyota
Takao
Sagami
Fujino
Kaminohara
Yagawa
Taniho
Kawahara
Meiwa
Iwakiri
Shimoike
Murabe
Tachibana
Nakagawa
Tachikawa
Ichinose
Tsuji
Komori
Tachiouji
Meiwa
Umpires:
Gouji
Hirano
Tamura
Satou
Strike. Batter out.
He must totally trust you.
Who ?
Batting fourth, third baseman, Tachibana.
Well, you could also say that
my best friend has a big heart.
What are you talking about ?
I'm talking about us spending the night together after the concert.
Ball.
Because you told him
about it, it saved me.
I thought about telling him.
He called me after I came home.
But it was from camp, and
his seniors were teasing him.
So he hung up right away.
He really is a big-shot.
If I were him, I wouldn't
be feeling at peace.
Out.
What happened ?
Well...
...it looks like he forgot
to step on home plate.
Even then, he went 3 for 4.
If he had that homerun,
it would have been for the cycle.
Ugh !
EYECATCH
He attacked me first.
I don't know who's at fault here, but it's clear who's stronger.
Picking on the weak isn't cool.
When I fight, I fight to the end.
Or are you going
to pick up this fight ?
You'd better refrain.
It's clear who's stronger.
...?
Baseball club ?
Just established.
Are you sure that baseball club
guys can afford to get into a fight ?
Whether it's a baseball club or the tea ceremony club...
...there's no club where its members are allowed to get into a fight.
I have this habit where I do practice
swings without checking my surroundings.
No matter how hard
you try, it'll be all in vain.
As long as Tachibana Hideo is around, you can never go to the Koushien.
Hard work is never wasted,
even if it doesn't lead to the Koushien.
I don't know what he was like as a child, but I wouldn't want to hang out with him.
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
0:04:02.00 0:04:03.00
Hide-chan.
He's not here.
...?
Do you want a piece of apple ?
I don't want a piece of apple.
Oh, I see.
Who are you ?
Sagawa Shuuji.
I'm Hide-chan's childhood friend.
We used to be good friends.
We always did things together.
What was mine was Hide-chan's. What was Hide-chan's was mine.
If you come any closer,
I'm going to shout.
You shouldn't do that.
It'll be dangerous if I get startled and my hand slips as I peel the apple.
Oh, a cockroach.
That's such an overused tactic.
It's flying.
Stop that already...
Shit !
Hey ! Open up !
What's the ruckus ?
You're being a nuisance to the neighbors.
Hey.
Hi, Hiro.
Do you want an apple ?
You little...! It's mine !
Sorry about that.
I have this habit where I do practice
swings without checking my surroundings.
Here.
If you have a message
for Hideo, I'll take it.
Tell him to work hard and become more famous.
Tachibana Hideo is
the pride of us brothers.
Brothers ?
Oh, welcome home, Hide-chan.
What are you doing ?
Can't you tell ?
We're comparing heights.
I'm just trying to figure out how much taller I'm going to get.
Do it in your room.
Here. It's something your
childhood friend left behind.
He was here ?
He seems like a tough fighter, but he seems to dislike cockroaches.
He was already in the room. I was taken by surprise.
I almost shouted.
I was surprised, too, to see him for the first time in a long while.
Okay, let's pull ourselves together.
Let's go !
One more !
He's working overtime today, too.
Hikari !
Hey !
Hikari, let's walk home together.
Yeah.
You're so handsome !
Look this way, please !
What's going on ?
If you could act as his girlfriend for a day, it would be great.
He told a friend from his previous school that he had a girlfriend ?
And out of the blue, that
friend is coming to visit him.
Yeah.
You're the perfect fit for the
description he gave his friend, he says.
Do you believe him ?
What do you mean ?
He's totally lying to you.
He's my childhood friend.
That was five years ago.
You should be objective and see what he's like now.
I can bet that this friend
of his won't show up.
I don't want to be
alone with that guy.
No matter how much I ask ?
There's something
wrong with you, too.
Why are you obeying him ?
Is he blackmailing you or something ?
I got it.
You'll accept it only when
you're going out with Hiro.
Hide-chan !
That's what it is, isn't it ?
What's with that flashy towel ?
Oh, this ?
This is Koga's towel.
As I was resting just now,
she kindly handed it to me.
I see.
It smells nice.
Kunimi !
Koga, thanks for this.
It's not yours ?
Huh ?
Um...
...that's my towel.
Here.
Here, use this.
Thank you.
Hey, let's run one more lap.
Sure !
Okay !
Wow, it smells nice.
...
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Koga Haruka:
Tachibana Hideo:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Koga Fujio:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Suzuki Masami
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Matsumoto Yasunori
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Arikawa:
Head Umpire:
Girl:
Chiba Isshin
Yamazaki Takumi
Konishi Hiroko
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
Hiro, the Senkawa High School
Baseball Club finally has a ballpark.
Yeah, we're going to play a game to commemorate its completion.
Which school did you invite ?
Hiryuu West, I hear.
Hiryuu West ?
You mean that school that got barred from official competition because of a brawling incident ?
They look bad-mannered, but...
Right, we shouldn't judge people based on their appearance...
Next episode of H2 is, "A Commemoration Game ! Dangerous Guys Are Coming."
Next episode of H2 is
A Commemoration Game !
Dangerous Guys Are Coming.
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?