Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
Hideo's childhood friend, Sagawa Shuuji.
He bothers me, but I have
other things to take care of.
Our ballpark is finally completed.
Episode 28
A Commemorative Game !
Dangerous Guys Are Coming
It's looking more and
more like a ballpark.
We'll finally be able to use our
ballpark starting next week, right ?
Our ballpark...!
Private School - Senkawa High School
Guys, we have our opponent for
the ballpark commemoration game.
Which team is it, Captain ?
It's a team that made it to the quarterfinals in the summer tournament last year.
Oh, I'm surprised that a good team like that has accepted to play us.
So which one is it ?
Hiryuu West.
What ?!
What the heck ?!
It's supposed to be the memorable first game for our baseball team.
But of all the teams,
Hiryuu West is our opponent ?
Is there a problem ?
You don't know ?
They're a violent team that was barred for a year for an in-game brawling incident.
That suspension just ended recently.
Apparently, they've been
looking for a practice partner...
...but haven't been able to find one, and they've been in need of help.
Of course !
Hiryuu West is notoriously bad !
I hear they bean people like crazy.
Wasn't the reason for the brawl also because of a bean ball ?
That's right. They hit somebody, and yet
they got mad when someone complained.
I might get a fever
and miss the game...
You shouldn't judge
people by a rumor.
I guess, but...
They did actually
get suspended, after all.
No, there are no bad
people who play baseball.
But...
Yeah...
Don't worry.
I have a plan, just in case. You shouldn't worry.
That's all.
He doesn't seem like an ordinary guy.
Right.
He disappears without
watching us practice.
Senkawa High School
Baseball Club Ballpark,
Completion Commemoration Game
Senkawa High School
Baseball Club Ballpark,
Completion Commemoration Game
Baseball Club
Today, it doesn't matter
if we win or lose.
First, play an actual game, and
identify the areas of improvement.
The opponent made it to
the quarterfinals last year.
It's a suitable opponent for
gauging where we are right now.
Let's see how good the Senkawa High School Baseball Club is.
That's what the principal said.
He definitely isn't an ordinary guy.
Right.
Let's go.
Yes, sir !
Ah !
Huh ?
I forgot.
Dammit. They shouldn't be treating their main slugger this way.
Give me a break.
Hey, baseball club guy.
What ?!
Captain, they're here.
Yeah...
Here it is. This is the
place you're looking for...
Man, they're far scarier than I thought...
Father, Mother, please forgive me for dying before you...
What are you babbling about ?
We shouldn't judge people by
their appearance. Right, Kunimi ?
Yeah.
But if we meet them on the street,
maybe we shouldn't make eye contact.
I'm Yokomichi, the
coach for Hiryuu West.
Thank you for inviting us today.
I'm Koga, the coach here.
You may have heard many rumors...
...but they've learned from their
mistakes, so please be don't worry.
Old geezer, can we start practicing ?
Can we do some pre-game practice ?
Please.
Then let us borrow
the field for a while.
The old geezer says we can start.
It's important to properly
maintain your equipment.
Both teams, line up !
You're pitching ?
Yes, that's right.
If you're not confident that you can locate your pitches, don't aim for tight spots.
I'm a calm guy...
...but we have many short-tempered guys on our team.
Even if it just scrapes the
uniform, you might see blood.
Sure. I'll throw everything
right down the middle today.
Hey, hey. I'm not
threatening you or anything.
Team
Hiryuu West
Senkawa
Play ball !
Yeah.
Strike ! Batter out !
He really threw everything right down the middle.
I guess he's really
underestimating us.
Yeah ! Let's crush them !
We can't fool around
against a newborn team !
Yeah !
Go get them !
Hit them !
Out !
Are you all right, Yanagi ?
They didn't slide into you ?
Um, no.
But really, that guy
was going after his leg.
Definitely.
That was a routine play.
It's an aggressive play to break up the double play.
Hit by pitch.
Any pitcher can hit
a batter sometimes.
EYECATCH
Out !
Good job !
This is awful.
They say that
baseball is a combat sport.
But what if they get injured ?
You said there are no bad people who play baseball.
That's...right, but...
Then you should trust your own words.
Out !
I had no doubt that he
would slide into Noda.
He wanted an out,
so he blocked the plate.
He didn't want to make
an out, so he slid around.
That's all.
It's a routine defensive play,
and a routine base running play.
Baseball is a combat sport...
I'm sorry !
Thanks...
Nice effort.
Strike !
I'm sorry. The ball got away
from me because of the sweat.
I wonder about that.
Wasn't it a retaliation for
what happened earlier ?
No, it really was the sweat.
How can we
believe you scumbags ?
Are you saying it was intentional ?
Don't look down on us !
Hit by pitch.
Don't get rattled ! It just
scraped the uniform a little bit.
Watch out, Kunimi.
I don't want to say this, but they might retaliate.
Senior...
...your zipper's open.
...?
There's no need to worry.
There are no bad
people who play baseball.
I believe that, too.
That's right.
Ball.
Damn. He hit my
best pitch so easily.
You thought he'd
retaliate, didn't you ?
Huh ?
You've still got a ways to go.
I said there are no bad
people who play baseball.
Oh.
Strike !
Yeah !
Can I ask you a question ?
What is it ?
What was the "plan"
you had just in case ?
There's no need for that now.
Yes, but just for
reference, what was it ?
It was just a bluff.
What ?
Did you actually play baseball
when you were in high school ?
I was definitely in the baseball club.
I didn't get to play in a game even once in those three years, though.
The coach thoroughly hated me.
He was an absurd dictator coach.
I never understood a
thing he was telling us.
Does that sound like sour grapes ?
Not really.
In those three years, I kept thinking in the dugout about what I'd do if I were the coach.
Come to think of it...
...I probably held a desire since then to become a high school baseball coach.
Strike !
I'm happy that your
dream has been realized.
Yeah.
Wow...!
Out ! Game set !
Did you see my super play ?!
Nice.
I'm impressed that you
squared up and hit that pitch.
A pitch inside, and then a pitch away. That's playing it by the book.
Sometimes, the ball
slips away, though.
Well, I guess I'll let
you off the hook today.
Hiryuu West
Huh ?
How did you like playing a
game for the first time in a year ?
Don't ask me something
that goes without saying.
Let's go back and
start practicing, then.
What ? Now ?
Hey, geezer ! What kind of
crap are you talking about ?
We shouldn't judge people by rumors or appearances.
I guess so.
Even then, scary people are scary.
By the way,
who's driving that bus ?
Senkawa High School
Baseball Club Ballpark
Completion Commemoration Game
Hiryuu West
Has Been Here
So, did this give
you any information ?
They're good...!
I had no idea.
Our team is this good ?
You said it didn't
matter if we won or lost.
Our opponent was last year's quarterfinalist, you know ?
They were on a year-long hiatus.
From the fifth inning or so, their legs were getting tired from the lack of training.
I can see the Koushien, Haruka !
There.
You have an extreme weakness for the Koushien, right ?
That's good !
He's no ordinary guy.
Now, let's clean up our ballpark !
Yeah !
Kunimi Hiro:
Koga Haruka:
Noda Atsushi:
Kine Ryutarou:
Koga Fujio:
Coach Yokomichi:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Suzuki Masami
Tsuda Kenjirou
Takenaka Shinichi
Matsumoto Yasunori
Tsujimura Mahito
Next Episode
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Negishi:
Hironaga:
Yanagi Morimichi:
Arikawa:
Moriya:
Satou:
Sasaki:
Girl:
Furuta Nobuyuki
Takagi Wataru
Izaki Hisayoshi
Chiba Isshin
Yuuki Hiro
Narita Ken
Hoshi Souichiro
Konishi Hiroko
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
The red writing by Hiryuu West: This "has been here" message is often used by biker gangs and stuff.
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
Haruka's joke at the end to her brother: This is probably an irony. The phrase, to "have an extreme weakness for" something literally means "have no eyes for" something. And the coach's eyes, when Haruka takes the sunglasses off, are very tiny.
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Next Episode
I know that we shouldn't judge
people by their appearance, but...
Hideo's childhood friend,
Sagawa Shuuji, definitely looks fishy.
Yeah, I wonder if Hide-chan is being blackmailed by him.
I wonder what
happened in Hideo's past.
There must be something wrong with Hide-chan, to ask me to go on a date with him.
But you can't turn down Hideo's request, right ?
Next episode of H2 is,
"Hikari is in Trouble ! Shuuji's Trap !?"
A Memorial Game !
Next episode of H2 is
Hikari is in Trouble ! Shuuji's Trap !?
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?