Repeating seasons...
...and accumulating memories.
Like in childhood...
...I want to believe that I can freely fly in the sky.
When I stumble and look downward...
Tears flow and shine, but...
Back to the ground
A smile heals wounded wings.
The wind and the earth embrace me.
I don't care what anyone says...
...because I believe in myself.
Someday, I will come close...
...to this big, endless dream.
Presented by Central Anime
You can't judge people by how they look.
They may have seemed rough,
but they were all good guys.
But he really does seem dangerous.
Sagawa Shuuji. What happened between him and you, Hideo ?
Dangerous Guys Are Coming
Episode 29
Hikari is in Trouble ! Shuuji's Trap !?
What's with this dirty hat ?
Don't touch it !
Oh, scary.
...?
Aim for the Koushien !
Tachibana Hideo
The phone's ringing.
Hello.
Oh, Hide-chan.
It's me, Shuu.
Oh, hi.
About what I asked
you the other day...
Ah, that ?
To tell the truth...
It's okay.
Just pretend you didn't hear it.
What ?
When you think about it, it's stupid.
And I don't want to trouble you.
I'll be honest and tell the truth.
But...
It's fine.
After all, people at my previous
school think that I'm a liar anyway.
Bye.
Wait, Shuu.
Hikari told me.
I don't want to say it, but...
Then don't.
I don't want to hear you say bad
things about my childhood friend.
Sorry about that.
I've only been a friend of yours since junior high. That's a shallow friendship, I guess.
You're my best friend !
The best one I've ever had.
It's amazing that you can say stuff like that without feeling embarrassed.
So, can you tell me about your childhood friend ?
He had a brother who
was four years older.
He taught me how to play baseball.
He was the catcher and cleanup
hitter on the town's baseball team.
For me, he was the
star player I felt closest to.
Every day, until the sun went down, he played catch with me and Shuu.
Does his brother
still play baseball ?
He died.
When I was in fourth grade...
It's a shame that
the game got canceled.
There's no way we can
play a game in this weather.
It's a typhoon.
It was raining real
hard last night, too.
The field is totally soaked.
I wanted to surprise
those Minami-town guys.
After all, both of you have
improved so much in half a year.
We're talented, Hide-chan.
Moron, it shows how
good your coach is.
Tecchan, don't worry about it !
It's dangerous !
I'm fine.
I can reach it.
See.
Hide-chan, stop by our
house on the way home.
The three of us can play a game.
Okay.
We bought a new game.
Wow !
Shuu was so proud of his brother.
If only your hat
hadn't been blown away.
If only that typhoon hadn't come.
If only it hadn't rained
so hard the night before.
If only you hadn't played baseball.
If only his mother and father hadn't met.
Or gotten married.
If only, if only.
If only you hadn't been
born, you wouldn't die.
If we start talking about "ifs and buts"
after the game is over, there's no end to it.
You want another cup of coffee ?
Yeah.
So that's what it was.
I got what it was, but there's no guarantee
that the guy is still a good boy after five years.
That's what it is.
Even the lowest, worst criminal could be
kind of cute when he was in grade school.
He lied to his friend from his previous school that he had a girlfriend ?
That friend is coming to see him now, out of the blue ?
I totally match the description of the girlfriend that he gave his friend ?
Well ? Well ? Well ?
Anyway, why don't you help Hideo out here this time ?
Don't worry. I'll disguise
myself and watch over you.
If he does anything weird,
I'll jump out and rescue you.
He seems tough.
I know.
I'll try not to lose consciousness until after you've escaped.
Besides, you're really conceited to think
that he's going to do something to you.
Oh, that's what you told me.
You said I'm an attractive woman who makes men's hearts throb.
Um, anyway...
...it's not nice to judge people by their appearance or first impressions, you know ?
If you take the time and talk to them, sometimes they turn out to be good people.
Really ?
Just sometimes...
What ? Oh, really.
Thanks, Hide-chan.
Yeah, I got it.
Sagawa
Bye.
Oh, my. You caught cold
or something, Hide-chan ?
EYECATCH
Are you a destitute manga artist or something ?
...
Did you wait for long ?
Not really. I would have been
perfectly fine if you hadn't come.
Let's go, then.
To where ?
Where my friend is waiting for us.
It's not here ?
I'm counting on you, buddy.
Ku
Kuni
Kunimi.
I knew it ! It's Kunimi !
You must be mistaking
me for someone else.
It's too obvious and
unfashionable, moron.
What's with this outfit ?
You're making me laugh !
I don't want to hear that from you, of all people.
Listen.
What ?
If you don't shut up and leave...
What if I don't leave ?
Hmm...let's see...
I'm going to...
I'm going to tell people that you
poked a hole in our clubhouse...
...and tried to peep into the women's track team clubhouse next door.
What ? How did
you know my plan ?
I can see through
everything you're thinking.
Just go away.
Okay, sorry to intrude.
Damn. That was what
I was thinking of doing.
Well, the guy with the cold must be following them.
But still...
Today's High Score
I... I give up !
I can still take it !
Come back yesterday !
It's a shame that I
couldn't show off this punch.
Hmm...
We're not there yet ?
Almost.
Couldn't we have
met up back there ?
He's coming to this
town for the first time.
I had him come to a place that's easy to find, so that he wouldn't get lost.
Oh.
What are you doing ?
Nothing.
Oh, Hide-chan.
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been a while.
Your recent performance was amazing. You've made newspaper headlines.
Well...
You really have grown. You were playing around here back when...
Five years ago.
And now, you're a superstar.
This way ! This way !
Tecchan, come over here !
Hurry !
How many ?
Um, well, I'll leave it up to you.
Oh, I'm talking about your homeruns. How many have you hit already ?
Ah, well...
Hey, this is where we're
meeting up with your friend ?
Yeah.
You can see these three
chimneys from anywhere, right ?
But these factory ruins are creepy.
I didn't know.
This wasn't ruins five years ago.
Ifs and buts...
Tecchan, was it a good game ?
Tecchan is amazing.
It's an elementary school baseball game, but he's working hard.
Hide, focus and wait
for the right pitch !
You've got to match my brother's intensity !
Show your mettle ! Hit a walk-off !
Yeah !
Hide, don't dwell on it just
because you couldn't get a hit.
But I'm so frustrated...!
You tried your best.
And that's good enough.
But if only I had gotten a hit...
Hide, don't say "ifs and buts."
Okay ? No "ifs and buts."
Tecchan...
Why don't you come
over here and sit down ?
No thank you.
Oh, okay.
But really, I'm jealous.
I'm talking about Hide-chan.
He's become a star high school baseball player as a first year.
He has all the attention, and
people expect big things from him.
He's surrounded by
newspaper reporters and fans.
And on top of that, he has a beautiful girlfriend like you.
This world is so unfair.
If he has things people
would be envious of...
If he has so many things
people would be envious of...
...it means he's worked
so hard to attain those.
I'm fortunate that I'm
a childhood friend of his.
You're not listening to me, are you ?
That famous guy listens to anything and everything I ask of him.
He buys me meals.
He lends me money.
And today...
...I get to borrow his girlfriend.
He really is charitable.
I guess he's being respectful of my dead brother.
If you come any closer,
I'm going to scream.
So a cockroach is going to
come flying again or something ?
T...that's right.
The cockroaches around
here are pretty big.
...
What kind of taste do you have ?
Shut up. It was half hidden,
so I thought it was a penguin.
That's right.
It's easy to mix them up.
Yesterday, I found
one in the kitchen...
...
What are you doing here ?
What about you ?
Weren't you watching Hikari ?
I wasn't worried because
I thought you were watching her.
Dammit !
Hiro !
What is it ?
He's here.
Hm ?
Well, there's no need to worry.
So you really trust him.
I trust him.
He's my childhood friend.
If you trusted him, you wouldn't be stalking him in disguise.
I guess something like that
may have happened in the past.
Let bygones be bygones ?
I'm thankful that I got to
know Tecchan, and you, too.
And him, too. He'd often get
misunderstood, but the truth is...
We've got to look for her !
Kunimi Hiro:
Amamiya Hikari:
Tachibana Hideo:
Kine Ryutarou:
Sagawa Shuuji:
Furumoto Shinnosuke
Imamura Keiko
Miyamoto Mitsuru
Takenaka Shinichi
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Nimbly jumping over a puddle...
Next Episode
...I want to get past a hardship like that.
Flower Store Lady:
Sagawa Tetsu:
Young Hideo:
Young Shuuji:
Mine Atsuko
Iwanaga Tetsuya
Neya Michiko
Konishi Hiroko
Like you, I run up the pedestrian bridge...
Notes:
If you must know the porn mag's title: "Sexy Sunday"
The phrase, "come back yesterday !" is a common one that means something along the line of "don't bother coming back."
...keeping up with the sunny sky, I want to feel courageous.
Notes:
Graffiti is nothing important but: "Explosive Run !" "Idiots !"
"Go get them !"
Doll tag Hiro caught: "Mr. Cockroach"
Board in old factory: the character that's on the board is "Yasu" or "An" and it can mean "cheap," but it's probably a part of a name or a word. Maybe it's "Safety" ["anzen"]
"How does he keep such a nice facial expression ?"
Encoding
Noname
Translation
Toshiaki
Editing
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Brain
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime(Kansas)
Production
Version 1.0
I thought with frustration, when I met you.
"I'm definitely glad we met."
Let's stay strong and move forward.
When I'm by myself I notice...
...that, beyond this dazzling feeling...
...yesterday, today, and tomorrow...
...there are more and more smiles.
Just by looking at you, see ?
My eyes will look kinder.
Hiro, you said you'd watch over me.
It's Hideo's fault.
He was taking his time.
Next episode of H2 is,
"Hikari's Lie, Hiro's Tears."
A Memorial Game !
Next episode of H2 is
Hikari's Lie, Hiro's Tears
Look forward to it !
Are you having a refreshing workout ?