This is a FREE release by Heed-Anime (floyd.pinto@gmail.com)
Subtitles by Kotomi
Azusa!
Bull's eye! Wow!
Isn't he great?
Every time!
Hey you freshmen, quit acting like a bunch of groupies!
It's nothing, it just takes practice.
Here I go again. watch this.
Incredible!
What was all that? You were leading them on.
Sorry, I got carried away.
The team captain should be more responsible.
What's wrong?
Satomi-kun...
What?
You're not jealous, are you?
Who, me?
Wanna go for coffee?
I can't
My fiancée's coming in from the country.
You never told me about a fiancée!
What in hell are you dating me for?
No, it happened when I was just a kid.
She's my cousin.
Cousin?
Your cousin is your fiancée?
Weird.
My aunt forced us into it. She was sort of domineering.
Sister, it's too soon for this decision. He's only six.
The earlier, the better.
Azusa is the Shiga family's only daughter.
She can't marry outside the clan.
Why must it be Yuzuru?
I trust him, knowing he's your son. Yuzuru will marry Azusa.
I'm head of this family. You will obey me.
Sister...
It's settled, Azusa. When you grow up, you'll be Yuzuru-san's wife.
Yes... Mother
Yes... Mother.
Anyway, I was forced into it.
My aunt passed away last winter, leaving Azusa all alone.
Father decided to take her in.
My aunt's death was kind of strange.
So you'll be head of the clan?
I see. Let's break up.
You don't get it at all! That was years ago!
She probably has plenty of boyfriends by now.
I doubt it. I'll bet she thinks about you all the time
No way!
You never know.
Well... maybe.
Let's go.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
I'll try to be a better captain, tomorrow.
Say hi to Azusa-san for me.
Sure.
I'm home.
I'm home. is Azusa here yet?
She's waiting for you.
She's probably all grown up.
Azusa!
Yuzuru-san.
You surprised me. You're really beautiful.
You've grown up, over the last five years.
You too.
So tell me about your boyfriends.
I've never spoken to a boy my age.
What? You're joking, right?
But... I have you.
Hey Yuzuru-san. Don't you want me to be your wife?
Sure I do. I like you.
Really?, You really like me?
Cross your heart and hope to die?
It's a promise.
What a tragedy.
And her daughter's left without any friends or family.
But what a peculiar death!
Thank you, you've been very helpful.
Do you have any plans, now that the estate is settled?
I'll take her with me to Tokyo.
But what about the main house?
I'll arrange for it to be sold.
No. I'll marry Yuzuru-san, and we'll take over the Shiga family.
Mother would have wanted it that way.
Azusa?
Yuzuru-san promised me.
Be silent!
Can it be light? It's sparkling too bright
City schools frighten me.
Can love be,
Dangerous?
Meetings made by chance will always be,
Hearts beat fiercely and,
Body trembling
Hey Shiga!
You've got guts!
What's going on?
She's my cousin. She just transferred here.
Be careful!
She's cute!
Hey, she's shaking.
Be careful!
Ouch, I'm stung.
What's wrong?
You are, you are trembling and burning
Hey, Azusa!
Ah, love is,
Dangerous
I can no longer turn back and look...
The autumn storm blew a chill wind on the Emperor's grief.
He couldn't forget his beautiful mistress.
So he sent Myobu to the lady's grandmother.
The moon shone beautifully on the night she left.
Ohta, you read.
Start wih the next passage.
Page 25, sixth line.
On nights like this, they would play the koto.
Her koto had always carried especially beautiful overtones.
Her voice also had a rare charm to it.
He was reminded of the poem,
"The darkness steals reality and turns it into dream"
It must be nice to have such a cute fiancée.
I told you not to worry about that!
I'm not worried!
But what's with her? Some cousin!
She's hanging all over you!
You are worried!
Don't follow me!
But we're both headed for the same club!
Azusa had a strict upbringing. She's never met any guys.
But I'm sure she'll start looking at other men now.
I don't think so.
You're the problem. She's really beautiful.
She sure is! I was really surprised yesterday!
She is?
I mean, she's beautiful, but you're really cute!
You didn't let me finish.
What's my being cute have to do with it?
Anyway, she's nothing to me. She's my cousin, nothing more.
I'll meet you at the gate.
Who's there?
Who is it?
Azusa-san.
Stay away from Yuzuru-san.
He's my fiancé. Don't interfere.
That was when you were children. He and I are...
Yuzuru-san is mine!
No! Stay back!
You'd better not tell Yuzuru-san about this.
She's late.
Shiga-kun!
Satomi.
What's wrong?
Azusa-san is...
Over there!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Help me, Yuzuru-san.
It's dangerous to be out here alone.
Not too bad looking.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I belong to Yuzuru-san. No one else may touch me.
Yuzuru, anything else?
No, thanks.
What's wrong with Satomi? She wouldn't say a single word.
Dessert?
Later.
This is Shiga. Is Satomi-san there?
Azusa.
Why'd you do that?
Yuzuru-san.
Do you hate me?
What's wrong with me? I've been faithful to you.
Don't cry.
But...
Dammit, why are you so stuck on me?
You told me you loved me.
That was years ago!
Is a childhood promise any less sacred?
Is it?
It's her fault.
She's trying to take Yuzuru-san.
What's wrong, Satomi?
You feeling okay?
We're going ahead. See you there.
It just shattered!
Satomi, are you all right?
Satomi!
You're bleeding.
Are you going home?
No. I don't want to be alone.
I'll stay for archery.
All right. I'll walk you there.
Azusa.
It couldn't be Azusa.
That's ridiculous.
How could she break the glass? That's impossible.
"You'd better not tell Yuzuru-san about this."
I can't tell him. Besides, he'd never believe me.
See you later.
Bye!
Here I am.
Satomi.
Satomi!
Stop!
Satomi. That was Azusa, wasn't it?
I don't know. I really don't know.
I want to go home.
Okay, let's go.
According to Dad, my aunt avoided her other relatives.
Was it because of Azusa?
Please don't talk about her.
Thanks for walking her home.
It's okay. See you later.
Shiga-kun...
Be careful.
Bye, Jun.
Silence.
Jun, what's wrong?
Jun! Who did this?
It was her. How could she do such a thing?
I'm next!
Where did you go?
I smell blood.
Azusa!
What did you do to Satomi?
Tell me! What did you do?
Stop it, Yuzuru! What are you saying?
What have you done? What's that blood on your coat?
I don't know! I didn't do anything!
How could you, Yuzuru-san?
Hello? Satomi-san?
Hello?
Satomi.
Shiga-kun, Jun's been killed. I can't go back to school.
Satomi, tell me. Did Azusa do something to you?
Is she there?
After school tomorrow, come to my house.
I will.
Don't let her know.
Okay.
Azusa,
I finally understand what those creatures were.
They were the hungry ghosts. They consume dead flesh.
I held back for the sake of our family. But I can't any more.
Mother!
Azusa.
I will not let you continue the Shiga family!
Stop, Mother!
This is the end of the Shiga clan!
No, I'm going to be Yuzuru-san's wife!
You're a demon!
Mother!
*MAIN FAMILY: My Aunt's death
*TEN YEARS AGO: Missing child
*SATOMI: -- ?
It's all my mother's fault.
That's it.
No one will come between Yuzuru-san and me.
Not my mother... not anyone.
That girl.
My grade school pictures.
Assami-sensei.
Satomi always sat next to me.
She's gone!
I'm sure she was sitting next to me!
Satomi is... disappearing.
That was Azusa's room.
Hello?
Yuzuru-kun?
No time to explain. I'll be right over.
Lock yourself in your room and don't come out.
Why?
Just do it, Satomi.
All right.
Yuzuru-san is mine!
He's mine!
Satomi? What's wrong?
Kill her.
Satomi!
Satomi.
Satomi, get back.
Yuzuru-san...
Stay back!
Why?
You're not Azusa!
Do you hate me that much?
Yuzuru-san...
Please, come here.
Azusa.
I belong to you.
What was all that?
Tell me you don't hate me.
It wasn't me.
It was them.
I belong to you.
Asleep inside your heart,
Telepathy stirs.
A voice only you hear,
It calls to you in love.
You feel it rising.
The place where you awake is,
A place atop the waves.
A place that rises strangely,
A rising dawn of blue.
Cold, the city rises,
A floating sea of steel,
Why does this make me feel so,
Alone and by myself?
Although I want to go,
To a place where you are,
But I go in circles,
Rowing with one oar.
That day was special, too,
You left your mark on me,
Impacting on my heart,
You draw a ring around,
My heart again.
Special thanks goes out to Blanchimont
What kind of gifts or skills,
Are needed to fall in love?
I want to have you near me,
I want to have you all.
The way your smile lights up,
The color of your eyes,
I want to hear the sound of,
The beat of your heart.
As long as it is us,
The future will always,
Continue on and on,
For all eternity.
Always inside your heart,
Telepathy stirs.
A voice only you hear,
It calls to you for love.